{"question": "Solve (771 + 333)", "answer": "The result of (771 + 333) is 1104\n\n####1104", "a": 771, "b": 333, "operator": "+", "result": 1104}
{"question": "Solve (507 * 623)", "answer": "The result of (507 * 623) is 315861\n\n####315861", "a": 507, "b": 623, "operator": "*", "result": 315861}
{"question": "Solve (375 * 534)", "answer": "The result of (375 * 534) is 200250\n\n####200250", "a": 375, "b": 534, "operator": "*", "result": 200250}
{"question": "Solve (687 * 263)", "answer": "The result of (687 * 263) is 180681\n\n####180681", "a": 687, "b": 263, "operator": "*", "result": 180681}
{"question": "Solve (694 - 324)", "answer": "The result of (694 - 324) is 370\n\n####370", "a": 694, "b": 324, "operator": "-", "result": 370}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 879)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 879) is 101085\n\n####101085", "a": 115, "b": 879, "operator": "*", "result": 101085}
{"question": "Solve (374 - 732)", "answer": "The result of (374 - 732) is -358\n\n####-358", "a": 374, "b": 732, "operator": "-", "result": -358}
{"question": "Solve (989 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (989 * 439) is 434171\n\n####434171", "a": 989, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 434171}
{"question": "Solve (156 + 751)", "answer": "The result of (156 + 751) is 907\n\n####907", "a": 156, "b": 751, "operator": "+", "result": 907}
{"question": "Solve (506 * 396)", "answer": "The result of (506 * 396) is 200376\n\n####200376", "a": 506, "b": 396, "operator": "*", "result": 200376}
{"question": "Solve (307 - 980)", "answer": "The result of (307 - 980) is -673\n\n####-673", "a": 307, "b": 980, "operator": "-", "result": -673}
{"question": "Solve (341 - 994)", "answer": "The result of (341 - 994) is -653\n\n####-653", "a": 341, "b": 994, "operator": "-", "result": -653}
{"question": "Solve (918 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (918 * 897) is 823446\n\n####823446", "a": 918, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 823446}
{"question": "Solve (993 + 402)", "answer": "The result of (993 + 402) is 1395\n\n####1395", "a": 993, "b": 402, "operator": "+", "result": 1395}
{"question": "Solve (525 * 647)", "answer": "The result of (525 * 647) is 339675\n\n####339675", "a": 525, "b": 647, "operator": "*", "result": 339675}
{"question": "Solve (637 + 460)", "answer": "The result of (637 + 460) is 1097\n\n####1097", "a": 637, "b": 460, "operator": "+", "result": 1097}
{"question": "Solve (455 * 746)", "answer": "The result of (455 * 746) is 339430\n\n####339430", "a": 455, "b": 746, "operator": "*", "result": 339430}
{"question": "Solve (631 / 718)", "answer": "The result of (631 / 718) is 0.8788\n\n####0.8788", "a": 631, "b": 718, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8788}
{"question": "Solve (72 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (72 / 300) is 0.24\n\n####0.24", "a": 72, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 0.24}
{"question": "Solve (198 + 778)", "answer": "The result of (198 + 778) is 976\n\n####976", "a": 198, "b": 778, "operator": "+", "result": 976}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 834)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 834) is 0.8453\n\n####0.8453", "a": 705, "b": 834, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8453}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 175) is 370\n\n####370", "a": 545, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 370}
{"question": "Solve (654 / 188)", "answer": "The result of (654 / 188) is 3.4787\n\n####3.4787", "a": 654, "b": 188, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4787}
{"question": "Solve (241 / 281)", "answer": "The result of (241 / 281) is 0.8577\n\n####0.8577", "a": 241, "b": 281, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8577}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 370)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 370) is 2.6514\n\n####2.6514", "a": 981, "b": 370, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6514}
{"question": "Solve (537 * 605)", "answer": "The result of (537 * 605) is 324885\n\n####324885", "a": 537, "b": 605, "operator": "*", "result": 324885}
{"question": "Solve (234 / 305)", "answer": "The result of (234 / 305) is 0.7672\n\n####0.7672", "a": 234, "b": 305, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7672}
{"question": "Solve (539 - 740)", "answer": "The result of (539 - 740) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 539, "b": 740, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (812 + 628)", "answer": "The result of (812 + 628) is 1440\n\n####1440", "a": 812, "b": 628, "operator": "+", "result": 1440}
{"question": "Solve (745 - 375)", "answer": "The result of (745 - 375) is 370\n\n####370", "a": 745, "b": 375, "operator": "-", "result": 370}
{"question": "Solve (547 + 800)", "answer": "The result of (547 + 800) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 547, "b": 800, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (9 / 678)", "answer": "The result of (9 / 678) is 0.0133\n\n####0.0133", "a": 9, "b": 678, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0133}
{"question": "Solve (485 / 843)", "answer": "The result of (485 / 843) is 0.5753\n\n####0.5753", "a": 485, "b": 843, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5753}
{"question": "Solve (211 * 202)", "answer": "The result of (211 * 202) is 42622\n\n####42622", "a": 211, "b": 202, "operator": "*", "result": 42622}
{"question": "Solve (944 - 807)", "answer": "The result of (944 - 807) is 137\n\n####137", "a": 944, "b": 807, "operator": "-", "result": 137}
{"question": "Solve (592 + 479)", "answer": "The result of (592 + 479) is 1071\n\n####1071", "a": 592, "b": 479, "operator": "+", "result": 1071}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 300) is 0.55\n\n####0.55", "a": 165, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 0.55}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 597)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 597) is -111\n\n####-111", "a": 486, "b": 597, "operator": "-", "result": -111}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 578)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 578) is -86\n\n####-86", "a": 492, "b": 578, "operator": "-", "result": -86}
{"question": "Solve (188 + 663)", "answer": "The result of (188 + 663) is 851\n\n####851", "a": 188, "b": 663, "operator": "+", "result": 851}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 185)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 185) is 3.7676\n\n####3.7676", "a": 697, "b": 185, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7676}
{"question": "Solve (495 - 241)", "answer": "The result of (495 - 241) is 254\n\n####254", "a": 495, "b": 241, "operator": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve (129 - 363)", "answer": "The result of (129 - 363) is -234\n\n####-234", "a": 129, "b": 363, "operator": "-", "result": -234}
{"question": "Solve (719 - 393)", "answer": "The result of (719 - 393) is 326\n\n####326", "a": 719, "b": 393, "operator": "-", "result": 326}
{"question": "Solve (345 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (345 / 567) is 0.6085\n\n####0.6085", "a": 345, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6085}
{"question": "Solve (930 * 149)", "answer": "The result of (930 * 149) is 138570\n\n####138570", "a": 930, "b": 149, "operator": "*", "result": 138570}
{"question": "Solve (957 - 52)", "answer": "The result of (957 - 52) is 905\n\n####905", "a": 957, "b": 52, "operator": "-", "result": 905}
{"question": "Solve (990 * 702)", "answer": "The result of (990 * 702) is 694980\n\n####694980", "a": 990, "b": 702, "operator": "*", "result": 694980}
{"question": "Solve (394 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (394 - 514) is -120\n\n####-120", "a": 394, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve (912 / 568)", "answer": "The result of (912 / 568) is 1.6056\n\n####1.6056", "a": 912, "b": 568, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6056}
{"question": "Solve (219 + 302)", "answer": "The result of (219 + 302) is 521\n\n####521", "a": 219, "b": 302, "operator": "+", "result": 521}
{"question": "Solve (699 * 930)", "answer": "The result of (699 * 930) is 650070\n\n####650070", "a": 699, "b": 930, "operator": "*", "result": 650070}
{"question": "Solve (167 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (167 * 862) is 143954\n\n####143954", "a": 167, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 143954}
{"question": "Solve (331 / 717)", "answer": "The result of (331 / 717) is 0.4616\n\n####0.4616", "a": 331, "b": 717, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4616}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 387)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 387) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 545, "b": 387, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (44 / 634)", "answer": "The result of (44 / 634) is 0.0694\n\n####0.0694", "a": 44, "b": 634, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0694}
{"question": "Solve (309 * 778)", "answer": "The result of (309 * 778) is 240402\n\n####240402", "a": 309, "b": 778, "operator": "*", "result": 240402}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 573)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 573) is 65895\n\n####65895", "a": 115, "b": 573, "operator": "*", "result": 65895}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 706) is -216\n\n####-216", "a": 490, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -216}
{"question": "Solve (798 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (798 * 485) is 387030\n\n####387030", "a": 798, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 387030}
{"question": "Solve (698 / 870)", "answer": "The result of (698 / 870) is 0.8023\n\n####0.8023", "a": 698, "b": 870, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8023}
{"question": "Solve (969 / 965)", "answer": "The result of (969 / 965) is 1.0041\n\n####1.0041", "a": 969, "b": 965, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0041}
{"question": "Solve (870 / 422)", "answer": "The result of (870 / 422) is 2.0616\n\n####2.0616", "a": 870, "b": 422, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0616}
{"question": "Solve (635 - 156)", "answer": "The result of (635 - 156) is 479\n\n####479", "a": 635, "b": 156, "operator": "-", "result": 479}
{"question": "Solve (48 * 199)", "answer": "The result of (48 * 199) is 9552\n\n####9552", "a": 48, "b": 199, "operator": "*", "result": 9552}
{"question": "Solve (901 + 842)", "answer": "The result of (901 + 842) is 1743\n\n####1743", "a": 901, "b": 842, "operator": "+", "result": 1743}
{"question": "Solve (115 + 534)", "answer": "The result of (115 + 534) is 649\n\n####649", "a": 115, "b": 534, "operator": "+", "result": 649}
{"question": "Solve (140 * 92)", "answer": "The result of (140 * 92) is 12880\n\n####12880", "a": 140, "b": 92, "operator": "*", "result": 12880}
{"question": "Solve (443 - 830)", "answer": "The result of (443 - 830) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 443, "b": 830, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 789)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 789) is -69\n\n####-69", "a": 720, "b": 789, "operator": "-", "result": -69}
{"question": "Solve (548 - 563)", "answer": "The result of (548 - 563) is -15\n\n####-15", "a": 548, "b": 563, "operator": "-", "result": -15}
{"question": "Solve (263 / 237)", "answer": "The result of (263 / 237) is 1.1097\n\n####1.1097", "a": 263, "b": 237, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1097}
{"question": "Solve (276 - 796)", "answer": "The result of (276 - 796) is -520\n\n####-520", "a": 276, "b": 796, "operator": "-", "result": -520}
{"question": "Solve (590 + 484)", "answer": "The result of (590 + 484) is 1074\n\n####1074", "a": 590, "b": 484, "operator": "+", "result": 1074}
{"question": "Solve (623 - 709)", "answer": "The result of (623 - 709) is -86\n\n####-86", "a": 623, "b": 709, "operator": "-", "result": -86}
{"question": "Solve (166 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (166 * 407) is 67562\n\n####67562", "a": 166, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 67562}
{"question": "Solve (192 - 682)", "answer": "The result of (192 - 682) is -490\n\n####-490", "a": 192, "b": 682, "operator": "-", "result": -490}
{"question": "Solve (644 / 573)", "answer": "The result of (644 / 573) is 1.1239\n\n####1.1239", "a": 644, "b": 573, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1239}
{"question": "Solve (933 + 354)", "answer": "The result of (933 + 354) is 1287\n\n####1287", "a": 933, "b": 354, "operator": "+", "result": 1287}
{"question": "Solve (399 * 765)", "answer": "The result of (399 * 765) is 305235\n\n####305235", "a": 399, "b": 765, "operator": "*", "result": 305235}
{"question": "Solve (373 - 758)", "answer": "The result of (373 - 758) is -385\n\n####-385", "a": 373, "b": 758, "operator": "-", "result": -385}
{"question": "Solve (369 / 557)", "answer": "The result of (369 / 557) is 0.6625\n\n####0.6625", "a": 369, "b": 557, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6625}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 988)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 988) is -894\n\n####-894", "a": 94, "b": 988, "operator": "-", "result": -894}
{"question": "Solve (925 / 428)", "answer": "The result of (925 / 428) is 2.1612\n\n####2.1612", "a": 925, "b": 428, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1612}
{"question": "Solve (139 + 936)", "answer": "The result of (139 + 936) is 1075\n\n####1075", "a": 139, "b": 936, "operator": "+", "result": 1075}
{"question": "Solve (83 / 335)", "answer": "The result of (83 / 335) is 0.2478\n\n####0.2478", "a": 83, "b": 335, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2478}
{"question": "Solve (895 - 912)", "answer": "The result of (895 - 912) is -17\n\n####-17", "a": 895, "b": 912, "operator": "-", "result": -17}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 60)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 60) is 298\n\n####298", "a": 358, "b": 60, "operator": "-", "result": 298}
{"question": "Solve (476 / 174)", "answer": "The result of (476 / 174) is 2.7356\n\n####2.7356", "a": 476, "b": 174, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7356}
{"question": "Solve (46 / 2)", "answer": "The result of (46 / 2) is 23.0\n\n####23.0", "a": 46, "b": 2, "operator": "/", "result": 23.0}
{"question": "Solve (904 * 432)", "answer": "The result of (904 * 432) is 390528\n\n####390528", "a": 904, "b": 432, "operator": "*", "result": 390528}
{"question": "Solve (825 * 419)", "answer": "The result of (825 * 419) is 345675\n\n####345675", "a": 825, "b": 419, "operator": "*", "result": 345675}
{"question": "Solve (864 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (864 - 342) is 522\n\n####522", "a": 864, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": 522}
{"question": "Solve (577 + 369)", "answer": "The result of (577 + 369) is 946\n\n####946", "a": 577, "b": 369, "operator": "+", "result": 946}
{"question": "Solve (265 + 871)", "answer": "The result of (265 + 871) is 1136\n\n####1136", "a": 265, "b": 871, "operator": "+", "result": 1136}
{"question": "Solve (46 - 951)", "answer": "The result of (46 - 951) is -905\n\n####-905", "a": 46, "b": 951, "operator": "-", "result": -905}
{"question": "Solve (568 - 848)", "answer": "The result of (568 - 848) is -280\n\n####-280", "a": 568, "b": 848, "operator": "-", "result": -280}
{"question": "Solve (932 - 972)", "answer": "The result of (932 - 972) is -40\n\n####-40", "a": 932, "b": 972, "operator": "-", "result": -40}
{"question": "Solve (967 / 687)", "answer": "The result of (967 / 687) is 1.4076\n\n####1.4076", "a": 967, "b": 687, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4076}
{"question": "Solve (737 - 406)", "answer": "The result of (737 - 406) is 331\n\n####331", "a": 737, "b": 406, "operator": "-", "result": 331}
{"question": "Solve (664 + 305)", "answer": "The result of (664 + 305) is 969\n\n####969", "a": 664, "b": 305, "operator": "+", "result": 969}
{"question": "Solve (906 * 631)", "answer": "The result of (906 * 631) is 571686\n\n####571686", "a": 906, "b": 631, "operator": "*", "result": 571686}
{"question": "Solve (136 + 500)", "answer": "The result of (136 + 500) is 636\n\n####636", "a": 136, "b": 500, "operator": "+", "result": 636}
{"question": "Solve (656 * 340)", "answer": "The result of (656 * 340) is 223040\n\n####223040", "a": 656, "b": 340, "operator": "*", "result": 223040}
{"question": "Solve (736 - 977)", "answer": "The result of (736 - 977) is -241\n\n####-241", "a": 736, "b": 977, "operator": "-", "result": -241}
{"question": "Solve (799 + 194)", "answer": "The result of (799 + 194) is 993\n\n####993", "a": 799, "b": 194, "operator": "+", "result": 993}
{"question": "Solve (341 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (341 * 215) is 73315\n\n####73315", "a": 341, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 73315}
{"question": "Solve (123 - 289)", "answer": "The result of (123 - 289) is -166\n\n####-166", "a": 123, "b": 289, "operator": "-", "result": -166}
{"question": "Solve (362 / 886)", "answer": "The result of (362 / 886) is 0.4086\n\n####0.4086", "a": 362, "b": 886, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4086}
{"question": "Solve (808 + 647)", "answer": "The result of (808 + 647) is 1455\n\n####1455", "a": 808, "b": 647, "operator": "+", "result": 1455}
{"question": "Solve (56 / 258)", "answer": "The result of (56 / 258) is 0.2171\n\n####0.2171", "a": 56, "b": 258, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2171}
{"question": "Solve (661 - 266)", "answer": "The result of (661 - 266) is 395\n\n####395", "a": 661, "b": 266, "operator": "-", "result": 395}
{"question": "Solve (627 / 115)", "answer": "The result of (627 / 115) is 5.4522\n\n####5.4522", "a": 627, "b": 115, "operator": "/", "result": 5.4522}
{"question": "Solve (389 / 744)", "answer": "The result of (389 / 744) is 0.5228\n\n####0.5228", "a": 389, "b": 744, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5228}
{"question": "Solve (896 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (896 / 327) is 2.7401\n\n####2.7401", "a": 896, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7401}
{"question": "Solve (977 - 662)", "answer": "The result of (977 - 662) is 315\n\n####315", "a": 977, "b": 662, "operator": "-", "result": 315}
{"question": "Solve (456 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (456 - 358) is 98\n\n####98", "a": 456, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve (174 / 47)", "answer": "The result of (174 / 47) is 3.7021\n\n####3.7021", "a": 174, "b": 47, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7021}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 439) is 158479\n\n####158479", "a": 361, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 158479}
{"question": "Solve (544 / 717)", "answer": "The result of (544 / 717) is 0.7587\n\n####0.7587", "a": 544, "b": 717, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7587}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 474)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 474) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 615, "b": 474, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (746 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (746 + 211) is 957\n\n####957", "a": 746, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 957}
{"question": "Solve (782 * 569)", "answer": "The result of (782 * 569) is 444958\n\n####444958", "a": 782, "b": 569, "operator": "*", "result": 444958}
{"question": "Solve (170 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (170 / 891) is 0.1908\n\n####0.1908", "a": 170, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1908}
{"question": "Solve (265 - 21)", "answer": "The result of (265 - 21) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 265, "b": 21, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (960 / 712)", "answer": "The result of (960 / 712) is 1.3483\n\n####1.3483", "a": 960, "b": 712, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3483}
{"question": "Solve (891 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (891 - 496) is 395\n\n####395", "a": 891, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": 395}
{"question": "Solve (12 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (12 - 485) is -473\n\n####-473", "a": 12, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": -473}
{"question": "Solve (764 + 340)", "answer": "The result of (764 + 340) is 1104\n\n####1104", "a": 764, "b": 340, "operator": "+", "result": 1104}
{"question": "Solve (556 - 67)", "answer": "The result of (556 - 67) is 489\n\n####489", "a": 556, "b": 67, "operator": "-", "result": 489}
{"question": "Solve (47 - 563)", "answer": "The result of (47 - 563) is -516\n\n####-516", "a": 47, "b": 563, "operator": "-", "result": -516}
{"question": "Solve (466 - 495)", "answer": "The result of (466 - 495) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 466, "b": 495, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (737 - 755)", "answer": "The result of (737 - 755) is -18\n\n####-18", "a": 737, "b": 755, "operator": "-", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve (121 - 92)", "answer": "The result of (121 - 92) is 29\n\n####29", "a": 121, "b": 92, "operator": "-", "result": 29}
{"question": "Solve (343 + 253)", "answer": "The result of (343 + 253) is 596\n\n####596", "a": 343, "b": 253, "operator": "+", "result": 596}
{"question": "Solve (388 / 867)", "answer": "The result of (388 / 867) is 0.4475\n\n####0.4475", "a": 388, "b": 867, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4475}
{"question": "Solve (639 - 681)", "answer": "The result of (639 - 681) is -42\n\n####-42", "a": 639, "b": 681, "operator": "-", "result": -42}
{"question": "Solve (270 - 65)", "answer": "The result of (270 - 65) is 205\n\n####205", "a": 270, "b": 65, "operator": "-", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve (456 * 689)", "answer": "The result of (456 * 689) is 314184\n\n####314184", "a": 456, "b": 689, "operator": "*", "result": 314184}
{"question": "Solve (663 / 804)", "answer": "The result of (663 / 804) is 0.8246\n\n####0.8246", "a": 663, "b": 804, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8246}
{"question": "Solve (963 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (963 / 489) is 1.9693\n\n####1.9693", "a": 963, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9693}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 179)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 179) is 110980\n\n####110980", "a": 620, "b": 179, "operator": "*", "result": 110980}
{"question": "Solve (17 + 610)", "answer": "The result of (17 + 610) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 17, "b": 610, "operator": "+", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (852 - 189)", "answer": "The result of (852 - 189) is 663\n\n####663", "a": 852, "b": 189, "operator": "-", "result": 663}
{"question": "Solve (581 / 297)", "answer": "The result of (581 / 297) is 1.9562\n\n####1.9562", "a": 581, "b": 297, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9562}
{"question": "Solve (747 * 129)", "answer": "The result of (747 * 129) is 96363\n\n####96363", "a": 747, "b": 129, "operator": "*", "result": 96363}
{"question": "Solve (462 * 23)", "answer": "The result of (462 * 23) is 10626\n\n####10626", "a": 462, "b": 23, "operator": "*", "result": 10626}
{"question": "Solve (550 / 971)", "answer": "The result of (550 / 971) is 0.5664\n\n####0.5664", "a": 550, "b": 971, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5664}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 596) is 548320\n\n####548320", "a": 920, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 548320}
{"question": "Solve (245 + 477)", "answer": "The result of (245 + 477) is 722\n\n####722", "a": 245, "b": 477, "operator": "+", "result": 722}
{"question": "Solve (690 + 397)", "answer": "The result of (690 + 397) is 1087\n\n####1087", "a": 690, "b": 397, "operator": "+", "result": 1087}
{"question": "Solve (932 / 183)", "answer": "The result of (932 / 183) is 5.0929\n\n####5.0929", "a": 932, "b": 183, "operator": "/", "result": 5.0929}
{"question": "Solve (400 / 167)", "answer": "The result of (400 / 167) is 2.3952\n\n####2.3952", "a": 400, "b": 167, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3952}
{"question": "Solve (993 * 173)", "answer": "The result of (993 * 173) is 171789\n\n####171789", "a": 993, "b": 173, "operator": "*", "result": 171789}
{"question": "Solve (473 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (473 * 861) is 407253\n\n####407253", "a": 473, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 407253}
{"question": "Solve (940 - 953)", "answer": "The result of (940 - 953) is -13\n\n####-13", "a": 940, "b": 953, "operator": "-", "result": -13}
{"question": "Solve (967 / 422)", "answer": "The result of (967 / 422) is 2.2915\n\n####2.2915", "a": 967, "b": 422, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2915}
{"question": "Solve (134 / 520)", "answer": "The result of (134 / 520) is 0.2577\n\n####0.2577", "a": 134, "b": 520, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2577}
{"question": "Solve (157 / 562)", "answer": "The result of (157 / 562) is 0.2794\n\n####0.2794", "a": 157, "b": 562, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2794}
{"question": "Solve (249 * 307)", "answer": "The result of (249 * 307) is 76443\n\n####76443", "a": 249, "b": 307, "operator": "*", "result": 76443}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 244)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 244) is 0.6762\n\n####0.6762", "a": 165, "b": 244, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6762}
{"question": "Solve (850 / 472)", "answer": "The result of (850 / 472) is 1.8008\n\n####1.8008", "a": 850, "b": 472, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8008}
{"question": "Solve (503 - 583)", "answer": "The result of (503 - 583) is -80\n\n####-80", "a": 503, "b": 583, "operator": "-", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve (472 / 503)", "answer": "The result of (472 / 503) is 0.9384\n\n####0.9384", "a": 472, "b": 503, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9384}
{"question": "Solve (5 / 480)", "answer": "The result of (5 / 480) is 0.0104\n\n####0.0104", "a": 5, "b": 480, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0104}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 661) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 608, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (513 / 785)", "answer": "The result of (513 / 785) is 0.6535\n\n####0.6535", "a": 513, "b": 785, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6535}
{"question": "Solve (938 * 162)", "answer": "The result of (938 * 162) is 151956\n\n####151956", "a": 938, "b": 162, "operator": "*", "result": 151956}
{"question": "Solve (35 + 34)", "answer": "The result of (35 + 34) is 69\n\n####69", "a": 35, "b": 34, "operator": "+", "result": 69}
{"question": "Solve (184 * 680)", "answer": "The result of (184 * 680) is 125120\n\n####125120", "a": 184, "b": 680, "operator": "*", "result": 125120}
{"question": "Solve (284 - 150)", "answer": "The result of (284 - 150) is 134\n\n####134", "a": 284, "b": 150, "operator": "-", "result": 134}
{"question": "Solve (51 + 262)", "answer": "The result of (51 + 262) is 313\n\n####313", "a": 51, "b": 262, "operator": "+", "result": 313}
{"question": "Solve (85 / 924)", "answer": "The result of (85 / 924) is 0.092\n\n####0.092", "a": 85, "b": 924, "operator": "/", "result": 0.092}
{"question": "Solve (33 + 971)", "answer": "The result of (33 + 971) is 1004\n\n####1004", "a": 33, "b": 971, "operator": "+", "result": 1004}
{"question": "Solve (11 - 224)", "answer": "The result of (11 - 224) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 11, "b": 224, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (988 + 813)", "answer": "The result of (988 + 813) is 1801\n\n####1801", "a": 988, "b": 813, "operator": "+", "result": 1801}
{"question": "Solve (681 * 370)", "answer": "The result of (681 * 370) is 251970\n\n####251970", "a": 681, "b": 370, "operator": "*", "result": 251970}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 385) is 0.7195\n\n####0.7195", "a": 277, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7195}
{"question": "Solve (145 + 419)", "answer": "The result of (145 + 419) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 145, "b": 419, "operator": "+", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (416 / 223)", "answer": "The result of (416 / 223) is 1.8655\n\n####1.8655", "a": 416, "b": 223, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8655}
{"question": "Solve (622 * 172)", "answer": "The result of (622 * 172) is 106984\n\n####106984", "a": 622, "b": 172, "operator": "*", "result": 106984}
{"question": "Solve (412 - 456)", "answer": "The result of (412 - 456) is -44\n\n####-44", "a": 412, "b": 456, "operator": "-", "result": -44}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 932) is -211\n\n####-211", "a": 721, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": -211}
{"question": "Solve (702 * 850)", "answer": "The result of (702 * 850) is 596700\n\n####596700", "a": 702, "b": 850, "operator": "*", "result": 596700}
{"question": "Solve (599 / 146)", "answer": "The result of (599 / 146) is 4.1027\n\n####4.1027", "a": 599, "b": 146, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1027}
{"question": "Solve (635 / 950)", "answer": "The result of (635 / 950) is 0.6684\n\n####0.6684", "a": 635, "b": 950, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6684}
{"question": "Solve (539 - 369)", "answer": "The result of (539 - 369) is 170\n\n####170", "a": 539, "b": 369, "operator": "-", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve (399 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (399 - 579) is -180\n\n####-180", "a": 399, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": -180}
{"question": "Solve (122 - 839)", "answer": "The result of (122 - 839) is -717\n\n####-717", "a": 122, "b": 839, "operator": "-", "result": -717}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 567) is -368\n\n####-368", "a": 199, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": -368}
{"question": "Solve (857 / 398)", "answer": "The result of (857 / 398) is 2.1533\n\n####2.1533", "a": 857, "b": 398, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1533}
{"question": "Solve (308 / 991)", "answer": "The result of (308 / 991) is 0.3108\n\n####0.3108", "a": 308, "b": 991, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3108}
{"question": "Solve (438 * 607)", "answer": "The result of (438 * 607) is 265866\n\n####265866", "a": 438, "b": 607, "operator": "*", "result": 265866}
{"question": "Solve (341 - 853)", "answer": "The result of (341 - 853) is -512\n\n####-512", "a": 341, "b": 853, "operator": "-", "result": -512}
{"question": "Solve (781 * 523)", "answer": "The result of (781 * 523) is 408463\n\n####408463", "a": 781, "b": 523, "operator": "*", "result": 408463}
{"question": "Solve (419 * 476)", "answer": "The result of (419 * 476) is 199444\n\n####199444", "a": 419, "b": 476, "operator": "*", "result": 199444}
{"question": "Solve (603 / 796)", "answer": "The result of (603 / 796) is 0.7575\n\n####0.7575", "a": 603, "b": 796, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7575}
{"question": "Solve (134 - 486)", "answer": "The result of (134 - 486) is -352\n\n####-352", "a": 134, "b": 486, "operator": "-", "result": -352}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 204)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 204) is 3468\n\n####3468", "a": 17, "b": 204, "operator": "*", "result": 3468}
{"question": "Solve (219 * 269)", "answer": "The result of (219 * 269) is 58911\n\n####58911", "a": 219, "b": 269, "operator": "*", "result": 58911}
{"question": "Solve (276 * 564)", "answer": "The result of (276 * 564) is 155664\n\n####155664", "a": 276, "b": 564, "operator": "*", "result": 155664}
{"question": "Solve (981 * 337)", "answer": "The result of (981 * 337) is 330597\n\n####330597", "a": 981, "b": 337, "operator": "*", "result": 330597}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 542)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 542) is 321\n\n####321", "a": 863, "b": 542, "operator": "-", "result": 321}
{"question": "Solve (402 + 903)", "answer": "The result of (402 + 903) is 1305\n\n####1305", "a": 402, "b": 903, "operator": "+", "result": 1305}
{"question": "Solve (588 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (588 / 453) is 1.298\n\n####1.298", "a": 588, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 1.298}
{"question": "Solve (577 + 584)", "answer": "The result of (577 + 584) is 1161\n\n####1161", "a": 577, "b": 584, "operator": "+", "result": 1161}
{"question": "Solve (469 + 755)", "answer": "The result of (469 + 755) is 1224\n\n####1224", "a": 469, "b": 755, "operator": "+", "result": 1224}
{"question": "Solve (933 + 3)", "answer": "The result of (933 + 3) is 936\n\n####936", "a": 933, "b": 3, "operator": "+", "result": 936}
{"question": "Solve (691 * 564)", "answer": "The result of (691 * 564) is 389724\n\n####389724", "a": 691, "b": 564, "operator": "*", "result": 389724}
{"question": "Solve (812 + 81)", "answer": "The result of (812 + 81) is 893\n\n####893", "a": 812, "b": 81, "operator": "+", "result": 893}
{"question": "Solve (567 * 742)", "answer": "The result of (567 * 742) is 420714\n\n####420714", "a": 567, "b": 742, "operator": "*", "result": 420714}
{"question": "Solve (919 * 326)", "answer": "The result of (919 * 326) is 299594\n\n####299594", "a": 919, "b": 326, "operator": "*", "result": 299594}
{"question": "Solve (696 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (696 - 932) is -236\n\n####-236", "a": 696, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": -236}
{"question": "Solve (429 / 962)", "answer": "The result of (429 / 962) is 0.4459\n\n####0.4459", "a": 429, "b": 962, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4459}
{"question": "Solve (737 / 194)", "answer": "The result of (737 / 194) is 3.799\n\n####3.799", "a": 737, "b": 194, "operator": "/", "result": 3.799}
{"question": "Solve (568 + 79)", "answer": "The result of (568 + 79) is 647\n\n####647", "a": 568, "b": 79, "operator": "+", "result": 647}
{"question": "Solve (499 / 97)", "answer": "The result of (499 / 97) is 5.1443\n\n####5.1443", "a": 499, "b": 97, "operator": "/", "result": 5.1443}
{"question": "Solve (247 * 902)", "answer": "The result of (247 * 902) is 222794\n\n####222794", "a": 247, "b": 902, "operator": "*", "result": 222794}
{"question": "Solve (659 / 409)", "answer": "The result of (659 / 409) is 1.6112\n\n####1.6112", "a": 659, "b": 409, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6112}
{"question": "Solve (977 - 215)", "answer": "The result of (977 - 215) is 762\n\n####762", "a": 977, "b": 215, "operator": "-", "result": 762}
{"question": "Solve (506 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (506 + 239) is 745\n\n####745", "a": 506, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 745}
{"question": "Solve (758 + 106)", "answer": "The result of (758 + 106) is 864\n\n####864", "a": 758, "b": 106, "operator": "+", "result": 864}
{"question": "Solve (609 + 291)", "answer": "The result of (609 + 291) is 900\n\n####900", "a": 609, "b": 291, "operator": "+", "result": 900}
{"question": "Solve (564 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (564 - 290) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 564, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (256 * 701)", "answer": "The result of (256 * 701) is 179456\n\n####179456", "a": 256, "b": 701, "operator": "*", "result": 179456}
{"question": "Solve (382 * 597)", "answer": "The result of (382 * 597) is 228054\n\n####228054", "a": 382, "b": 597, "operator": "*", "result": 228054}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 922)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 922) is -324\n\n####-324", "a": 598, "b": 922, "operator": "-", "result": -324}
{"question": "Solve (167 * 305)", "answer": "The result of (167 * 305) is 50935\n\n####50935", "a": 167, "b": 305, "operator": "*", "result": 50935}
{"question": "Solve (779 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (779 - 168) is 611\n\n####611", "a": 779, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": 611}
{"question": "Solve (422 - 911)", "answer": "The result of (422 - 911) is -489\n\n####-489", "a": 422, "b": 911, "operator": "-", "result": -489}
{"question": "Solve (219 / 982)", "answer": "The result of (219 / 982) is 0.223\n\n####0.223", "a": 219, "b": 982, "operator": "/", "result": 0.223}
{"question": "Solve (611 - 705)", "answer": "The result of (611 - 705) is -94\n\n####-94", "a": 611, "b": 705, "operator": "-", "result": -94}
{"question": "Solve (953 * 600)", "answer": "The result of (953 * 600) is 571800\n\n####571800", "a": 953, "b": 600, "operator": "*", "result": 571800}
{"question": "Solve (397 + 570)", "answer": "The result of (397 + 570) is 967\n\n####967", "a": 397, "b": 570, "operator": "+", "result": 967}
{"question": "Solve (243 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (243 - 604) is -361\n\n####-361", "a": 243, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -361}
{"question": "Solve (556 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (556 / 489) is 1.137\n\n####1.137", "a": 556, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 1.137}
{"question": "Solve (131 / 462)", "answer": "The result of (131 / 462) is 0.2835\n\n####0.2835", "a": 131, "b": 462, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2835}
{"question": "Solve (680 + 101)", "answer": "The result of (680 + 101) is 781\n\n####781", "a": 680, "b": 101, "operator": "+", "result": 781}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 272)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 272) is 1.1434\n\n####1.1434", "a": 311, "b": 272, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1434}
{"question": "Solve (375 - 586)", "answer": "The result of (375 - 586) is -211\n\n####-211", "a": 375, "b": 586, "operator": "-", "result": -211}
{"question": "Solve (596 - 984)", "answer": "The result of (596 - 984) is -388\n\n####-388", "a": 596, "b": 984, "operator": "-", "result": -388}
{"question": "Solve (124 + 915)", "answer": "The result of (124 + 915) is 1039\n\n####1039", "a": 124, "b": 915, "operator": "+", "result": 1039}
{"question": "Solve (519 / 602)", "answer": "The result of (519 / 602) is 0.8621\n\n####0.8621", "a": 519, "b": 602, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8621}
{"question": "Solve (849 * 565)", "answer": "The result of (849 * 565) is 479685\n\n####479685", "a": 849, "b": 565, "operator": "*", "result": 479685}
{"question": "Solve (564 + 10)", "answer": "The result of (564 + 10) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 564, "b": 10, "operator": "+", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (398 / 562)", "answer": "The result of (398 / 562) is 0.7082\n\n####0.7082", "a": 398, "b": 562, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7082}
{"question": "Solve (381 - 800)", "answer": "The result of (381 - 800) is -419\n\n####-419", "a": 381, "b": 800, "operator": "-", "result": -419}
{"question": "Solve (532 / 439)", "answer": "The result of (532 / 439) is 1.2118\n\n####1.2118", "a": 532, "b": 439, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2118}
{"question": "Solve (642 + 223)", "answer": "The result of (642 + 223) is 865\n\n####865", "a": 642, "b": 223, "operator": "+", "result": 865}
{"question": "Solve (794 - 644)", "answer": "The result of (794 - 644) is 150\n\n####150", "a": 794, "b": 644, "operator": "-", "result": 150}
{"question": "Solve (685 + 396)", "answer": "The result of (685 + 396) is 1081\n\n####1081", "a": 685, "b": 396, "operator": "+", "result": 1081}
{"question": "Solve (552 / 295)", "answer": "The result of (552 / 295) is 1.8712\n\n####1.8712", "a": 552, "b": 295, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8712}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 220)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 220) is 1106\n\n####1106", "a": 886, "b": 220, "operator": "+", "result": 1106}
{"question": "Solve (845 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (845 / 984) is 0.8587\n\n####0.8587", "a": 845, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8587}
{"question": "Solve (461 + 687)", "answer": "The result of (461 + 687) is 1148\n\n####1148", "a": 461, "b": 687, "operator": "+", "result": 1148}
{"question": "Solve (545 / 212)", "answer": "The result of (545 / 212) is 2.5708\n\n####2.5708", "a": 545, "b": 212, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5708}
{"question": "Solve (767 - 510)", "answer": "The result of (767 - 510) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 767, "b": 510, "operator": "-", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (697 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (697 * 407) is 283679\n\n####283679", "a": 697, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 283679}
{"question": "Solve (247 * 82)", "answer": "The result of (247 * 82) is 20254\n\n####20254", "a": 247, "b": 82, "operator": "*", "result": 20254}
{"question": "Solve (774 - 448)", "answer": "The result of (774 - 448) is 326\n\n####326", "a": 774, "b": 448, "operator": "-", "result": 326}
{"question": "Solve (784 / 471)", "answer": "The result of (784 / 471) is 1.6645\n\n####1.6645", "a": 784, "b": 471, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6645}
{"question": "Solve (932 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (932 / 206) is 4.5243\n\n####4.5243", "a": 932, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 4.5243}
{"question": "Solve (966 * 806)", "answer": "The result of (966 * 806) is 778596\n\n####778596", "a": 966, "b": 806, "operator": "*", "result": 778596}
{"question": "Solve (924 - 738)", "answer": "The result of (924 - 738) is 186\n\n####186", "a": 924, "b": 738, "operator": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve (703 - 189)", "answer": "The result of (703 - 189) is 514\n\n####514", "a": 703, "b": 189, "operator": "-", "result": 514}
{"question": "Solve (382 + 791)", "answer": "The result of (382 + 791) is 1173\n\n####1173", "a": 382, "b": 791, "operator": "+", "result": 1173}
{"question": "Solve (325 - 482)", "answer": "The result of (325 - 482) is -157\n\n####-157", "a": 325, "b": 482, "operator": "-", "result": -157}
{"question": "Solve (266 / 13)", "answer": "The result of (266 / 13) is 20.4615\n\n####20.4615", "a": 266, "b": 13, "operator": "/", "result": 20.4615}
{"question": "Solve (770 * 35)", "answer": "The result of (770 * 35) is 26950\n\n####26950", "a": 770, "b": 35, "operator": "*", "result": 26950}
{"question": "Solve (416 / 607)", "answer": "The result of (416 / 607) is 0.6853\n\n####0.6853", "a": 416, "b": 607, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6853}
{"question": "Solve (391 + 339)", "answer": "The result of (391 + 339) is 730\n\n####730", "a": 391, "b": 339, "operator": "+", "result": 730}
{"question": "Solve (427 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (427 / 891) is 0.4792\n\n####0.4792", "a": 427, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4792}
{"question": "Solve (173 * 108)", "answer": "The result of (173 * 108) is 18684\n\n####18684", "a": 173, "b": 108, "operator": "*", "result": 18684}
{"question": "Solve (62 - 62)", "answer": "The result of (62 - 62) is 0\n\n####0", "a": 62, "b": 62, "operator": "-", "result": 0}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 785)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 785) is 79285\n\n####79285", "a": 101, "b": 785, "operator": "*", "result": 79285}
{"question": "Solve (964 - 561)", "answer": "The result of (964 - 561) is 403\n\n####403", "a": 964, "b": 561, "operator": "-", "result": 403}
{"question": "Solve (268 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (268 - 245) is 23\n\n####23", "a": 268, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 23}
{"question": "Solve (513 / 626)", "answer": "The result of (513 / 626) is 0.8195\n\n####0.8195", "a": 513, "b": 626, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8195}
{"question": "Solve (362 + 193)", "answer": "The result of (362 + 193) is 555\n\n####555", "a": 362, "b": 193, "operator": "+", "result": 555}
{"question": "Solve (610 * 334)", "answer": "The result of (610 * 334) is 203740\n\n####203740", "a": 610, "b": 334, "operator": "*", "result": 203740}
{"question": "Solve (476 + 151)", "answer": "The result of (476 + 151) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 476, "b": 151, "operator": "+", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (424 * 66)", "answer": "The result of (424 * 66) is 27984\n\n####27984", "a": 424, "b": 66, "operator": "*", "result": 27984}
{"question": "Solve (657 - 407)", "answer": "The result of (657 - 407) is 250\n\n####250", "a": 657, "b": 407, "operator": "-", "result": 250}
{"question": "Solve (12 + 370)", "answer": "The result of (12 + 370) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 12, "b": 370, "operator": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (378 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (378 - 932) is -554\n\n####-554", "a": 378, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": -554}
{"question": "Solve (711 * 531)", "answer": "The result of (711 * 531) is 377541\n\n####377541", "a": 711, "b": 531, "operator": "*", "result": 377541}
{"question": "Solve (401 / 823)", "answer": "The result of (401 / 823) is 0.4872\n\n####0.4872", "a": 401, "b": 823, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4872}
{"question": "Solve (805 + 252)", "answer": "The result of (805 + 252) is 1057\n\n####1057", "a": 805, "b": 252, "operator": "+", "result": 1057}
{"question": "Solve (93 * 354)", "answer": "The result of (93 * 354) is 32922\n\n####32922", "a": 93, "b": 354, "operator": "*", "result": 32922}
{"question": "Solve (440 * 31)", "answer": "The result of (440 * 31) is 13640\n\n####13640", "a": 440, "b": 31, "operator": "*", "result": 13640}
{"question": "Solve (988 - 158)", "answer": "The result of (988 - 158) is 830\n\n####830", "a": 988, "b": 158, "operator": "-", "result": 830}
{"question": "Solve (267 + 63)", "answer": "The result of (267 + 63) is 330\n\n####330", "a": 267, "b": 63, "operator": "+", "result": 330}
{"question": "Solve (956 / 293)", "answer": "The result of (956 / 293) is 3.2628\n\n####3.2628", "a": 956, "b": 293, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2628}
{"question": "Solve (659 / 222)", "answer": "The result of (659 / 222) is 2.9685\n\n####2.9685", "a": 659, "b": 222, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9685}
{"question": "Solve (959 - 563)", "answer": "The result of (959 - 563) is 396\n\n####396", "a": 959, "b": 563, "operator": "-", "result": 396}
{"question": "Solve (448 / 218)", "answer": "The result of (448 / 218) is 2.055\n\n####2.055", "a": 448, "b": 218, "operator": "/", "result": 2.055}
{"question": "Solve (579 + 871)", "answer": "The result of (579 + 871) is 1450\n\n####1450", "a": 579, "b": 871, "operator": "+", "result": 1450}
{"question": "Solve (592 * 183)", "answer": "The result of (592 * 183) is 108336\n\n####108336", "a": 592, "b": 183, "operator": "*", "result": 108336}
{"question": "Solve (559 + 895)", "answer": "The result of (559 + 895) is 1454\n\n####1454", "a": 559, "b": 895, "operator": "+", "result": 1454}
{"question": "Solve (381 - 44)", "answer": "The result of (381 - 44) is 337\n\n####337", "a": 381, "b": 44, "operator": "-", "result": 337}
{"question": "Solve (947 / 883)", "answer": "The result of (947 / 883) is 1.0725\n\n####1.0725", "a": 947, "b": 883, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0725}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 986)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 986) is -662\n\n####-662", "a": 324, "b": 986, "operator": "-", "result": -662}
{"question": "Solve (179 + 928)", "answer": "The result of (179 + 928) is 1107\n\n####1107", "a": 179, "b": 928, "operator": "+", "result": 1107}
{"question": "Solve (149 - 842)", "answer": "The result of (149 - 842) is -693\n\n####-693", "a": 149, "b": 842, "operator": "-", "result": -693}
{"question": "Solve (413 + 253)", "answer": "The result of (413 + 253) is 666\n\n####666", "a": 413, "b": 253, "operator": "+", "result": 666}
{"question": "Solve (494 - 911)", "answer": "The result of (494 - 911) is -417\n\n####-417", "a": 494, "b": 911, "operator": "-", "result": -417}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 259)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 259) is 377\n\n####377", "a": 636, "b": 259, "operator": "-", "result": 377}
{"question": "Solve (624 / 613)", "answer": "The result of (624 / 613) is 1.0179\n\n####1.0179", "a": 624, "b": 613, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0179}
{"question": "Solve (137 * 599)", "answer": "The result of (137 * 599) is 82063\n\n####82063", "a": 137, "b": 599, "operator": "*", "result": 82063}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 277)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 277) is 2.4477\n\n####2.4477", "a": 678, "b": 277, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4477}
{"question": "Solve (231 / 923)", "answer": "The result of (231 / 923) is 0.2503\n\n####0.2503", "a": 231, "b": 923, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2503}
{"question": "Solve (640 - 552)", "answer": "The result of (640 - 552) is 88\n\n####88", "a": 640, "b": 552, "operator": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve (393 * 729)", "answer": "The result of (393 * 729) is 286497\n\n####286497", "a": 393, "b": 729, "operator": "*", "result": 286497}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 538)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 538) is -493\n\n####-493", "a": 45, "b": 538, "operator": "-", "result": -493}
{"question": "Solve (360 - 910)", "answer": "The result of (360 - 910) is -550\n\n####-550", "a": 360, "b": 910, "operator": "-", "result": -550}
{"question": "Solve (690 / 556)", "answer": "The result of (690 / 556) is 1.241\n\n####1.241", "a": 690, "b": 556, "operator": "/", "result": 1.241}
{"question": "Solve (140 - 170)", "answer": "The result of (140 - 170) is -30\n\n####-30", "a": 140, "b": 170, "operator": "-", "result": -30}
{"question": "Solve (247 * 763)", "answer": "The result of (247 * 763) is 188461\n\n####188461", "a": 247, "b": 763, "operator": "*", "result": 188461}
{"question": "Solve (443 / 977)", "answer": "The result of (443 / 977) is 0.4534\n\n####0.4534", "a": 443, "b": 977, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4534}
{"question": "Solve (559 * 450)", "answer": "The result of (559 * 450) is 251550\n\n####251550", "a": 559, "b": 450, "operator": "*", "result": 251550}
{"question": "Solve (717 + 466)", "answer": "The result of (717 + 466) is 1183\n\n####1183", "a": 717, "b": 466, "operator": "+", "result": 1183}
{"question": "Solve (783 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (783 / 322) is 2.4317\n\n####2.4317", "a": 783, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4317}
{"question": "Solve (520 / 94)", "answer": "The result of (520 / 94) is 5.5319\n\n####5.5319", "a": 520, "b": 94, "operator": "/", "result": 5.5319}
{"question": "Solve (527 / 104)", "answer": "The result of (527 / 104) is 5.0673\n\n####5.0673", "a": 527, "b": 104, "operator": "/", "result": 5.0673}
{"question": "Solve (276 * 888)", "answer": "The result of (276 * 888) is 245088\n\n####245088", "a": 276, "b": 888, "operator": "*", "result": 245088}
{"question": "Solve (702 + 351)", "answer": "The result of (702 + 351) is 1053\n\n####1053", "a": 702, "b": 351, "operator": "+", "result": 1053}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 864)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 864) is 1541\n\n####1541", "a": 677, "b": 864, "operator": "+", "result": 1541}
{"question": "Solve (635 + 48)", "answer": "The result of (635 + 48) is 683\n\n####683", "a": 635, "b": 48, "operator": "+", "result": 683}
{"question": "Solve (671 * 474)", "answer": "The result of (671 * 474) is 318054\n\n####318054", "a": 671, "b": 474, "operator": "*", "result": 318054}
{"question": "Solve (116 - 618)", "answer": "The result of (116 - 618) is -502\n\n####-502", "a": 116, "b": 618, "operator": "-", "result": -502}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 817)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 817) is 0.8299\n\n####0.8299", "a": 678, "b": 817, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8299}
{"question": "Solve (213 / 90)", "answer": "The result of (213 / 90) is 2.3667\n\n####2.3667", "a": 213, "b": 90, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3667}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 751) is -494\n\n####-494", "a": 257, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": -494}
{"question": "Solve (167 + 986)", "answer": "The result of (167 + 986) is 1153\n\n####1153", "a": 167, "b": 986, "operator": "+", "result": 1153}
{"question": "Solve (817 / 974)", "answer": "The result of (817 / 974) is 0.8388\n\n####0.8388", "a": 817, "b": 974, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8388}
{"question": "Solve (515 * 344)", "answer": "The result of (515 * 344) is 177160\n\n####177160", "a": 515, "b": 344, "operator": "*", "result": 177160}
{"question": "Solve (623 * 411)", "answer": "The result of (623 * 411) is 256053\n\n####256053", "a": 623, "b": 411, "operator": "*", "result": 256053}
{"question": "Solve (28 - 635)", "answer": "The result of (28 - 635) is -607\n\n####-607", "a": 28, "b": 635, "operator": "-", "result": -607}
{"question": "Solve (447 / 435)", "answer": "The result of (447 / 435) is 1.0276\n\n####1.0276", "a": 447, "b": 435, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0276}
{"question": "Solve (497 * 375)", "answer": "The result of (497 * 375) is 186375\n\n####186375", "a": 497, "b": 375, "operator": "*", "result": 186375}
{"question": "Solve (419 / 566)", "answer": "The result of (419 / 566) is 0.7403\n\n####0.7403", "a": 419, "b": 566, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7403}
{"question": "Solve (458 / 242)", "answer": "The result of (458 / 242) is 1.8926\n\n####1.8926", "a": 458, "b": 242, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8926}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 250)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 250) is 101750\n\n####101750", "a": 407, "b": 250, "operator": "*", "result": 101750}
{"question": "Solve (465 * 728)", "answer": "The result of (465 * 728) is 338520\n\n####338520", "a": 465, "b": 728, "operator": "*", "result": 338520}
{"question": "Solve (790 / 401)", "answer": "The result of (790 / 401) is 1.9701\n\n####1.9701", "a": 790, "b": 401, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9701}
{"question": "Solve (650 * 668)", "answer": "The result of (650 * 668) is 434200\n\n####434200", "a": 650, "b": 668, "operator": "*", "result": 434200}
{"question": "Solve (989 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (989 / 891) is 1.11\n\n####1.11", "a": 989, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 1.11}
{"question": "Solve (967 / 374)", "answer": "The result of (967 / 374) is 2.5856\n\n####2.5856", "a": 967, "b": 374, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5856}
{"question": "Solve (405 / 742)", "answer": "The result of (405 / 742) is 0.5458\n\n####0.5458", "a": 405, "b": 742, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5458}
{"question": "Solve (679 - 901)", "answer": "The result of (679 - 901) is -222\n\n####-222", "a": 679, "b": 901, "operator": "-", "result": -222}
{"question": "Solve (739 / 291)", "answer": "The result of (739 / 291) is 2.5395\n\n####2.5395", "a": 739, "b": 291, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5395}
{"question": "Solve (290 / 46)", "answer": "The result of (290 / 46) is 6.3043\n\n####6.3043", "a": 290, "b": 46, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3043}
{"question": "Solve (955 + 814)", "answer": "The result of (955 + 814) is 1769\n\n####1769", "a": 955, "b": 814, "operator": "+", "result": 1769}
{"question": "Solve (927 / 434)", "answer": "The result of (927 / 434) is 2.1359\n\n####2.1359", "a": 927, "b": 434, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1359}
{"question": "Solve (539 + 120)", "answer": "The result of (539 + 120) is 659\n\n####659", "a": 539, "b": 120, "operator": "+", "result": 659}
{"question": "Solve (668 - 199)", "answer": "The result of (668 - 199) is 469\n\n####469", "a": 668, "b": 199, "operator": "-", "result": 469}
{"question": "Solve (637 + 916)", "answer": "The result of (637 + 916) is 1553\n\n####1553", "a": 637, "b": 916, "operator": "+", "result": 1553}
{"question": "Solve (688 * 971)", "answer": "The result of (688 * 971) is 668048\n\n####668048", "a": 688, "b": 971, "operator": "*", "result": 668048}
{"question": "Solve (579 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (579 - 802) is -223\n\n####-223", "a": 579, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -223}
{"question": "Solve (769 / 265)", "answer": "The result of (769 / 265) is 2.9019\n\n####2.9019", "a": 769, "b": 265, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9019}
{"question": "Solve (562 + 24)", "answer": "The result of (562 + 24) is 586\n\n####586", "a": 562, "b": 24, "operator": "+", "result": 586}
{"question": "Solve (13 / 552)", "answer": "The result of (13 / 552) is 0.0236\n\n####0.0236", "a": 13, "b": 552, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0236}
{"question": "Solve (551 - 657)", "answer": "The result of (551 - 657) is -106\n\n####-106", "a": 551, "b": 657, "operator": "-", "result": -106}
{"question": "Solve (60 * 84)", "answer": "The result of (60 * 84) is 5040\n\n####5040", "a": 60, "b": 84, "operator": "*", "result": 5040}
{"question": "Solve (51 - 456)", "answer": "The result of (51 - 456) is -405\n\n####-405", "a": 51, "b": 456, "operator": "-", "result": -405}
{"question": "Solve (728 - 684)", "answer": "The result of (728 - 684) is 44\n\n####44", "a": 728, "b": 684, "operator": "-", "result": 44}
{"question": "Solve (103 * 124)", "answer": "The result of (103 * 124) is 12772\n\n####12772", "a": 103, "b": 124, "operator": "*", "result": 12772}
{"question": "Solve (510 * 761)", "answer": "The result of (510 * 761) is 388110\n\n####388110", "a": 510, "b": 761, "operator": "*", "result": 388110}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 571)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 571) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 358, "b": 571, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (290 + 680)", "answer": "The result of (290 + 680) is 970\n\n####970", "a": 290, "b": 680, "operator": "+", "result": 970}
{"question": "Solve (155 - 179)", "answer": "The result of (155 - 179) is -24\n\n####-24", "a": 155, "b": 179, "operator": "-", "result": -24}
{"question": "Solve (625 - 786)", "answer": "The result of (625 - 786) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 625, "b": 786, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (809 * 212)", "answer": "The result of (809 * 212) is 171508\n\n####171508", "a": 809, "b": 212, "operator": "*", "result": 171508}
{"question": "Solve (69 - 584)", "answer": "The result of (69 - 584) is -515\n\n####-515", "a": 69, "b": 584, "operator": "-", "result": -515}
{"question": "Solve (814 * 947)", "answer": "The result of (814 * 947) is 770858\n\n####770858", "a": 814, "b": 947, "operator": "*", "result": 770858}
{"question": "Solve (740 + 806)", "answer": "The result of (740 + 806) is 1546\n\n####1546", "a": 740, "b": 806, "operator": "+", "result": 1546}
{"question": "Solve (614 - 920)", "answer": "The result of (614 - 920) is -306\n\n####-306", "a": 614, "b": 920, "operator": "-", "result": -306}
{"question": "Solve (195 + 248)", "answer": "The result of (195 + 248) is 443\n\n####443", "a": 195, "b": 248, "operator": "+", "result": 443}
{"question": "Solve (787 / 524)", "answer": "The result of (787 / 524) is 1.5019\n\n####1.5019", "a": 787, "b": 524, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5019}
{"question": "Solve (534 + 331)", "answer": "The result of (534 + 331) is 865\n\n####865", "a": 534, "b": 331, "operator": "+", "result": 865}
{"question": "Solve (111 - 529)", "answer": "The result of (111 - 529) is -418\n\n####-418", "a": 111, "b": 529, "operator": "-", "result": -418}
{"question": "Solve (805 + 956)", "answer": "The result of (805 + 956) is 1761\n\n####1761", "a": 805, "b": 956, "operator": "+", "result": 1761}
{"question": "Solve (436 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (436 + 259) is 695\n\n####695", "a": 436, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 695}
{"question": "Solve (235 / 57)", "answer": "The result of (235 / 57) is 4.1228\n\n####4.1228", "a": 235, "b": 57, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1228}
{"question": "Solve (104 * 176)", "answer": "The result of (104 * 176) is 18304\n\n####18304", "a": 104, "b": 176, "operator": "*", "result": 18304}
{"question": "Solve (216 + 128)", "answer": "The result of (216 + 128) is 344\n\n####344", "a": 216, "b": 128, "operator": "+", "result": 344}
{"question": "Solve (273 + 693)", "answer": "The result of (273 + 693) is 966\n\n####966", "a": 273, "b": 693, "operator": "+", "result": 966}
{"question": "Solve (617 + 399)", "answer": "The result of (617 + 399) is 1016\n\n####1016", "a": 617, "b": 399, "operator": "+", "result": 1016}
{"question": "Solve (646 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (646 / 873) is 0.74\n\n####0.74", "a": 646, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 0.74}
{"question": "Solve (533 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (533 / 53) is 10.0566\n\n####10.0566", "a": 533, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 10.0566}
{"question": "Solve (127 + 546)", "answer": "The result of (127 + 546) is 673\n\n####673", "a": 127, "b": 546, "operator": "+", "result": 673}
{"question": "Solve (847 - 813)", "answer": "The result of (847 - 813) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 847, "b": 813, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (637 * 190)", "answer": "The result of (637 * 190) is 121030\n\n####121030", "a": 637, "b": 190, "operator": "*", "result": 121030}
{"question": "Solve (833 * 804)", "answer": "The result of (833 * 804) is 669732\n\n####669732", "a": 833, "b": 804, "operator": "*", "result": 669732}
{"question": "Solve (258 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (258 - 825) is -567\n\n####-567", "a": 258, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": -567}
{"question": "Solve (169 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (169 - 492) is -323\n\n####-323", "a": 169, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": -323}
{"question": "Solve (563 * 677)", "answer": "The result of (563 * 677) is 381151\n\n####381151", "a": 563, "b": 677, "operator": "*", "result": 381151}
{"question": "Solve (539 + 193)", "answer": "The result of (539 + 193) is 732\n\n####732", "a": 539, "b": 193, "operator": "+", "result": 732}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 560)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 560) is 227920\n\n####227920", "a": 407, "b": 560, "operator": "*", "result": 227920}
{"question": "Solve (889 - 887)", "answer": "The result of (889 - 887) is 2\n\n####2", "a": 889, "b": 887, "operator": "-", "result": 2}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 807)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 807) is -700\n\n####-700", "a": 107, "b": 807, "operator": "-", "result": -700}
{"question": "Solve (422 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (422 - 756) is -334\n\n####-334", "a": 422, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -334}
{"question": "Solve (373 / 95)", "answer": "The result of (373 / 95) is 3.9263\n\n####3.9263", "a": 373, "b": 95, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9263}
{"question": "Solve (847 - 422)", "answer": "The result of (847 - 422) is 425\n\n####425", "a": 847, "b": 422, "operator": "-", "result": 425}
{"question": "Solve (322 / 591)", "answer": "The result of (322 / 591) is 0.5448\n\n####0.5448", "a": 322, "b": 591, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5448}
{"question": "Solve (823 / 85)", "answer": "The result of (823 / 85) is 9.6824\n\n####9.6824", "a": 823, "b": 85, "operator": "/", "result": 9.6824}
{"question": "Solve (7 * 645)", "answer": "The result of (7 * 645) is 4515\n\n####4515", "a": 7, "b": 645, "operator": "*", "result": 4515}
{"question": "Solve (420 + 263)", "answer": "The result of (420 + 263) is 683\n\n####683", "a": 420, "b": 263, "operator": "+", "result": 683}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 433)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 433) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 297, "b": 433, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (889 - 599)", "answer": "The result of (889 - 599) is 290\n\n####290", "a": 889, "b": 599, "operator": "-", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve (486 * 563)", "answer": "The result of (486 * 563) is 273618\n\n####273618", "a": 486, "b": 563, "operator": "*", "result": 273618}
{"question": "Solve (885 * 569)", "answer": "The result of (885 * 569) is 503565\n\n####503565", "a": 885, "b": 569, "operator": "*", "result": 503565}
{"question": "Solve (716 * 534)", "answer": "The result of (716 * 534) is 382344\n\n####382344", "a": 716, "b": 534, "operator": "*", "result": 382344}
{"question": "Solve (86 * 571)", "answer": "The result of (86 * 571) is 49106\n\n####49106", "a": 86, "b": 571, "operator": "*", "result": 49106}
{"question": "Solve (854 * 519)", "answer": "The result of (854 * 519) is 443226\n\n####443226", "a": 854, "b": 519, "operator": "*", "result": 443226}
{"question": "Solve (842 / 488)", "answer": "The result of (842 / 488) is 1.7254\n\n####1.7254", "a": 842, "b": 488, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7254}
{"question": "Solve (219 + 393)", "answer": "The result of (219 + 393) is 612\n\n####612", "a": 219, "b": 393, "operator": "+", "result": 612}
{"question": "Solve (274 - 637)", "answer": "The result of (274 - 637) is -363\n\n####-363", "a": 274, "b": 637, "operator": "-", "result": -363}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 50)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 50) is 565\n\n####565", "a": 615, "b": 50, "operator": "-", "result": 565}
{"question": "Solve (906 * 587)", "answer": "The result of (906 * 587) is 531822\n\n####531822", "a": 906, "b": 587, "operator": "*", "result": 531822}
{"question": "Solve (565 - 689)", "answer": "The result of (565 - 689) is -124\n\n####-124", "a": 565, "b": 689, "operator": "-", "result": -124}
{"question": "Solve (864 * 147)", "answer": "The result of (864 * 147) is 127008\n\n####127008", "a": 864, "b": 147, "operator": "*", "result": 127008}
{"question": "Solve (195 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (195 / 567) is 0.3439\n\n####0.3439", "a": 195, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3439}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 768) is 1.263\n\n####1.263", "a": 970, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 1.263}
{"question": "Solve (989 + 204)", "answer": "The result of (989 + 204) is 1193\n\n####1193", "a": 989, "b": 204, "operator": "+", "result": 1193}
{"question": "Solve (711 + 738)", "answer": "The result of (711 + 738) is 1449\n\n####1449", "a": 711, "b": 738, "operator": "+", "result": 1449}
{"question": "Solve (748 + 295)", "answer": "The result of (748 + 295) is 1043\n\n####1043", "a": 748, "b": 295, "operator": "+", "result": 1043}
{"question": "Solve (664 * 474)", "answer": "The result of (664 * 474) is 314736\n\n####314736", "a": 664, "b": 474, "operator": "*", "result": 314736}
{"question": "Solve (900 / 1)", "answer": "The result of (900 / 1) is 900.0\n\n####900.0", "a": 900, "b": 1, "operator": "/", "result": 900.0}
{"question": "Solve (228 * 681)", "answer": "The result of (228 * 681) is 155268\n\n####155268", "a": 228, "b": 681, "operator": "*", "result": 155268}
{"question": "Solve (749 * 627)", "answer": "The result of (749 * 627) is 469623\n\n####469623", "a": 749, "b": 627, "operator": "*", "result": 469623}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 312)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 312) is 254\n\n####254", "a": 566, "b": 312, "operator": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve (411 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (411 * 596) is 244956\n\n####244956", "a": 411, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 244956}
{"question": "Solve (789 + 167)", "answer": "The result of (789 + 167) is 956\n\n####956", "a": 789, "b": 167, "operator": "+", "result": 956}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 392)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 392) is 83104\n\n####83104", "a": 212, "b": 392, "operator": "*", "result": 83104}
{"question": "Solve (567 + 652)", "answer": "The result of (567 + 652) is 1219\n\n####1219", "a": 567, "b": 652, "operator": "+", "result": 1219}
{"question": "Solve (489 + 318)", "answer": "The result of (489 + 318) is 807\n\n####807", "a": 489, "b": 318, "operator": "+", "result": 807}
{"question": "Solve (776 - 64)", "answer": "The result of (776 - 64) is 712\n\n####712", "a": 776, "b": 64, "operator": "-", "result": 712}
{"question": "Solve (844 - 695)", "answer": "The result of (844 - 695) is 149\n\n####149", "a": 844, "b": 695, "operator": "-", "result": 149}
{"question": "Solve (129 / 405)", "answer": "The result of (129 / 405) is 0.3185\n\n####0.3185", "a": 129, "b": 405, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3185}
{"question": "Solve (353 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (353 - 449) is -96\n\n####-96", "a": 353, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": -96}
{"question": "Solve (596 + 789)", "answer": "The result of (596 + 789) is 1385\n\n####1385", "a": 596, "b": 789, "operator": "+", "result": 1385}
{"question": "Solve (770 * 395)", "answer": "The result of (770 * 395) is 304150\n\n####304150", "a": 770, "b": 395, "operator": "*", "result": 304150}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 40)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 40) is 3.4\n\n####3.4", "a": 136, "b": 40, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4}
{"question": "Solve (185 / 868)", "answer": "The result of (185 / 868) is 0.2131\n\n####0.2131", "a": 185, "b": 868, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2131}
{"question": "Solve (961 * 571)", "answer": "The result of (961 * 571) is 548731\n\n####548731", "a": 961, "b": 571, "operator": "*", "result": 548731}
{"question": "Solve (50 - 424)", "answer": "The result of (50 - 424) is -374\n\n####-374", "a": 50, "b": 424, "operator": "-", "result": -374}
{"question": "Solve (195 + 264)", "answer": "The result of (195 + 264) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 195, "b": 264, "operator": "+", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (411 - 785)", "answer": "The result of (411 - 785) is -374\n\n####-374", "a": 411, "b": 785, "operator": "-", "result": -374}
{"question": "Solve (517 + 145)", "answer": "The result of (517 + 145) is 662\n\n####662", "a": 517, "b": 145, "operator": "+", "result": 662}
{"question": "Solve (41 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (41 / 567) is 0.0723\n\n####0.0723", "a": 41, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0723}
{"question": "Solve (796 * 107)", "answer": "The result of (796 * 107) is 85172\n\n####85172", "a": 796, "b": 107, "operator": "*", "result": 85172}
{"question": "Solve (158 - 367)", "answer": "The result of (158 - 367) is -209\n\n####-209", "a": 158, "b": 367, "operator": "-", "result": -209}
{"question": "Solve (901 + 741)", "answer": "The result of (901 + 741) is 1642\n\n####1642", "a": 901, "b": 741, "operator": "+", "result": 1642}
{"question": "Solve (993 - 165)", "answer": "The result of (993 - 165) is 828\n\n####828", "a": 993, "b": 165, "operator": "-", "result": 828}
{"question": "Solve (818 / 125)", "answer": "The result of (818 / 125) is 6.544\n\n####6.544", "a": 818, "b": 125, "operator": "/", "result": 6.544}
{"question": "Solve (480 - 153)", "answer": "The result of (480 - 153) is 327\n\n####327", "a": 480, "b": 153, "operator": "-", "result": 327}
{"question": "Solve (525 - 57)", "answer": "The result of (525 - 57) is 468\n\n####468", "a": 525, "b": 57, "operator": "-", "result": 468}
{"question": "Solve (429 / 877)", "answer": "The result of (429 / 877) is 0.4892\n\n####0.4892", "a": 429, "b": 877, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4892}
{"question": "Solve (744 * 255)", "answer": "The result of (744 * 255) is 189720\n\n####189720", "a": 744, "b": 255, "operator": "*", "result": 189720}
{"question": "Solve (658 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (658 - 166) is 492\n\n####492", "a": 658, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 492}
{"question": "Solve (204 / 296)", "answer": "The result of (204 / 296) is 0.6892\n\n####0.6892", "a": 204, "b": 296, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6892}
{"question": "Solve (622 / 233)", "answer": "The result of (622 / 233) is 2.6695\n\n####2.6695", "a": 622, "b": 233, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6695}
{"question": "Solve (19 / 187)", "answer": "The result of (19 / 187) is 0.1016\n\n####0.1016", "a": 19, "b": 187, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1016}
{"question": "Solve (690 - 560)", "answer": "The result of (690 - 560) is 130\n\n####130", "a": 690, "b": 560, "operator": "-", "result": 130}
{"question": "Solve (882 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (882 * 939) is 828198\n\n####828198", "a": 882, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 828198}
{"question": "Solve (666 * 506)", "answer": "The result of (666 * 506) is 336996\n\n####336996", "a": 666, "b": 506, "operator": "*", "result": 336996}
{"question": "Solve (133 / 439)", "answer": "The result of (133 / 439) is 0.303\n\n####0.303", "a": 133, "b": 439, "operator": "/", "result": 0.303}
{"question": "Solve (210 - 840)", "answer": "The result of (210 - 840) is -630\n\n####-630", "a": 210, "b": 840, "operator": "-", "result": -630}
{"question": "Solve (890 / 293)", "answer": "The result of (890 / 293) is 3.0375\n\n####3.0375", "a": 890, "b": 293, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0375}
{"question": "Solve (752 - 808)", "answer": "The result of (752 - 808) is -56\n\n####-56", "a": 752, "b": 808, "operator": "-", "result": -56}
{"question": "Solve (148 + 485)", "answer": "The result of (148 + 485) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 148, "b": 485, "operator": "+", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (206 - 865)", "answer": "The result of (206 - 865) is -659\n\n####-659", "a": 206, "b": 865, "operator": "-", "result": -659}
{"question": "Solve (190 * 30)", "answer": "The result of (190 * 30) is 5700\n\n####5700", "a": 190, "b": 30, "operator": "*", "result": 5700}
{"question": "Solve (333 * 252)", "answer": "The result of (333 * 252) is 83916\n\n####83916", "a": 333, "b": 252, "operator": "*", "result": 83916}
{"question": "Solve (468 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (468 / 768) is 0.6094\n\n####0.6094", "a": 468, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6094}
{"question": "Solve (392 - 632)", "answer": "The result of (392 - 632) is -240\n\n####-240", "a": 392, "b": 632, "operator": "-", "result": -240}
{"question": "Solve (627 / 495)", "answer": "The result of (627 / 495) is 1.2667\n\n####1.2667", "a": 627, "b": 495, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2667}
{"question": "Solve (76 - 436)", "answer": "The result of (76 - 436) is -360\n\n####-360", "a": 76, "b": 436, "operator": "-", "result": -360}
{"question": "Solve (333 / 332)", "answer": "The result of (333 / 332) is 1.003\n\n####1.003", "a": 333, "b": 332, "operator": "/", "result": 1.003}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 628)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 628) is 283856\n\n####283856", "a": 452, "b": 628, "operator": "*", "result": 283856}
{"question": "Solve (610 * 64)", "answer": "The result of (610 * 64) is 39040\n\n####39040", "a": 610, "b": 64, "operator": "*", "result": 39040}
{"question": "Solve (540 * 774)", "answer": "The result of (540 * 774) is 417960\n\n####417960", "a": 540, "b": 774, "operator": "*", "result": 417960}
{"question": "Solve (428 * 960)", "answer": "The result of (428 * 960) is 410880\n\n####410880", "a": 428, "b": 960, "operator": "*", "result": 410880}
{"question": "Solve (902 - 93)", "answer": "The result of (902 - 93) is 809\n\n####809", "a": 902, "b": 93, "operator": "-", "result": 809}
{"question": "Solve (971 + 582)", "answer": "The result of (971 + 582) is 1553\n\n####1553", "a": 971, "b": 582, "operator": "+", "result": 1553}
{"question": "Solve (793 / 530)", "answer": "The result of (793 / 530) is 1.4962\n\n####1.4962", "a": 793, "b": 530, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4962}
{"question": "Solve (417 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (417 * 251) is 104667\n\n####104667", "a": 417, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 104667}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 938)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 938) is 0.3316\n\n####0.3316", "a": 311, "b": 938, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3316}
{"question": "Solve (868 - 900)", "answer": "The result of (868 - 900) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 868, "b": 900, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 2) is 529\n\n####529", "a": 531, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 529}
{"question": "Solve (860 / 857)", "answer": "The result of (860 / 857) is 1.0035\n\n####1.0035", "a": 860, "b": 857, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0035}
{"question": "Solve (756 + 643)", "answer": "The result of (756 + 643) is 1399\n\n####1399", "a": 756, "b": 643, "operator": "+", "result": 1399}
{"question": "Solve (100 + 20)", "answer": "The result of (100 + 20) is 120\n\n####120", "a": 100, "b": 20, "operator": "+", "result": 120}
{"question": "Solve (144 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (144 / 230) is 0.6261\n\n####0.6261", "a": 144, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6261}
{"question": "Solve (109 - 854)", "answer": "The result of (109 - 854) is -745\n\n####-745", "a": 109, "b": 854, "operator": "-", "result": -745}
{"question": "Solve (395 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (395 - 449) is -54\n\n####-54", "a": 395, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": -54}
{"question": "Solve (774 - 704)", "answer": "The result of (774 - 704) is 70\n\n####70", "a": 774, "b": 704, "operator": "-", "result": 70}
{"question": "Solve (809 * 651)", "answer": "The result of (809 * 651) is 526659\n\n####526659", "a": 809, "b": 651, "operator": "*", "result": 526659}
{"question": "Solve (349 * 413)", "answer": "The result of (349 * 413) is 144137\n\n####144137", "a": 349, "b": 413, "operator": "*", "result": 144137}
{"question": "Solve (993 * 721)", "answer": "The result of (993 * 721) is 715953\n\n####715953", "a": 993, "b": 721, "operator": "*", "result": 715953}
{"question": "Solve (897 - 244)", "answer": "The result of (897 - 244) is 653\n\n####653", "a": 897, "b": 244, "operator": "-", "result": 653}
{"question": "Solve (187 - 772)", "answer": "The result of (187 - 772) is -585\n\n####-585", "a": 187, "b": 772, "operator": "-", "result": -585}
{"question": "Solve (589 / 792)", "answer": "The result of (589 / 792) is 0.7437\n\n####0.7437", "a": 589, "b": 792, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7437}
{"question": "Solve (46 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (46 * 870) is 40020\n\n####40020", "a": 46, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 40020}
{"question": "Solve (495 + 832)", "answer": "The result of (495 + 832) is 1327\n\n####1327", "a": 495, "b": 832, "operator": "+", "result": 1327}
{"question": "Solve (484 * 811)", "answer": "The result of (484 * 811) is 392524\n\n####392524", "a": 484, "b": 811, "operator": "*", "result": 392524}
{"question": "Solve (226 / 856)", "answer": "The result of (226 / 856) is 0.264\n\n####0.264", "a": 226, "b": 856, "operator": "/", "result": 0.264}
{"question": "Solve (167 - 388)", "answer": "The result of (167 - 388) is -221\n\n####-221", "a": 167, "b": 388, "operator": "-", "result": -221}
{"question": "Solve (295 + 614)", "answer": "The result of (295 + 614) is 909\n\n####909", "a": 295, "b": 614, "operator": "+", "result": 909}
{"question": "Solve (749 / 449)", "answer": "The result of (749 / 449) is 1.6682\n\n####1.6682", "a": 749, "b": 449, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6682}
{"question": "Solve (335 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (335 + 868) is 1203\n\n####1203", "a": 335, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 1203}
{"question": "Solve (789 * 243)", "answer": "The result of (789 * 243) is 191727\n\n####191727", "a": 789, "b": 243, "operator": "*", "result": 191727}
{"question": "Solve (316 * 314)", "answer": "The result of (316 * 314) is 99224\n\n####99224", "a": 316, "b": 314, "operator": "*", "result": 99224}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 743)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 743) is 157516\n\n####157516", "a": 212, "b": 743, "operator": "*", "result": 157516}
{"question": "Solve (401 / 652)", "answer": "The result of (401 / 652) is 0.615\n\n####0.615", "a": 401, "b": 652, "operator": "/", "result": 0.615}
{"question": "Solve (162 * 258)", "answer": "The result of (162 * 258) is 41796\n\n####41796", "a": 162, "b": 258, "operator": "*", "result": 41796}
{"question": "Solve (802 / 343)", "answer": "The result of (802 / 343) is 2.3382\n\n####2.3382", "a": 802, "b": 343, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3382}
{"question": "Solve (325 - 702)", "answer": "The result of (325 - 702) is -377\n\n####-377", "a": 325, "b": 702, "operator": "-", "result": -377}
{"question": "Solve (821 - 657)", "answer": "The result of (821 - 657) is 164\n\n####164", "a": 821, "b": 657, "operator": "-", "result": 164}
{"question": "Solve (644 / 911)", "answer": "The result of (644 / 911) is 0.7069\n\n####0.7069", "a": 644, "b": 911, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7069}
{"question": "Solve (531 + 988)", "answer": "The result of (531 + 988) is 1519\n\n####1519", "a": 531, "b": 988, "operator": "+", "result": 1519}
{"question": "Solve (999 + 125)", "answer": "The result of (999 + 125) is 1124\n\n####1124", "a": 999, "b": 125, "operator": "+", "result": 1124}
{"question": "Solve (318 + 453)", "answer": "The result of (318 + 453) is 771\n\n####771", "a": 318, "b": 453, "operator": "+", "result": 771}
{"question": "Solve (723 - 429)", "answer": "The result of (723 - 429) is 294\n\n####294", "a": 723, "b": 429, "operator": "-", "result": 294}
{"question": "Solve (890 - 278)", "answer": "The result of (890 - 278) is 612\n\n####612", "a": 890, "b": 278, "operator": "-", "result": 612}
{"question": "Solve (978 - 930)", "answer": "The result of (978 - 930) is 48\n\n####48", "a": 978, "b": 930, "operator": "-", "result": 48}
{"question": "Solve (397 / 208)", "answer": "The result of (397 / 208) is 1.9087\n\n####1.9087", "a": 397, "b": 208, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9087}
{"question": "Solve (945 / 790)", "answer": "The result of (945 / 790) is 1.1962\n\n####1.1962", "a": 945, "b": 790, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1962}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 505)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 505) is 353\n\n####353", "a": 858, "b": 505, "operator": "-", "result": 353}
{"question": "Solve (55 / 795)", "answer": "The result of (55 / 795) is 0.0692\n\n####0.0692", "a": 55, "b": 795, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0692}
{"question": "Solve (956 - 719)", "answer": "The result of (956 - 719) is 237\n\n####237", "a": 956, "b": 719, "operator": "-", "result": 237}
{"question": "Solve (605 * 683)", "answer": "The result of (605 * 683) is 413215\n\n####413215", "a": 605, "b": 683, "operator": "*", "result": 413215}
{"question": "Solve (343 / 123)", "answer": "The result of (343 / 123) is 2.7886\n\n####2.7886", "a": 343, "b": 123, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7886}
{"question": "Solve (956 - 864)", "answer": "The result of (956 - 864) is 92\n\n####92", "a": 956, "b": 864, "operator": "-", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve (214 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (214 * 387) is 82818\n\n####82818", "a": 214, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 82818}
{"question": "Solve (347 * 888)", "answer": "The result of (347 * 888) is 308136\n\n####308136", "a": 347, "b": 888, "operator": "*", "result": 308136}
{"question": "Solve (125 * 994)", "answer": "The result of (125 * 994) is 124250\n\n####124250", "a": 125, "b": 994, "operator": "*", "result": 124250}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 550)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 550) is -457\n\n####-457", "a": 93, "b": 550, "operator": "-", "result": -457}
{"question": "Solve (886 * 486)", "answer": "The result of (886 * 486) is 430596\n\n####430596", "a": 886, "b": 486, "operator": "*", "result": 430596}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 184)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 184) is 3128\n\n####3128", "a": 17, "b": 184, "operator": "*", "result": 3128}
{"question": "Solve (393 + 308)", "answer": "The result of (393 + 308) is 701\n\n####701", "a": 393, "b": 308, "operator": "+", "result": 701}
{"question": "Solve (304 / 935)", "answer": "The result of (304 / 935) is 0.3251\n\n####0.3251", "a": 304, "b": 935, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3251}
{"question": "Solve (946 - 223)", "answer": "The result of (946 - 223) is 723\n\n####723", "a": 946, "b": 223, "operator": "-", "result": 723}
{"question": "Solve (725 / 392)", "answer": "The result of (725 / 392) is 1.8495\n\n####1.8495", "a": 725, "b": 392, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8495}
{"question": "Solve (146 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (146 / 891) is 0.1639\n\n####0.1639", "a": 146, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1639}
{"question": "Solve (263 + 299)", "answer": "The result of (263 + 299) is 562\n\n####562", "a": 263, "b": 299, "operator": "+", "result": 562}
{"question": "Solve (866 - 795)", "answer": "The result of (866 - 795) is 71\n\n####71", "a": 866, "b": 795, "operator": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve (655 - 987)", "answer": "The result of (655 - 987) is -332\n\n####-332", "a": 655, "b": 987, "operator": "-", "result": -332}
{"question": "Solve (168 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (168 / 821) is 0.2046\n\n####0.2046", "a": 168, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2046}
{"question": "Solve (933 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (933 - 537) is 396\n\n####396", "a": 933, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": 396}
{"question": "Solve (322 + 405)", "answer": "The result of (322 + 405) is 727\n\n####727", "a": 322, "b": 405, "operator": "+", "result": 727}
{"question": "Solve (820 / 226)", "answer": "The result of (820 / 226) is 3.6283\n\n####3.6283", "a": 820, "b": 226, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6283}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 555)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 555) is 0.764\n\n####0.764", "a": 424, "b": 555, "operator": "/", "result": 0.764}
{"question": "Solve (149 - 8)", "answer": "The result of (149 - 8) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 149, "b": 8, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (718 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (718 / 236) is 3.0424\n\n####3.0424", "a": 718, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0424}
{"question": "Solve (643 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (643 * 884) is 568412\n\n####568412", "a": 643, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 568412}
{"question": "Solve (498 + 653)", "answer": "The result of (498 + 653) is 1151\n\n####1151", "a": 498, "b": 653, "operator": "+", "result": 1151}
{"question": "Solve (996 - 272)", "answer": "The result of (996 - 272) is 724\n\n####724", "a": 996, "b": 272, "operator": "-", "result": 724}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 862)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 862) is -268\n\n####-268", "a": 594, "b": 862, "operator": "-", "result": -268}
{"question": "Solve (213 + 883)", "answer": "The result of (213 + 883) is 1096\n\n####1096", "a": 213, "b": 883, "operator": "+", "result": 1096}
{"question": "Solve (399 * 451)", "answer": "The result of (399 * 451) is 179949\n\n####179949", "a": 399, "b": 451, "operator": "*", "result": 179949}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 219)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 219) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 476, "b": 219, "operator": "-", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (802 * 818)", "answer": "The result of (802 * 818) is 656036\n\n####656036", "a": 802, "b": 818, "operator": "*", "result": 656036}
{"question": "Solve (847 / 444)", "answer": "The result of (847 / 444) is 1.9077\n\n####1.9077", "a": 847, "b": 444, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9077}
{"question": "Solve (877 / 116)", "answer": "The result of (877 / 116) is 7.5603\n\n####7.5603", "a": 877, "b": 116, "operator": "/", "result": 7.5603}
{"question": "Solve (910 + 563)", "answer": "The result of (910 + 563) is 1473\n\n####1473", "a": 910, "b": 563, "operator": "+", "result": 1473}
{"question": "Solve (645 / 819)", "answer": "The result of (645 / 819) is 0.7875\n\n####0.7875", "a": 645, "b": 819, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7875}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 515)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 515) is 1.4757\n\n####1.4757", "a": 760, "b": 515, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4757}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 542)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 542) is 526282\n\n####526282", "a": 971, "b": 542, "operator": "*", "result": 526282}
{"question": "Solve (444 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (444 - 195) is 249\n\n####249", "a": 444, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": 249}
{"question": "Solve (579 * 788)", "answer": "The result of (579 * 788) is 456252\n\n####456252", "a": 579, "b": 788, "operator": "*", "result": 456252}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 472)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 472) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 763, "b": 472, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (999 - 43)", "answer": "The result of (999 - 43) is 956\n\n####956", "a": 999, "b": 43, "operator": "-", "result": 956}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 718)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 718) is 0.9708\n\n####0.9708", "a": 697, "b": 718, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9708}
{"question": "Solve (156 + 917)", "answer": "The result of (156 + 917) is 1073\n\n####1073", "a": 156, "b": 917, "operator": "+", "result": 1073}
{"question": "Solve (949 - 14)", "answer": "The result of (949 - 14) is 935\n\n####935", "a": 949, "b": 14, "operator": "-", "result": 935}
{"question": "Solve (539 + 209)", "answer": "The result of (539 + 209) is 748\n\n####748", "a": 539, "b": 209, "operator": "+", "result": 748}
{"question": "Solve (391 / 85)", "answer": "The result of (391 / 85) is 4.6\n\n####4.6", "a": 391, "b": 85, "operator": "/", "result": 4.6}
{"question": "Solve (699 * 241)", "answer": "The result of (699 * 241) is 168459\n\n####168459", "a": 699, "b": 241, "operator": "*", "result": 168459}
{"question": "Solve (809 - 383)", "answer": "The result of (809 - 383) is 426\n\n####426", "a": 809, "b": 383, "operator": "-", "result": 426}
{"question": "Solve (813 * 564)", "answer": "The result of (813 * 564) is 458532\n\n####458532", "a": 813, "b": 564, "operator": "*", "result": 458532}
{"question": "Solve (409 - 676)", "answer": "The result of (409 - 676) is -267\n\n####-267", "a": 409, "b": 676, "operator": "-", "result": -267}
{"question": "Solve (897 / 689)", "answer": "The result of (897 / 689) is 1.3019\n\n####1.3019", "a": 897, "b": 689, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3019}
{"question": "Solve (880 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (880 - 344) is 536\n\n####536", "a": 880, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": 536}
{"question": "Solve (431 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (431 / 873) is 0.4937\n\n####0.4937", "a": 431, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4937}
{"question": "Solve (6 - 308)", "answer": "The result of (6 - 308) is -302\n\n####-302", "a": 6, "b": 308, "operator": "-", "result": -302}
{"question": "Solve (780 * 514)", "answer": "The result of (780 * 514) is 400920\n\n####400920", "a": 780, "b": 514, "operator": "*", "result": 400920}
{"question": "Solve (866 / 103)", "answer": "The result of (866 / 103) is 8.4078\n\n####8.4078", "a": 866, "b": 103, "operator": "/", "result": 8.4078}
{"question": "Solve (327 * 837)", "answer": "The result of (327 * 837) is 273699\n\n####273699", "a": 327, "b": 837, "operator": "*", "result": 273699}
{"question": "Solve (260 * 509)", "answer": "The result of (260 * 509) is 132340\n\n####132340", "a": 260, "b": 509, "operator": "*", "result": 132340}
{"question": "Solve (751 / 153)", "answer": "The result of (751 / 153) is 4.9085\n\n####4.9085", "a": 751, "b": 153, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9085}
{"question": "Solve (708 + 315)", "answer": "The result of (708 + 315) is 1023\n\n####1023", "a": 708, "b": 315, "operator": "+", "result": 1023}
{"question": "Solve (771 + 874)", "answer": "The result of (771 + 874) is 1645\n\n####1645", "a": 771, "b": 874, "operator": "+", "result": 1645}
{"question": "Solve (618 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (618 - 849) is -231\n\n####-231", "a": 618, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -231}
{"question": "Solve (661 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (661 * 932) is 616052\n\n####616052", "a": 661, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 616052}
{"question": "Solve (164 - 569)", "answer": "The result of (164 - 569) is -405\n\n####-405", "a": 164, "b": 569, "operator": "-", "result": -405}
{"question": "Solve (997 + 699)", "answer": "The result of (997 + 699) is 1696\n\n####1696", "a": 997, "b": 699, "operator": "+", "result": 1696}
{"question": "Solve (189 * 507)", "answer": "The result of (189 * 507) is 95823\n\n####95823", "a": 189, "b": 507, "operator": "*", "result": 95823}
{"question": "Solve (570 * 923)", "answer": "The result of (570 * 923) is 526110\n\n####526110", "a": 570, "b": 923, "operator": "*", "result": 526110}
{"question": "Solve (103 / 291)", "answer": "The result of (103 / 291) is 0.354\n\n####0.354", "a": 103, "b": 291, "operator": "/", "result": 0.354}
{"question": "Solve (591 * 111)", "answer": "The result of (591 * 111) is 65601\n\n####65601", "a": 591, "b": 111, "operator": "*", "result": 65601}
{"question": "Solve (935 + 869)", "answer": "The result of (935 + 869) is 1804\n\n####1804", "a": 935, "b": 869, "operator": "+", "result": 1804}
{"question": "Solve (761 * 734)", "answer": "The result of (761 * 734) is 558574\n\n####558574", "a": 761, "b": 734, "operator": "*", "result": 558574}
{"question": "Solve (857 / 630)", "answer": "The result of (857 / 630) is 1.3603\n\n####1.3603", "a": 857, "b": 630, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3603}
{"question": "Solve (609 / 552)", "answer": "The result of (609 / 552) is 1.1033\n\n####1.1033", "a": 609, "b": 552, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1033}
{"question": "Solve (14 / 955)", "answer": "The result of (14 / 955) is 0.0147\n\n####0.0147", "a": 14, "b": 955, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0147}
{"question": "Solve (587 / 55)", "answer": "The result of (587 / 55) is 10.6727\n\n####10.6727", "a": 587, "b": 55, "operator": "/", "result": 10.6727}
{"question": "Solve (277 * 401)", "answer": "The result of (277 * 401) is 111077\n\n####111077", "a": 277, "b": 401, "operator": "*", "result": 111077}
{"question": "Solve (180 * 713)", "answer": "The result of (180 * 713) is 128340\n\n####128340", "a": 180, "b": 713, "operator": "*", "result": 128340}
{"question": "Solve (226 / 234)", "answer": "The result of (226 / 234) is 0.9658\n\n####0.9658", "a": 226, "b": 234, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9658}
{"question": "Solve (392 + 98)", "answer": "The result of (392 + 98) is 490\n\n####490", "a": 392, "b": 98, "operator": "+", "result": 490}
{"question": "Solve (185 / 902)", "answer": "The result of (185 / 902) is 0.2051\n\n####0.2051", "a": 185, "b": 902, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2051}
{"question": "Solve (293 - 589)", "answer": "The result of (293 - 589) is -296\n\n####-296", "a": 293, "b": 589, "operator": "-", "result": -296}
{"question": "Solve (968 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (968 / 43) is 22.5116\n\n####22.5116", "a": 968, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 22.5116}
{"question": "Solve (229 * 408)", "answer": "The result of (229 * 408) is 93432\n\n####93432", "a": 229, "b": 408, "operator": "*", "result": 93432}
{"question": "Solve (132 + 927)", "answer": "The result of (132 + 927) is 1059\n\n####1059", "a": 132, "b": 927, "operator": "+", "result": 1059}
{"question": "Solve (613 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (613 - 485) is 128\n\n####128", "a": 613, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": 128}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 885)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 885) is -791\n\n####-791", "a": 94, "b": 885, "operator": "-", "result": -791}
{"question": "Solve (722 + 191)", "answer": "The result of (722 + 191) is 913\n\n####913", "a": 722, "b": 191, "operator": "+", "result": 913}
{"question": "Solve (398 + 394)", "answer": "The result of (398 + 394) is 792\n\n####792", "a": 398, "b": 394, "operator": "+", "result": 792}
{"question": "Solve (861 / 523)", "answer": "The result of (861 / 523) is 1.6463\n\n####1.6463", "a": 861, "b": 523, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6463}
{"question": "Solve (552 - 563)", "answer": "The result of (552 - 563) is -11\n\n####-11", "a": 552, "b": 563, "operator": "-", "result": -11}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 238) is 198\n\n####198", "a": 436, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 198}
{"question": "Solve (275 / 965)", "answer": "The result of (275 / 965) is 0.285\n\n####0.285", "a": 275, "b": 965, "operator": "/", "result": 0.285}
{"question": "Solve (98 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (98 / 773) is 0.1268\n\n####0.1268", "a": 98, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1268}
{"question": "Solve (266 + 572)", "answer": "The result of (266 + 572) is 838\n\n####838", "a": 266, "b": 572, "operator": "+", "result": 838}
{"question": "Solve (179 / 842)", "answer": "The result of (179 / 842) is 0.2126\n\n####0.2126", "a": 179, "b": 842, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2126}
{"question": "Solve (220 / 985)", "answer": "The result of (220 / 985) is 0.2234\n\n####0.2234", "a": 220, "b": 985, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2234}
{"question": "Solve (244 + 600)", "answer": "The result of (244 + 600) is 844\n\n####844", "a": 244, "b": 600, "operator": "+", "result": 844}
{"question": "Solve (82 + 884)", "answer": "The result of (82 + 884) is 966\n\n####966", "a": 82, "b": 884, "operator": "+", "result": 966}
{"question": "Solve (376 + 910)", "answer": "The result of (376 + 910) is 1286\n\n####1286", "a": 376, "b": 910, "operator": "+", "result": 1286}
{"question": "Solve (97 / 256)", "answer": "The result of (97 / 256) is 0.3789\n\n####0.3789", "a": 97, "b": 256, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3789}
{"question": "Solve (296 + 717)", "answer": "The result of (296 + 717) is 1013\n\n####1013", "a": 296, "b": 717, "operator": "+", "result": 1013}
{"question": "Solve (693 / 84)", "answer": "The result of (693 / 84) is 8.25\n\n####8.25", "a": 693, "b": 84, "operator": "/", "result": 8.25}
{"question": "Solve (628 / 923)", "answer": "The result of (628 / 923) is 0.6804\n\n####0.6804", "a": 628, "b": 923, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6804}
{"question": "Solve (549 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (549 / 669) is 0.8206\n\n####0.8206", "a": 549, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8206}
{"question": "Solve (153 * 235)", "answer": "The result of (153 * 235) is 35955\n\n####35955", "a": 153, "b": 235, "operator": "*", "result": 35955}
{"question": "Solve (222 * 676)", "answer": "The result of (222 * 676) is 150072\n\n####150072", "a": 222, "b": 676, "operator": "*", "result": 150072}
{"question": "Solve (320 / 636)", "answer": "The result of (320 / 636) is 0.5031\n\n####0.5031", "a": 320, "b": 636, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5031}
{"question": "Solve (23 * 600)", "answer": "The result of (23 * 600) is 13800\n\n####13800", "a": 23, "b": 600, "operator": "*", "result": 13800}
{"question": "Solve (754 * 477)", "answer": "The result of (754 * 477) is 359658\n\n####359658", "a": 754, "b": 477, "operator": "*", "result": 359658}
{"question": "Solve (293 + 870)", "answer": "The result of (293 + 870) is 1163\n\n####1163", "a": 293, "b": 870, "operator": "+", "result": 1163}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 637)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 637) is 0.4804\n\n####0.4804", "a": 306, "b": 637, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4804}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 27) is 493\n\n####493", "a": 520, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 493}
{"question": "Solve (558 * 667)", "answer": "The result of (558 * 667) is 372186\n\n####372186", "a": 558, "b": 667, "operator": "*", "result": 372186}
{"question": "Solve (392 - 930)", "answer": "The result of (392 - 930) is -538\n\n####-538", "a": 392, "b": 930, "operator": "-", "result": -538}
{"question": "Solve (267 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (267 / 411) is 0.6496\n\n####0.6496", "a": 267, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6496}
{"question": "Solve (708 * 9)", "answer": "The result of (708 * 9) is 6372\n\n####6372", "a": 708, "b": 9, "operator": "*", "result": 6372}
{"question": "Solve (673 * 466)", "answer": "The result of (673 * 466) is 313618\n\n####313618", "a": 673, "b": 466, "operator": "*", "result": 313618}
{"question": "Solve (123 - 347)", "answer": "The result of (123 - 347) is -224\n\n####-224", "a": 123, "b": 347, "operator": "-", "result": -224}
{"question": "Solve (406 / 400)", "answer": "The result of (406 / 400) is 1.015\n\n####1.015", "a": 406, "b": 400, "operator": "/", "result": 1.015}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 925)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 925) is 0.5265\n\n####0.5265", "a": 487, "b": 925, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5265}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 446)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 446) is 275\n\n####275", "a": 721, "b": 446, "operator": "-", "result": 275}
{"question": "Solve (767 - 955)", "answer": "The result of (767 - 955) is -188\n\n####-188", "a": 767, "b": 955, "operator": "-", "result": -188}
{"question": "Solve (918 + 209)", "answer": "The result of (918 + 209) is 1127\n\n####1127", "a": 918, "b": 209, "operator": "+", "result": 1127}
{"question": "Solve (663 * 962)", "answer": "The result of (663 * 962) is 637806\n\n####637806", "a": 663, "b": 962, "operator": "*", "result": 637806}
{"question": "Solve (935 + 466)", "answer": "The result of (935 + 466) is 1401\n\n####1401", "a": 935, "b": 466, "operator": "+", "result": 1401}
{"question": "Solve (547 * 648)", "answer": "The result of (547 * 648) is 354456\n\n####354456", "a": 547, "b": 648, "operator": "*", "result": 354456}
{"question": "Solve (937 + 265)", "answer": "The result of (937 + 265) is 1202\n\n####1202", "a": 937, "b": 265, "operator": "+", "result": 1202}
{"question": "Solve (290 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (290 / 773) is 0.3752\n\n####0.3752", "a": 290, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3752}
{"question": "Solve (26 / 608)", "answer": "The result of (26 / 608) is 0.0428\n\n####0.0428", "a": 26, "b": 608, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0428}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 422)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 422) is 247292\n\n####247292", "a": 586, "b": 422, "operator": "*", "result": 247292}
{"question": "Solve (13 * 953)", "answer": "The result of (13 * 953) is 12389\n\n####12389", "a": 13, "b": 953, "operator": "*", "result": 12389}
{"question": "Solve (92 / 788)", "answer": "The result of (92 / 788) is 0.1168\n\n####0.1168", "a": 92, "b": 788, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1168}
{"question": "Solve (268 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (268 + 184) is 452\n\n####452", "a": 268, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 452}
{"question": "Solve (477 * 325)", "answer": "The result of (477 * 325) is 155025\n\n####155025", "a": 477, "b": 325, "operator": "*", "result": 155025}
{"question": "Solve (649 / 541)", "answer": "The result of (649 / 541) is 1.1996\n\n####1.1996", "a": 649, "b": 541, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1996}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 672)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 672) is 410592\n\n####410592", "a": 611, "b": 672, "operator": "*", "result": 410592}
{"question": "Solve (536 - 710)", "answer": "The result of (536 - 710) is -174\n\n####-174", "a": 536, "b": 710, "operator": "-", "result": -174}
{"question": "Solve (127 + 393)", "answer": "The result of (127 + 393) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 127, "b": 393, "operator": "+", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (764 / 219)", "answer": "The result of (764 / 219) is 3.4886\n\n####3.4886", "a": 764, "b": 219, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4886}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 366)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 366) is -296\n\n####-296", "a": 70, "b": 366, "operator": "-", "result": -296}
{"question": "Solve (196 / 532)", "answer": "The result of (196 / 532) is 0.3684\n\n####0.3684", "a": 196, "b": 532, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3684}
{"question": "Solve (6 - 375)", "answer": "The result of (6 - 375) is -369\n\n####-369", "a": 6, "b": 375, "operator": "-", "result": -369}
{"question": "Solve (721 / 948)", "answer": "The result of (721 / 948) is 0.7605\n\n####0.7605", "a": 721, "b": 948, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7605}
{"question": "Solve (927 - 616)", "answer": "The result of (927 - 616) is 311\n\n####311", "a": 927, "b": 616, "operator": "-", "result": 311}
{"question": "Solve (435 / 833)", "answer": "The result of (435 / 833) is 0.5222\n\n####0.5222", "a": 435, "b": 833, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5222}
{"question": "Solve (692 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (692 + 31) is 723\n\n####723", "a": 692, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 723}
{"question": "Solve (92 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (92 - 276) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 92, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (923 - 592)", "answer": "The result of (923 - 592) is 331\n\n####331", "a": 923, "b": 592, "operator": "-", "result": 331}
{"question": "Solve (69 - 839)", "answer": "The result of (69 - 839) is -770\n\n####-770", "a": 69, "b": 839, "operator": "-", "result": -770}
{"question": "Solve (972 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (972 * 485) is 471420\n\n####471420", "a": 972, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 471420}
{"question": "Solve (863 * 6)", "answer": "The result of (863 * 6) is 5178\n\n####5178", "a": 863, "b": 6, "operator": "*", "result": 5178}
{"question": "Solve (756 + 672)", "answer": "The result of (756 + 672) is 1428\n\n####1428", "a": 756, "b": 672, "operator": "+", "result": 1428}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 819)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 819) is 0.6215\n\n####0.6215", "a": 509, "b": 819, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6215}
{"question": "Solve (756 * 753)", "answer": "The result of (756 * 753) is 569268\n\n####569268", "a": 756, "b": 753, "operator": "*", "result": 569268}
{"question": "Solve (997 - 833)", "answer": "The result of (997 - 833) is 164\n\n####164", "a": 997, "b": 833, "operator": "-", "result": 164}
{"question": "Solve (178 - 719)", "answer": "The result of (178 - 719) is -541\n\n####-541", "a": 178, "b": 719, "operator": "-", "result": -541}
{"question": "Solve (655 / 249)", "answer": "The result of (655 / 249) is 2.6305\n\n####2.6305", "a": 655, "b": 249, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6305}
{"question": "Solve (379 * 617)", "answer": "The result of (379 * 617) is 233843\n\n####233843", "a": 379, "b": 617, "operator": "*", "result": 233843}
{"question": "Solve (687 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (687 * 142) is 97554\n\n####97554", "a": 687, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 97554}
{"question": "Solve (322 * 839)", "answer": "The result of (322 * 839) is 270158\n\n####270158", "a": 322, "b": 839, "operator": "*", "result": 270158}
{"question": "Solve (874 / 42)", "answer": "The result of (874 / 42) is 20.8095\n\n####20.8095", "a": 874, "b": 42, "operator": "/", "result": 20.8095}
{"question": "Solve (934 / 238)", "answer": "The result of (934 / 238) is 3.9244\n\n####3.9244", "a": 934, "b": 238, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9244}
{"question": "Solve (855 + 138)", "answer": "The result of (855 + 138) is 993\n\n####993", "a": 855, "b": 138, "operator": "+", "result": 993}
{"question": "Solve (839 * 391)", "answer": "The result of (839 * 391) is 328049\n\n####328049", "a": 839, "b": 391, "operator": "*", "result": 328049}
{"question": "Solve (366 - 153)", "answer": "The result of (366 - 153) is 213\n\n####213", "a": 366, "b": 153, "operator": "-", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 942)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 942) is -266\n\n####-266", "a": 676, "b": 942, "operator": "-", "result": -266}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 70)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 70) is 3.8429\n\n####3.8429", "a": 269, "b": 70, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8429}
{"question": "Solve (937 / 924)", "answer": "The result of (937 / 924) is 1.0141\n\n####1.0141", "a": 937, "b": 924, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0141}
{"question": "Solve (214 / 818)", "answer": "The result of (214 / 818) is 0.2616\n\n####0.2616", "a": 214, "b": 818, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2616}
{"question": "Solve (67 + 691)", "answer": "The result of (67 + 691) is 758\n\n####758", "a": 67, "b": 691, "operator": "+", "result": 758}
{"question": "Solve (404 + 61)", "answer": "The result of (404 + 61) is 465\n\n####465", "a": 404, "b": 61, "operator": "+", "result": 465}
{"question": "Solve (576 - 691)", "answer": "The result of (576 - 691) is -115\n\n####-115", "a": 576, "b": 691, "operator": "-", "result": -115}
{"question": "Solve (126 / 510)", "answer": "The result of (126 / 510) is 0.2471\n\n####0.2471", "a": 126, "b": 510, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2471}
{"question": "Solve (167 + 66)", "answer": "The result of (167 + 66) is 233\n\n####233", "a": 167, "b": 66, "operator": "+", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve (468 - 252)", "answer": "The result of (468 - 252) is 216\n\n####216", "a": 468, "b": 252, "operator": "-", "result": 216}
{"question": "Solve (253 + 801)", "answer": "The result of (253 + 801) is 1054\n\n####1054", "a": 253, "b": 801, "operator": "+", "result": 1054}
{"question": "Solve (3 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (3 * 145) is 435\n\n####435", "a": 3, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 435}
{"question": "Solve (120 * 310)", "answer": "The result of (120 * 310) is 37200\n\n####37200", "a": 120, "b": 310, "operator": "*", "result": 37200}
{"question": "Solve (326 + 628)", "answer": "The result of (326 + 628) is 954\n\n####954", "a": 326, "b": 628, "operator": "+", "result": 954}
{"question": "Solve (646 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (646 / 821) is 0.7868\n\n####0.7868", "a": 646, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7868}
{"question": "Solve (903 + 599)", "answer": "The result of (903 + 599) is 1502\n\n####1502", "a": 903, "b": 599, "operator": "+", "result": 1502}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 513)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 513) is 0.1969\n\n####0.1969", "a": 101, "b": 513, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1969}
{"question": "Solve (630 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (630 * 22) is 13860\n\n####13860", "a": 630, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 13860}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 178)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 178) is 1005\n\n####1005", "a": 827, "b": 178, "operator": "+", "result": 1005}
{"question": "Solve (62 / 182)", "answer": "The result of (62 / 182) is 0.3407\n\n####0.3407", "a": 62, "b": 182, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3407}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 232)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 232) is 2.0991\n\n####2.0991", "a": 487, "b": 232, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0991}
{"question": "Solve (501 / 194)", "answer": "The result of (501 / 194) is 2.5825\n\n####2.5825", "a": 501, "b": 194, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5825}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 449) is -126\n\n####-126", "a": 323, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": -126}
{"question": "Solve (307 - 135)", "answer": "The result of (307 - 135) is 172\n\n####172", "a": 307, "b": 135, "operator": "-", "result": 172}
{"question": "Solve (587 * 221)", "answer": "The result of (587 * 221) is 129727\n\n####129727", "a": 587, "b": 221, "operator": "*", "result": 129727}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 169) is 807\n\n####807", "a": 976, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": 807}
{"question": "Solve (779 * 840)", "answer": "The result of (779 * 840) is 654360\n\n####654360", "a": 779, "b": 840, "operator": "*", "result": 654360}
{"question": "Solve (172 / 132)", "answer": "The result of (172 / 132) is 1.303\n\n####1.303", "a": 172, "b": 132, "operator": "/", "result": 1.303}
{"question": "Solve (882 * 116)", "answer": "The result of (882 * 116) is 102312\n\n####102312", "a": 882, "b": 116, "operator": "*", "result": 102312}
{"question": "Solve (204 / 738)", "answer": "The result of (204 / 738) is 0.2764\n\n####0.2764", "a": 204, "b": 738, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2764}
{"question": "Solve (819 - 683)", "answer": "The result of (819 - 683) is 136\n\n####136", "a": 819, "b": 683, "operator": "-", "result": 136}
{"question": "Solve (620 - 621)", "answer": "The result of (620 - 621) is -1\n\n####-1", "a": 620, "b": 621, "operator": "-", "result": -1}
{"question": "Solve (968 / 499)", "answer": "The result of (968 / 499) is 1.9399\n\n####1.9399", "a": 968, "b": 499, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9399}
{"question": "Solve (300 / 587)", "answer": "The result of (300 / 587) is 0.5111\n\n####0.5111", "a": 300, "b": 587, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5111}
{"question": "Solve (504 - 776)", "answer": "The result of (504 - 776) is -272\n\n####-272", "a": 504, "b": 776, "operator": "-", "result": -272}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 7)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 7) is 1484\n\n####1484", "a": 212, "b": 7, "operator": "*", "result": 1484}
{"question": "Solve (302 / 644)", "answer": "The result of (302 / 644) is 0.4689\n\n####0.4689", "a": 302, "b": 644, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4689}
{"question": "Solve (663 - 637)", "answer": "The result of (663 - 637) is 26\n\n####26", "a": 663, "b": 637, "operator": "-", "result": 26}
{"question": "Solve (298 - 7)", "answer": "The result of (298 - 7) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 298, "b": 7, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (736 / 4)", "answer": "The result of (736 / 4) is 184.0\n\n####184.0", "a": 736, "b": 4, "operator": "/", "result": 184.0}
{"question": "Solve (979 * 973)", "answer": "The result of (979 * 973) is 952567\n\n####952567", "a": 979, "b": 973, "operator": "*", "result": 952567}
{"question": "Solve (724 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (724 / 376) is 1.9255\n\n####1.9255", "a": 724, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9255}
{"question": "Solve (345 * 89)", "answer": "The result of (345 * 89) is 30705\n\n####30705", "a": 345, "b": 89, "operator": "*", "result": 30705}
{"question": "Solve (421 - 10)", "answer": "The result of (421 - 10) is 411\n\n####411", "a": 421, "b": 10, "operator": "-", "result": 411}
{"question": "Solve (719 * 734)", "answer": "The result of (719 * 734) is 527746\n\n####527746", "a": 719, "b": 734, "operator": "*", "result": 527746}
{"question": "Solve (30 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (30 / 984) is 0.0305\n\n####0.0305", "a": 30, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0305}
{"question": "Solve (546 + 857)", "answer": "The result of (546 + 857) is 1403\n\n####1403", "a": 546, "b": 857, "operator": "+", "result": 1403}
{"question": "Solve (977 - 465)", "answer": "The result of (977 - 465) is 512\n\n####512", "a": 977, "b": 465, "operator": "-", "result": 512}
{"question": "Solve (804 / 359)", "answer": "The result of (804 / 359) is 2.2396\n\n####2.2396", "a": 804, "b": 359, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2396}
{"question": "Solve (942 / 292)", "answer": "The result of (942 / 292) is 3.226\n\n####3.226", "a": 942, "b": 292, "operator": "/", "result": 3.226}
{"question": "Solve (721 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (721 + 358) is 1079\n\n####1079", "a": 721, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 1079}
{"question": "Solve (728 * 307)", "answer": "The result of (728 * 307) is 223496\n\n####223496", "a": 728, "b": 307, "operator": "*", "result": 223496}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 285)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 285) is 708\n\n####708", "a": 423, "b": 285, "operator": "+", "result": 708}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 47)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 47) is 10.3617\n\n####10.3617", "a": 487, "b": 47, "operator": "/", "result": 10.3617}
{"question": "Solve (228 * 837)", "answer": "The result of (228 * 837) is 190836\n\n####190836", "a": 228, "b": 837, "operator": "*", "result": 190836}
{"question": "Solve (347 + 59)", "answer": "The result of (347 + 59) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 347, "b": 59, "operator": "+", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (961 - 33)", "answer": "The result of (961 - 33) is 928\n\n####928", "a": 961, "b": 33, "operator": "-", "result": 928}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 182)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 182) is 1.1319\n\n####1.1319", "a": 206, "b": 182, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1319}
{"question": "Solve (67 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (67 / 87) is 0.7701\n\n####0.7701", "a": 67, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7701}
{"question": "Solve (690 + 193)", "answer": "The result of (690 + 193) is 883\n\n####883", "a": 690, "b": 193, "operator": "+", "result": 883}
{"question": "Solve (349 - 728)", "answer": "The result of (349 - 728) is -379\n\n####-379", "a": 349, "b": 728, "operator": "-", "result": -379}
{"question": "Solve (231 / 656)", "answer": "The result of (231 / 656) is 0.3521\n\n####0.3521", "a": 231, "b": 656, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3521}
{"question": "Solve (804 / 409)", "answer": "The result of (804 / 409) is 1.9658\n\n####1.9658", "a": 804, "b": 409, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9658}
{"question": "Solve (220 * 421)", "answer": "The result of (220 * 421) is 92620\n\n####92620", "a": 220, "b": 421, "operator": "*", "result": 92620}
{"question": "Solve (863 + 518)", "answer": "The result of (863 + 518) is 1381\n\n####1381", "a": 863, "b": 518, "operator": "+", "result": 1381}
{"question": "Solve (100 / 192)", "answer": "The result of (100 / 192) is 0.5208\n\n####0.5208", "a": 100, "b": 192, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5208}
{"question": "Solve (494 * 95)", "answer": "The result of (494 * 95) is 46930\n\n####46930", "a": 494, "b": 95, "operator": "*", "result": 46930}
{"question": "Solve (366 - 789)", "answer": "The result of (366 - 789) is -423\n\n####-423", "a": 366, "b": 789, "operator": "-", "result": -423}
{"question": "Solve (348 - 720)", "answer": "The result of (348 - 720) is -372\n\n####-372", "a": 348, "b": 720, "operator": "-", "result": -372}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 526)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 526) is 5\n\n####5", "a": 531, "b": 526, "operator": "-", "result": 5}
{"question": "Solve (112 - 599)", "answer": "The result of (112 - 599) is -487\n\n####-487", "a": 112, "b": 599, "operator": "-", "result": -487}
{"question": "Solve (67 + 913)", "answer": "The result of (67 + 913) is 980\n\n####980", "a": 67, "b": 913, "operator": "+", "result": 980}
{"question": "Solve (494 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (494 / 334) is 1.479\n\n####1.479", "a": 494, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 1.479}
{"question": "Solve (83 - 136)", "answer": "The result of (83 - 136) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 83, "b": 136, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 691)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 691) is 969\n\n####969", "a": 278, "b": 691, "operator": "+", "result": 969}
{"question": "Solve (856 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (856 - 500) is 356\n\n####356", "a": 856, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": 356}
{"question": "Solve (75 * 725)", "answer": "The result of (75 * 725) is 54375\n\n####54375", "a": 75, "b": 725, "operator": "*", "result": 54375}
{"question": "Solve (601 - 902)", "answer": "The result of (601 - 902) is -301\n\n####-301", "a": 601, "b": 902, "operator": "-", "result": -301}
{"question": "Solve (210 - 406)", "answer": "The result of (210 - 406) is -196\n\n####-196", "a": 210, "b": 406, "operator": "-", "result": -196}
{"question": "Solve (955 - 460)", "answer": "The result of (955 - 460) is 495\n\n####495", "a": 955, "b": 460, "operator": "-", "result": 495}
{"question": "Solve (36 * 262)", "answer": "The result of (36 * 262) is 9432\n\n####9432", "a": 36, "b": 262, "operator": "*", "result": 9432}
{"question": "Solve (773 / 880)", "answer": "The result of (773 / 880) is 0.8784\n\n####0.8784", "a": 773, "b": 880, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8784}
{"question": "Solve (51 + 433)", "answer": "The result of (51 + 433) is 484\n\n####484", "a": 51, "b": 433, "operator": "+", "result": 484}
{"question": "Solve (841 - 643)", "answer": "The result of (841 - 643) is 198\n\n####198", "a": 841, "b": 643, "operator": "-", "result": 198}
{"question": "Solve (125 + 377)", "answer": "The result of (125 + 377) is 502\n\n####502", "a": 125, "b": 377, "operator": "+", "result": 502}
{"question": "Solve (968 - 173)", "answer": "The result of (968 - 173) is 795\n\n####795", "a": 968, "b": 173, "operator": "-", "result": 795}
{"question": "Solve (963 + 520)", "answer": "The result of (963 + 520) is 1483\n\n####1483", "a": 963, "b": 520, "operator": "+", "result": 1483}
{"question": "Solve (927 / 14)", "answer": "The result of (927 / 14) is 66.2143\n\n####66.2143", "a": 927, "b": 14, "operator": "/", "result": 66.2143}
{"question": "Solve (567 * 613)", "answer": "The result of (567 * 613) is 347571\n\n####347571", "a": 567, "b": 613, "operator": "*", "result": 347571}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 411)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 411) is 65\n\n####65", "a": 476, "b": 411, "operator": "-", "result": 65}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 426)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 426) is 210\n\n####210", "a": 636, "b": 426, "operator": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 445)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 445) is -94\n\n####-94", "a": 351, "b": 445, "operator": "-", "result": -94}
{"question": "Solve (831 / 743)", "answer": "The result of (831 / 743) is 1.1184\n\n####1.1184", "a": 831, "b": 743, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1184}
{"question": "Solve (857 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (857 + 11) is 868\n\n####868", "a": 857, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 868}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 710)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 710) is 1682\n\n####1682", "a": 972, "b": 710, "operator": "+", "result": 1682}
{"question": "Solve (258 * 980)", "answer": "The result of (258 * 980) is 252840\n\n####252840", "a": 258, "b": 980, "operator": "*", "result": 252840}
{"question": "Solve (50 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (50 * 423) is 21150\n\n####21150", "a": 50, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 21150}
{"question": "Solve (917 + 152)", "answer": "The result of (917 + 152) is 1069\n\n####1069", "a": 917, "b": 152, "operator": "+", "result": 1069}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 307)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 307) is 238\n\n####238", "a": 545, "b": 307, "operator": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve (157 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (157 - 730) is -573\n\n####-573", "a": 157, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -573}
{"question": "Solve (288 * 285)", "answer": "The result of (288 * 285) is 82080\n\n####82080", "a": 288, "b": 285, "operator": "*", "result": 82080}
{"question": "Solve (155 - 395)", "answer": "The result of (155 - 395) is -240\n\n####-240", "a": 155, "b": 395, "operator": "-", "result": -240}
{"question": "Solve (231 + 961)", "answer": "The result of (231 + 961) is 1192\n\n####1192", "a": 231, "b": 961, "operator": "+", "result": 1192}
{"question": "Solve (276 + 729)", "answer": "The result of (276 + 729) is 1005\n\n####1005", "a": 276, "b": 729, "operator": "+", "result": 1005}
{"question": "Solve (414 / 402)", "answer": "The result of (414 / 402) is 1.0299\n\n####1.0299", "a": 414, "b": 402, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0299}
{"question": "Solve (74 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (74 + 19) is 93\n\n####93", "a": 74, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 93}
{"question": "Solve (141 * 609)", "answer": "The result of (141 * 609) is 85869\n\n####85869", "a": 141, "b": 609, "operator": "*", "result": 85869}
{"question": "Solve (45 / 400)", "answer": "The result of (45 / 400) is 0.1125\n\n####0.1125", "a": 45, "b": 400, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1125}
{"question": "Solve (886 / 149)", "answer": "The result of (886 / 149) is 5.9463\n\n####5.9463", "a": 886, "b": 149, "operator": "/", "result": 5.9463}
{"question": "Solve (54 * 179)", "answer": "The result of (54 * 179) is 9666\n\n####9666", "a": 54, "b": 179, "operator": "*", "result": 9666}
{"question": "Solve (630 + 634)", "answer": "The result of (630 + 634) is 1264\n\n####1264", "a": 630, "b": 634, "operator": "+", "result": 1264}
{"question": "Solve (340 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (340 - 520) is -180\n\n####-180", "a": 340, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": -180}
{"question": "Solve (746 - 285)", "answer": "The result of (746 - 285) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 746, "b": 285, "operator": "-", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (449 * 771)", "answer": "The result of (449 * 771) is 346179\n\n####346179", "a": 449, "b": 771, "operator": "*", "result": 346179}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 510)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 510) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 309, "b": 510, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (572 - 553)", "answer": "The result of (572 - 553) is 19\n\n####19", "a": 572, "b": 553, "operator": "-", "result": 19}
{"question": "Solve (981 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (981 + 805) is 1786\n\n####1786", "a": 981, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1786}
{"question": "Solve (66 / 52)", "answer": "The result of (66 / 52) is 1.2692\n\n####1.2692", "a": 66, "b": 52, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2692}
{"question": "Solve (256 * 638)", "answer": "The result of (256 * 638) is 163328\n\n####163328", "a": 256, "b": 638, "operator": "*", "result": 163328}
{"question": "Solve (724 * 148)", "answer": "The result of (724 * 148) is 107152\n\n####107152", "a": 724, "b": 148, "operator": "*", "result": 107152}
{"question": "Solve (678 * 643)", "answer": "The result of (678 * 643) is 435954\n\n####435954", "a": 678, "b": 643, "operator": "*", "result": 435954}
{"question": "Solve (838 / 552)", "answer": "The result of (838 / 552) is 1.5181\n\n####1.5181", "a": 838, "b": 552, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5181}
{"question": "Solve (569 * 214)", "answer": "The result of (569 * 214) is 121766\n\n####121766", "a": 569, "b": 214, "operator": "*", "result": 121766}
{"question": "Solve (396 + 466)", "answer": "The result of (396 + 466) is 862\n\n####862", "a": 396, "b": 466, "operator": "+", "result": 862}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 848)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 848) is 19\n\n####19", "a": 867, "b": 848, "operator": "-", "result": 19}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 61) is 22814\n\n####22814", "a": 374, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 22814}
{"question": "Solve (844 - 962)", "answer": "The result of (844 - 962) is -118\n\n####-118", "a": 844, "b": 962, "operator": "-", "result": -118}
{"question": "Solve (415 + 43)", "answer": "The result of (415 + 43) is 458\n\n####458", "a": 415, "b": 43, "operator": "+", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve (877 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (877 - 354) is 523\n\n####523", "a": 877, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": 523}
{"question": "Solve (927 / 961)", "answer": "The result of (927 / 961) is 0.9646\n\n####0.9646", "a": 927, "b": 961, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9646}
{"question": "Solve (244 * 566)", "answer": "The result of (244 * 566) is 138104\n\n####138104", "a": 244, "b": 566, "operator": "*", "result": 138104}
{"question": "Solve (23 + 936)", "answer": "The result of (23 + 936) is 959\n\n####959", "a": 23, "b": 936, "operator": "+", "result": 959}
{"question": "Solve (12 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (12 / 300) is 0.04\n\n####0.04", "a": 12, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 0.04}
{"question": "Solve (752 + 533)", "answer": "The result of (752 + 533) is 1285\n\n####1285", "a": 752, "b": 533, "operator": "+", "result": 1285}
{"question": "Solve (167 - 186)", "answer": "The result of (167 - 186) is -19\n\n####-19", "a": 167, "b": 186, "operator": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 455)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 455) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 938, "b": 455, "operator": "-", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (705 - 727)", "answer": "The result of (705 - 727) is -22\n\n####-22", "a": 705, "b": 727, "operator": "-", "result": -22}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 592)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 592) is 1253\n\n####1253", "a": 661, "b": 592, "operator": "+", "result": 1253}
{"question": "Solve (256 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (256 / 327) is 0.7829\n\n####0.7829", "a": 256, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7829}
{"question": "Solve (377 + 557)", "answer": "The result of (377 + 557) is 934\n\n####934", "a": 377, "b": 557, "operator": "+", "result": 934}
{"question": "Solve (994 * 52)", "answer": "The result of (994 * 52) is 51688\n\n####51688", "a": 994, "b": 52, "operator": "*", "result": 51688}
{"question": "Solve (595 * 259)", "answer": "The result of (595 * 259) is 154105\n\n####154105", "a": 595, "b": 259, "operator": "*", "result": 154105}
{"question": "Solve (962 + 634)", "answer": "The result of (962 + 634) is 1596\n\n####1596", "a": 962, "b": 634, "operator": "+", "result": 1596}
{"question": "Solve (568 / 514)", "answer": "The result of (568 / 514) is 1.1051\n\n####1.1051", "a": 568, "b": 514, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1051}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 760)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 760) is -215\n\n####-215", "a": 545, "b": 760, "operator": "-", "result": -215}
{"question": "Solve (386 + 857)", "answer": "The result of (386 + 857) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 386, "b": 857, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (756 / 139)", "answer": "The result of (756 / 139) is 5.4388\n\n####5.4388", "a": 756, "b": 139, "operator": "/", "result": 5.4388}
{"question": "Solve (493 * 32)", "answer": "The result of (493 * 32) is 15776\n\n####15776", "a": 493, "b": 32, "operator": "*", "result": 15776}
{"question": "Solve (901 * 538)", "answer": "The result of (901 * 538) is 484738\n\n####484738", "a": 901, "b": 538, "operator": "*", "result": 484738}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 82)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 82) is 2.4634\n\n####2.4634", "a": 202, "b": 82, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4634}
{"question": "Solve (8 - 73)", "answer": "The result of (8 - 73) is -65\n\n####-65", "a": 8, "b": 73, "operator": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 134)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 134) is 296\n\n####296", "a": 430, "b": 134, "operator": "-", "result": 296}
{"question": "Solve (618 - 85)", "answer": "The result of (618 - 85) is 533\n\n####533", "a": 618, "b": 85, "operator": "-", "result": 533}
{"question": "Solve (67 / 223)", "answer": "The result of (67 / 223) is 0.3004\n\n####0.3004", "a": 67, "b": 223, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3004}
{"question": "Solve (267 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (267 - 500) is -233\n\n####-233", "a": 267, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": -233}
{"question": "Solve (374 + 965)", "answer": "The result of (374 + 965) is 1339\n\n####1339", "a": 374, "b": 965, "operator": "+", "result": 1339}
{"question": "Solve (151 * 842)", "answer": "The result of (151 * 842) is 127142\n\n####127142", "a": 151, "b": 842, "operator": "*", "result": 127142}
{"question": "Solve (248 * 556)", "answer": "The result of (248 * 556) is 137888\n\n####137888", "a": 248, "b": 556, "operator": "*", "result": 137888}
{"question": "Solve (575 + 15)", "answer": "The result of (575 + 15) is 590\n\n####590", "a": 575, "b": 15, "operator": "+", "result": 590}
{"question": "Solve (482 - 553)", "answer": "The result of (482 - 553) is -71\n\n####-71", "a": 482, "b": 553, "operator": "-", "result": -71}
{"question": "Solve (987 / 140)", "answer": "The result of (987 / 140) is 7.05\n\n####7.05", "a": 987, "b": 140, "operator": "/", "result": 7.05}
{"question": "Solve (597 - 638)", "answer": "The result of (597 - 638) is -41\n\n####-41", "a": 597, "b": 638, "operator": "-", "result": -41}
{"question": "Solve (197 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (197 / 686) is 0.2872\n\n####0.2872", "a": 197, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2872}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 15)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 15) is 7845\n\n####7845", "a": 523, "b": 15, "operator": "*", "result": 7845}
{"question": "Solve (808 - 404)", "answer": "The result of (808 - 404) is 404\n\n####404", "a": 808, "b": 404, "operator": "-", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve (588 / 463)", "answer": "The result of (588 / 463) is 1.27\n\n####1.27", "a": 588, "b": 463, "operator": "/", "result": 1.27}
{"question": "Solve (306 + 737)", "answer": "The result of (306 + 737) is 1043\n\n####1043", "a": 306, "b": 737, "operator": "+", "result": 1043}
{"question": "Solve (681 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (681 / 334) is 2.0389\n\n####2.0389", "a": 681, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0389}
{"question": "Solve (343 - 105)", "answer": "The result of (343 - 105) is 238\n\n####238", "a": 343, "b": 105, "operator": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve (235 + 44)", "answer": "The result of (235 + 44) is 279\n\n####279", "a": 235, "b": 44, "operator": "+", "result": 279}
{"question": "Solve (685 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (685 * 86) is 58910\n\n####58910", "a": 685, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 58910}
{"question": "Solve (656 - 578)", "answer": "The result of (656 - 578) is 78\n\n####78", "a": 656, "b": 578, "operator": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve (702 * 517)", "answer": "The result of (702 * 517) is 362934\n\n####362934", "a": 702, "b": 517, "operator": "*", "result": 362934}
{"question": "Solve (412 - 89)", "answer": "The result of (412 - 89) is 323\n\n####323", "a": 412, "b": 89, "operator": "-", "result": 323}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 105)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 105) is 203\n\n####203", "a": 308, "b": 105, "operator": "-", "result": 203}
{"question": "Solve (211 * 750)", "answer": "The result of (211 * 750) is 158250\n\n####158250", "a": 211, "b": 750, "operator": "*", "result": 158250}
{"question": "Solve (134 + 342)", "answer": "The result of (134 + 342) is 476\n\n####476", "a": 134, "b": 342, "operator": "+", "result": 476}
{"question": "Solve (994 - 303)", "answer": "The result of (994 - 303) is 691\n\n####691", "a": 994, "b": 303, "operator": "-", "result": 691}
{"question": "Solve (457 * 640)", "answer": "The result of (457 * 640) is 292480\n\n####292480", "a": 457, "b": 640, "operator": "*", "result": 292480}
{"question": "Solve (612 - 559)", "answer": "The result of (612 - 559) is 53\n\n####53", "a": 612, "b": 559, "operator": "-", "result": 53}
{"question": "Solve (276 * 605)", "answer": "The result of (276 * 605) is 166980\n\n####166980", "a": 276, "b": 605, "operator": "*", "result": 166980}
{"question": "Solve (147 * 401)", "answer": "The result of (147 * 401) is 58947\n\n####58947", "a": 147, "b": 401, "operator": "*", "result": 58947}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 363)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 363) is 312\n\n####312", "a": 675, "b": 363, "operator": "-", "result": 312}
{"question": "Solve (556 / 659)", "answer": "The result of (556 / 659) is 0.8437\n\n####0.8437", "a": 556, "b": 659, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8437}
{"question": "Solve (106 - 191)", "answer": "The result of (106 - 191) is -85\n\n####-85", "a": 106, "b": 191, "operator": "-", "result": -85}
{"question": "Solve (741 / 293)", "answer": "The result of (741 / 293) is 2.529\n\n####2.529", "a": 741, "b": 293, "operator": "/", "result": 2.529}
{"question": "Solve (83 / 37)", "answer": "The result of (83 / 37) is 2.2432\n\n####2.2432", "a": 83, "b": 37, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2432}
{"question": "Solve (407 + 223)", "answer": "The result of (407 + 223) is 630\n\n####630", "a": 407, "b": 223, "operator": "+", "result": 630}
{"question": "Solve (999 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (999 * 910) is 909090\n\n####909090", "a": 999, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 909090}
{"question": "Solve (356 - 801)", "answer": "The result of (356 - 801) is -445\n\n####-445", "a": 356, "b": 801, "operator": "-", "result": -445}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 349)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 349) is -92\n\n####-92", "a": 257, "b": 349, "operator": "-", "result": -92}
{"question": "Solve (837 + 158)", "answer": "The result of (837 + 158) is 995\n\n####995", "a": 837, "b": 158, "operator": "+", "result": 995}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 836)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 836) is -791\n\n####-791", "a": 45, "b": 836, "operator": "-", "result": -791}
{"question": "Solve (761 + 809)", "answer": "The result of (761 + 809) is 1570\n\n####1570", "a": 761, "b": 809, "operator": "+", "result": 1570}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 826)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 826) is 0.3354\n\n####0.3354", "a": 277, "b": 826, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3354}
{"question": "Solve (198 - 571)", "answer": "The result of (198 - 571) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 198, "b": 571, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (753 + 442)", "answer": "The result of (753 + 442) is 1195\n\n####1195", "a": 753, "b": 442, "operator": "+", "result": 1195}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 108)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 108) is 4.713\n\n####4.713", "a": 509, "b": 108, "operator": "/", "result": 4.713}
{"question": "Solve (523 - 419)", "answer": "The result of (523 - 419) is 104\n\n####104", "a": 523, "b": 419, "operator": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve (569 + 955)", "answer": "The result of (569 + 955) is 1524\n\n####1524", "a": 569, "b": 955, "operator": "+", "result": 1524}
{"question": "Solve (380 / 932)", "answer": "The result of (380 / 932) is 0.4077\n\n####0.4077", "a": 380, "b": 932, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4077}
{"question": "Solve (371 * 537)", "answer": "The result of (371 * 537) is 199227\n\n####199227", "a": 371, "b": 537, "operator": "*", "result": 199227}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 644)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 644) is 31\n\n####31", "a": 675, "b": 644, "operator": "-", "result": 31}
{"question": "Solve (912 + 510)", "answer": "The result of (912 + 510) is 1422\n\n####1422", "a": 912, "b": 510, "operator": "+", "result": 1422}
{"question": "Solve (703 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (703 / 376) is 1.8697\n\n####1.8697", "a": 703, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8697}
{"question": "Solve (431 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (431 - 317) is 114\n\n####114", "a": 431, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve (122 * 269)", "answer": "The result of (122 * 269) is 32818\n\n####32818", "a": 122, "b": 269, "operator": "*", "result": 32818}
{"question": "Solve (390 + 243)", "answer": "The result of (390 + 243) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 390, "b": 243, "operator": "+", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (572 - 367)", "answer": "The result of (572 - 367) is 205\n\n####205", "a": 572, "b": 367, "operator": "-", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve (380 - 373)", "answer": "The result of (380 - 373) is 7\n\n####7", "a": 380, "b": 373, "operator": "-", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve (599 - 476)", "answer": "The result of (599 - 476) is 123\n\n####123", "a": 599, "b": 476, "operator": "-", "result": 123}
{"question": "Solve (694 * 437)", "answer": "The result of (694 * 437) is 303278\n\n####303278", "a": 694, "b": 437, "operator": "*", "result": 303278}
{"question": "Solve (947 * 981)", "answer": "The result of (947 * 981) is 929007\n\n####929007", "a": 947, "b": 981, "operator": "*", "result": 929007}
{"question": "Solve (740 + 566)", "answer": "The result of (740 + 566) is 1306\n\n####1306", "a": 740, "b": 566, "operator": "+", "result": 1306}
{"question": "Solve (120 * 171)", "answer": "The result of (120 * 171) is 20520\n\n####20520", "a": 120, "b": 171, "operator": "*", "result": 20520}
{"question": "Solve (821 - 627)", "answer": "The result of (821 - 627) is 194\n\n####194", "a": 821, "b": 627, "operator": "-", "result": 194}
{"question": "Solve (837 * 764)", "answer": "The result of (837 * 764) is 639468\n\n####639468", "a": 837, "b": 764, "operator": "*", "result": 639468}
{"question": "Solve (976 / 304)", "answer": "The result of (976 / 304) is 3.2105\n\n####3.2105", "a": 976, "b": 304, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2105}
{"question": "Solve (755 - 396)", "answer": "The result of (755 - 396) is 359\n\n####359", "a": 755, "b": 396, "operator": "-", "result": 359}
{"question": "Solve (456 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (456 + 19) is 475\n\n####475", "a": 456, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 475}
{"question": "Solve (116 * 190)", "answer": "The result of (116 * 190) is 22040\n\n####22040", "a": 116, "b": 190, "operator": "*", "result": 22040}
{"question": "Solve (648 + 539)", "answer": "The result of (648 + 539) is 1187\n\n####1187", "a": 648, "b": 539, "operator": "+", "result": 1187}
{"question": "Solve (790 / 762)", "answer": "The result of (790 / 762) is 1.0367\n\n####1.0367", "a": 790, "b": 762, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0367}
{"question": "Solve (289 * 572)", "answer": "The result of (289 * 572) is 165308\n\n####165308", "a": 289, "b": 572, "operator": "*", "result": 165308}
{"question": "Solve (440 * 660)", "answer": "The result of (440 * 660) is 290400\n\n####290400", "a": 440, "b": 660, "operator": "*", "result": 290400}
{"question": "Solve (114 + 336)", "answer": "The result of (114 + 336) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 114, "b": 336, "operator": "+", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 432)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 432) is 1.831\n\n####1.831", "a": 791, "b": 432, "operator": "/", "result": 1.831}
{"question": "Solve (928 / 884)", "answer": "The result of (928 / 884) is 1.0498\n\n####1.0498", "a": 928, "b": 884, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0498}
{"question": "Solve (209 - 773)", "answer": "The result of (209 - 773) is -564\n\n####-564", "a": 209, "b": 773, "operator": "-", "result": -564}
{"question": "Solve (591 / 493)", "answer": "The result of (591 / 493) is 1.1988\n\n####1.1988", "a": 591, "b": 493, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1988}
{"question": "Solve (182 - 320)", "answer": "The result of (182 - 320) is -138\n\n####-138", "a": 182, "b": 320, "operator": "-", "result": -138}
{"question": "Solve (427 * 316)", "answer": "The result of (427 * 316) is 134932\n\n####134932", "a": 427, "b": 316, "operator": "*", "result": 134932}
{"question": "Solve (100 / 774)", "answer": "The result of (100 / 774) is 0.1292\n\n####0.1292", "a": 100, "b": 774, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1292}
{"question": "Solve (765 - 308)", "answer": "The result of (765 - 308) is 457\n\n####457", "a": 765, "b": 308, "operator": "-", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve (275 * 338)", "answer": "The result of (275 * 338) is 92950\n\n####92950", "a": 275, "b": 338, "operator": "*", "result": 92950}
{"question": "Solve (534 - 430)", "answer": "The result of (534 - 430) is 104\n\n####104", "a": 534, "b": 430, "operator": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve (869 / 253)", "answer": "The result of (869 / 253) is 3.4348\n\n####3.4348", "a": 869, "b": 253, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4348}
{"question": "Solve (656 * 671)", "answer": "The result of (656 * 671) is 440176\n\n####440176", "a": 656, "b": 671, "operator": "*", "result": 440176}
{"question": "Solve (334 - 33)", "answer": "The result of (334 - 33) is 301\n\n####301", "a": 334, "b": 33, "operator": "-", "result": 301}
{"question": "Solve (125 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (125 - 500) is -375\n\n####-375", "a": 125, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": -375}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 476)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 476) is 110\n\n####110", "a": 586, "b": 476, "operator": "-", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve (513 - 674)", "answer": "The result of (513 - 674) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 513, "b": 674, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 313)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 313) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 828, "b": 313, "operator": "-", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (207 + 588)", "answer": "The result of (207 + 588) is 795\n\n####795", "a": 207, "b": 588, "operator": "+", "result": 795}
{"question": "Solve (371 - 796)", "answer": "The result of (371 - 796) is -425\n\n####-425", "a": 371, "b": 796, "operator": "-", "result": -425}
{"question": "Solve (617 - 652)", "answer": "The result of (617 - 652) is -35\n\n####-35", "a": 617, "b": 652, "operator": "-", "result": -35}
{"question": "Solve (61 / 213)", "answer": "The result of (61 / 213) is 0.2864\n\n####0.2864", "a": 61, "b": 213, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2864}
{"question": "Solve (807 * 627)", "answer": "The result of (807 * 627) is 505989\n\n####505989", "a": 807, "b": 627, "operator": "*", "result": 505989}
{"question": "Solve (872 / 812)", "answer": "The result of (872 / 812) is 1.0739\n\n####1.0739", "a": 872, "b": 812, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0739}
{"question": "Solve (502 * 883)", "answer": "The result of (502 * 883) is 443266\n\n####443266", "a": 502, "b": 883, "operator": "*", "result": 443266}
{"question": "Solve (806 / 123)", "answer": "The result of (806 / 123) is 6.5528\n\n####6.5528", "a": 806, "b": 123, "operator": "/", "result": 6.5528}
{"question": "Solve (396 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (396 - 409) is -13\n\n####-13", "a": 396, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": -13}
{"question": "Solve (295 / 246)", "answer": "The result of (295 / 246) is 1.1992\n\n####1.1992", "a": 295, "b": 246, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1992}
{"question": "Solve (68 - 458)", "answer": "The result of (68 - 458) is -390\n\n####-390", "a": 68, "b": 458, "operator": "-", "result": -390}
{"question": "Solve (340 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (340 - 358) is -18\n\n####-18", "a": 340, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve (353 + 423)", "answer": "The result of (353 + 423) is 776\n\n####776", "a": 353, "b": 423, "operator": "+", "result": 776}
{"question": "Solve (383 / 110)", "answer": "The result of (383 / 110) is 3.4818\n\n####3.4818", "a": 383, "b": 110, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4818}
{"question": "Solve (869 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (869 - 408) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 869, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (674 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (674 - 283) is 391\n\n####391", "a": 674, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 391}
{"question": "Solve (552 + 548)", "answer": "The result of (552 + 548) is 1100\n\n####1100", "a": 552, "b": 548, "operator": "+", "result": 1100}
{"question": "Solve (43 * 751)", "answer": "The result of (43 * 751) is 32293\n\n####32293", "a": 43, "b": 751, "operator": "*", "result": 32293}
{"question": "Solve (806 / 162)", "answer": "The result of (806 / 162) is 4.9753\n\n####4.9753", "a": 806, "b": 162, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9753}
{"question": "Solve (161 * 888)", "answer": "The result of (161 * 888) is 142968\n\n####142968", "a": 161, "b": 888, "operator": "*", "result": 142968}
{"question": "Solve (281 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (281 / 489) is 0.5746\n\n####0.5746", "a": 281, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5746}
{"question": "Solve (777 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (777 * 939) is 729603\n\n####729603", "a": 777, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 729603}
{"question": "Solve (30 + 171)", "answer": "The result of (30 + 171) is 201\n\n####201", "a": 30, "b": 171, "operator": "+", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve (861 - 713)", "answer": "The result of (861 - 713) is 148\n\n####148", "a": 861, "b": 713, "operator": "-", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 382)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 382) is 660\n\n####660", "a": 278, "b": 382, "operator": "+", "result": 660}
{"question": "Solve (8 / 634)", "answer": "The result of (8 / 634) is 0.0126\n\n####0.0126", "a": 8, "b": 634, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0126}
{"question": "Solve (201 * 585)", "answer": "The result of (201 * 585) is 117585\n\n####117585", "a": 201, "b": 585, "operator": "*", "result": 117585}
{"question": "Solve (724 * 656)", "answer": "The result of (724 * 656) is 474944\n\n####474944", "a": 724, "b": 656, "operator": "*", "result": 474944}
{"question": "Solve (9 - 96)", "answer": "The result of (9 - 96) is -87\n\n####-87", "a": 9, "b": 96, "operator": "-", "result": -87}
{"question": "Solve (995 + 830)", "answer": "The result of (995 + 830) is 1825\n\n####1825", "a": 995, "b": 830, "operator": "+", "result": 1825}
{"question": "Solve (650 + 586)", "answer": "The result of (650 + 586) is 1236\n\n####1236", "a": 650, "b": 586, "operator": "+", "result": 1236}
{"question": "Solve (246 * 365)", "answer": "The result of (246 * 365) is 89790\n\n####89790", "a": 246, "b": 365, "operator": "*", "result": 89790}
{"question": "Solve (482 * 290)", "answer": "The result of (482 * 290) is 139780\n\n####139780", "a": 482, "b": 290, "operator": "*", "result": 139780}
{"question": "Solve (482 + 926)", "answer": "The result of (482 + 926) is 1408\n\n####1408", "a": 482, "b": 926, "operator": "+", "result": 1408}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 345)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 345) is -301\n\n####-301", "a": 44, "b": 345, "operator": "-", "result": -301}
{"question": "Solve (911 * 270)", "answer": "The result of (911 * 270) is 245970\n\n####245970", "a": 911, "b": 270, "operator": "*", "result": 245970}
{"question": "Solve (628 - 646)", "answer": "The result of (628 - 646) is -18\n\n####-18", "a": 628, "b": 646, "operator": "-", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve (641 / 286)", "answer": "The result of (641 / 286) is 2.2413\n\n####2.2413", "a": 641, "b": 286, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2413}
{"question": "Solve (216 - 829)", "answer": "The result of (216 - 829) is -613\n\n####-613", "a": 216, "b": 829, "operator": "-", "result": -613}
{"question": "Solve (254 - 597)", "answer": "The result of (254 - 597) is -343\n\n####-343", "a": 254, "b": 597, "operator": "-", "result": -343}
{"question": "Solve (882 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (882 / 322) is 2.7391\n\n####2.7391", "a": 882, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7391}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 280)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 280) is 642\n\n####642", "a": 922, "b": 280, "operator": "-", "result": 642}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 611)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 611) is -587\n\n####-587", "a": 24, "b": 611, "operator": "-", "result": -587}
{"question": "Solve (568 - 800)", "answer": "The result of (568 - 800) is -232\n\n####-232", "a": 568, "b": 800, "operator": "-", "result": -232}
{"question": "Solve (702 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (702 * 762) is 534924\n\n####534924", "a": 702, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 534924}
{"question": "Solve (632 - 671)", "answer": "The result of (632 - 671) is -39\n\n####-39", "a": 632, "b": 671, "operator": "-", "result": -39}
{"question": "Solve (982 + 334)", "answer": "The result of (982 + 334) is 1316\n\n####1316", "a": 982, "b": 334, "operator": "+", "result": 1316}
{"question": "Solve (372 + 719)", "answer": "The result of (372 + 719) is 1091\n\n####1091", "a": 372, "b": 719, "operator": "+", "result": 1091}
{"question": "Solve (706 / 433)", "answer": "The result of (706 / 433) is 1.6305\n\n####1.6305", "a": 706, "b": 433, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6305}
{"question": "Solve (166 * 60)", "answer": "The result of (166 * 60) is 9960\n\n####9960", "a": 166, "b": 60, "operator": "*", "result": 9960}
{"question": "Solve (242 / 234)", "answer": "The result of (242 / 234) is 1.0342\n\n####1.0342", "a": 242, "b": 234, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0342}
{"question": "Solve (306 - 801)", "answer": "The result of (306 - 801) is -495\n\n####-495", "a": 306, "b": 801, "operator": "-", "result": -495}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 102)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 102) is 988\n\n####988", "a": 886, "b": 102, "operator": "+", "result": 988}
{"question": "Solve (188 / 323)", "answer": "The result of (188 / 323) is 0.582\n\n####0.582", "a": 188, "b": 323, "operator": "/", "result": 0.582}
{"question": "Solve (372 - 394)", "answer": "The result of (372 - 394) is -22\n\n####-22", "a": 372, "b": 394, "operator": "-", "result": -22}
{"question": "Solve (238 / 433)", "answer": "The result of (238 / 433) is 0.5497\n\n####0.5497", "a": 238, "b": 433, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5497}
{"question": "Solve (986 + 631)", "answer": "The result of (986 + 631) is 1617\n\n####1617", "a": 986, "b": 631, "operator": "+", "result": 1617}
{"question": "Solve (53 * 341)", "answer": "The result of (53 * 341) is 18073\n\n####18073", "a": 53, "b": 341, "operator": "*", "result": 18073}
{"question": "Solve (574 - 333)", "answer": "The result of (574 - 333) is 241\n\n####241", "a": 574, "b": 333, "operator": "-", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve (391 + 638)", "answer": "The result of (391 + 638) is 1029\n\n####1029", "a": 391, "b": 638, "operator": "+", "result": 1029}
{"question": "Solve (732 - 591)", "answer": "The result of (732 - 591) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 732, "b": 591, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (795 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (795 - 384) is 411\n\n####411", "a": 795, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": 411}
{"question": "Solve (2 / 796)", "answer": "The result of (2 / 796) is 0.0025\n\n####0.0025", "a": 2, "b": 796, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0025}
{"question": "Solve (38 + 874)", "answer": "The result of (38 + 874) is 912\n\n####912", "a": 38, "b": 874, "operator": "+", "result": 912}
{"question": "Solve (725 * 975)", "answer": "The result of (725 * 975) is 706875\n\n####706875", "a": 725, "b": 975, "operator": "*", "result": 706875}
{"question": "Solve (919 / 620)", "answer": "The result of (919 / 620) is 1.4823\n\n####1.4823", "a": 919, "b": 620, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4823}
{"question": "Solve (224 * 364)", "answer": "The result of (224 * 364) is 81536\n\n####81536", "a": 224, "b": 364, "operator": "*", "result": 81536}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 252)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 252) is 34020\n\n####34020", "a": 135, "b": 252, "operator": "*", "result": 34020}
{"question": "Solve (139 * 146)", "answer": "The result of (139 * 146) is 20294\n\n####20294", "a": 139, "b": 146, "operator": "*", "result": 20294}
{"question": "Solve (450 * 804)", "answer": "The result of (450 * 804) is 361800\n\n####361800", "a": 450, "b": 804, "operator": "*", "result": 361800}
{"question": "Solve (595 / 386)", "answer": "The result of (595 / 386) is 1.5415\n\n####1.5415", "a": 595, "b": 386, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5415}
{"question": "Solve (160 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (160 - 250) is -90\n\n####-90", "a": 160, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": -90}
{"question": "Solve (314 / 626)", "answer": "The result of (314 / 626) is 0.5016\n\n####0.5016", "a": 314, "b": 626, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5016}
{"question": "Solve (204 * 559)", "answer": "The result of (204 * 559) is 114036\n\n####114036", "a": 204, "b": 559, "operator": "*", "result": 114036}
{"question": "Solve (906 * 107)", "answer": "The result of (906 * 107) is 96942\n\n####96942", "a": 906, "b": 107, "operator": "*", "result": 96942}
{"question": "Solve (553 * 82)", "answer": "The result of (553 * 82) is 45346\n\n####45346", "a": 553, "b": 82, "operator": "*", "result": 45346}
{"question": "Solve (718 - 106)", "answer": "The result of (718 - 106) is 612\n\n####612", "a": 718, "b": 106, "operator": "-", "result": 612}
{"question": "Solve (223 * 130)", "answer": "The result of (223 * 130) is 28990\n\n####28990", "a": 223, "b": 130, "operator": "*", "result": 28990}
{"question": "Solve (829 * 487)", "answer": "The result of (829 * 487) is 403723\n\n####403723", "a": 829, "b": 487, "operator": "*", "result": 403723}
{"question": "Solve (879 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (879 / 695) is 1.2647\n\n####1.2647", "a": 879, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2647}
{"question": "Solve (295 * 808)", "answer": "The result of (295 * 808) is 238360\n\n####238360", "a": 295, "b": 808, "operator": "*", "result": 238360}
{"question": "Solve (991 - 664)", "answer": "The result of (991 - 664) is 327\n\n####327", "a": 991, "b": 664, "operator": "-", "result": 327}
{"question": "Solve (899 * 735)", "answer": "The result of (899 * 735) is 660765\n\n####660765", "a": 899, "b": 735, "operator": "*", "result": 660765}
{"question": "Solve (647 * 830)", "answer": "The result of (647 * 830) is 537010\n\n####537010", "a": 647, "b": 830, "operator": "*", "result": 537010}
{"question": "Solve (527 * 785)", "answer": "The result of (527 * 785) is 413695\n\n####413695", "a": 527, "b": 785, "operator": "*", "result": 413695}
{"question": "Solve (471 - 336)", "answer": "The result of (471 - 336) is 135\n\n####135", "a": 471, "b": 336, "operator": "-", "result": 135}
{"question": "Solve (308 * 860)", "answer": "The result of (308 * 860) is 264880\n\n####264880", "a": 308, "b": 860, "operator": "*", "result": 264880}
{"question": "Solve (290 / 692)", "answer": "The result of (290 / 692) is 0.4191\n\n####0.4191", "a": 290, "b": 692, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4191}
{"question": "Solve (87 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (87 * 698) is 60726\n\n####60726", "a": 87, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 60726}
{"question": "Solve (977 / 604)", "answer": "The result of (977 / 604) is 1.6175\n\n####1.6175", "a": 977, "b": 604, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6175}
{"question": "Solve (508 / 51)", "answer": "The result of (508 / 51) is 9.9608\n\n####9.9608", "a": 508, "b": 51, "operator": "/", "result": 9.9608}
{"question": "Solve (357 - 177)", "answer": "The result of (357 - 177) is 180\n\n####180", "a": 357, "b": 177, "operator": "-", "result": 180}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 319)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 319) is 0.4232\n\n####0.4232", "a": 135, "b": 319, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4232}
{"question": "Solve (424 * 622)", "answer": "The result of (424 * 622) is 263728\n\n####263728", "a": 424, "b": 622, "operator": "*", "result": 263728}
{"question": "Solve (981 + 700)", "answer": "The result of (981 + 700) is 1681\n\n####1681", "a": 981, "b": 700, "operator": "+", "result": 1681}
{"question": "Solve (470 / 915)", "answer": "The result of (470 / 915) is 0.5137\n\n####0.5137", "a": 470, "b": 915, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5137}
{"question": "Solve (534 - 75)", "answer": "The result of (534 - 75) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 534, "b": 75, "operator": "-", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (462 + 290)", "answer": "The result of (462 + 290) is 752\n\n####752", "a": 462, "b": 290, "operator": "+", "result": 752}
{"question": "Solve (913 * 973)", "answer": "The result of (913 * 973) is 888349\n\n####888349", "a": 913, "b": 973, "operator": "*", "result": 888349}
{"question": "Solve (91 / 482)", "answer": "The result of (91 / 482) is 0.1888\n\n####0.1888", "a": 91, "b": 482, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1888}
{"question": "Solve (88 + 256)", "answer": "The result of (88 + 256) is 344\n\n####344", "a": 88, "b": 256, "operator": "+", "result": 344}
{"question": "Solve (676 / 685)", "answer": "The result of (676 / 685) is 0.9869\n\n####0.9869", "a": 676, "b": 685, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9869}
{"question": "Solve (494 - 468)", "answer": "The result of (494 - 468) is 26\n\n####26", "a": 494, "b": 468, "operator": "-", "result": 26}
{"question": "Solve (46 - 246)", "answer": "The result of (46 - 246) is -200\n\n####-200", "a": 46, "b": 246, "operator": "-", "result": -200}
{"question": "Solve (284 - 754)", "answer": "The result of (284 - 754) is -470\n\n####-470", "a": 284, "b": 754, "operator": "-", "result": -470}
{"question": "Solve (168 / 629)", "answer": "The result of (168 / 629) is 0.2671\n\n####0.2671", "a": 168, "b": 629, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2671}
{"question": "Solve (216 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (216 * 102) is 22032\n\n####22032", "a": 216, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 22032}
{"question": "Solve (154 * 226)", "answer": "The result of (154 * 226) is 34804\n\n####34804", "a": 154, "b": 226, "operator": "*", "result": 34804}
{"question": "Solve (478 * 150)", "answer": "The result of (478 * 150) is 71700\n\n####71700", "a": 478, "b": 150, "operator": "*", "result": 71700}
{"question": "Solve (315 * 31)", "answer": "The result of (315 * 31) is 9765\n\n####9765", "a": 315, "b": 31, "operator": "*", "result": 9765}
{"question": "Solve (654 + 938)", "answer": "The result of (654 + 938) is 1592\n\n####1592", "a": 654, "b": 938, "operator": "+", "result": 1592}
{"question": "Solve (578 - 644)", "answer": "The result of (578 - 644) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 578, "b": 644, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (611 - 531)", "answer": "The result of (611 - 531) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 611, "b": 531, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (12 - 484)", "answer": "The result of (12 - 484) is -472\n\n####-472", "a": 12, "b": 484, "operator": "-", "result": -472}
{"question": "Solve (854 * 532)", "answer": "The result of (854 * 532) is 454328\n\n####454328", "a": 854, "b": 532, "operator": "*", "result": 454328}
{"question": "Solve (945 / 562)", "answer": "The result of (945 / 562) is 1.6815\n\n####1.6815", "a": 945, "b": 562, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6815}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 580)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 580) is 236060\n\n####236060", "a": 407, "b": 580, "operator": "*", "result": 236060}
{"question": "Solve (725 + 736)", "answer": "The result of (725 + 736) is 1461\n\n####1461", "a": 725, "b": 736, "operator": "+", "result": 1461}
{"question": "Solve (97 - 414)", "answer": "The result of (97 - 414) is -317\n\n####-317", "a": 97, "b": 414, "operator": "-", "result": -317}
{"question": "Solve (152 + 384)", "answer": "The result of (152 + 384) is 536\n\n####536", "a": 152, "b": 384, "operator": "+", "result": 536}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 653)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 653) is -474\n\n####-474", "a": 179, "b": 653, "operator": "-", "result": -474}
{"question": "Solve (885 / 3)", "answer": "The result of (885 / 3) is 295.0\n\n####295.0", "a": 885, "b": 3, "operator": "/", "result": 295.0}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 860)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 860) is 7\n\n####7", "a": 867, "b": 860, "operator": "-", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve (653 + 829)", "answer": "The result of (653 + 829) is 1482\n\n####1482", "a": 653, "b": 829, "operator": "+", "result": 1482}
{"question": "Solve (65 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (65 * 86) is 5590\n\n####5590", "a": 65, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 5590}
{"question": "Solve (489 / 824)", "answer": "The result of (489 / 824) is 0.5934\n\n####0.5934", "a": 489, "b": 824, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5934}
{"question": "Solve (281 - 748)", "answer": "The result of (281 - 748) is -467\n\n####-467", "a": 281, "b": 748, "operator": "-", "result": -467}
{"question": "Solve (280 - 529)", "answer": "The result of (280 - 529) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 280, "b": 529, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (809 + 584)", "answer": "The result of (809 + 584) is 1393\n\n####1393", "a": 809, "b": 584, "operator": "+", "result": 1393}
{"question": "Solve (257 + 43)", "answer": "The result of (257 + 43) is 300\n\n####300", "a": 257, "b": 43, "operator": "+", "result": 300}
{"question": "Solve (261 * 530)", "answer": "The result of (261 * 530) is 138330\n\n####138330", "a": 261, "b": 530, "operator": "*", "result": 138330}
{"question": "Solve (659 * 816)", "answer": "The result of (659 * 816) is 537744\n\n####537744", "a": 659, "b": 816, "operator": "*", "result": 537744}
{"question": "Solve (39 / 807)", "answer": "The result of (39 / 807) is 0.0483\n\n####0.0483", "a": 39, "b": 807, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0483}
{"question": "Solve (935 / 595)", "answer": "The result of (935 / 595) is 1.5714\n\n####1.5714", "a": 935, "b": 595, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5714}
{"question": "Solve (265 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (265 + 11) is 276\n\n####276", "a": 265, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 276}
{"question": "Solve (291 / 726)", "answer": "The result of (291 / 726) is 0.4008\n\n####0.4008", "a": 291, "b": 726, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4008}
{"question": "Solve (556 - 800)", "answer": "The result of (556 - 800) is -244\n\n####-244", "a": 556, "b": 800, "operator": "-", "result": -244}
{"question": "Solve (641 + 365)", "answer": "The result of (641 + 365) is 1006\n\n####1006", "a": 641, "b": 365, "operator": "+", "result": 1006}
{"question": "Solve (780 / 710)", "answer": "The result of (780 / 710) is 1.0986\n\n####1.0986", "a": 780, "b": 710, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0986}
{"question": "Solve (666 + 600)", "answer": "The result of (666 + 600) is 1266\n\n####1266", "a": 666, "b": 600, "operator": "+", "result": 1266}
{"question": "Solve (89 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (89 - 701) is -612\n\n####-612", "a": 89, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": -612}
{"question": "Solve (777 / 684)", "answer": "The result of (777 / 684) is 1.136\n\n####1.136", "a": 777, "b": 684, "operator": "/", "result": 1.136}
{"question": "Solve (735 - 355)", "answer": "The result of (735 - 355) is 380\n\n####380", "a": 735, "b": 355, "operator": "-", "result": 380}
{"question": "Solve (146 * 79)", "answer": "The result of (146 * 79) is 11534\n\n####11534", "a": 146, "b": 79, "operator": "*", "result": 11534}
{"question": "Solve (39 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (39 - 701) is -662\n\n####-662", "a": 39, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": -662}
{"question": "Solve (559 / 9)", "answer": "The result of (559 / 9) is 62.1111\n\n####62.1111", "a": 559, "b": 9, "operator": "/", "result": 62.1111}
{"question": "Solve (672 - 615)", "answer": "The result of (672 - 615) is 57\n\n####57", "a": 672, "b": 615, "operator": "-", "result": 57}
{"question": "Solve (699 - 429)", "answer": "The result of (699 - 429) is 270\n\n####270", "a": 699, "b": 429, "operator": "-", "result": 270}
{"question": "Solve (847 / 727)", "answer": "The result of (847 / 727) is 1.1651\n\n####1.1651", "a": 847, "b": 727, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1651}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 740)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 740) is 1011\n\n####1011", "a": 271, "b": 740, "operator": "+", "result": 1011}
{"question": "Solve (939 - 950)", "answer": "The result of (939 - 950) is -11\n\n####-11", "a": 939, "b": 950, "operator": "-", "result": -11}
{"question": "Solve (456 + 580)", "answer": "The result of (456 + 580) is 1036\n\n####1036", "a": 456, "b": 580, "operator": "+", "result": 1036}
{"question": "Solve (272 - 951)", "answer": "The result of (272 - 951) is -679\n\n####-679", "a": 272, "b": 951, "operator": "-", "result": -679}
{"question": "Solve (454 - 178)", "answer": "The result of (454 - 178) is 276\n\n####276", "a": 454, "b": 178, "operator": "-", "result": 276}
{"question": "Solve (15 - 439)", "answer": "The result of (15 - 439) is -424\n\n####-424", "a": 15, "b": 439, "operator": "-", "result": -424}
{"question": "Solve (557 - 155)", "answer": "The result of (557 - 155) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 557, "b": 155, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (9 - 713)", "answer": "The result of (9 - 713) is -704\n\n####-704", "a": 9, "b": 713, "operator": "-", "result": -704}
{"question": "Solve (427 * 542)", "answer": "The result of (427 * 542) is 231434\n\n####231434", "a": 427, "b": 542, "operator": "*", "result": 231434}
{"question": "Solve (63 - 172)", "answer": "The result of (63 - 172) is -109\n\n####-109", "a": 63, "b": 172, "operator": "-", "result": -109}
{"question": "Solve (514 / 325)", "answer": "The result of (514 / 325) is 1.5815\n\n####1.5815", "a": 514, "b": 325, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5815}
{"question": "Solve (905 * 207)", "answer": "The result of (905 * 207) is 187335\n\n####187335", "a": 905, "b": 207, "operator": "*", "result": 187335}
{"question": "Solve (79 - 433)", "answer": "The result of (79 - 433) is -354\n\n####-354", "a": 79, "b": 433, "operator": "-", "result": -354}
{"question": "Solve (577 * 320)", "answer": "The result of (577 * 320) is 184640\n\n####184640", "a": 577, "b": 320, "operator": "*", "result": 184640}
{"question": "Solve (720 + 38)", "answer": "The result of (720 + 38) is 758\n\n####758", "a": 720, "b": 38, "operator": "+", "result": 758}
{"question": "Solve (715 / 553)", "answer": "The result of (715 / 553) is 1.2929\n\n####1.2929", "a": 715, "b": 553, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2929}
{"question": "Solve (170 - 804)", "answer": "The result of (170 - 804) is -634\n\n####-634", "a": 170, "b": 804, "operator": "-", "result": -634}
{"question": "Solve (241 + 251)", "answer": "The result of (241 + 251) is 492\n\n####492", "a": 241, "b": 251, "operator": "+", "result": 492}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 384)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 384) is 34176\n\n####34176", "a": 89, "b": 384, "operator": "*", "result": 34176}
{"question": "Solve (11 / 846)", "answer": "The result of (11 / 846) is 0.013\n\n####0.013", "a": 11, "b": 846, "operator": "/", "result": 0.013}
{"question": "Solve (416 + 855)", "answer": "The result of (416 + 855) is 1271\n\n####1271", "a": 416, "b": 855, "operator": "+", "result": 1271}
{"question": "Solve (748 + 411)", "answer": "The result of (748 + 411) is 1159\n\n####1159", "a": 748, "b": 411, "operator": "+", "result": 1159}
{"question": "Solve (996 / 800)", "answer": "The result of (996 / 800) is 1.245\n\n####1.245", "a": 996, "b": 800, "operator": "/", "result": 1.245}
{"question": "Solve (974 / 502)", "answer": "The result of (974 / 502) is 1.9402\n\n####1.9402", "a": 974, "b": 502, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9402}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 161)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 161) is 1104\n\n####1104", "a": 943, "b": 161, "operator": "+", "result": 1104}
{"question": "Solve (898 * 170)", "answer": "The result of (898 * 170) is 152660\n\n####152660", "a": 898, "b": 170, "operator": "*", "result": 152660}
{"question": "Solve (916 / 213)", "answer": "The result of (916 / 213) is 4.3005\n\n####4.3005", "a": 916, "b": 213, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3005}
{"question": "Solve (946 / 967)", "answer": "The result of (946 / 967) is 0.9783\n\n####0.9783", "a": 946, "b": 967, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9783}
{"question": "Solve (975 - 523)", "answer": "The result of (975 - 523) is 452\n\n####452", "a": 975, "b": 523, "operator": "-", "result": 452}
{"question": "Solve (640 / 22)", "answer": "The result of (640 / 22) is 29.0909\n\n####29.0909", "a": 640, "b": 22, "operator": "/", "result": 29.0909}
{"question": "Solve (872 - 5)", "answer": "The result of (872 - 5) is 867\n\n####867", "a": 872, "b": 5, "operator": "-", "result": 867}
{"question": "Solve (334 + 547)", "answer": "The result of (334 + 547) is 881\n\n####881", "a": 334, "b": 547, "operator": "+", "result": 881}
{"question": "Solve (620 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (620 - 998) is -378\n\n####-378", "a": 620, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -378}
{"question": "Solve (376 * 532)", "answer": "The result of (376 * 532) is 200032\n\n####200032", "a": 376, "b": 532, "operator": "*", "result": 200032}
{"question": "Solve (556 / 92)", "answer": "The result of (556 / 92) is 6.0435\n\n####6.0435", "a": 556, "b": 92, "operator": "/", "result": 6.0435}
{"question": "Solve (667 / 765)", "answer": "The result of (667 / 765) is 0.8719\n\n####0.8719", "a": 667, "b": 765, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8719}
{"question": "Solve (368 * 436)", "answer": "The result of (368 * 436) is 160448\n\n####160448", "a": 368, "b": 436, "operator": "*", "result": 160448}
{"question": "Solve (424 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (424 + 380) is 804\n\n####804", "a": 424, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 804}
{"question": "Solve (875 + 302)", "answer": "The result of (875 + 302) is 1177\n\n####1177", "a": 875, "b": 302, "operator": "+", "result": 1177}
{"question": "Solve (971 - 880)", "answer": "The result of (971 - 880) is 91\n\n####91", "a": 971, "b": 880, "operator": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve (638 - 619)", "answer": "The result of (638 - 619) is 19\n\n####19", "a": 638, "b": 619, "operator": "-", "result": 19}
{"question": "Solve (209 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (209 * 407) is 85063\n\n####85063", "a": 209, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 85063}
{"question": "Solve (89 - 122)", "answer": "The result of (89 - 122) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 89, "b": 122, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 322) is 2.1398\n\n####2.1398", "a": 689, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1398}
{"question": "Solve (322 / 136)", "answer": "The result of (322 / 136) is 2.3676\n\n####2.3676", "a": 322, "b": 136, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3676}
{"question": "Solve (511 - 198)", "answer": "The result of (511 - 198) is 313\n\n####313", "a": 511, "b": 198, "operator": "-", "result": 313}
{"question": "Solve (559 - 569)", "answer": "The result of (559 - 569) is -10\n\n####-10", "a": 559, "b": 569, "operator": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve (140 / 904)", "answer": "The result of (140 / 904) is 0.1549\n\n####0.1549", "a": 140, "b": 904, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1549}
{"question": "Solve (43 / 890)", "answer": "The result of (43 / 890) is 0.0483\n\n####0.0483", "a": 43, "b": 890, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0483}
{"question": "Solve (947 * 157)", "answer": "The result of (947 * 157) is 148679\n\n####148679", "a": 947, "b": 157, "operator": "*", "result": 148679}
{"question": "Solve (500 * 268)", "answer": "The result of (500 * 268) is 134000\n\n####134000", "a": 500, "b": 268, "operator": "*", "result": 134000}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 169)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 169) is 350\n\n####350", "a": 181, "b": 169, "operator": "+", "result": 350}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 245) is 231\n\n####231", "a": 476, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 231}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 625)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 625) is 1071\n\n####1071", "a": 446, "b": 625, "operator": "+", "result": 1071}
{"question": "Solve (727 / 837)", "answer": "The result of (727 / 837) is 0.8686\n\n####0.8686", "a": 727, "b": 837, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8686}
{"question": "Solve (710 - 167)", "answer": "The result of (710 - 167) is 543\n\n####543", "a": 710, "b": 167, "operator": "-", "result": 543}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 68)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 68) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 40, "b": 68, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (727 - 207)", "answer": "The result of (727 - 207) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 727, "b": 207, "operator": "-", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (441 + 561)", "answer": "The result of (441 + 561) is 1002\n\n####1002", "a": 441, "b": 561, "operator": "+", "result": 1002}
{"question": "Solve (953 + 246)", "answer": "The result of (953 + 246) is 1199\n\n####1199", "a": 953, "b": 246, "operator": "+", "result": 1199}
{"question": "Solve (532 * 720)", "answer": "The result of (532 * 720) is 383040\n\n####383040", "a": 532, "b": 720, "operator": "*", "result": 383040}
{"question": "Solve (396 - 875)", "answer": "The result of (396 - 875) is -479\n\n####-479", "a": 396, "b": 875, "operator": "-", "result": -479}
{"question": "Solve (232 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (232 - 779) is -547\n\n####-547", "a": 232, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": -547}
{"question": "Solve (767 / 725)", "answer": "The result of (767 / 725) is 1.0579\n\n####1.0579", "a": 767, "b": 725, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0579}
{"question": "Solve (326 * 568)", "answer": "The result of (326 * 568) is 185168\n\n####185168", "a": 326, "b": 568, "operator": "*", "result": 185168}
{"question": "Solve (884 + 681)", "answer": "The result of (884 + 681) is 1565\n\n####1565", "a": 884, "b": 681, "operator": "+", "result": 1565}
{"question": "Solve (335 + 946)", "answer": "The result of (335 + 946) is 1281\n\n####1281", "a": 335, "b": 946, "operator": "+", "result": 1281}
{"question": "Solve (866 + 772)", "answer": "The result of (866 + 772) is 1638\n\n####1638", "a": 866, "b": 772, "operator": "+", "result": 1638}
{"question": "Solve (497 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (497 - 206) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 497, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (633 * 872)", "answer": "The result of (633 * 872) is 551976\n\n####551976", "a": 633, "b": 872, "operator": "*", "result": 551976}
{"question": "Solve (145 / 866)", "answer": "The result of (145 / 866) is 0.1674\n\n####0.1674", "a": 145, "b": 866, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1674}
{"question": "Solve (662 / 467)", "answer": "The result of (662 / 467) is 1.4176\n\n####1.4176", "a": 662, "b": 467, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4176}
{"question": "Solve (861 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (861 * 548) is 471828\n\n####471828", "a": 861, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 471828}
{"question": "Solve (487 * 211)", "answer": "The result of (487 * 211) is 102757\n\n####102757", "a": 487, "b": 211, "operator": "*", "result": 102757}
{"question": "Solve (307 + 979)", "answer": "The result of (307 + 979) is 1286\n\n####1286", "a": 307, "b": 979, "operator": "+", "result": 1286}
{"question": "Solve (120 + 179)", "answer": "The result of (120 + 179) is 299\n\n####299", "a": 120, "b": 179, "operator": "+", "result": 299}
{"question": "Solve (77 + 383)", "answer": "The result of (77 + 383) is 460\n\n####460", "a": 77, "b": 383, "operator": "+", "result": 460}
{"question": "Solve (125 + 261)", "answer": "The result of (125 + 261) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 125, "b": 261, "operator": "+", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (245 * 965)", "answer": "The result of (245 * 965) is 236425\n\n####236425", "a": 245, "b": 965, "operator": "*", "result": 236425}
{"question": "Solve (488 * 220)", "answer": "The result of (488 * 220) is 107360\n\n####107360", "a": 488, "b": 220, "operator": "*", "result": 107360}
{"question": "Solve (167 + 167)", "answer": "The result of (167 + 167) is 334\n\n####334", "a": 167, "b": 167, "operator": "+", "result": 334}
{"question": "Solve (13 / 425)", "answer": "The result of (13 / 425) is 0.0306\n\n####0.0306", "a": 13, "b": 425, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0306}
{"question": "Solve (409 * 331)", "answer": "The result of (409 * 331) is 135379\n\n####135379", "a": 409, "b": 331, "operator": "*", "result": 135379}
{"question": "Solve (865 + 106)", "answer": "The result of (865 + 106) is 971\n\n####971", "a": 865, "b": 106, "operator": "+", "result": 971}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 695) is 0.1453\n\n####0.1453", "a": 101, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1453}
{"question": "Solve (557 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (557 - 609) is -52\n\n####-52", "a": 557, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": -52}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 201)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 201) is 0.7114\n\n####0.7114", "a": 143, "b": 201, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7114}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 249)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 249) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 271, "b": 249, "operator": "+", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 130)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 130) is 194\n\n####194", "a": 324, "b": 130, "operator": "-", "result": 194}
{"question": "Solve (508 / 546)", "answer": "The result of (508 / 546) is 0.9304\n\n####0.9304", "a": 508, "b": 546, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9304}
{"question": "Solve (190 * 424)", "answer": "The result of (190 * 424) is 80560\n\n####80560", "a": 190, "b": 424, "operator": "*", "result": 80560}
{"question": "Solve (880 + 757)", "answer": "The result of (880 + 757) is 1637\n\n####1637", "a": 880, "b": 757, "operator": "+", "result": 1637}
{"question": "Solve (709 / 709)", "answer": "The result of (709 / 709) is 1.0\n\n####1.0", "a": 709, "b": 709, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0}
{"question": "Solve (341 - 73)", "answer": "The result of (341 - 73) is 268\n\n####268", "a": 341, "b": 73, "operator": "-", "result": 268}
{"question": "Solve (909 + 992)", "answer": "The result of (909 + 992) is 1901\n\n####1901", "a": 909, "b": 992, "operator": "+", "result": 1901}
{"question": "Solve (15 * 589)", "answer": "The result of (15 * 589) is 8835\n\n####8835", "a": 15, "b": 589, "operator": "*", "result": 8835}
{"question": "Solve (143 * 707)", "answer": "The result of (143 * 707) is 101101\n\n####101101", "a": 143, "b": 707, "operator": "*", "result": 101101}
{"question": "Solve (63 + 557)", "answer": "The result of (63 + 557) is 620\n\n####620", "a": 63, "b": 557, "operator": "+", "result": 620}
{"question": "Solve (735 * 953)", "answer": "The result of (735 * 953) is 700455\n\n####700455", "a": 735, "b": 953, "operator": "*", "result": 700455}
{"question": "Solve (403 * 220)", "answer": "The result of (403 * 220) is 88660\n\n####88660", "a": 403, "b": 220, "operator": "*", "result": 88660}
{"question": "Solve (410 * 742)", "answer": "The result of (410 * 742) is 304220\n\n####304220", "a": 410, "b": 742, "operator": "*", "result": 304220}
{"question": "Solve (419 - 797)", "answer": "The result of (419 - 797) is -378\n\n####-378", "a": 419, "b": 797, "operator": "-", "result": -378}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 403)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 403) is 2.1042\n\n####2.1042", "a": 848, "b": 403, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1042}
{"question": "Solve (208 + 650)", "answer": "The result of (208 + 650) is 858\n\n####858", "a": 208, "b": 650, "operator": "+", "result": 858}
{"question": "Solve (325 * 472)", "answer": "The result of (325 * 472) is 153400\n\n####153400", "a": 325, "b": 472, "operator": "*", "result": 153400}
{"question": "Solve (566 * 335)", "answer": "The result of (566 * 335) is 189610\n\n####189610", "a": 566, "b": 335, "operator": "*", "result": 189610}
{"question": "Solve (216 + 415)", "answer": "The result of (216 + 415) is 631\n\n####631", "a": 216, "b": 415, "operator": "+", "result": 631}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 564)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 564) is 86\n\n####86", "a": 650, "b": 564, "operator": "-", "result": 86}
{"question": "Solve (709 + 397)", "answer": "The result of (709 + 397) is 1106\n\n####1106", "a": 709, "b": 397, "operator": "+", "result": 1106}
{"question": "Solve (176 - 650)", "answer": "The result of (176 - 650) is -474\n\n####-474", "a": 176, "b": 650, "operator": "-", "result": -474}
{"question": "Solve (443 + 916)", "answer": "The result of (443 + 916) is 1359\n\n####1359", "a": 443, "b": 916, "operator": "+", "result": 1359}
{"question": "Solve (770 * 338)", "answer": "The result of (770 * 338) is 260260\n\n####260260", "a": 770, "b": 338, "operator": "*", "result": 260260}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 262) is 332\n\n####332", "a": 594, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": 332}
{"question": "Solve (897 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (897 / 334) is 2.6856\n\n####2.6856", "a": 897, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6856}
{"question": "Solve (882 - 121)", "answer": "The result of (882 - 121) is 761\n\n####761", "a": 882, "b": 121, "operator": "-", "result": 761}
{"question": "Solve (258 - 139)", "answer": "The result of (258 - 139) is 119\n\n####119", "a": 258, "b": 139, "operator": "-", "result": 119}
{"question": "Solve (323 / 113)", "answer": "The result of (323 / 113) is 2.8584\n\n####2.8584", "a": 323, "b": 113, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8584}
{"question": "Solve (648 / 718)", "answer": "The result of (648 / 718) is 0.9025\n\n####0.9025", "a": 648, "b": 718, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9025}
{"question": "Solve (445 + 619)", "answer": "The result of (445 + 619) is 1064\n\n####1064", "a": 445, "b": 619, "operator": "+", "result": 1064}
{"question": "Solve (36 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (36 - 579) is -543\n\n####-543", "a": 36, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": -543}
{"question": "Solve (409 + 939)", "answer": "The result of (409 + 939) is 1348\n\n####1348", "a": 409, "b": 939, "operator": "+", "result": 1348}
{"question": "Solve (56 * 942)", "answer": "The result of (56 * 942) is 52752\n\n####52752", "a": 56, "b": 942, "operator": "*", "result": 52752}
{"question": "Solve (832 / 702)", "answer": "The result of (832 / 702) is 1.1852\n\n####1.1852", "a": 832, "b": 702, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1852}
{"question": "Solve (175 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (175 - 2) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 175, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (276 / 265)", "answer": "The result of (276 / 265) is 1.0415\n\n####1.0415", "a": 276, "b": 265, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0415}
{"question": "Solve (856 * 163)", "answer": "The result of (856 * 163) is 139528\n\n####139528", "a": 856, "b": 163, "operator": "*", "result": 139528}
{"question": "Solve (46 + 766)", "answer": "The result of (46 + 766) is 812\n\n####812", "a": 46, "b": 766, "operator": "+", "result": 812}
{"question": "Solve (399 + 222)", "answer": "The result of (399 + 222) is 621\n\n####621", "a": 399, "b": 222, "operator": "+", "result": 621}
{"question": "Solve (187 / 67)", "answer": "The result of (187 / 67) is 2.791\n\n####2.791", "a": 187, "b": 67, "operator": "/", "result": 2.791}
{"question": "Solve (283 / 715)", "answer": "The result of (283 / 715) is 0.3958\n\n####0.3958", "a": 283, "b": 715, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3958}
{"question": "Solve (899 * 578)", "answer": "The result of (899 * 578) is 519622\n\n####519622", "a": 899, "b": 578, "operator": "*", "result": 519622}
{"question": "Solve (833 * 76)", "answer": "The result of (833 * 76) is 63308\n\n####63308", "a": 833, "b": 76, "operator": "*", "result": 63308}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 377)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 377) is 1.8249\n\n####1.8249", "a": 688, "b": 377, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8249}
{"question": "Solve (114 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (114 / 686) is 0.1662\n\n####0.1662", "a": 114, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1662}
{"question": "Solve (571 + 422)", "answer": "The result of (571 + 422) is 993\n\n####993", "a": 571, "b": 422, "operator": "+", "result": 993}
{"question": "Solve (912 * 671)", "answer": "The result of (912 * 671) is 611952\n\n####611952", "a": 912, "b": 671, "operator": "*", "result": 611952}
{"question": "Solve (384 * 471)", "answer": "The result of (384 * 471) is 180864\n\n####180864", "a": 384, "b": 471, "operator": "*", "result": 180864}
{"question": "Solve (226 * 3)", "answer": "The result of (226 * 3) is 678\n\n####678", "a": 226, "b": 3, "operator": "*", "result": 678}
{"question": "Solve (167 * 757)", "answer": "The result of (167 * 757) is 126419\n\n####126419", "a": 167, "b": 757, "operator": "*", "result": 126419}
{"question": "Solve (617 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (617 / 87) is 7.092\n\n####7.092", "a": 617, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 7.092}
{"question": "Solve (182 * 196)", "answer": "The result of (182 * 196) is 35672\n\n####35672", "a": 182, "b": 196, "operator": "*", "result": 35672}
{"question": "Solve (423 - 128)", "answer": "The result of (423 - 128) is 295\n\n####295", "a": 423, "b": 128, "operator": "-", "result": 295}
{"question": "Solve (714 / 372)", "answer": "The result of (714 / 372) is 1.9194\n\n####1.9194", "a": 714, "b": 372, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9194}
{"question": "Solve (820 - 362)", "answer": "The result of (820 - 362) is 458\n\n####458", "a": 820, "b": 362, "operator": "-", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve (331 / 39)", "answer": "The result of (331 / 39) is 8.4872\n\n####8.4872", "a": 331, "b": 39, "operator": "/", "result": 8.4872}
{"question": "Solve (358 * 193)", "answer": "The result of (358 * 193) is 69094\n\n####69094", "a": 358, "b": 193, "operator": "*", "result": 69094}
{"question": "Solve (189 / 727)", "answer": "The result of (189 / 727) is 0.26\n\n####0.26", "a": 189, "b": 727, "operator": "/", "result": 0.26}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 166) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 323, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (784 * 825)", "answer": "The result of (784 * 825) is 646800\n\n####646800", "a": 784, "b": 825, "operator": "*", "result": 646800}
{"question": "Solve (91 - 478)", "answer": "The result of (91 - 478) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 91, "b": 478, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (785 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (785 * 862) is 676670\n\n####676670", "a": 785, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 676670}
{"question": "Solve (578 + 746)", "answer": "The result of (578 + 746) is 1324\n\n####1324", "a": 578, "b": 746, "operator": "+", "result": 1324}
{"question": "Solve (686 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (686 * 400) is 274400\n\n####274400", "a": 686, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 274400}
{"question": "Solve (347 * 899)", "answer": "The result of (347 * 899) is 311953\n\n####311953", "a": 347, "b": 899, "operator": "*", "result": 311953}
{"question": "Solve (605 * 475)", "answer": "The result of (605 * 475) is 287375\n\n####287375", "a": 605, "b": 475, "operator": "*", "result": 287375}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 87)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 87) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 204, "b": 87, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (952 + 627)", "answer": "The result of (952 + 627) is 1579\n\n####1579", "a": 952, "b": 627, "operator": "+", "result": 1579}
{"question": "Solve (547 * 856)", "answer": "The result of (547 * 856) is 468232\n\n####468232", "a": 547, "b": 856, "operator": "*", "result": 468232}
{"question": "Solve (718 / 25)", "answer": "The result of (718 / 25) is 28.72\n\n####28.72", "a": 718, "b": 25, "operator": "/", "result": 28.72}
{"question": "Solve (74 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (74 - 802) is -728\n\n####-728", "a": 74, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -728}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 898)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 898) is 1169\n\n####1169", "a": 271, "b": 898, "operator": "+", "result": 1169}
{"question": "Solve (791 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (791 * 911) is 720601\n\n####720601", "a": 791, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 720601}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 431) is -252\n\n####-252", "a": 179, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": -252}
{"question": "Solve (84 - 926)", "answer": "The result of (84 - 926) is -842\n\n####-842", "a": 84, "b": 926, "operator": "-", "result": -842}
{"question": "Solve (7 / 308)", "answer": "The result of (7 / 308) is 0.0227\n\n####0.0227", "a": 7, "b": 308, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0227}
{"question": "Solve (96 - 180)", "answer": "The result of (96 - 180) is -84\n\n####-84", "a": 96, "b": 180, "operator": "-", "result": -84}
{"question": "Solve (674 * 500)", "answer": "The result of (674 * 500) is 337000\n\n####337000", "a": 674, "b": 500, "operator": "*", "result": 337000}
{"question": "Solve (568 * 282)", "answer": "The result of (568 * 282) is 160176\n\n####160176", "a": 568, "b": 282, "operator": "*", "result": 160176}
{"question": "Solve (322 * 412)", "answer": "The result of (322 * 412) is 132664\n\n####132664", "a": 322, "b": 412, "operator": "*", "result": 132664}
{"question": "Solve (415 / 506)", "answer": "The result of (415 / 506) is 0.8202\n\n####0.8202", "a": 415, "b": 506, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8202}
{"question": "Solve (820 / 432)", "answer": "The result of (820 / 432) is 1.8981\n\n####1.8981", "a": 820, "b": 432, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8981}
{"question": "Solve (755 / 373)", "answer": "The result of (755 / 373) is 2.0241\n\n####2.0241", "a": 755, "b": 373, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0241}
{"question": "Solve (512 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (512 + 259) is 771\n\n####771", "a": 512, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 771}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 936)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 936) is -757\n\n####-757", "a": 179, "b": 936, "operator": "-", "result": -757}
{"question": "Solve (683 * 871)", "answer": "The result of (683 * 871) is 594893\n\n####594893", "a": 683, "b": 871, "operator": "*", "result": 594893}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 126)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 126) is 122346\n\n####122346", "a": 971, "b": 126, "operator": "*", "result": 122346}
{"question": "Solve (834 * 298)", "answer": "The result of (834 * 298) is 248532\n\n####248532", "a": 834, "b": 298, "operator": "*", "result": 248532}
{"question": "Solve (946 - 743)", "answer": "The result of (946 - 743) is 203\n\n####203", "a": 946, "b": 743, "operator": "-", "result": 203}
{"question": "Solve (140 * 355)", "answer": "The result of (140 * 355) is 49700\n\n####49700", "a": 140, "b": 355, "operator": "*", "result": 49700}
{"question": "Solve (904 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (904 - 295) is 609\n\n####609", "a": 904, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": 609}
{"question": "Solve (361 + 595)", "answer": "The result of (361 + 595) is 956\n\n####956", "a": 361, "b": 595, "operator": "+", "result": 956}
{"question": "Solve (898 / 361)", "answer": "The result of (898 / 361) is 2.4875\n\n####2.4875", "a": 898, "b": 361, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4875}
{"question": "Solve (764 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (764 - 206) is 558\n\n####558", "a": 764, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": 558}
{"question": "Solve (747 - 931)", "answer": "The result of (747 - 931) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 747, "b": 931, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (72 + 101)", "answer": "The result of (72 + 101) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 72, "b": 101, "operator": "+", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (564 - 508)", "answer": "The result of (564 - 508) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 564, "b": 508, "operator": "-", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (618 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (618 * 823) is 508614\n\n####508614", "a": 618, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 508614}
{"question": "Solve (292 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (292 - 876) is -584\n\n####-584", "a": 292, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -584}
{"question": "Solve (786 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (786 / 427) is 1.8407\n\n####1.8407", "a": 786, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8407}
{"question": "Solve (263 * 158)", "answer": "The result of (263 * 158) is 41554\n\n####41554", "a": 263, "b": 158, "operator": "*", "result": 41554}
{"question": "Solve (899 - 891)", "answer": "The result of (899 - 891) is 8\n\n####8", "a": 899, "b": 891, "operator": "-", "result": 8}
{"question": "Solve (684 / 559)", "answer": "The result of (684 / 559) is 1.2236\n\n####1.2236", "a": 684, "b": 559, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2236}
{"question": "Solve (477 * 576)", "answer": "The result of (477 * 576) is 274752\n\n####274752", "a": 477, "b": 576, "operator": "*", "result": 274752}
{"question": "Solve (328 * 613)", "answer": "The result of (328 * 613) is 201064\n\n####201064", "a": 328, "b": 613, "operator": "*", "result": 201064}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 569)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 569) is 0.283\n\n####0.283", "a": 161, "b": 569, "operator": "/", "result": 0.283}
{"question": "Solve (679 - 938)", "answer": "The result of (679 - 938) is -259\n\n####-259", "a": 679, "b": 938, "operator": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve (656 / 161)", "answer": "The result of (656 / 161) is 4.0745\n\n####4.0745", "a": 656, "b": 161, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0745}
{"question": "Solve (806 + 582)", "answer": "The result of (806 + 582) is 1388\n\n####1388", "a": 806, "b": 582, "operator": "+", "result": 1388}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 469)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 469) is 2.0341\n\n####2.0341", "a": 954, "b": 469, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0341}
{"question": "Solve (481 / 443)", "answer": "The result of (481 / 443) is 1.0858\n\n####1.0858", "a": 481, "b": 443, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0858}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 115)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 115) is 15\n\n####15", "a": 130, "b": 115, "operator": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 48)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 48) is 82\n\n####82", "a": 130, "b": 48, "operator": "-", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve (702 - 462)", "answer": "The result of (702 - 462) is 240\n\n####240", "a": 702, "b": 462, "operator": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve (328 * 123)", "answer": "The result of (328 * 123) is 40344\n\n####40344", "a": 328, "b": 123, "operator": "*", "result": 40344}
{"question": "Solve (75 / 169)", "answer": "The result of (75 / 169) is 0.4438\n\n####0.4438", "a": 75, "b": 169, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4438}
{"question": "Solve (862 / 727)", "answer": "The result of (862 / 727) is 1.1857\n\n####1.1857", "a": 862, "b": 727, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1857}
{"question": "Solve (666 / 973)", "answer": "The result of (666 / 973) is 0.6845\n\n####0.6845", "a": 666, "b": 973, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6845}
{"question": "Solve (116 * 238)", "answer": "The result of (116 * 238) is 27608\n\n####27608", "a": 116, "b": 238, "operator": "*", "result": 27608}
{"question": "Solve (593 / 380)", "answer": "The result of (593 / 380) is 1.5605\n\n####1.5605", "a": 593, "b": 380, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5605}
{"question": "Solve (553 - 696)", "answer": "The result of (553 - 696) is -143\n\n####-143", "a": 553, "b": 696, "operator": "-", "result": -143}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 884) is 611728\n\n####611728", "a": 692, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 611728}
{"question": "Solve (265 + 110)", "answer": "The result of (265 + 110) is 375\n\n####375", "a": 265, "b": 110, "operator": "+", "result": 375}
{"question": "Solve (133 + 477)", "answer": "The result of (133 + 477) is 610\n\n####610", "a": 133, "b": 477, "operator": "+", "result": 610}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 324)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 324) is 197964\n\n####197964", "a": 611, "b": 324, "operator": "*", "result": 197964}
{"question": "Solve (263 + 501)", "answer": "The result of (263 + 501) is 764\n\n####764", "a": 263, "b": 501, "operator": "+", "result": 764}
{"question": "Solve (658 / 501)", "answer": "The result of (658 / 501) is 1.3134\n\n####1.3134", "a": 658, "b": 501, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3134}
{"question": "Solve (630 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (630 / 815) is 0.773\n\n####0.773", "a": 630, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 0.773}
{"question": "Solve (239 + 576)", "answer": "The result of (239 + 576) is 815\n\n####815", "a": 239, "b": 576, "operator": "+", "result": 815}
{"question": "Solve (874 / 302)", "answer": "The result of (874 / 302) is 2.894\n\n####2.894", "a": 874, "b": 302, "operator": "/", "result": 2.894}
{"question": "Solve (508 / 707)", "answer": "The result of (508 / 707) is 0.7185\n\n####0.7185", "a": 508, "b": 707, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7185}
{"question": "Solve (912 / 333)", "answer": "The result of (912 / 333) is 2.7387\n\n####2.7387", "a": 912, "b": 333, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7387}
{"question": "Solve (392 / 277)", "answer": "The result of (392 / 277) is 1.4152\n\n####1.4152", "a": 392, "b": 277, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4152}
{"question": "Solve (628 / 209)", "answer": "The result of (628 / 209) is 3.0048\n\n####3.0048", "a": 628, "b": 209, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0048}
{"question": "Solve (755 + 593)", "answer": "The result of (755 + 593) is 1348\n\n####1348", "a": 755, "b": 593, "operator": "+", "result": 1348}
{"question": "Solve (939 / 490)", "answer": "The result of (939 / 490) is 1.9163\n\n####1.9163", "a": 939, "b": 490, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9163}
{"question": "Solve (695 / 970)", "answer": "The result of (695 / 970) is 0.7165\n\n####0.7165", "a": 695, "b": 970, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7165}
{"question": "Solve (147 * 338)", "answer": "The result of (147 * 338) is 49686\n\n####49686", "a": 147, "b": 338, "operator": "*", "result": 49686}
{"question": "Solve (821 * 772)", "answer": "The result of (821 * 772) is 633812\n\n####633812", "a": 821, "b": 772, "operator": "*", "result": 633812}
{"question": "Solve (164 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (164 * 390) is 63960\n\n####63960", "a": 164, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 63960}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 751)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 751) is 0.1904\n\n####0.1904", "a": 143, "b": 751, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1904}
{"question": "Solve (604 * 503)", "answer": "The result of (604 * 503) is 303812\n\n####303812", "a": 604, "b": 503, "operator": "*", "result": 303812}
{"question": "Solve (567 + 635)", "answer": "The result of (567 + 635) is 1202\n\n####1202", "a": 567, "b": 635, "operator": "+", "result": 1202}
{"question": "Solve (494 * 96)", "answer": "The result of (494 * 96) is 47424\n\n####47424", "a": 494, "b": 96, "operator": "*", "result": 47424}
{"question": "Solve (805 * 235)", "answer": "The result of (805 * 235) is 189175\n\n####189175", "a": 805, "b": 235, "operator": "*", "result": 189175}
{"question": "Solve (963 + 299)", "answer": "The result of (963 + 299) is 1262\n\n####1262", "a": 963, "b": 299, "operator": "+", "result": 1262}
{"question": "Solve (588 * 488)", "answer": "The result of (588 * 488) is 286944\n\n####286944", "a": 588, "b": 488, "operator": "*", "result": 286944}
{"question": "Solve (195 - 794)", "answer": "The result of (195 - 794) is -599\n\n####-599", "a": 195, "b": 794, "operator": "-", "result": -599}
{"question": "Solve (237 * 602)", "answer": "The result of (237 * 602) is 142674\n\n####142674", "a": 237, "b": 602, "operator": "*", "result": 142674}
{"question": "Solve (300 + 898)", "answer": "The result of (300 + 898) is 1198\n\n####1198", "a": 300, "b": 898, "operator": "+", "result": 1198}
{"question": "Solve (155 - 675)", "answer": "The result of (155 - 675) is -520\n\n####-520", "a": 155, "b": 675, "operator": "-", "result": -520}
{"question": "Solve (926 - 973)", "answer": "The result of (926 - 973) is -47\n\n####-47", "a": 926, "b": 973, "operator": "-", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve (769 + 733)", "answer": "The result of (769 + 733) is 1502\n\n####1502", "a": 769, "b": 733, "operator": "+", "result": 1502}
{"question": "Solve (381 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (381 - 579) is -198\n\n####-198", "a": 381, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": -198}
{"question": "Solve (780 / 77)", "answer": "The result of (780 / 77) is 10.1299\n\n####10.1299", "a": 780, "b": 77, "operator": "/", "result": 10.1299}
{"question": "Solve (596 + 486)", "answer": "The result of (596 + 486) is 1082\n\n####1082", "a": 596, "b": 486, "operator": "+", "result": 1082}
{"question": "Solve (106 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (106 * 932) is 98792\n\n####98792", "a": 106, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 98792}
{"question": "Solve (378 - 93)", "answer": "The result of (378 - 93) is 285\n\n####285", "a": 378, "b": 93, "operator": "-", "result": 285}
{"question": "Solve (412 - 56)", "answer": "The result of (412 - 56) is 356\n\n####356", "a": 412, "b": 56, "operator": "-", "result": 356}
{"question": "Solve (414 * 422)", "answer": "The result of (414 * 422) is 174708\n\n####174708", "a": 414, "b": 422, "operator": "*", "result": 174708}
{"question": "Solve (894 + 5)", "answer": "The result of (894 + 5) is 899\n\n####899", "a": 894, "b": 5, "operator": "+", "result": 899}
{"question": "Solve (91 + 970)", "answer": "The result of (91 + 970) is 1061\n\n####1061", "a": 91, "b": 970, "operator": "+", "result": 1061}
{"question": "Solve (238 + 328)", "answer": "The result of (238 + 328) is 566\n\n####566", "a": 238, "b": 328, "operator": "+", "result": 566}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 211)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 211) is 647\n\n####647", "a": 858, "b": 211, "operator": "-", "result": 647}
{"question": "Solve (323 / 749)", "answer": "The result of (323 / 749) is 0.4312\n\n####0.4312", "a": 323, "b": 749, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4312}
{"question": "Solve (376 - 596)", "answer": "The result of (376 - 596) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 376, "b": 596, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (235 * 731)", "answer": "The result of (235 * 731) is 171785\n\n####171785", "a": 235, "b": 731, "operator": "*", "result": 171785}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 362)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 362) is 365\n\n####365", "a": 3, "b": 362, "operator": "+", "result": 365}
{"question": "Solve (960 / 775)", "answer": "The result of (960 / 775) is 1.2387\n\n####1.2387", "a": 960, "b": 775, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2387}
{"question": "Solve (496 / 133)", "answer": "The result of (496 / 133) is 3.7293\n\n####3.7293", "a": 496, "b": 133, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7293}
{"question": "Solve (8 + 581)", "answer": "The result of (8 + 581) is 589\n\n####589", "a": 8, "b": 581, "operator": "+", "result": 589}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 381)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 381) is 416\n\n####416", "a": 797, "b": 381, "operator": "-", "result": 416}
{"question": "Solve (281 * 392)", "answer": "The result of (281 * 392) is 110152\n\n####110152", "a": 281, "b": 392, "operator": "*", "result": 110152}
{"question": "Solve (198 + 14)", "answer": "The result of (198 + 14) is 212\n\n####212", "a": 198, "b": 14, "operator": "+", "result": 212}
{"question": "Solve (315 * 876)", "answer": "The result of (315 * 876) is 275940\n\n####275940", "a": 315, "b": 876, "operator": "*", "result": 275940}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 747)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 747) is -389\n\n####-389", "a": 358, "b": 747, "operator": "-", "result": -389}
{"question": "Solve (411 * 709)", "answer": "The result of (411 * 709) is 291399\n\n####291399", "a": 411, "b": 709, "operator": "*", "result": 291399}
{"question": "Solve (819 + 296)", "answer": "The result of (819 + 296) is 1115\n\n####1115", "a": 819, "b": 296, "operator": "+", "result": 1115}
{"question": "Solve (153 - 77)", "answer": "The result of (153 - 77) is 76\n\n####76", "a": 153, "b": 77, "operator": "-", "result": 76}
{"question": "Solve (664 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (664 - 344) is 320\n\n####320", "a": 664, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": 320}
{"question": "Solve (415 + 192)", "answer": "The result of (415 + 192) is 607\n\n####607", "a": 415, "b": 192, "operator": "+", "result": 607}
{"question": "Solve (623 * 349)", "answer": "The result of (623 * 349) is 217427\n\n####217427", "a": 623, "b": 349, "operator": "*", "result": 217427}
{"question": "Solve (551 * 17)", "answer": "The result of (551 * 17) is 9367\n\n####9367", "a": 551, "b": 17, "operator": "*", "result": 9367}
{"question": "Solve (626 + 936)", "answer": "The result of (626 + 936) is 1562\n\n####1562", "a": 626, "b": 936, "operator": "+", "result": 1562}
{"question": "Solve (742 / 582)", "answer": "The result of (742 / 582) is 1.2749\n\n####1.2749", "a": 742, "b": 582, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2749}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 719)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 719) is 152428\n\n####152428", "a": 212, "b": 719, "operator": "*", "result": 152428}
{"question": "Solve (592 - 986)", "answer": "The result of (592 - 986) is -394\n\n####-394", "a": 592, "b": 986, "operator": "-", "result": -394}
{"question": "Solve (508 + 489)", "answer": "The result of (508 + 489) is 997\n\n####997", "a": 508, "b": 489, "operator": "+", "result": 997}
{"question": "Solve (647 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (647 / 390) is 1.659\n\n####1.659", "a": 647, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 1.659}
{"question": "Solve (488 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (488 + 805) is 1293\n\n####1293", "a": 488, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1293}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 548)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 548) is 0.3686\n\n####0.3686", "a": 202, "b": 548, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3686}
{"question": "Solve (750 * 322)", "answer": "The result of (750 * 322) is 241500\n\n####241500", "a": 750, "b": 322, "operator": "*", "result": 241500}
{"question": "Solve (32 + 952)", "answer": "The result of (32 + 952) is 984\n\n####984", "a": 32, "b": 952, "operator": "+", "result": 984}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 256) is -39\n\n####-39", "a": 217, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": -39}
{"question": "Solve (611 + 558)", "answer": "The result of (611 + 558) is 1169\n\n####1169", "a": 611, "b": 558, "operator": "+", "result": 1169}
{"question": "Solve (427 / 109)", "answer": "The result of (427 / 109) is 3.9174\n\n####3.9174", "a": 427, "b": 109, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9174}
{"question": "Solve (951 + 581)", "answer": "The result of (951 + 581) is 1532\n\n####1532", "a": 951, "b": 581, "operator": "+", "result": 1532}
{"question": "Solve (450 + 8)", "answer": "The result of (450 + 8) is 458\n\n####458", "a": 450, "b": 8, "operator": "+", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve (712 + 924)", "answer": "The result of (712 + 924) is 1636\n\n####1636", "a": 712, "b": 924, "operator": "+", "result": 1636}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 78)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 78) is 852\n\n####852", "a": 930, "b": 78, "operator": "-", "result": 852}
{"question": "Solve (453 / 421)", "answer": "The result of (453 / 421) is 1.076\n\n####1.076", "a": 453, "b": 421, "operator": "/", "result": 1.076}
{"question": "Solve (770 + 361)", "answer": "The result of (770 + 361) is 1131\n\n####1131", "a": 770, "b": 361, "operator": "+", "result": 1131}
{"question": "Solve (672 - 888)", "answer": "The result of (672 - 888) is -216\n\n####-216", "a": 672, "b": 888, "operator": "-", "result": -216}
{"question": "Solve (119 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (119 * 390) is 46410\n\n####46410", "a": 119, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 46410}
{"question": "Solve (503 / 702)", "answer": "The result of (503 / 702) is 0.7165\n\n####0.7165", "a": 503, "b": 702, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7165}
{"question": "Solve (804 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (804 - 162) is 642\n\n####642", "a": 804, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 642}
{"question": "Solve (777 + 585)", "answer": "The result of (777 + 585) is 1362\n\n####1362", "a": 777, "b": 585, "operator": "+", "result": 1362}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 457)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 457) is 340\n\n####340", "a": 797, "b": 457, "operator": "-", "result": 340}
{"question": "Solve (471 - 868)", "answer": "The result of (471 - 868) is -397\n\n####-397", "a": 471, "b": 868, "operator": "-", "result": -397}
{"question": "Solve (496 + 767)", "answer": "The result of (496 + 767) is 1263\n\n####1263", "a": 496, "b": 767, "operator": "+", "result": 1263}
{"question": "Solve (678 + 792)", "answer": "The result of (678 + 792) is 1470\n\n####1470", "a": 678, "b": 792, "operator": "+", "result": 1470}
{"question": "Solve (480 + 982)", "answer": "The result of (480 + 982) is 1462\n\n####1462", "a": 480, "b": 982, "operator": "+", "result": 1462}
{"question": "Solve (975 - 447)", "answer": "The result of (975 - 447) is 528\n\n####528", "a": 975, "b": 447, "operator": "-", "result": 528}
{"question": "Solve (988 - 61)", "answer": "The result of (988 - 61) is 927\n\n####927", "a": 988, "b": 61, "operator": "-", "result": 927}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 941)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 941) is 1.0425\n\n####1.0425", "a": 981, "b": 941, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0425}
{"question": "Solve (526 - 103)", "answer": "The result of (526 - 103) is 423\n\n####423", "a": 526, "b": 103, "operator": "-", "result": 423}
{"question": "Solve (943 * 378)", "answer": "The result of (943 * 378) is 356454\n\n####356454", "a": 943, "b": 378, "operator": "*", "result": 356454}
{"question": "Solve (988 / 281)", "answer": "The result of (988 / 281) is 3.516\n\n####3.516", "a": 988, "b": 281, "operator": "/", "result": 3.516}
{"question": "Solve (371 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (371 / 230) is 1.613\n\n####1.613", "a": 371, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 1.613}
{"question": "Solve (662 - 528)", "answer": "The result of (662 - 528) is 134\n\n####134", "a": 662, "b": 528, "operator": "-", "result": 134}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 476)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 476) is 359380\n\n####359380", "a": 755, "b": 476, "operator": "*", "result": 359380}
{"question": "Solve (212 + 297)", "answer": "The result of (212 + 297) is 509\n\n####509", "a": 212, "b": 297, "operator": "+", "result": 509}
{"question": "Solve (747 * 881)", "answer": "The result of (747 * 881) is 658107\n\n####658107", "a": 747, "b": 881, "operator": "*", "result": 658107}
{"question": "Solve (709 * 835)", "answer": "The result of (709 * 835) is 592015\n\n####592015", "a": 709, "b": 835, "operator": "*", "result": 592015}
{"question": "Solve (534 / 86)", "answer": "The result of (534 / 86) is 6.2093\n\n####6.2093", "a": 534, "b": 86, "operator": "/", "result": 6.2093}
{"question": "Solve (388 * 589)", "answer": "The result of (388 * 589) is 228532\n\n####228532", "a": 388, "b": 589, "operator": "*", "result": 228532}
{"question": "Solve (99 + 125)", "answer": "The result of (99 + 125) is 224\n\n####224", "a": 99, "b": 125, "operator": "+", "result": 224}
{"question": "Solve (734 * 584)", "answer": "The result of (734 * 584) is 428656\n\n####428656", "a": 734, "b": 584, "operator": "*", "result": 428656}
{"question": "Solve (363 * 630)", "answer": "The result of (363 * 630) is 228690\n\n####228690", "a": 363, "b": 630, "operator": "*", "result": 228690}
{"question": "Solve (816 / 129)", "answer": "The result of (816 / 129) is 6.3256\n\n####6.3256", "a": 816, "b": 129, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3256}
{"question": "Solve (414 - 227)", "answer": "The result of (414 - 227) is 187\n\n####187", "a": 414, "b": 227, "operator": "-", "result": 187}
{"question": "Solve (980 + 242)", "answer": "The result of (980 + 242) is 1222\n\n####1222", "a": 980, "b": 242, "operator": "+", "result": 1222}
{"question": "Solve (53 / 833)", "answer": "The result of (53 / 833) is 0.0636\n\n####0.0636", "a": 53, "b": 833, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0636}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 156)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 156) is 318\n\n####318", "a": 474, "b": 156, "operator": "-", "result": 318}
{"question": "Solve (831 - 557)", "answer": "The result of (831 - 557) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 831, "b": 557, "operator": "-", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 461)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 461) is 348055\n\n####348055", "a": 755, "b": 461, "operator": "*", "result": 348055}
{"question": "Solve (120 / 877)", "answer": "The result of (120 / 877) is 0.1368\n\n####0.1368", "a": 120, "b": 877, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1368}
{"question": "Solve (391 - 126)", "answer": "The result of (391 - 126) is 265\n\n####265", "a": 391, "b": 126, "operator": "-", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve (388 + 471)", "answer": "The result of (388 + 471) is 859\n\n####859", "a": 388, "b": 471, "operator": "+", "result": 859}
{"question": "Solve (625 + 430)", "answer": "The result of (625 + 430) is 1055\n\n####1055", "a": 625, "b": 430, "operator": "+", "result": 1055}
{"question": "Solve (41 * 243)", "answer": "The result of (41 * 243) is 9963\n\n####9963", "a": 41, "b": 243, "operator": "*", "result": 9963}
{"question": "Solve (506 / 398)", "answer": "The result of (506 / 398) is 1.2714\n\n####1.2714", "a": 506, "b": 398, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2714}
{"question": "Solve (694 - 952)", "answer": "The result of (694 - 952) is -258\n\n####-258", "a": 694, "b": 952, "operator": "-", "result": -258}
{"question": "Solve (243 * 252)", "answer": "The result of (243 * 252) is 61236\n\n####61236", "a": 243, "b": 252, "operator": "*", "result": 61236}
{"question": "Solve (510 - 835)", "answer": "The result of (510 - 835) is -325\n\n####-325", "a": 510, "b": 835, "operator": "-", "result": -325}
{"question": "Solve (39 * 27)", "answer": "The result of (39 * 27) is 1053\n\n####1053", "a": 39, "b": 27, "operator": "*", "result": 1053}
{"question": "Solve (781 * 304)", "answer": "The result of (781 * 304) is 237424\n\n####237424", "a": 781, "b": 304, "operator": "*", "result": 237424}
{"question": "Solve (237 / 344)", "answer": "The result of (237 / 344) is 0.689\n\n####0.689", "a": 237, "b": 344, "operator": "/", "result": 0.689}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 676)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 676) is -311\n\n####-311", "a": 365, "b": 676, "operator": "-", "result": -311}
{"question": "Solve (981 + 420)", "answer": "The result of (981 + 420) is 1401\n\n####1401", "a": 981, "b": 420, "operator": "+", "result": 1401}
{"question": "Solve (318 / 118)", "answer": "The result of (318 / 118) is 2.6949\n\n####2.6949", "a": 318, "b": 118, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6949}
{"question": "Solve (63 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (63 - 700) is -637\n\n####-637", "a": 63, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -637}
{"question": "Solve (753 / 15)", "answer": "The result of (753 / 15) is 50.2\n\n####50.2", "a": 753, "b": 15, "operator": "/", "result": 50.2}
{"question": "Solve (370 / 767)", "answer": "The result of (370 / 767) is 0.4824\n\n####0.4824", "a": 370, "b": 767, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4824}
{"question": "Solve (360 * 213)", "answer": "The result of (360 * 213) is 76680\n\n####76680", "a": 360, "b": 213, "operator": "*", "result": 76680}
{"question": "Solve (295 + 373)", "answer": "The result of (295 + 373) is 668\n\n####668", "a": 295, "b": 373, "operator": "+", "result": 668}
{"question": "Solve (53 - 984)", "answer": "The result of (53 - 984) is -931\n\n####-931", "a": 53, "b": 984, "operator": "-", "result": -931}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 220)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 220) is 29\n\n####29", "a": 249, "b": 220, "operator": "-", "result": 29}
{"question": "Solve (371 - 903)", "answer": "The result of (371 - 903) is -532\n\n####-532", "a": 371, "b": 903, "operator": "-", "result": -532}
{"question": "Solve (651 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (651 * 762) is 496062\n\n####496062", "a": 651, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 496062}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 739)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 739) is 1.3275\n\n####1.3275", "a": 981, "b": 739, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3275}
{"question": "Solve (505 + 226)", "answer": "The result of (505 + 226) is 731\n\n####731", "a": 505, "b": 226, "operator": "+", "result": 731}
{"question": "Solve (118 + 970)", "answer": "The result of (118 + 970) is 1088\n\n####1088", "a": 118, "b": 970, "operator": "+", "result": 1088}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 865)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 865) is -514\n\n####-514", "a": 351, "b": 865, "operator": "-", "result": -514}
{"question": "Solve (51 - 831)", "answer": "The result of (51 - 831) is -780\n\n####-780", "a": 51, "b": 831, "operator": "-", "result": -780}
{"question": "Solve (623 / 755)", "answer": "The result of (623 / 755) is 0.8252\n\n####0.8252", "a": 623, "b": 755, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8252}
{"question": "Solve (221 + 401)", "answer": "The result of (221 + 401) is 622\n\n####622", "a": 221, "b": 401, "operator": "+", "result": 622}
{"question": "Solve (979 + 336)", "answer": "The result of (979 + 336) is 1315\n\n####1315", "a": 979, "b": 336, "operator": "+", "result": 1315}
{"question": "Solve (93 / 360)", "answer": "The result of (93 / 360) is 0.2583\n\n####0.2583", "a": 93, "b": 360, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2583}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 442)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 442) is 50830\n\n####50830", "a": 115, "b": 442, "operator": "*", "result": 50830}
{"question": "Solve (369 - 182)", "answer": "The result of (369 - 182) is 187\n\n####187", "a": 369, "b": 182, "operator": "-", "result": 187}
{"question": "Solve (881 * 174)", "answer": "The result of (881 * 174) is 153294\n\n####153294", "a": 881, "b": 174, "operator": "*", "result": 153294}
{"question": "Solve (837 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (837 - 384) is 453\n\n####453", "a": 837, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": 453}
{"question": "Solve (406 / 746)", "answer": "The result of (406 / 746) is 0.5442\n\n####0.5442", "a": 406, "b": 746, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5442}
{"question": "Solve (700 / 586)", "answer": "The result of (700 / 586) is 1.1945\n\n####1.1945", "a": 700, "b": 586, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1945}
{"question": "Solve (691 + 939)", "answer": "The result of (691 + 939) is 1630\n\n####1630", "a": 691, "b": 939, "operator": "+", "result": 1630}
{"question": "Solve (634 / 907)", "answer": "The result of (634 / 907) is 0.699\n\n####0.699", "a": 634, "b": 907, "operator": "/", "result": 0.699}
{"question": "Solve (753 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (753 - 945) is -192\n\n####-192", "a": 753, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -192}
{"question": "Solve (958 + 18)", "answer": "The result of (958 + 18) is 976\n\n####976", "a": 958, "b": 18, "operator": "+", "result": 976}
{"question": "Solve (137 + 176)", "answer": "The result of (137 + 176) is 313\n\n####313", "a": 137, "b": 176, "operator": "+", "result": 313}
{"question": "Solve (621 - 649)", "answer": "The result of (621 - 649) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 621, "b": 649, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (477 / 956)", "answer": "The result of (477 / 956) is 0.499\n\n####0.499", "a": 477, "b": 956, "operator": "/", "result": 0.499}
{"question": "Solve (319 - 688)", "answer": "The result of (319 - 688) is -369\n\n####-369", "a": 319, "b": 688, "operator": "-", "result": -369}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 585)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 585) is 342810\n\n####342810", "a": 586, "b": 585, "operator": "*", "result": 342810}
{"question": "Solve (665 + 18)", "answer": "The result of (665 + 18) is 683\n\n####683", "a": 665, "b": 18, "operator": "+", "result": 683}
{"question": "Solve (124 + 978)", "answer": "The result of (124 + 978) is 1102\n\n####1102", "a": 124, "b": 978, "operator": "+", "result": 1102}
{"question": "Solve (196 / 760)", "answer": "The result of (196 / 760) is 0.2579\n\n####0.2579", "a": 196, "b": 760, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2579}
{"question": "Solve (462 + 469)", "answer": "The result of (462 + 469) is 931\n\n####931", "a": 462, "b": 469, "operator": "+", "result": 931}
{"question": "Solve (876 / 933)", "answer": "The result of (876 / 933) is 0.9389\n\n####0.9389", "a": 876, "b": 933, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9389}
{"question": "Solve (171 * 761)", "answer": "The result of (171 * 761) is 130131\n\n####130131", "a": 171, "b": 761, "operator": "*", "result": 130131}
{"question": "Solve (829 * 561)", "answer": "The result of (829 * 561) is 465069\n\n####465069", "a": 829, "b": 561, "operator": "*", "result": 465069}
{"question": "Solve (298 / 238)", "answer": "The result of (298 / 238) is 1.2521\n\n####1.2521", "a": 298, "b": 238, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2521}
{"question": "Solve (527 - 80)", "answer": "The result of (527 - 80) is 447\n\n####447", "a": 527, "b": 80, "operator": "-", "result": 447}
{"question": "Solve (78 - 68)", "answer": "The result of (78 - 68) is 10\n\n####10", "a": 78, "b": 68, "operator": "-", "result": 10}
{"question": "Solve (308 * 248)", "answer": "The result of (308 * 248) is 76384\n\n####76384", "a": 308, "b": 248, "operator": "*", "result": 76384}
{"question": "Solve (983 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (983 * 142) is 139586\n\n####139586", "a": 983, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 139586}
{"question": "Solve (235 - 793)", "answer": "The result of (235 - 793) is -558\n\n####-558", "a": 235, "b": 793, "operator": "-", "result": -558}
{"question": "Solve (668 / 435)", "answer": "The result of (668 / 435) is 1.5356\n\n####1.5356", "a": 668, "b": 435, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5356}
{"question": "Solve (27 - 548)", "answer": "The result of (27 - 548) is -521\n\n####-521", "a": 27, "b": 548, "operator": "-", "result": -521}
{"question": "Solve (921 - 817)", "answer": "The result of (921 - 817) is 104\n\n####104", "a": 921, "b": 817, "operator": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve (495 - 643)", "answer": "The result of (495 - 643) is -148\n\n####-148", "a": 495, "b": 643, "operator": "-", "result": -148}
{"question": "Solve (993 - 613)", "answer": "The result of (993 - 613) is 380\n\n####380", "a": 993, "b": 613, "operator": "-", "result": 380}
{"question": "Solve (39 + 638)", "answer": "The result of (39 + 638) is 677\n\n####677", "a": 39, "b": 638, "operator": "+", "result": 677}
{"question": "Solve (486 + 42)", "answer": "The result of (486 + 42) is 528\n\n####528", "a": 486, "b": 42, "operator": "+", "result": 528}
{"question": "Solve (317 - 176)", "answer": "The result of (317 - 176) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 317, "b": 176, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (441 / 342)", "answer": "The result of (441 / 342) is 1.2895\n\n####1.2895", "a": 441, "b": 342, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2895}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 579)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 579) is 36477\n\n####36477", "a": 63, "b": 579, "operator": "*", "result": 36477}
{"question": "Solve (366 * 662)", "answer": "The result of (366 * 662) is 242292\n\n####242292", "a": 366, "b": 662, "operator": "*", "result": 242292}
{"question": "Solve (640 * 782)", "answer": "The result of (640 * 782) is 500480\n\n####500480", "a": 640, "b": 782, "operator": "*", "result": 500480}
{"question": "Solve (526 * 442)", "answer": "The result of (526 * 442) is 232492\n\n####232492", "a": 526, "b": 442, "operator": "*", "result": 232492}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 523)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 523) is 127\n\n####127", "a": 650, "b": 523, "operator": "-", "result": 127}
{"question": "Solve (475 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (475 * 387) is 183825\n\n####183825", "a": 475, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 183825}
{"question": "Solve (164 + 447)", "answer": "The result of (164 + 447) is 611\n\n####611", "a": 164, "b": 447, "operator": "+", "result": 611}
{"question": "Solve (511 - 147)", "answer": "The result of (511 - 147) is 364\n\n####364", "a": 511, "b": 147, "operator": "-", "result": 364}
{"question": "Solve (203 - 815)", "answer": "The result of (203 - 815) is -612\n\n####-612", "a": 203, "b": 815, "operator": "-", "result": -612}
{"question": "Solve (35 * 319)", "answer": "The result of (35 * 319) is 11165\n\n####11165", "a": 35, "b": 319, "operator": "*", "result": 11165}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 106)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 106) is 60526\n\n####60526", "a": 571, "b": 106, "operator": "*", "result": 60526}
{"question": "Solve (417 * 11)", "answer": "The result of (417 * 11) is 4587\n\n####4587", "a": 417, "b": 11, "operator": "*", "result": 4587}
{"question": "Solve (132 - 881)", "answer": "The result of (132 - 881) is -749\n\n####-749", "a": 132, "b": 881, "operator": "-", "result": -749}
{"question": "Solve (160 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (160 - 409) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 160, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (520 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (520 * 690) is 358800\n\n####358800", "a": 520, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 358800}
{"question": "Solve (97 - 386)", "answer": "The result of (97 - 386) is -289\n\n####-289", "a": 97, "b": 386, "operator": "-", "result": -289}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 54)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 54) is 5.5\n\n####5.5", "a": 297, "b": 54, "operator": "/", "result": 5.5}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 296)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 296) is -244\n\n####-244", "a": 52, "b": 296, "operator": "-", "result": -244}
{"question": "Solve (312 * 914)", "answer": "The result of (312 * 914) is 285168\n\n####285168", "a": 312, "b": 914, "operator": "*", "result": 285168}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 986)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 986) is 1909\n\n####1909", "a": 923, "b": 986, "operator": "+", "result": 1909}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 646)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 646) is 262922\n\n####262922", "a": 407, "b": 646, "operator": "*", "result": 262922}
{"question": "Solve (99 / 546)", "answer": "The result of (99 / 546) is 0.1813\n\n####0.1813", "a": 99, "b": 546, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1813}
{"question": "Solve (998 + 140)", "answer": "The result of (998 + 140) is 1138\n\n####1138", "a": 998, "b": 140, "operator": "+", "result": 1138}
{"question": "Solve (18 - 443)", "answer": "The result of (18 - 443) is -425\n\n####-425", "a": 18, "b": 443, "operator": "-", "result": -425}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 753)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 753) is 114\n\n####114", "a": 867, "b": 753, "operator": "-", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve (76 - 540)", "answer": "The result of (76 - 540) is -464\n\n####-464", "a": 76, "b": 540, "operator": "-", "result": -464}
{"question": "Solve (293 + 644)", "answer": "The result of (293 + 644) is 937\n\n####937", "a": 293, "b": 644, "operator": "+", "result": 937}
{"question": "Solve (775 / 595)", "answer": "The result of (775 / 595) is 1.3025\n\n####1.3025", "a": 775, "b": 595, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3025}
{"question": "Solve (37 - 677)", "answer": "The result of (37 - 677) is -640\n\n####-640", "a": 37, "b": 677, "operator": "-", "result": -640}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 998) is -680\n\n####-680", "a": 318, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -680}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 869)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 869) is 1.1162\n\n####1.1162", "a": 970, "b": 869, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1162}
{"question": "Solve (470 - 436)", "answer": "The result of (470 - 436) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 470, "b": 436, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (701 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (701 - 779) is -78\n\n####-78", "a": 701, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": -78}
{"question": "Solve (718 * 885)", "answer": "The result of (718 * 885) is 635430\n\n####635430", "a": 718, "b": 885, "operator": "*", "result": 635430}
{"question": "Solve (76 + 847)", "answer": "The result of (76 + 847) is 923\n\n####923", "a": 76, "b": 847, "operator": "+", "result": 923}
{"question": "Solve (354 * 56)", "answer": "The result of (354 * 56) is 19824\n\n####19824", "a": 354, "b": 56, "operator": "*", "result": 19824}
{"question": "Solve (682 / 720)", "answer": "The result of (682 / 720) is 0.9472\n\n####0.9472", "a": 682, "b": 720, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9472}
{"question": "Solve (76 / 644)", "answer": "The result of (76 / 644) is 0.118\n\n####0.118", "a": 76, "b": 644, "operator": "/", "result": 0.118}
{"question": "Solve (442 - 759)", "answer": "The result of (442 - 759) is -317\n\n####-317", "a": 442, "b": 759, "operator": "-", "result": -317}
{"question": "Solve (151 - 793)", "answer": "The result of (151 - 793) is -642\n\n####-642", "a": 151, "b": 793, "operator": "-", "result": -642}
{"question": "Solve (657 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (657 - 547) is 110\n\n####110", "a": 657, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve (770 / 62)", "answer": "The result of (770 / 62) is 12.4194\n\n####12.4194", "a": 770, "b": 62, "operator": "/", "result": 12.4194}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 749)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 749) is 0.7437\n\n####0.7437", "a": 557, "b": 749, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7437}
{"question": "Solve (507 / 117)", "answer": "The result of (507 / 117) is 4.3333\n\n####4.3333", "a": 507, "b": 117, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3333}
{"question": "Solve (899 - 920)", "answer": "The result of (899 - 920) is -21\n\n####-21", "a": 899, "b": 920, "operator": "-", "result": -21}
{"question": "Solve (404 * 487)", "answer": "The result of (404 * 487) is 196748\n\n####196748", "a": 404, "b": 487, "operator": "*", "result": 196748}
{"question": "Solve (353 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (353 * 870) is 307110\n\n####307110", "a": 353, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 307110}
{"question": "Solve (991 + 728)", "answer": "The result of (991 + 728) is 1719\n\n####1719", "a": 991, "b": 728, "operator": "+", "result": 1719}
{"question": "Solve (928 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (928 / 294) is 3.1565\n\n####3.1565", "a": 928, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1565}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 282)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 282) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 490, "b": 282, "operator": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (140 + 291)", "answer": "The result of (140 + 291) is 431\n\n####431", "a": 140, "b": 291, "operator": "+", "result": 431}
{"question": "Solve (700 * 447)", "answer": "The result of (700 * 447) is 312900\n\n####312900", "a": 700, "b": 447, "operator": "*", "result": 312900}
{"question": "Solve (769 * 167)", "answer": "The result of (769 * 167) is 128423\n\n####128423", "a": 769, "b": 167, "operator": "*", "result": 128423}
{"question": "Solve (815 / 77)", "answer": "The result of (815 / 77) is 10.5844\n\n####10.5844", "a": 815, "b": 77, "operator": "/", "result": 10.5844}
{"question": "Solve (776 * 839)", "answer": "The result of (776 * 839) is 651064\n\n####651064", "a": 776, "b": 839, "operator": "*", "result": 651064}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 570)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 570) is 0.6333\n\n####0.6333", "a": 361, "b": 570, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6333}
{"question": "Solve (655 * 602)", "answer": "The result of (655 * 602) is 394310\n\n####394310", "a": 655, "b": 602, "operator": "*", "result": 394310}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 679)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 679) is 44814\n\n####44814", "a": 66, "b": 679, "operator": "*", "result": 44814}
{"question": "Solve (913 - 718)", "answer": "The result of (913 - 718) is 195\n\n####195", "a": 913, "b": 718, "operator": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 554)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 554) is 509680\n\n####509680", "a": 920, "b": 554, "operator": "*", "result": 509680}
{"question": "Solve (38 - 528)", "answer": "The result of (38 - 528) is -490\n\n####-490", "a": 38, "b": 528, "operator": "-", "result": -490}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 609)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 609) is 1.1314\n\n####1.1314", "a": 689, "b": 609, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1314}
{"question": "Solve (231 / 363)", "answer": "The result of (231 / 363) is 0.6364\n\n####0.6364", "a": 231, "b": 363, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6364}
{"question": "Solve (616 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (616 / 334) is 1.8443\n\n####1.8443", "a": 616, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8443}
{"question": "Solve (138 + 173)", "answer": "The result of (138 + 173) is 311\n\n####311", "a": 138, "b": 173, "operator": "+", "result": 311}
{"question": "Solve (873 * 367)", "answer": "The result of (873 * 367) is 320391\n\n####320391", "a": 873, "b": 367, "operator": "*", "result": 320391}
{"question": "Solve (272 * 979)", "answer": "The result of (272 * 979) is 266288\n\n####266288", "a": 272, "b": 979, "operator": "*", "result": 266288}
{"question": "Solve (428 + 314)", "answer": "The result of (428 + 314) is 742\n\n####742", "a": 428, "b": 314, "operator": "+", "result": 742}
{"question": "Solve (928 + 263)", "answer": "The result of (928 + 263) is 1191\n\n####1191", "a": 928, "b": 263, "operator": "+", "result": 1191}
{"question": "Solve (31 / 752)", "answer": "The result of (31 / 752) is 0.0412\n\n####0.0412", "a": 31, "b": 752, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0412}
{"question": "Solve (642 / 572)", "answer": "The result of (642 / 572) is 1.1224\n\n####1.1224", "a": 642, "b": 572, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1224}
{"question": "Solve (574 + 515)", "answer": "The result of (574 + 515) is 1089\n\n####1089", "a": 574, "b": 515, "operator": "+", "result": 1089}
{"question": "Solve (693 * 712)", "answer": "The result of (693 * 712) is 493416\n\n####493416", "a": 693, "b": 712, "operator": "*", "result": 493416}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 810)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 810) is 1.2111\n\n####1.2111", "a": 981, "b": 810, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2111}
{"question": "Solve (539 * 97)", "answer": "The result of (539 * 97) is 52283\n\n####52283", "a": 539, "b": 97, "operator": "*", "result": 52283}
{"question": "Solve (982 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (982 - 45) is 937\n\n####937", "a": 982, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 937}
{"question": "Solve (393 + 28)", "answer": "The result of (393 + 28) is 421\n\n####421", "a": 393, "b": 28, "operator": "+", "result": 421}
{"question": "Solve (585 / 272)", "answer": "The result of (585 / 272) is 2.1507\n\n####2.1507", "a": 585, "b": 272, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1507}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 320)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 320) is 75520\n\n####75520", "a": 236, "b": 320, "operator": "*", "result": 75520}
{"question": "Solve (166 + 523)", "answer": "The result of (166 + 523) is 689\n\n####689", "a": 166, "b": 523, "operator": "+", "result": 689}
{"question": "Solve (772 / 241)", "answer": "The result of (772 / 241) is 3.2033\n\n####3.2033", "a": 772, "b": 241, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2033}
{"question": "Solve (403 - 768)", "answer": "The result of (403 - 768) is -365\n\n####-365", "a": 403, "b": 768, "operator": "-", "result": -365}
{"question": "Solve (116 / 713)", "answer": "The result of (116 / 713) is 0.1627\n\n####0.1627", "a": 116, "b": 713, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1627}
{"question": "Solve (514 - 955)", "answer": "The result of (514 - 955) is -441\n\n####-441", "a": 514, "b": 955, "operator": "-", "result": -441}
{"question": "Solve (90 + 395)", "answer": "The result of (90 + 395) is 485\n\n####485", "a": 90, "b": 395, "operator": "+", "result": 485}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 84)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 84) is 42672\n\n####42672", "a": 508, "b": 84, "operator": "*", "result": 42672}
{"question": "Solve (465 + 415)", "answer": "The result of (465 + 415) is 880\n\n####880", "a": 465, "b": 415, "operator": "+", "result": 880}
{"question": "Solve (263 + 912)", "answer": "The result of (263 + 912) is 1175\n\n####1175", "a": 263, "b": 912, "operator": "+", "result": 1175}
{"question": "Solve (300 / 194)", "answer": "The result of (300 / 194) is 1.5464\n\n####1.5464", "a": 300, "b": 194, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5464}
{"question": "Solve (903 * 474)", "answer": "The result of (903 * 474) is 428022\n\n####428022", "a": 903, "b": 474, "operator": "*", "result": 428022}
{"question": "Solve (564 / 565)", "answer": "The result of (564 / 565) is 0.9982\n\n####0.9982", "a": 564, "b": 565, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9982}
{"question": "Solve (206 * 98)", "answer": "The result of (206 * 98) is 20188\n\n####20188", "a": 206, "b": 98, "operator": "*", "result": 20188}
{"question": "Solve (325 * 333)", "answer": "The result of (325 * 333) is 108225\n\n####108225", "a": 325, "b": 333, "operator": "*", "result": 108225}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 320)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 320) is 15\n\n####15", "a": 335, "b": 320, "operator": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve (595 - 565)", "answer": "The result of (595 - 565) is 30\n\n####30", "a": 595, "b": 565, "operator": "-", "result": 30}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 313)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 313) is 408\n\n####408", "a": 721, "b": 313, "operator": "-", "result": 408}
{"question": "Solve (4 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (4 * 332) is 1328\n\n####1328", "a": 4, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 1328}
{"question": "Solve (248 - 458)", "answer": "The result of (248 - 458) is -210\n\n####-210", "a": 248, "b": 458, "operator": "-", "result": -210}
{"question": "Solve (176 / 689)", "answer": "The result of (176 / 689) is 0.2554\n\n####0.2554", "a": 176, "b": 689, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2554}
{"question": "Solve (90 / 337)", "answer": "The result of (90 / 337) is 0.2671\n\n####0.2671", "a": 90, "b": 337, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2671}
{"question": "Solve (806 * 322)", "answer": "The result of (806 * 322) is 259532\n\n####259532", "a": 806, "b": 322, "operator": "*", "result": 259532}
{"question": "Solve (847 + 632)", "answer": "The result of (847 + 632) is 1479\n\n####1479", "a": 847, "b": 632, "operator": "+", "result": 1479}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 877)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 877) is 1849\n\n####1849", "a": 972, "b": 877, "operator": "+", "result": 1849}
{"question": "Solve (950 - 899)", "answer": "The result of (950 - 899) is 51\n\n####51", "a": 950, "b": 899, "operator": "-", "result": 51}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 6) is 804\n\n####804", "a": 810, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 804}
{"question": "Solve (828 * 938)", "answer": "The result of (828 * 938) is 776664\n\n####776664", "a": 828, "b": 938, "operator": "*", "result": 776664}
{"question": "Solve (338 + 331)", "answer": "The result of (338 + 331) is 669\n\n####669", "a": 338, "b": 331, "operator": "+", "result": 669}
{"question": "Solve (474 * 323)", "answer": "The result of (474 * 323) is 153102\n\n####153102", "a": 474, "b": 323, "operator": "*", "result": 153102}
{"question": "Solve (221 / 533)", "answer": "The result of (221 / 533) is 0.4146\n\n####0.4146", "a": 221, "b": 533, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4146}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 677)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 677) is 1.0295\n\n####1.0295", "a": 697, "b": 677, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0295}
{"question": "Solve (461 / 379)", "answer": "The result of (461 / 379) is 1.2164\n\n####1.2164", "a": 461, "b": 379, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2164}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 446)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 446) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 720, "b": 446, "operator": "-", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (502 + 574)", "answer": "The result of (502 + 574) is 1076\n\n####1076", "a": 502, "b": 574, "operator": "+", "result": 1076}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 792)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 792) is 0.3927\n\n####0.3927", "a": 311, "b": 792, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3927}
{"question": "Solve (728 * 382)", "answer": "The result of (728 * 382) is 278096\n\n####278096", "a": 728, "b": 382, "operator": "*", "result": 278096}
{"question": "Solve (696 * 254)", "answer": "The result of (696 * 254) is 176784\n\n####176784", "a": 696, "b": 254, "operator": "*", "result": 176784}
{"question": "Solve (988 * 733)", "answer": "The result of (988 * 733) is 724204\n\n####724204", "a": 988, "b": 733, "operator": "*", "result": 724204}
{"question": "Solve (386 * 197)", "answer": "The result of (386 * 197) is 76042\n\n####76042", "a": 386, "b": 197, "operator": "*", "result": 76042}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 132)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 132) is 455\n\n####455", "a": 587, "b": 132, "operator": "-", "result": 455}
{"question": "Solve (690 + 814)", "answer": "The result of (690 + 814) is 1504\n\n####1504", "a": 690, "b": 814, "operator": "+", "result": 1504}
{"question": "Solve (233 - 606)", "answer": "The result of (233 - 606) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 233, "b": 606, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (326 - 52)", "answer": "The result of (326 - 52) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 326, "b": 52, "operator": "-", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (238 - 747)", "answer": "The result of (238 - 747) is -509\n\n####-509", "a": 238, "b": 747, "operator": "-", "result": -509}
{"question": "Solve (433 * 651)", "answer": "The result of (433 * 651) is 281883\n\n####281883", "a": 433, "b": 651, "operator": "*", "result": 281883}
{"question": "Solve (352 / 776)", "answer": "The result of (352 / 776) is 0.4536\n\n####0.4536", "a": 352, "b": 776, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4536}
{"question": "Solve (132 - 920)", "answer": "The result of (132 - 920) is -788\n\n####-788", "a": 132, "b": 920, "operator": "-", "result": -788}
{"question": "Solve (814 - 339)", "answer": "The result of (814 - 339) is 475\n\n####475", "a": 814, "b": 339, "operator": "-", "result": 475}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 331)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 331) is 1303\n\n####1303", "a": 972, "b": 331, "operator": "+", "result": 1303}
{"question": "Solve (829 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (829 - 295) is 534\n\n####534", "a": 829, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": 534}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 388) is 1.8608\n\n####1.8608", "a": 722, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8608}
{"question": "Solve (544 * 411)", "answer": "The result of (544 * 411) is 223584\n\n####223584", "a": 544, "b": 411, "operator": "*", "result": 223584}
{"question": "Solve (791 * 914)", "answer": "The result of (791 * 914) is 722974\n\n####722974", "a": 791, "b": 914, "operator": "*", "result": 722974}
{"question": "Solve (268 - 504)", "answer": "The result of (268 - 504) is -236\n\n####-236", "a": 268, "b": 504, "operator": "-", "result": -236}
{"question": "Solve (89 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (89 + 358) is 447\n\n####447", "a": 89, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 447}
{"question": "Solve (974 - 377)", "answer": "The result of (974 - 377) is 597\n\n####597", "a": 974, "b": 377, "operator": "-", "result": 597}
{"question": "Solve (438 * 907)", "answer": "The result of (438 * 907) is 397266\n\n####397266", "a": 438, "b": 907, "operator": "*", "result": 397266}
{"question": "Solve (46 - 603)", "answer": "The result of (46 - 603) is -557\n\n####-557", "a": 46, "b": 603, "operator": "-", "result": -557}
{"question": "Solve (416 + 690)", "answer": "The result of (416 + 690) is 1106\n\n####1106", "a": 416, "b": 690, "operator": "+", "result": 1106}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 161)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 161) is 325\n\n####325", "a": 486, "b": 161, "operator": "-", "result": 325}
{"question": "Solve (445 / 837)", "answer": "The result of (445 / 837) is 0.5317\n\n####0.5317", "a": 445, "b": 837, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5317}
{"question": "Solve (296 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (296 / 914) is 0.3239\n\n####0.3239", "a": 296, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3239}
{"question": "Solve (801 / 446)", "answer": "The result of (801 / 446) is 1.796\n\n####1.796", "a": 801, "b": 446, "operator": "/", "result": 1.796}
{"question": "Solve (945 - 553)", "answer": "The result of (945 - 553) is 392\n\n####392", "a": 945, "b": 553, "operator": "-", "result": 392}
{"question": "Solve (273 / 158)", "answer": "The result of (273 / 158) is 1.7278\n\n####1.7278", "a": 273, "b": 158, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7278}
{"question": "Solve (761 * 291)", "answer": "The result of (761 * 291) is 221451\n\n####221451", "a": 761, "b": 291, "operator": "*", "result": 221451}
{"question": "Solve (526 + 168)", "answer": "The result of (526 + 168) is 694\n\n####694", "a": 526, "b": 168, "operator": "+", "result": 694}
{"question": "Solve (963 * 799)", "answer": "The result of (963 * 799) is 769437\n\n####769437", "a": 963, "b": 799, "operator": "*", "result": 769437}
{"question": "Solve (625 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (625 - 802) is -177\n\n####-177", "a": 625, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -177}
{"question": "Solve (181 * 429)", "answer": "The result of (181 * 429) is 77649\n\n####77649", "a": 181, "b": 429, "operator": "*", "result": 77649}
{"question": "Solve (328 - 618)", "answer": "The result of (328 - 618) is -290\n\n####-290", "a": 328, "b": 618, "operator": "-", "result": -290}
{"question": "Solve (945 * 206)", "answer": "The result of (945 * 206) is 194670\n\n####194670", "a": 945, "b": 206, "operator": "*", "result": 194670}
{"question": "Solve (510 / 130)", "answer": "The result of (510 / 130) is 3.9231\n\n####3.9231", "a": 510, "b": 130, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9231}
{"question": "Solve (383 + 77)", "answer": "The result of (383 + 77) is 460\n\n####460", "a": 383, "b": 77, "operator": "+", "result": 460}
{"question": "Solve (507 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (507 * 780) is 395460\n\n####395460", "a": 507, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 395460}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 150)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 150) is 2550\n\n####2550", "a": 17, "b": 150, "operator": "*", "result": 2550}
{"question": "Solve (899 / 181)", "answer": "The result of (899 / 181) is 4.9669\n\n####4.9669", "a": 899, "b": 181, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9669}
{"question": "Solve (640 + 788)", "answer": "The result of (640 + 788) is 1428\n\n####1428", "a": 640, "b": 788, "operator": "+", "result": 1428}
{"question": "Solve (590 * 914)", "answer": "The result of (590 * 914) is 539260\n\n####539260", "a": 590, "b": 914, "operator": "*", "result": 539260}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 799)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 799) is 361148\n\n####361148", "a": 452, "b": 799, "operator": "*", "result": 361148}
{"question": "Solve (827 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (827 / 43) is 19.2326\n\n####19.2326", "a": 827, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 19.2326}
{"question": "Solve (84 / 743)", "answer": "The result of (84 / 743) is 0.1131\n\n####0.1131", "a": 84, "b": 743, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1131}
{"question": "Solve (852 / 775)", "answer": "The result of (852 / 775) is 1.0994\n\n####1.0994", "a": 852, "b": 775, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0994}
{"question": "Solve (580 + 396)", "answer": "The result of (580 + 396) is 976\n\n####976", "a": 580, "b": 396, "operator": "+", "result": 976}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 281)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 281) is 561\n\n####561", "a": 842, "b": 281, "operator": "-", "result": 561}
{"question": "Solve (145 / 437)", "answer": "The result of (145 / 437) is 0.3318\n\n####0.3318", "a": 145, "b": 437, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3318}
{"question": "Solve (720 + 685)", "answer": "The result of (720 + 685) is 1405\n\n####1405", "a": 720, "b": 685, "operator": "+", "result": 1405}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 561)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 561) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 833, "b": 561, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (588 - 523)", "answer": "The result of (588 - 523) is 65\n\n####65", "a": 588, "b": 523, "operator": "-", "result": 65}
{"question": "Solve (712 / 366)", "answer": "The result of (712 / 366) is 1.9454\n\n####1.9454", "a": 712, "b": 366, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9454}
{"question": "Solve (125 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (125 / 230) is 0.5435\n\n####0.5435", "a": 125, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5435}
{"question": "Solve (764 * 97)", "answer": "The result of (764 * 97) is 74108\n\n####74108", "a": 764, "b": 97, "operator": "*", "result": 74108}
{"question": "Solve (278 - 125)", "answer": "The result of (278 - 125) is 153\n\n####153", "a": 278, "b": 125, "operator": "-", "result": 153}
{"question": "Solve (90 + 584)", "answer": "The result of (90 + 584) is 674\n\n####674", "a": 90, "b": 584, "operator": "+", "result": 674}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 400) is 54000\n\n####54000", "a": 135, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 54000}
{"question": "Solve (483 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (483 / 560) is 0.8625\n\n####0.8625", "a": 483, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8625}
{"question": "Solve (9 * 461)", "answer": "The result of (9 * 461) is 4149\n\n####4149", "a": 9, "b": 461, "operator": "*", "result": 4149}
{"question": "Solve (250 * 419)", "answer": "The result of (250 * 419) is 104750\n\n####104750", "a": 250, "b": 419, "operator": "*", "result": 104750}
{"question": "Solve (822 * 153)", "answer": "The result of (822 * 153) is 125766\n\n####125766", "a": 822, "b": 153, "operator": "*", "result": 125766}
{"question": "Solve (598 / 3)", "answer": "The result of (598 / 3) is 199.3333\n\n####199.3333", "a": 598, "b": 3, "operator": "/", "result": 199.3333}
{"question": "Solve (597 / 424)", "answer": "The result of (597 / 424) is 1.408\n\n####1.408", "a": 597, "b": 424, "operator": "/", "result": 1.408}
{"question": "Solve (444 * 662)", "answer": "The result of (444 * 662) is 293928\n\n####293928", "a": 444, "b": 662, "operator": "*", "result": 293928}
{"question": "Solve (828 + 966)", "answer": "The result of (828 + 966) is 1794\n\n####1794", "a": 828, "b": 966, "operator": "+", "result": 1794}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 638)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 638) is 1.1912\n\n####1.1912", "a": 760, "b": 638, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1912}
{"question": "Solve (339 + 183)", "answer": "The result of (339 + 183) is 522\n\n####522", "a": 339, "b": 183, "operator": "+", "result": 522}
{"question": "Solve (635 / 350)", "answer": "The result of (635 / 350) is 1.8143\n\n####1.8143", "a": 635, "b": 350, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8143}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 385)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 385) is 235235\n\n####235235", "a": 611, "b": 385, "operator": "*", "result": 235235}
{"question": "Solve (826 + 490)", "answer": "The result of (826 + 490) is 1316\n\n####1316", "a": 826, "b": 490, "operator": "+", "result": 1316}
{"question": "Solve (997 / 168)", "answer": "The result of (997 / 168) is 5.9345\n\n####5.9345", "a": 997, "b": 168, "operator": "/", "result": 5.9345}
{"question": "Solve (155 + 609)", "answer": "The result of (155 + 609) is 764\n\n####764", "a": 155, "b": 609, "operator": "+", "result": 764}
{"question": "Solve (49 + 33)", "answer": "The result of (49 + 33) is 82\n\n####82", "a": 49, "b": 33, "operator": "+", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve (553 / 784)", "answer": "The result of (553 / 784) is 0.7054\n\n####0.7054", "a": 553, "b": 784, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7054}
{"question": "Solve (904 - 499)", "answer": "The result of (904 - 499) is 405\n\n####405", "a": 904, "b": 499, "operator": "-", "result": 405}
{"question": "Solve (881 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (881 - 609) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 881, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (259 + 598)", "answer": "The result of (259 + 598) is 857\n\n####857", "a": 259, "b": 598, "operator": "+", "result": 857}
{"question": "Solve (5 / 111)", "answer": "The result of (5 / 111) is 0.045\n\n####0.045", "a": 5, "b": 111, "operator": "/", "result": 0.045}
{"question": "Solve (639 + 545)", "answer": "The result of (639 + 545) is 1184\n\n####1184", "a": 639, "b": 545, "operator": "+", "result": 1184}
{"question": "Solve (412 / 33)", "answer": "The result of (412 / 33) is 12.4848\n\n####12.4848", "a": 412, "b": 33, "operator": "/", "result": 12.4848}
{"question": "Solve (816 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (816 - 849) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 816, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (912 / 130)", "answer": "The result of (912 / 130) is 7.0154\n\n####7.0154", "a": 912, "b": 130, "operator": "/", "result": 7.0154}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 587)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 587) is -222\n\n####-222", "a": 365, "b": 587, "operator": "-", "result": -222}
{"question": "Solve (952 - 265)", "answer": "The result of (952 - 265) is 687\n\n####687", "a": 952, "b": 265, "operator": "-", "result": 687}
{"question": "Solve (546 / 201)", "answer": "The result of (546 / 201) is 2.7164\n\n####2.7164", "a": 546, "b": 201, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7164}
{"question": "Solve (154 - 589)", "answer": "The result of (154 - 589) is -435\n\n####-435", "a": 154, "b": 589, "operator": "-", "result": -435}
{"question": "Solve (131 / 116)", "answer": "The result of (131 / 116) is 1.1293\n\n####1.1293", "a": 131, "b": 116, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1293}
{"question": "Solve (391 + 667)", "answer": "The result of (391 + 667) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 391, "b": 667, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (193 / 441)", "answer": "The result of (193 / 441) is 0.4376\n\n####0.4376", "a": 193, "b": 441, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4376}
{"question": "Solve (818 / 37)", "answer": "The result of (818 / 37) is 22.1081\n\n####22.1081", "a": 818, "b": 37, "operator": "/", "result": 22.1081}
{"question": "Solve (846 / 275)", "answer": "The result of (846 / 275) is 3.0764\n\n####3.0764", "a": 846, "b": 275, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0764}
{"question": "Solve (218 - 575)", "answer": "The result of (218 - 575) is -357\n\n####-357", "a": 218, "b": 575, "operator": "-", "result": -357}
{"question": "Solve (364 - 812)", "answer": "The result of (364 - 812) is -448\n\n####-448", "a": 364, "b": 812, "operator": "-", "result": -448}
{"question": "Solve (226 * 11)", "answer": "The result of (226 * 11) is 2486\n\n####2486", "a": 226, "b": 11, "operator": "*", "result": 2486}
{"question": "Solve (340 / 31)", "answer": "The result of (340 / 31) is 10.9677\n\n####10.9677", "a": 340, "b": 31, "operator": "/", "result": 10.9677}
{"question": "Solve (605 * 771)", "answer": "The result of (605 * 771) is 466455\n\n####466455", "a": 605, "b": 771, "operator": "*", "result": 466455}
{"question": "Solve (785 + 363)", "answer": "The result of (785 + 363) is 1148\n\n####1148", "a": 785, "b": 363, "operator": "+", "result": 1148}
{"question": "Solve (143 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (143 - 168) is -25\n\n####-25", "a": 143, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": -25}
{"question": "Solve (929 * 922)", "answer": "The result of (929 * 922) is 856538\n\n####856538", "a": 929, "b": 922, "operator": "*", "result": 856538}
{"question": "Solve (610 * 500)", "answer": "The result of (610 * 500) is 305000\n\n####305000", "a": 610, "b": 500, "operator": "*", "result": 305000}
{"question": "Solve (103 + 729)", "answer": "The result of (103 + 729) is 832\n\n####832", "a": 103, "b": 729, "operator": "+", "result": 832}
{"question": "Solve (58 / 316)", "answer": "The result of (58 / 316) is 0.1835\n\n####0.1835", "a": 58, "b": 316, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1835}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 437)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 437) is 860\n\n####860", "a": 423, "b": 437, "operator": "+", "result": 860}
{"question": "Solve (811 * 612)", "answer": "The result of (811 * 612) is 496332\n\n####496332", "a": 811, "b": 612, "operator": "*", "result": 496332}
{"question": "Solve (139 + 303)", "answer": "The result of (139 + 303) is 442\n\n####442", "a": 139, "b": 303, "operator": "+", "result": 442}
{"question": "Solve (263 - 926)", "answer": "The result of (263 - 926) is -663\n\n####-663", "a": 263, "b": 926, "operator": "-", "result": -663}
{"question": "Solve (522 - 725)", "answer": "The result of (522 - 725) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 522, "b": 725, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (673 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (673 * 251) is 168923\n\n####168923", "a": 673, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 168923}
{"question": "Solve (592 - 659)", "answer": "The result of (592 - 659) is -67\n\n####-67", "a": 592, "b": 659, "operator": "-", "result": -67}
{"question": "Solve (170 - 852)", "answer": "The result of (170 - 852) is -682\n\n####-682", "a": 170, "b": 852, "operator": "-", "result": -682}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 413)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 413) is 0.4988\n\n####0.4988", "a": 206, "b": 413, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4988}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 471) is 339\n\n####339", "a": 810, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": 339}
{"question": "Solve (54 * 555)", "answer": "The result of (54 * 555) is 29970\n\n####29970", "a": 54, "b": 555, "operator": "*", "result": 29970}
{"question": "Solve (86 * 321)", "answer": "The result of (86 * 321) is 27606\n\n####27606", "a": 86, "b": 321, "operator": "*", "result": 27606}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 8)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 8) is 33.625\n\n####33.625", "a": 269, "b": 8, "operator": "/", "result": 33.625}
{"question": "Solve (279 / 902)", "answer": "The result of (279 / 902) is 0.3093\n\n####0.3093", "a": 279, "b": 902, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3093}
{"question": "Solve (731 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (731 - 162) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 731, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (279 / 646)", "answer": "The result of (279 / 646) is 0.4319\n\n####0.4319", "a": 279, "b": 646, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4319}
{"question": "Solve (875 / 244)", "answer": "The result of (875 / 244) is 3.5861\n\n####3.5861", "a": 875, "b": 244, "operator": "/", "result": 3.5861}
{"question": "Solve (393 + 773)", "answer": "The result of (393 + 773) is 1166\n\n####1166", "a": 393, "b": 773, "operator": "+", "result": 1166}
{"question": "Solve (741 * 392)", "answer": "The result of (741 * 392) is 290472\n\n####290472", "a": 741, "b": 392, "operator": "*", "result": 290472}
{"question": "Solve (302 * 699)", "answer": "The result of (302 * 699) is 211098\n\n####211098", "a": 302, "b": 699, "operator": "*", "result": 211098}
{"question": "Solve (718 + 525)", "answer": "The result of (718 + 525) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 718, "b": 525, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 465)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 465) is 122760\n\n####122760", "a": 264, "b": 465, "operator": "*", "result": 122760}
{"question": "Solve (139 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (139 / 43) is 3.2326\n\n####3.2326", "a": 139, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2326}
{"question": "Solve (507 / 217)", "answer": "The result of (507 / 217) is 2.3364\n\n####2.3364", "a": 507, "b": 217, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3364}
{"question": "Solve (316 + 347)", "answer": "The result of (316 + 347) is 663\n\n####663", "a": 316, "b": 347, "operator": "+", "result": 663}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 432)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 432) is 331\n\n####331", "a": 763, "b": 432, "operator": "-", "result": 331}
{"question": "Solve (648 - 569)", "answer": "The result of (648 - 569) is 79\n\n####79", "a": 648, "b": 569, "operator": "-", "result": 79}
{"question": "Solve (121 + 214)", "answer": "The result of (121 + 214) is 335\n\n####335", "a": 121, "b": 214, "operator": "+", "result": 335}
{"question": "Solve (681 - 389)", "answer": "The result of (681 - 389) is 292\n\n####292", "a": 681, "b": 389, "operator": "-", "result": 292}
{"question": "Solve (82 - 187)", "answer": "The result of (82 - 187) is -105\n\n####-105", "a": 82, "b": 187, "operator": "-", "result": -105}
{"question": "Solve (337 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (337 - 846) is -509\n\n####-509", "a": 337, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -509}
{"question": "Solve (908 * 757)", "answer": "The result of (908 * 757) is 687356\n\n####687356", "a": 908, "b": 757, "operator": "*", "result": 687356}
{"question": "Solve (780 + 833)", "answer": "The result of (780 + 833) is 1613\n\n####1613", "a": 780, "b": 833, "operator": "+", "result": 1613}
{"question": "Solve (58 + 139)", "answer": "The result of (58 + 139) is 197\n\n####197", "a": 58, "b": 139, "operator": "+", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve (680 / 37)", "answer": "The result of (680 / 37) is 18.3784\n\n####18.3784", "a": 680, "b": 37, "operator": "/", "result": 18.3784}
{"question": "Solve (614 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (614 / 53) is 11.5849\n\n####11.5849", "a": 614, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 11.5849}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 605)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 605) is -152\n\n####-152", "a": 453, "b": 605, "operator": "-", "result": -152}
{"question": "Solve (377 + 231)", "answer": "The result of (377 + 231) is 608\n\n####608", "a": 377, "b": 231, "operator": "+", "result": 608}
{"question": "Solve (6 / 878)", "answer": "The result of (6 / 878) is 0.0068\n\n####0.0068", "a": 6, "b": 878, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0068}
{"question": "Solve (612 / 462)", "answer": "The result of (612 / 462) is 1.3247\n\n####1.3247", "a": 612, "b": 462, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3247}
{"question": "Solve (973 + 883)", "answer": "The result of (973 + 883) is 1856\n\n####1856", "a": 973, "b": 883, "operator": "+", "result": 1856}
{"question": "Solve (57 * 985)", "answer": "The result of (57 * 985) is 56145\n\n####56145", "a": 57, "b": 985, "operator": "*", "result": 56145}
{"question": "Solve (562 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (562 / 290) is 1.9379\n\n####1.9379", "a": 562, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9379}
{"question": "Solve (844 + 919)", "answer": "The result of (844 + 919) is 1763\n\n####1763", "a": 844, "b": 919, "operator": "+", "result": 1763}
{"question": "Solve (406 + 899)", "answer": "The result of (406 + 899) is 1305\n\n####1305", "a": 406, "b": 899, "operator": "+", "result": 1305}
{"question": "Solve (539 + 408)", "answer": "The result of (539 + 408) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 539, "b": 408, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (488 - 716)", "answer": "The result of (488 - 716) is -228\n\n####-228", "a": 488, "b": 716, "operator": "-", "result": -228}
{"question": "Solve (1 / 770)", "answer": "The result of (1 / 770) is 0.0013\n\n####0.0013", "a": 1, "b": 770, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0013}
{"question": "Solve (684 - 939)", "answer": "The result of (684 - 939) is -255\n\n####-255", "a": 684, "b": 939, "operator": "-", "result": -255}
{"question": "Solve (630 * 741)", "answer": "The result of (630 * 741) is 466830\n\n####466830", "a": 630, "b": 741, "operator": "*", "result": 466830}
{"question": "Solve (778 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (778 * 698) is 543044\n\n####543044", "a": 778, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 543044}
{"question": "Solve (755 - 332)", "answer": "The result of (755 - 332) is 423\n\n####423", "a": 755, "b": 332, "operator": "-", "result": 423}
{"question": "Solve (513 + 453)", "answer": "The result of (513 + 453) is 966\n\n####966", "a": 513, "b": 453, "operator": "+", "result": 966}
{"question": "Solve (902 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (902 - 846) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 902, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (225 + 41)", "answer": "The result of (225 + 41) is 266\n\n####266", "a": 225, "b": 41, "operator": "+", "result": 266}
{"question": "Solve (422 * 316)", "answer": "The result of (422 * 316) is 133352\n\n####133352", "a": 422, "b": 316, "operator": "*", "result": 133352}
{"question": "Solve (16 + 241)", "answer": "The result of (16 + 241) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 16, "b": 241, "operator": "+", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 144) is 4.8958\n\n####4.8958", "a": 705, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 4.8958}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 39)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 39) is 1\n\n####1", "a": 40, "b": 39, "operator": "-", "result": 1}
{"question": "Solve (299 + 374)", "answer": "The result of (299 + 374) is 673\n\n####673", "a": 299, "b": 374, "operator": "+", "result": 673}
{"question": "Solve (845 * 37)", "answer": "The result of (845 * 37) is 31265\n\n####31265", "a": 845, "b": 37, "operator": "*", "result": 31265}
{"question": "Solve (968 - 107)", "answer": "The result of (968 - 107) is 861\n\n####861", "a": 968, "b": 107, "operator": "-", "result": 861}
{"question": "Solve (168 + 720)", "answer": "The result of (168 + 720) is 888\n\n####888", "a": 168, "b": 720, "operator": "+", "result": 888}
{"question": "Solve (791 - 237)", "answer": "The result of (791 - 237) is 554\n\n####554", "a": 791, "b": 237, "operator": "-", "result": 554}
{"question": "Solve (410 * 30)", "answer": "The result of (410 * 30) is 12300\n\n####12300", "a": 410, "b": 30, "operator": "*", "result": 12300}
{"question": "Solve (461 - 335)", "answer": "The result of (461 - 335) is 126\n\n####126", "a": 461, "b": 335, "operator": "-", "result": 126}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 671)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 671) is 1117\n\n####1117", "a": 446, "b": 671, "operator": "+", "result": 1117}
{"question": "Solve (143 + 217)", "answer": "The result of (143 + 217) is 360\n\n####360", "a": 143, "b": 217, "operator": "+", "result": 360}
{"question": "Solve (596 + 798)", "answer": "The result of (596 + 798) is 1394\n\n####1394", "a": 596, "b": 798, "operator": "+", "result": 1394}
{"question": "Solve (78 * 83)", "answer": "The result of (78 * 83) is 6474\n\n####6474", "a": 78, "b": 83, "operator": "*", "result": 6474}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 107)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 107) is 74044\n\n####74044", "a": 692, "b": 107, "operator": "*", "result": 74044}
{"question": "Solve (638 * 47)", "answer": "The result of (638 * 47) is 29986\n\n####29986", "a": 638, "b": 47, "operator": "*", "result": 29986}
{"question": "Solve (195 / 869)", "answer": "The result of (195 / 869) is 0.2244\n\n####0.2244", "a": 195, "b": 869, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2244}
{"question": "Solve (486 / 212)", "answer": "The result of (486 / 212) is 2.2925\n\n####2.2925", "a": 486, "b": 212, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2925}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 767)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 767) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 423, "b": 767, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (898 + 938)", "answer": "The result of (898 + 938) is 1836\n\n####1836", "a": 898, "b": 938, "operator": "+", "result": 1836}
{"question": "Solve (757 + 718)", "answer": "The result of (757 + 718) is 1475\n\n####1475", "a": 757, "b": 718, "operator": "+", "result": 1475}
{"question": "Solve (519 * 353)", "answer": "The result of (519 * 353) is 183207\n\n####183207", "a": 519, "b": 353, "operator": "*", "result": 183207}
{"question": "Solve (91 * 148)", "answer": "The result of (91 * 148) is 13468\n\n####13468", "a": 91, "b": 148, "operator": "*", "result": 13468}
{"question": "Solve (145 * 759)", "answer": "The result of (145 * 759) is 110055\n\n####110055", "a": 145, "b": 759, "operator": "*", "result": 110055}
{"question": "Solve (643 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (643 / 701) is 0.9173\n\n####0.9173", "a": 643, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9173}
{"question": "Solve (914 + 632)", "answer": "The result of (914 + 632) is 1546\n\n####1546", "a": 914, "b": 632, "operator": "+", "result": 1546}
{"question": "Solve (915 / 413)", "answer": "The result of (915 / 413) is 2.2155\n\n####2.2155", "a": 915, "b": 413, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2155}
{"question": "Solve (163 + 769)", "answer": "The result of (163 + 769) is 932\n\n####932", "a": 163, "b": 769, "operator": "+", "result": 932}
{"question": "Solve (125 - 271)", "answer": "The result of (125 - 271) is -146\n\n####-146", "a": 125, "b": 271, "operator": "-", "result": -146}
{"question": "Solve (336 / 733)", "answer": "The result of (336 / 733) is 0.4584\n\n####0.4584", "a": 336, "b": 733, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4584}
{"question": "Solve (453 * 737)", "answer": "The result of (453 * 737) is 333861\n\n####333861", "a": 453, "b": 737, "operator": "*", "result": 333861}
{"question": "Solve (556 / 634)", "answer": "The result of (556 / 634) is 0.877\n\n####0.877", "a": 556, "b": 634, "operator": "/", "result": 0.877}
{"question": "Solve (965 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (965 - 810) is 155\n\n####155", "a": 965, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": 155}
{"question": "Solve (485 / 529)", "answer": "The result of (485 / 529) is 0.9168\n\n####0.9168", "a": 485, "b": 529, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9168}
{"question": "Solve (92 + 439)", "answer": "The result of (92 + 439) is 531\n\n####531", "a": 92, "b": 439, "operator": "+", "result": 531}
{"question": "Solve (771 / 2)", "answer": "The result of (771 / 2) is 385.5\n\n####385.5", "a": 771, "b": 2, "operator": "/", "result": 385.5}
{"question": "Solve (612 / 866)", "answer": "The result of (612 / 866) is 0.7067\n\n####0.7067", "a": 612, "b": 866, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7067}
{"question": "Solve (699 / 222)", "answer": "The result of (699 / 222) is 3.1486\n\n####3.1486", "a": 699, "b": 222, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1486}
{"question": "Solve (656 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (656 - 661) is -5\n\n####-5", "a": 656, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -5}
{"question": "Solve (218 + 577)", "answer": "The result of (218 + 577) is 795\n\n####795", "a": 218, "b": 577, "operator": "+", "result": 795}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 869)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 869) is 232892\n\n####232892", "a": 268, "b": 869, "operator": "*", "result": 232892}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 481)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 481) is 169\n\n####169", "a": 650, "b": 481, "operator": "-", "result": 169}
{"question": "Solve (681 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (681 / 914) is 0.7451\n\n####0.7451", "a": 681, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7451}
{"question": "Solve (540 * 63)", "answer": "The result of (540 * 63) is 34020\n\n####34020", "a": 540, "b": 63, "operator": "*", "result": 34020}
{"question": "Solve (74 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (74 / 885) is 0.0836\n\n####0.0836", "a": 74, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0836}
{"question": "Solve (584 / 937)", "answer": "The result of (584 / 937) is 0.6233\n\n####0.6233", "a": 584, "b": 937, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6233}
{"question": "Solve (76 - 113)", "answer": "The result of (76 - 113) is -37\n\n####-37", "a": 76, "b": 113, "operator": "-", "result": -37}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 148)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 148) is 187\n\n####187", "a": 335, "b": 148, "operator": "-", "result": 187}
{"question": "Solve (538 + 221)", "answer": "The result of (538 + 221) is 759\n\n####759", "a": 538, "b": 221, "operator": "+", "result": 759}
{"question": "Solve (238 * 887)", "answer": "The result of (238 * 887) is 211106\n\n####211106", "a": 238, "b": 887, "operator": "*", "result": 211106}
{"question": "Solve (218 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (218 * 61) is 13298\n\n####13298", "a": 218, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 13298}
{"question": "Solve (882 - 131)", "answer": "The result of (882 - 131) is 751\n\n####751", "a": 882, "b": 131, "operator": "-", "result": 751}
{"question": "Solve (25 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (25 - 730) is -705\n\n####-705", "a": 25, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -705}
{"question": "Solve (54 - 464)", "answer": "The result of (54 - 464) is -410\n\n####-410", "a": 54, "b": 464, "operator": "-", "result": -410}
{"question": "Solve (709 - 454)", "answer": "The result of (709 - 454) is 255\n\n####255", "a": 709, "b": 454, "operator": "-", "result": 255}
{"question": "Solve (209 * 398)", "answer": "The result of (209 * 398) is 83182\n\n####83182", "a": 209, "b": 398, "operator": "*", "result": 83182}
{"question": "Solve (580 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (580 - 849) is -269\n\n####-269", "a": 580, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -269}
{"question": "Solve (413 / 944)", "answer": "The result of (413 / 944) is 0.4375\n\n####0.4375", "a": 413, "b": 944, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4375}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 276)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 276) is 1162\n\n####1162", "a": 886, "b": 276, "operator": "+", "result": 1162}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 796)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 796) is 732320\n\n####732320", "a": 920, "b": 796, "operator": "*", "result": 732320}
{"question": "Solve (596 - 432)", "answer": "The result of (596 - 432) is 164\n\n####164", "a": 596, "b": 432, "operator": "-", "result": 164}
{"question": "Solve (435 - 67)", "answer": "The result of (435 - 67) is 368\n\n####368", "a": 435, "b": 67, "operator": "-", "result": 368}
{"question": "Solve (65 * 416)", "answer": "The result of (65 * 416) is 27040\n\n####27040", "a": 65, "b": 416, "operator": "*", "result": 27040}
{"question": "Solve (552 / 711)", "answer": "The result of (552 / 711) is 0.7764\n\n####0.7764", "a": 552, "b": 711, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7764}
{"question": "Solve (449 - 581)", "answer": "The result of (449 - 581) is -132\n\n####-132", "a": 449, "b": 581, "operator": "-", "result": -132}
{"question": "Solve (423 / 899)", "answer": "The result of (423 / 899) is 0.4705\n\n####0.4705", "a": 423, "b": 899, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4705}
{"question": "Solve (816 / 226)", "answer": "The result of (816 / 226) is 3.6106\n\n####3.6106", "a": 816, "b": 226, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6106}
{"question": "Solve (567 - 895)", "answer": "The result of (567 - 895) is -328\n\n####-328", "a": 567, "b": 895, "operator": "-", "result": -328}
{"question": "Solve (176 - 585)", "answer": "The result of (176 - 585) is -409\n\n####-409", "a": 176, "b": 585, "operator": "-", "result": -409}
{"question": "Solve (312 + 584)", "answer": "The result of (312 + 584) is 896\n\n####896", "a": 312, "b": 584, "operator": "+", "result": 896}
{"question": "Solve (288 / 915)", "answer": "The result of (288 / 915) is 0.3148\n\n####0.3148", "a": 288, "b": 915, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3148}
{"question": "Solve (604 + 630)", "answer": "The result of (604 + 630) is 1234\n\n####1234", "a": 604, "b": 630, "operator": "+", "result": 1234}
{"question": "Solve (512 / 845)", "answer": "The result of (512 / 845) is 0.6059\n\n####0.6059", "a": 512, "b": 845, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6059}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 506)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 506) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 304, "b": 506, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (655 / 882)", "answer": "The result of (655 / 882) is 0.7426\n\n####0.7426", "a": 655, "b": 882, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7426}
{"question": "Solve (560 / 956)", "answer": "The result of (560 / 956) is 0.5858\n\n####0.5858", "a": 560, "b": 956, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5858}
{"question": "Solve (626 / 25)", "answer": "The result of (626 / 25) is 25.04\n\n####25.04", "a": 626, "b": 25, "operator": "/", "result": 25.04}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 677)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 677) is 0.2112\n\n####0.2112", "a": 143, "b": 677, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2112}
{"question": "Solve (517 * 827)", "answer": "The result of (517 * 827) is 427559\n\n####427559", "a": 517, "b": 827, "operator": "*", "result": 427559}
{"question": "Solve (874 / 630)", "answer": "The result of (874 / 630) is 1.3873\n\n####1.3873", "a": 874, "b": 630, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3873}
{"question": "Solve (934 * 966)", "answer": "The result of (934 * 966) is 902244\n\n####902244", "a": 934, "b": 966, "operator": "*", "result": 902244}
{"question": "Solve (836 + 913)", "answer": "The result of (836 + 913) is 1749\n\n####1749", "a": 836, "b": 913, "operator": "+", "result": 1749}
{"question": "Solve (182 + 646)", "answer": "The result of (182 + 646) is 828\n\n####828", "a": 182, "b": 646, "operator": "+", "result": 828}
{"question": "Solve (719 - 368)", "answer": "The result of (719 - 368) is 351\n\n####351", "a": 719, "b": 368, "operator": "-", "result": 351}
{"question": "Solve (900 * 347)", "answer": "The result of (900 * 347) is 312300\n\n####312300", "a": 900, "b": 347, "operator": "*", "result": 312300}
{"question": "Solve (814 / 963)", "answer": "The result of (814 / 963) is 0.8453\n\n####0.8453", "a": 814, "b": 963, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8453}
{"question": "Solve (718 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (718 * 510) is 366180\n\n####366180", "a": 718, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 366180}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 626)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 626) is 1.1134\n\n####1.1134", "a": 697, "b": 626, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1134}
{"question": "Solve (500 + 70)", "answer": "The result of (500 + 70) is 570\n\n####570", "a": 500, "b": 70, "operator": "+", "result": 570}
{"question": "Solve (211 / 149)", "answer": "The result of (211 / 149) is 1.4161\n\n####1.4161", "a": 211, "b": 149, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4161}
{"question": "Solve (229 / 921)", "answer": "The result of (229 / 921) is 0.2486\n\n####0.2486", "a": 229, "b": 921, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2486}
{"question": "Solve (258 + 623)", "answer": "The result of (258 + 623) is 881\n\n####881", "a": 258, "b": 623, "operator": "+", "result": 881}
{"question": "Solve (555 / 653)", "answer": "The result of (555 / 653) is 0.8499\n\n####0.8499", "a": 555, "b": 653, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8499}
{"question": "Solve (244 - 48)", "answer": "The result of (244 - 48) is 196\n\n####196", "a": 244, "b": 48, "operator": "-", "result": 196}
{"question": "Solve (151 + 369)", "answer": "The result of (151 + 369) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 151, "b": 369, "operator": "+", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 500)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 500) is 31500\n\n####31500", "a": 63, "b": 500, "operator": "*", "result": 31500}
{"question": "Solve (779 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (779 / 686) is 1.1356\n\n####1.1356", "a": 779, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1356}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 900)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 900) is -651\n\n####-651", "a": 249, "b": 900, "operator": "-", "result": -651}
{"question": "Solve (128 - 331)", "answer": "The result of (128 - 331) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 128, "b": 331, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (90 / 810)", "answer": "The result of (90 / 810) is 0.1111\n\n####0.1111", "a": 90, "b": 810, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1111}
{"question": "Solve (188 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (188 * 102) is 19176\n\n####19176", "a": 188, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 19176}
{"question": "Solve (724 + 347)", "answer": "The result of (724 + 347) is 1071\n\n####1071", "a": 724, "b": 347, "operator": "+", "result": 1071}
{"question": "Solve (813 * 410)", "answer": "The result of (813 * 410) is 333330\n\n####333330", "a": 813, "b": 410, "operator": "*", "result": 333330}
{"question": "Solve (623 - 915)", "answer": "The result of (623 - 915) is -292\n\n####-292", "a": 623, "b": 915, "operator": "-", "result": -292}
{"question": "Solve (793 - 304)", "answer": "The result of (793 - 304) is 489\n\n####489", "a": 793, "b": 304, "operator": "-", "result": 489}
{"question": "Solve (33 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (33 / 686) is 0.0481\n\n####0.0481", "a": 33, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0481}
{"question": "Solve (855 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (855 + 380) is 1235\n\n####1235", "a": 855, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 1235}
{"question": "Solve (155 + 23)", "answer": "The result of (155 + 23) is 178\n\n####178", "a": 155, "b": 23, "operator": "+", "result": 178}
{"question": "Solve (527 * 945)", "answer": "The result of (527 * 945) is 498015\n\n####498015", "a": 527, "b": 945, "operator": "*", "result": 498015}
{"question": "Solve (291 * 973)", "answer": "The result of (291 * 973) is 283143\n\n####283143", "a": 291, "b": 973, "operator": "*", "result": 283143}
{"question": "Solve (644 / 582)", "answer": "The result of (644 / 582) is 1.1065\n\n####1.1065", "a": 644, "b": 582, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1065}
{"question": "Solve (266 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (266 - 256) is 10\n\n####10", "a": 266, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": 10}
{"question": "Solve (789 + 273)", "answer": "The result of (789 + 273) is 1062\n\n####1062", "a": 789, "b": 273, "operator": "+", "result": 1062}
{"question": "Solve (230 / 824)", "answer": "The result of (230 / 824) is 0.2791\n\n####0.2791", "a": 230, "b": 824, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2791}
{"question": "Solve (123 + 118)", "answer": "The result of (123 + 118) is 241\n\n####241", "a": 123, "b": 118, "operator": "+", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve (433 * 607)", "answer": "The result of (433 * 607) is 262831\n\n####262831", "a": 433, "b": 607, "operator": "*", "result": 262831}
{"question": "Solve (306 + 672)", "answer": "The result of (306 + 672) is 978\n\n####978", "a": 306, "b": 672, "operator": "+", "result": 978}
{"question": "Solve (478 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (478 - 321) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 478, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (459 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (459 * 897) is 411723\n\n####411723", "a": 459, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 411723}
{"question": "Solve (850 - 655)", "answer": "The result of (850 - 655) is 195\n\n####195", "a": 850, "b": 655, "operator": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve (839 - 628)", "answer": "The result of (839 - 628) is 211\n\n####211", "a": 839, "b": 628, "operator": "-", "result": 211}
{"question": "Solve (310 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (310 - 166) is 144\n\n####144", "a": 310, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve (171 - 555)", "answer": "The result of (171 - 555) is -384\n\n####-384", "a": 171, "b": 555, "operator": "-", "result": -384}
{"question": "Solve (854 + 172)", "answer": "The result of (854 + 172) is 1026\n\n####1026", "a": 854, "b": 172, "operator": "+", "result": 1026}
{"question": "Solve (562 - 544)", "answer": "The result of (562 - 544) is 18\n\n####18", "a": 562, "b": 544, "operator": "-", "result": 18}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 205)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 205) is 545\n\n####545", "a": 750, "b": 205, "operator": "-", "result": 545}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 912)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 912) is -608\n\n####-608", "a": 304, "b": 912, "operator": "-", "result": -608}
{"question": "Solve (344 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (344 - 512) is -168\n\n####-168", "a": 344, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": -168}
{"question": "Solve (809 - 942)", "answer": "The result of (809 - 942) is -133\n\n####-133", "a": 809, "b": 942, "operator": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve (760 * 691)", "answer": "The result of (760 * 691) is 525160\n\n####525160", "a": 760, "b": 691, "operator": "*", "result": 525160}
{"question": "Solve (767 - 75)", "answer": "The result of (767 - 75) is 692\n\n####692", "a": 767, "b": 75, "operator": "-", "result": 692}
{"question": "Solve (353 * 905)", "answer": "The result of (353 * 905) is 319465\n\n####319465", "a": 353, "b": 905, "operator": "*", "result": 319465}
{"question": "Solve (594 * 710)", "answer": "The result of (594 * 710) is 421740\n\n####421740", "a": 594, "b": 710, "operator": "*", "result": 421740}
{"question": "Solve (230 / 516)", "answer": "The result of (230 / 516) is 0.4457\n\n####0.4457", "a": 230, "b": 516, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4457}
{"question": "Solve (632 / 267)", "answer": "The result of (632 / 267) is 2.367\n\n####2.367", "a": 632, "b": 267, "operator": "/", "result": 2.367}
{"question": "Solve (189 / 35)", "answer": "The result of (189 / 35) is 5.4\n\n####5.4", "a": 189, "b": 35, "operator": "/", "result": 5.4}
{"question": "Solve (123 - 978)", "answer": "The result of (123 - 978) is -855\n\n####-855", "a": 123, "b": 978, "operator": "-", "result": -855}
{"question": "Solve (772 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (772 / 390) is 1.9795\n\n####1.9795", "a": 772, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9795}
{"question": "Solve (852 + 408)", "answer": "The result of (852 + 408) is 1260\n\n####1260", "a": 852, "b": 408, "operator": "+", "result": 1260}
{"question": "Solve (187 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (187 * 910) is 170170\n\n####170170", "a": 187, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 170170}
{"question": "Solve (952 / 207)", "answer": "The result of (952 / 207) is 4.599\n\n####4.599", "a": 952, "b": 207, "operator": "/", "result": 4.599}
{"question": "Solve (518 - 305)", "answer": "The result of (518 - 305) is 213\n\n####213", "a": 518, "b": 305, "operator": "-", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve (246 * 570)", "answer": "The result of (246 * 570) is 140220\n\n####140220", "a": 246, "b": 570, "operator": "*", "result": 140220}
{"question": "Solve (367 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (367 * 142) is 52114\n\n####52114", "a": 367, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 52114}
{"question": "Solve (170 / 439)", "answer": "The result of (170 / 439) is 0.3872\n\n####0.3872", "a": 170, "b": 439, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3872}
{"question": "Solve (836 * 185)", "answer": "The result of (836 * 185) is 154660\n\n####154660", "a": 836, "b": 185, "operator": "*", "result": 154660}
{"question": "Solve (839 - 277)", "answer": "The result of (839 - 277) is 562\n\n####562", "a": 839, "b": 277, "operator": "-", "result": 562}
{"question": "Solve (898 / 283)", "answer": "The result of (898 / 283) is 3.1731\n\n####3.1731", "a": 898, "b": 283, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1731}
{"question": "Solve (702 / 894)", "answer": "The result of (702 / 894) is 0.7852\n\n####0.7852", "a": 702, "b": 894, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7852}
{"question": "Solve (154 - 393)", "answer": "The result of (154 - 393) is -239\n\n####-239", "a": 154, "b": 393, "operator": "-", "result": -239}
{"question": "Solve (139 - 91)", "answer": "The result of (139 - 91) is 48\n\n####48", "a": 139, "b": 91, "operator": "-", "result": 48}
{"question": "Solve (993 * 454)", "answer": "The result of (993 * 454) is 450822\n\n####450822", "a": 993, "b": 454, "operator": "*", "result": 450822}
{"question": "Solve (925 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (925 + 184) is 1109\n\n####1109", "a": 925, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 1109}
{"question": "Solve (847 / 316)", "answer": "The result of (847 / 316) is 2.6804\n\n####2.6804", "a": 847, "b": 316, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6804}
{"question": "Solve (353 - 516)", "answer": "The result of (353 - 516) is -163\n\n####-163", "a": 353, "b": 516, "operator": "-", "result": -163}
{"question": "Solve (93 + 100)", "answer": "The result of (93 + 100) is 193\n\n####193", "a": 93, "b": 100, "operator": "+", "result": 193}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 368)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 368) is 1.8424\n\n####1.8424", "a": 678, "b": 368, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8424}
{"question": "Solve (217 * 636)", "answer": "The result of (217 * 636) is 138012\n\n####138012", "a": 217, "b": 636, "operator": "*", "result": 138012}
{"question": "Solve (57 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (57 - 431) is -374\n\n####-374", "a": 57, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": -374}
{"question": "Solve (30 * 62)", "answer": "The result of (30 * 62) is 1860\n\n####1860", "a": 30, "b": 62, "operator": "*", "result": 1860}
{"question": "Solve (585 / 802)", "answer": "The result of (585 / 802) is 0.7294\n\n####0.7294", "a": 585, "b": 802, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7294}
{"question": "Solve (606 - 231)", "answer": "The result of (606 - 231) is 375\n\n####375", "a": 606, "b": 231, "operator": "-", "result": 375}
{"question": "Solve (770 * 337)", "answer": "The result of (770 * 337) is 259490\n\n####259490", "a": 770, "b": 337, "operator": "*", "result": 259490}
{"question": "Solve (570 * 169)", "answer": "The result of (570 * 169) is 96330\n\n####96330", "a": 570, "b": 169, "operator": "*", "result": 96330}
{"question": "Solve (696 - 424)", "answer": "The result of (696 - 424) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 696, "b": 424, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (444 / 188)", "answer": "The result of (444 / 188) is 2.3617\n\n####2.3617", "a": 444, "b": 188, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3617}
{"question": "Solve (926 * 528)", "answer": "The result of (926 * 528) is 488928\n\n####488928", "a": 926, "b": 528, "operator": "*", "result": 488928}
{"question": "Solve (294 - 600)", "answer": "The result of (294 - 600) is -306\n\n####-306", "a": 294, "b": 600, "operator": "-", "result": -306}
{"question": "Solve (457 / 565)", "answer": "The result of (457 / 565) is 0.8088\n\n####0.8088", "a": 457, "b": 565, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8088}
{"question": "Solve (847 + 847)", "answer": "The result of (847 + 847) is 1694\n\n####1694", "a": 847, "b": 847, "operator": "+", "result": 1694}
{"question": "Solve (978 + 275)", "answer": "The result of (978 + 275) is 1253\n\n####1253", "a": 978, "b": 275, "operator": "+", "result": 1253}
{"question": "Solve (386 * 166)", "answer": "The result of (386 * 166) is 64076\n\n####64076", "a": 386, "b": 166, "operator": "*", "result": 64076}
{"question": "Solve (651 + 860)", "answer": "The result of (651 + 860) is 1511\n\n####1511", "a": 651, "b": 860, "operator": "+", "result": 1511}
{"question": "Solve (104 / 99)", "answer": "The result of (104 / 99) is 1.0505\n\n####1.0505", "a": 104, "b": 99, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0505}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 882)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 882) is 1543\n\n####1543", "a": 661, "b": 882, "operator": "+", "result": 1543}
{"question": "Solve (362 / 7)", "answer": "The result of (362 / 7) is 51.7143\n\n####51.7143", "a": 362, "b": 7, "operator": "/", "result": 51.7143}
{"question": "Solve (341 + 733)", "answer": "The result of (341 + 733) is 1074\n\n####1074", "a": 341, "b": 733, "operator": "+", "result": 1074}
{"question": "Solve (419 + 622)", "answer": "The result of (419 + 622) is 1041\n\n####1041", "a": 419, "b": 622, "operator": "+", "result": 1041}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 344) is 86\n\n####86", "a": 430, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": 86}
{"question": "Solve (495 - 461)", "answer": "The result of (495 - 461) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 495, "b": 461, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 530)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 530) is 1.434\n\n####1.434", "a": 760, "b": 530, "operator": "/", "result": 1.434}
{"question": "Solve (45 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (45 + 19) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 45, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (233 - 38)", "answer": "The result of (233 - 38) is 195\n\n####195", "a": 233, "b": 38, "operator": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 800)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 800) is 0.0125\n\n####0.0125", "a": 10, "b": 800, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0125}
{"question": "Solve (873 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (873 - 358) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 873, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (286 / 324)", "answer": "The result of (286 / 324) is 0.8827\n\n####0.8827", "a": 286, "b": 324, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8827}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 558)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 558) is 0.362\n\n####0.362", "a": 202, "b": 558, "operator": "/", "result": 0.362}
{"question": "Solve (524 / 525)", "answer": "The result of (524 / 525) is 0.9981\n\n####0.9981", "a": 524, "b": 525, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9981}
{"question": "Solve (562 / 576)", "answer": "The result of (562 / 576) is 0.9757\n\n####0.9757", "a": 562, "b": 576, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9757}
{"question": "Solve (906 / 921)", "answer": "The result of (906 / 921) is 0.9837\n\n####0.9837", "a": 906, "b": 921, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9837}
{"question": "Solve (266 * 63)", "answer": "The result of (266 * 63) is 16758\n\n####16758", "a": 266, "b": 63, "operator": "*", "result": 16758}
{"question": "Solve (337 + 450)", "answer": "The result of (337 + 450) is 787\n\n####787", "a": 337, "b": 450, "operator": "+", "result": 787}
{"question": "Solve (92 - 260)", "answer": "The result of (92 - 260) is -168\n\n####-168", "a": 92, "b": 260, "operator": "-", "result": -168}
{"question": "Solve (100 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (100 / 545) is 0.1835\n\n####0.1835", "a": 100, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1835}
{"question": "Solve (684 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (684 - 724) is -40\n\n####-40", "a": 684, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -40}
{"question": "Solve (392 / 285)", "answer": "The result of (392 / 285) is 1.3754\n\n####1.3754", "a": 392, "b": 285, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3754}
{"question": "Solve (442 / 183)", "answer": "The result of (442 / 183) is 2.4153\n\n####2.4153", "a": 442, "b": 183, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4153}
{"question": "Solve (954 - 448)", "answer": "The result of (954 - 448) is 506\n\n####506", "a": 954, "b": 448, "operator": "-", "result": 506}
{"question": "Solve (658 / 455)", "answer": "The result of (658 / 455) is 1.4462\n\n####1.4462", "a": 658, "b": 455, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4462}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 755)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 755) is 1.0477\n\n####1.0477", "a": 791, "b": 755, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0477}
{"question": "Solve (960 / 233)", "answer": "The result of (960 / 233) is 4.1202\n\n####4.1202", "a": 960, "b": 233, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1202}
{"question": "Solve (483 + 881)", "answer": "The result of (483 + 881) is 1364\n\n####1364", "a": 483, "b": 881, "operator": "+", "result": 1364}
{"question": "Solve (673 / 685)", "answer": "The result of (673 / 685) is 0.9825\n\n####0.9825", "a": 673, "b": 685, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9825}
{"question": "Solve (378 * 919)", "answer": "The result of (378 * 919) is 347382\n\n####347382", "a": 378, "b": 919, "operator": "*", "result": 347382}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 317) is 624\n\n####624", "a": 941, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 624}
{"question": "Solve (54 / 850)", "answer": "The result of (54 / 850) is 0.0635\n\n####0.0635", "a": 54, "b": 850, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0635}
{"question": "Solve (636 / 540)", "answer": "The result of (636 / 540) is 1.1778\n\n####1.1778", "a": 636, "b": 540, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1778}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 809)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 809) is 1015\n\n####1015", "a": 206, "b": 809, "operator": "+", "result": 1015}
{"question": "Solve (147 - 394)", "answer": "The result of (147 - 394) is -247\n\n####-247", "a": 147, "b": 394, "operator": "-", "result": -247}
{"question": "Solve (901 * 920)", "answer": "The result of (901 * 920) is 828920\n\n####828920", "a": 901, "b": 920, "operator": "*", "result": 828920}
{"question": "Solve (74 / 876)", "answer": "The result of (74 / 876) is 0.0845\n\n####0.0845", "a": 74, "b": 876, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0845}
{"question": "Solve (780 / 184)", "answer": "The result of (780 / 184) is 4.2391\n\n####4.2391", "a": 780, "b": 184, "operator": "/", "result": 4.2391}
{"question": "Solve (971 + 619)", "answer": "The result of (971 + 619) is 1590\n\n####1590", "a": 971, "b": 619, "operator": "+", "result": 1590}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 16)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 16) is 950\n\n####950", "a": 966, "b": 16, "operator": "-", "result": 950}
{"question": "Solve (776 + 399)", "answer": "The result of (776 + 399) is 1175\n\n####1175", "a": 776, "b": 399, "operator": "+", "result": 1175}
{"question": "Solve (706 + 918)", "answer": "The result of (706 + 918) is 1624\n\n####1624", "a": 706, "b": 918, "operator": "+", "result": 1624}
{"question": "Solve (191 * 640)", "answer": "The result of (191 * 640) is 122240\n\n####122240", "a": 191, "b": 640, "operator": "*", "result": 122240}
{"question": "Solve (266 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (266 - 547) is -281\n\n####-281", "a": 266, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": -281}
{"question": "Solve (317 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (317 + 868) is 1185\n\n####1185", "a": 317, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 1185}
{"question": "Solve (185 - 652)", "answer": "The result of (185 - 652) is -467\n\n####-467", "a": 185, "b": 652, "operator": "-", "result": -467}
{"question": "Solve (682 + 514)", "answer": "The result of (682 + 514) is 1196\n\n####1196", "a": 682, "b": 514, "operator": "+", "result": 1196}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 475) is 0.3389\n\n####0.3389", "a": 161, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3389}
{"question": "Solve (943 / 636)", "answer": "The result of (943 / 636) is 1.4827\n\n####1.4827", "a": 943, "b": 636, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4827}
{"question": "Solve (506 / 196)", "answer": "The result of (506 / 196) is 2.5816\n\n####2.5816", "a": 506, "b": 196, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5816}
{"question": "Solve (916 + 501)", "answer": "The result of (916 + 501) is 1417\n\n####1417", "a": 916, "b": 501, "operator": "+", "result": 1417}
{"question": "Solve (606 - 293)", "answer": "The result of (606 - 293) is 313\n\n####313", "a": 606, "b": 293, "operator": "-", "result": 313}
{"question": "Solve (778 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (778 / 984) is 0.7907\n\n####0.7907", "a": 778, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7907}
{"question": "Solve (10 - 111)", "answer": "The result of (10 - 111) is -101\n\n####-101", "a": 10, "b": 111, "operator": "-", "result": -101}
{"question": "Solve (182 - 934)", "answer": "The result of (182 - 934) is -752\n\n####-752", "a": 182, "b": 934, "operator": "-", "result": -752}
{"question": "Solve (306 - 573)", "answer": "The result of (306 - 573) is -267\n\n####-267", "a": 306, "b": 573, "operator": "-", "result": -267}
{"question": "Solve (954 * 427)", "answer": "The result of (954 * 427) is 407358\n\n####407358", "a": 954, "b": 427, "operator": "*", "result": 407358}
{"question": "Solve (378 - 213)", "answer": "The result of (378 - 213) is 165\n\n####165", "a": 378, "b": 213, "operator": "-", "result": 165}
{"question": "Solve (821 - 786)", "answer": "The result of (821 - 786) is 35\n\n####35", "a": 821, "b": 786, "operator": "-", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve (374 - 692)", "answer": "The result of (374 - 692) is -318\n\n####-318", "a": 374, "b": 692, "operator": "-", "result": -318}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 510)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 510) is -281\n\n####-281", "a": 229, "b": 510, "operator": "-", "result": -281}
{"question": "Solve (370 - 840)", "answer": "The result of (370 - 840) is -470\n\n####-470", "a": 370, "b": 840, "operator": "-", "result": -470}
{"question": "Solve (390 + 208)", "answer": "The result of (390 + 208) is 598\n\n####598", "a": 390, "b": 208, "operator": "+", "result": 598}
{"question": "Solve (376 * 812)", "answer": "The result of (376 * 812) is 305312\n\n####305312", "a": 376, "b": 812, "operator": "*", "result": 305312}
{"question": "Solve (722 - 5)", "answer": "The result of (722 - 5) is 717\n\n####717", "a": 722, "b": 5, "operator": "-", "result": 717}
{"question": "Solve (131 - 681)", "answer": "The result of (131 - 681) is -550\n\n####-550", "a": 131, "b": 681, "operator": "-", "result": -550}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 94)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 94) is 8.0851\n\n####8.0851", "a": 760, "b": 94, "operator": "/", "result": 8.0851}
{"question": "Solve (816 - 607)", "answer": "The result of (816 - 607) is 209\n\n####209", "a": 816, "b": 607, "operator": "-", "result": 209}
{"question": "Solve (559 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (559 / 885) is 0.6316\n\n####0.6316", "a": 559, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6316}
{"question": "Solve (136 + 882)", "answer": "The result of (136 + 882) is 1018\n\n####1018", "a": 136, "b": 882, "operator": "+", "result": 1018}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 599)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 599) is 0.1686\n\n####0.1686", "a": 101, "b": 599, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1686}
{"question": "Solve (772 + 801)", "answer": "The result of (772 + 801) is 1573\n\n####1573", "a": 772, "b": 801, "operator": "+", "result": 1573}
{"question": "Solve (598 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (598 / 701) is 0.8531\n\n####0.8531", "a": 598, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8531}
{"question": "Solve (743 - 650)", "answer": "The result of (743 - 650) is 93\n\n####93", "a": 743, "b": 650, "operator": "-", "result": 93}
{"question": "Solve (998 * 695)", "answer": "The result of (998 * 695) is 693610\n\n####693610", "a": 998, "b": 695, "operator": "*", "result": 693610}
{"question": "Solve (617 + 549)", "answer": "The result of (617 + 549) is 1166\n\n####1166", "a": 617, "b": 549, "operator": "+", "result": 1166}
{"question": "Solve (949 / 375)", "answer": "The result of (949 / 375) is 2.5307\n\n####2.5307", "a": 949, "b": 375, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5307}
{"question": "Solve (374 / 170)", "answer": "The result of (374 / 170) is 2.2\n\n####2.2", "a": 374, "b": 170, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2}
{"question": "Solve (605 + 180)", "answer": "The result of (605 + 180) is 785\n\n####785", "a": 605, "b": 180, "operator": "+", "result": 785}
{"question": "Solve (690 - 10)", "answer": "The result of (690 - 10) is 680\n\n####680", "a": 690, "b": 10, "operator": "-", "result": 680}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 139)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 139) is 302\n\n####302", "a": 441, "b": 139, "operator": "-", "result": 302}
{"question": "Solve (885 - 570)", "answer": "The result of (885 - 570) is 315\n\n####315", "a": 885, "b": 570, "operator": "-", "result": 315}
{"question": "Solve (348 / 578)", "answer": "The result of (348 / 578) is 0.6021\n\n####0.6021", "a": 348, "b": 578, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6021}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 9)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 9) is 85\n\n####85", "a": 94, "b": 9, "operator": "-", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve (445 - 800)", "answer": "The result of (445 - 800) is -355\n\n####-355", "a": 445, "b": 800, "operator": "-", "result": -355}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 117) is 187\n\n####187", "a": 304, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": 187}
{"question": "Solve (546 * 254)", "answer": "The result of (546 * 254) is 138684\n\n####138684", "a": 546, "b": 254, "operator": "*", "result": 138684}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 379)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 379) is -302\n\n####-302", "a": 77, "b": 379, "operator": "-", "result": -302}
{"question": "Solve (947 - 938)", "answer": "The result of (947 - 938) is 9\n\n####9", "a": 947, "b": 938, "operator": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve (31 / 784)", "answer": "The result of (31 / 784) is 0.0395\n\n####0.0395", "a": 31, "b": 784, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0395}
{"question": "Solve (78 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (78 + 487) is 565\n\n####565", "a": 78, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 565}
{"question": "Solve (293 / 442)", "answer": "The result of (293 / 442) is 0.6629\n\n####0.6629", "a": 293, "b": 442, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6629}
{"question": "Solve (442 - 560)", "answer": "The result of (442 - 560) is -118\n\n####-118", "a": 442, "b": 560, "operator": "-", "result": -118}
{"question": "Solve (648 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (648 - 276) is 372\n\n####372", "a": 648, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": 372}
{"question": "Solve (837 - 448)", "answer": "The result of (837 - 448) is 389\n\n####389", "a": 837, "b": 448, "operator": "-", "result": 389}
{"question": "Solve (768 / 108)", "answer": "The result of (768 / 108) is 7.1111\n\n####7.1111", "a": 768, "b": 108, "operator": "/", "result": 7.1111}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 374)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 374) is -330\n\n####-330", "a": 44, "b": 374, "operator": "-", "result": -330}
{"question": "Solve (880 / 367)", "answer": "The result of (880 / 367) is 2.3978\n\n####2.3978", "a": 880, "b": 367, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3978}
{"question": "Solve (622 - 246)", "answer": "The result of (622 - 246) is 376\n\n####376", "a": 622, "b": 246, "operator": "-", "result": 376}
{"question": "Solve (401 - 569)", "answer": "The result of (401 - 569) is -168\n\n####-168", "a": 401, "b": 569, "operator": "-", "result": -168}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 484)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 484) is 0.6136\n\n####0.6136", "a": 297, "b": 484, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6136}
{"question": "Solve (108 + 987)", "answer": "The result of (108 + 987) is 1095\n\n####1095", "a": 108, "b": 987, "operator": "+", "result": 1095}
{"question": "Solve (447 - 866)", "answer": "The result of (447 - 866) is -419\n\n####-419", "a": 447, "b": 866, "operator": "-", "result": -419}
{"question": "Solve (646 + 200)", "answer": "The result of (646 + 200) is 846\n\n####846", "a": 646, "b": 200, "operator": "+", "result": 846}
{"question": "Solve (168 + 739)", "answer": "The result of (168 + 739) is 907\n\n####907", "a": 168, "b": 739, "operator": "+", "result": 907}
{"question": "Solve (644 + 185)", "answer": "The result of (644 + 185) is 829\n\n####829", "a": 644, "b": 185, "operator": "+", "result": 829}
{"question": "Solve (635 / 837)", "answer": "The result of (635 / 837) is 0.7587\n\n####0.7587", "a": 635, "b": 837, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7587}
{"question": "Solve (163 * 949)", "answer": "The result of (163 * 949) is 154687\n\n####154687", "a": 163, "b": 949, "operator": "*", "result": 154687}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 968)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 968) is 0.2779\n\n####0.2779", "a": 269, "b": 968, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2779}
{"question": "Solve (591 * 821)", "answer": "The result of (591 * 821) is 485211\n\n####485211", "a": 591, "b": 821, "operator": "*", "result": 485211}
{"question": "Solve (233 / 898)", "answer": "The result of (233 / 898) is 0.2595\n\n####0.2595", "a": 233, "b": 898, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2595}
{"question": "Solve (520 / 696)", "answer": "The result of (520 / 696) is 0.7471\n\n####0.7471", "a": 520, "b": 696, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7471}
{"question": "Solve (855 - 270)", "answer": "The result of (855 - 270) is 585\n\n####585", "a": 855, "b": 270, "operator": "-", "result": 585}
{"question": "Solve (895 - 214)", "answer": "The result of (895 - 214) is 681\n\n####681", "a": 895, "b": 214, "operator": "-", "result": 681}
{"question": "Solve (922 * 382)", "answer": "The result of (922 * 382) is 352204\n\n####352204", "a": 922, "b": 382, "operator": "*", "result": 352204}
{"question": "Solve (118 * 365)", "answer": "The result of (118 * 365) is 43070\n\n####43070", "a": 118, "b": 365, "operator": "*", "result": 43070}
{"question": "Solve (944 * 393)", "answer": "The result of (944 * 393) is 370992\n\n####370992", "a": 944, "b": 393, "operator": "*", "result": 370992}
{"question": "Solve (22 + 629)", "answer": "The result of (22 + 629) is 651\n\n####651", "a": 22, "b": 629, "operator": "+", "result": 651}
{"question": "Solve (153 + 90)", "answer": "The result of (153 + 90) is 243\n\n####243", "a": 153, "b": 90, "operator": "+", "result": 243}
{"question": "Solve (532 + 527)", "answer": "The result of (532 + 527) is 1059\n\n####1059", "a": 532, "b": 527, "operator": "+", "result": 1059}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 185)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 185) is 1.7568\n\n####1.7568", "a": 325, "b": 185, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7568}
{"question": "Solve (386 + 732)", "answer": "The result of (386 + 732) is 1118\n\n####1118", "a": 386, "b": 732, "operator": "+", "result": 1118}
{"question": "Solve (255 / 380)", "answer": "The result of (255 / 380) is 0.6711\n\n####0.6711", "a": 255, "b": 380, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6711}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 252)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 252) is 143892\n\n####143892", "a": 571, "b": 252, "operator": "*", "result": 143892}
{"question": "Solve (173 + 254)", "answer": "The result of (173 + 254) is 427\n\n####427", "a": 173, "b": 254, "operator": "+", "result": 427}
{"question": "Solve (951 + 636)", "answer": "The result of (951 + 636) is 1587\n\n####1587", "a": 951, "b": 636, "operator": "+", "result": 1587}
{"question": "Solve (753 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (753 / 144) is 5.2292\n\n####5.2292", "a": 753, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2292}
{"question": "Solve (570 - 191)", "answer": "The result of (570 - 191) is 379\n\n####379", "a": 570, "b": 191, "operator": "-", "result": 379}
{"question": "Solve (605 + 194)", "answer": "The result of (605 + 194) is 799\n\n####799", "a": 605, "b": 194, "operator": "+", "result": 799}
{"question": "Solve (651 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (651 - 998) is -347\n\n####-347", "a": 651, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -347}
{"question": "Solve (194 + 996)", "answer": "The result of (194 + 996) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 194, "b": 996, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (627 + 143)", "answer": "The result of (627 + 143) is 770\n\n####770", "a": 627, "b": 143, "operator": "+", "result": 770}
{"question": "Solve (422 / 937)", "answer": "The result of (422 / 937) is 0.4504\n\n####0.4504", "a": 422, "b": 937, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4504}
{"question": "Solve (350 - 681)", "answer": "The result of (350 - 681) is -331\n\n####-331", "a": 350, "b": 681, "operator": "-", "result": -331}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 798)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 798) is 485184\n\n####485184", "a": 608, "b": 798, "operator": "*", "result": 485184}
{"question": "Solve (30 / 690)", "answer": "The result of (30 / 690) is 0.0435\n\n####0.0435", "a": 30, "b": 690, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0435}
{"question": "Solve (239 * 592)", "answer": "The result of (239 * 592) is 141488\n\n####141488", "a": 239, "b": 592, "operator": "*", "result": 141488}
{"question": "Solve (527 * 275)", "answer": "The result of (527 * 275) is 144925\n\n####144925", "a": 527, "b": 275, "operator": "*", "result": 144925}
{"question": "Solve (382 - 585)", "answer": "The result of (382 - 585) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 382, "b": 585, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 701) is -656\n\n####-656", "a": 45, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": -656}
{"question": "Solve (402 * 587)", "answer": "The result of (402 * 587) is 235974\n\n####235974", "a": 402, "b": 587, "operator": "*", "result": 235974}
{"question": "Solve (658 - 323)", "answer": "The result of (658 - 323) is 335\n\n####335", "a": 658, "b": 323, "operator": "-", "result": 335}
{"question": "Solve (428 * 277)", "answer": "The result of (428 * 277) is 118556\n\n####118556", "a": 428, "b": 277, "operator": "*", "result": 118556}
{"question": "Solve (802 * 842)", "answer": "The result of (802 * 842) is 675284\n\n####675284", "a": 802, "b": 842, "operator": "*", "result": 675284}
{"question": "Solve (547 / 287)", "answer": "The result of (547 / 287) is 1.9059\n\n####1.9059", "a": 547, "b": 287, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9059}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 919)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 919) is 836290\n\n####836290", "a": 910, "b": 919, "operator": "*", "result": 836290}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 694)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 694) is 697\n\n####697", "a": 3, "b": 694, "operator": "+", "result": 697}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 307)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 307) is -262\n\n####-262", "a": 45, "b": 307, "operator": "-", "result": -262}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 763)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 763) is -287\n\n####-287", "a": 476, "b": 763, "operator": "-", "result": -287}
{"question": "Solve (554 / 907)", "answer": "The result of (554 / 907) is 0.6108\n\n####0.6108", "a": 554, "b": 907, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6108}
{"question": "Solve (704 * 370)", "answer": "The result of (704 * 370) is 260480\n\n####260480", "a": 704, "b": 370, "operator": "*", "result": 260480}
{"question": "Solve (386 / 736)", "answer": "The result of (386 / 736) is 0.5245\n\n####0.5245", "a": 386, "b": 736, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5245}
{"question": "Solve (739 + 431)", "answer": "The result of (739 + 431) is 1170\n\n####1170", "a": 739, "b": 431, "operator": "+", "result": 1170}
{"question": "Solve (500 / 696)", "answer": "The result of (500 / 696) is 0.7184\n\n####0.7184", "a": 500, "b": 696, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7184}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 543)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 543) is 93\n\n####93", "a": 636, "b": 543, "operator": "-", "result": 93}
{"question": "Solve (10 + 34)", "answer": "The result of (10 + 34) is 44\n\n####44", "a": 10, "b": 34, "operator": "+", "result": 44}
{"question": "Solve (711 - 841)", "answer": "The result of (711 - 841) is -130\n\n####-130", "a": 711, "b": 841, "operator": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve (727 / 691)", "answer": "The result of (727 / 691) is 1.0521\n\n####1.0521", "a": 727, "b": 691, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0521}
{"question": "Solve (295 / 958)", "answer": "The result of (295 / 958) is 0.3079\n\n####0.3079", "a": 295, "b": 958, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3079}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 83)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 83) is -31\n\n####-31", "a": 52, "b": 83, "operator": "-", "result": -31}
{"question": "Solve (630 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (630 / 560) is 1.125\n\n####1.125", "a": 630, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 1.125}
{"question": "Solve (201 + 422)", "answer": "The result of (201 + 422) is 623\n\n####623", "a": 201, "b": 422, "operator": "+", "result": 623}
{"question": "Solve (218 - 244)", "answer": "The result of (218 - 244) is -26\n\n####-26", "a": 218, "b": 244, "operator": "-", "result": -26}
{"question": "Solve (769 * 144)", "answer": "The result of (769 * 144) is 110736\n\n####110736", "a": 769, "b": 144, "operator": "*", "result": 110736}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 305)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 305) is 0.4459\n\n####0.4459", "a": 136, "b": 305, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4459}
{"question": "Solve (141 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (141 - 822) is -681\n\n####-681", "a": 141, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": -681}
{"question": "Solve (527 - 236)", "answer": "The result of (527 - 236) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 527, "b": 236, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (680 - 360)", "answer": "The result of (680 - 360) is 320\n\n####320", "a": 680, "b": 360, "operator": "-", "result": 320}
{"question": "Solve (8 - 565)", "answer": "The result of (8 - 565) is -557\n\n####-557", "a": 8, "b": 565, "operator": "-", "result": -557}
{"question": "Solve (25 * 887)", "answer": "The result of (25 * 887) is 22175\n\n####22175", "a": 25, "b": 887, "operator": "*", "result": 22175}
{"question": "Solve (931 - 74)", "answer": "The result of (931 - 74) is 857\n\n####857", "a": 931, "b": 74, "operator": "-", "result": 857}
{"question": "Solve (871 * 708)", "answer": "The result of (871 * 708) is 616668\n\n####616668", "a": 871, "b": 708, "operator": "*", "result": 616668}
{"question": "Solve (401 / 36)", "answer": "The result of (401 / 36) is 11.1389\n\n####11.1389", "a": 401, "b": 36, "operator": "/", "result": 11.1389}
{"question": "Solve (496 - 980)", "answer": "The result of (496 - 980) is -484\n\n####-484", "a": 496, "b": 980, "operator": "-", "result": -484}
{"question": "Solve (649 * 55)", "answer": "The result of (649 * 55) is 35695\n\n####35695", "a": 649, "b": 55, "operator": "*", "result": 35695}
{"question": "Solve (525 / 320)", "answer": "The result of (525 / 320) is 1.6406\n\n####1.6406", "a": 525, "b": 320, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6406}
{"question": "Solve (833 + 707)", "answer": "The result of (833 + 707) is 1540\n\n####1540", "a": 833, "b": 707, "operator": "+", "result": 1540}
{"question": "Solve (475 * 539)", "answer": "The result of (475 * 539) is 256025\n\n####256025", "a": 475, "b": 539, "operator": "*", "result": 256025}
{"question": "Solve (683 * 32)", "answer": "The result of (683 * 32) is 21856\n\n####21856", "a": 683, "b": 32, "operator": "*", "result": 21856}
{"question": "Solve (76 + 448)", "answer": "The result of (76 + 448) is 524\n\n####524", "a": 76, "b": 448, "operator": "+", "result": 524}
{"question": "Solve (477 + 372)", "answer": "The result of (477 + 372) is 849\n\n####849", "a": 477, "b": 372, "operator": "+", "result": 849}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 657)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 657) is -624\n\n####-624", "a": 33, "b": 657, "operator": "-", "result": -624}
{"question": "Solve (603 - 591)", "answer": "The result of (603 - 591) is 12\n\n####12", "a": 603, "b": 591, "operator": "-", "result": 12}
{"question": "Solve (836 - 885)", "answer": "The result of (836 - 885) is -49\n\n####-49", "a": 836, "b": 885, "operator": "-", "result": -49}
{"question": "Solve (772 / 808)", "answer": "The result of (772 / 808) is 0.9554\n\n####0.9554", "a": 772, "b": 808, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9554}
{"question": "Solve (771 + 984)", "answer": "The result of (771 + 984) is 1755\n\n####1755", "a": 771, "b": 984, "operator": "+", "result": 1755}
{"question": "Solve (728 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (728 * 86) is 62608\n\n####62608", "a": 728, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 62608}
{"question": "Solve (759 + 600)", "answer": "The result of (759 + 600) is 1359\n\n####1359", "a": 759, "b": 600, "operator": "+", "result": 1359}
{"question": "Solve (262 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (262 - 647) is -385\n\n####-385", "a": 262, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": -385}
{"question": "Solve (485 * 298)", "answer": "The result of (485 * 298) is 144530\n\n####144530", "a": 485, "b": 298, "operator": "*", "result": 144530}
{"question": "Solve (133 - 573)", "answer": "The result of (133 - 573) is -440\n\n####-440", "a": 133, "b": 573, "operator": "-", "result": -440}
{"question": "Solve (662 + 820)", "answer": "The result of (662 + 820) is 1482\n\n####1482", "a": 662, "b": 820, "operator": "+", "result": 1482}
{"question": "Solve (230 - 720)", "answer": "The result of (230 - 720) is -490\n\n####-490", "a": 230, "b": 720, "operator": "-", "result": -490}
{"question": "Solve (227 * 955)", "answer": "The result of (227 * 955) is 216785\n\n####216785", "a": 227, "b": 955, "operator": "*", "result": 216785}
{"question": "Solve (866 + 942)", "answer": "The result of (866 + 942) is 1808\n\n####1808", "a": 866, "b": 942, "operator": "+", "result": 1808}
{"question": "Solve (595 - 656)", "answer": "The result of (595 - 656) is -61\n\n####-61", "a": 595, "b": 656, "operator": "-", "result": -61}
{"question": "Solve (892 * 767)", "answer": "The result of (892 * 767) is 684164\n\n####684164", "a": 892, "b": 767, "operator": "*", "result": 684164}
{"question": "Solve (564 / 452)", "answer": "The result of (564 / 452) is 1.2478\n\n####1.2478", "a": 564, "b": 452, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2478}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 321)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 321) is 0.9097\n\n####0.9097", "a": 292, "b": 321, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9097}
{"question": "Solve (380 * 492)", "answer": "The result of (380 * 492) is 186960\n\n####186960", "a": 380, "b": 492, "operator": "*", "result": 186960}
{"question": "Solve (703 * 859)", "answer": "The result of (703 * 859) is 603877\n\n####603877", "a": 703, "b": 859, "operator": "*", "result": 603877}
{"question": "Solve (226 + 198)", "answer": "The result of (226 + 198) is 424\n\n####424", "a": 226, "b": 198, "operator": "+", "result": 424}
{"question": "Solve (430 * 660)", "answer": "The result of (430 * 660) is 283800\n\n####283800", "a": 430, "b": 660, "operator": "*", "result": 283800}
{"question": "Solve (693 * 409)", "answer": "The result of (693 * 409) is 283437\n\n####283437", "a": 693, "b": 409, "operator": "*", "result": 283437}
{"question": "Solve (703 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (703 - 431) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 703, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (524 - 186)", "answer": "The result of (524 - 186) is 338\n\n####338", "a": 524, "b": 186, "operator": "-", "result": 338}
{"question": "Solve (209 + 989)", "answer": "The result of (209 + 989) is 1198\n\n####1198", "a": 209, "b": 989, "operator": "+", "result": 1198}
{"question": "Solve (66 - 154)", "answer": "The result of (66 - 154) is -88\n\n####-88", "a": 66, "b": 154, "operator": "-", "result": -88}
{"question": "Solve (266 + 544)", "answer": "The result of (266 + 544) is 810\n\n####810", "a": 266, "b": 544, "operator": "+", "result": 810}
{"question": "Solve (136 - 350)", "answer": "The result of (136 - 350) is -214\n\n####-214", "a": 136, "b": 350, "operator": "-", "result": -214}
{"question": "Solve (632 + 39)", "answer": "The result of (632 + 39) is 671\n\n####671", "a": 632, "b": 39, "operator": "+", "result": 671}
{"question": "Solve (869 + 59)", "answer": "The result of (869 + 59) is 928\n\n####928", "a": 869, "b": 59, "operator": "+", "result": 928}
{"question": "Solve (718 / 543)", "answer": "The result of (718 / 543) is 1.3223\n\n####1.3223", "a": 718, "b": 543, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3223}
{"question": "Solve (389 / 637)", "answer": "The result of (389 / 637) is 0.6107\n\n####0.6107", "a": 389, "b": 637, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6107}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 241)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 241) is 664\n\n####664", "a": 423, "b": 241, "operator": "+", "result": 664}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 401)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 401) is 105864\n\n####105864", "a": 264, "b": 401, "operator": "*", "result": 105864}
{"question": "Solve (495 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (495 / 144) is 3.4375\n\n####3.4375", "a": 495, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4375}
{"question": "Solve (258 / 336)", "answer": "The result of (258 / 336) is 0.7679\n\n####0.7679", "a": 258, "b": 336, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7679}
{"question": "Solve (97 / 28)", "answer": "The result of (97 / 28) is 3.4643\n\n####3.4643", "a": 97, "b": 28, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4643}
{"question": "Solve (854 + 924)", "answer": "The result of (854 + 924) is 1778\n\n####1778", "a": 854, "b": 924, "operator": "+", "result": 1778}
{"question": "Solve (61 / 967)", "answer": "The result of (61 / 967) is 0.0631\n\n####0.0631", "a": 61, "b": 967, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0631}
{"question": "Solve (824 + 937)", "answer": "The result of (824 + 937) is 1761\n\n####1761", "a": 824, "b": 937, "operator": "+", "result": 1761}
{"question": "Solve (265 * 228)", "answer": "The result of (265 * 228) is 60420\n\n####60420", "a": 265, "b": 228, "operator": "*", "result": 60420}
{"question": "Solve (327 / 347)", "answer": "The result of (327 / 347) is 0.9424\n\n####0.9424", "a": 327, "b": 347, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9424}
{"question": "Solve (887 - 333)", "answer": "The result of (887 - 333) is 554\n\n####554", "a": 887, "b": 333, "operator": "-", "result": 554}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 185)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 185) is 3.6649\n\n####3.6649", "a": 678, "b": 185, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6649}
{"question": "Solve (843 - 33)", "answer": "The result of (843 - 33) is 810\n\n####810", "a": 843, "b": 33, "operator": "-", "result": 810}
{"question": "Solve (878 * 366)", "answer": "The result of (878 * 366) is 321348\n\n####321348", "a": 878, "b": 366, "operator": "*", "result": 321348}
{"question": "Solve (65 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (65 * 944) is 61360\n\n####61360", "a": 65, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 61360}
{"question": "Solve (278 * 699)", "answer": "The result of (278 * 699) is 194322\n\n####194322", "a": 278, "b": 699, "operator": "*", "result": 194322}
{"question": "Solve (784 * 277)", "answer": "The result of (784 * 277) is 217168\n\n####217168", "a": 784, "b": 277, "operator": "*", "result": 217168}
{"question": "Solve (106 * 734)", "answer": "The result of (106 * 734) is 77804\n\n####77804", "a": 106, "b": 734, "operator": "*", "result": 77804}
{"question": "Solve (506 - 304)", "answer": "The result of (506 - 304) is 202\n\n####202", "a": 506, "b": 304, "operator": "-", "result": 202}
{"question": "Solve (25 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (25 + 11) is 36\n\n####36", "a": 25, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 36}
{"question": "Solve (587 / 675)", "answer": "The result of (587 / 675) is 0.8696\n\n####0.8696", "a": 587, "b": 675, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8696}
{"question": "Solve (984 / 243)", "answer": "The result of (984 / 243) is 4.0494\n\n####4.0494", "a": 984, "b": 243, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0494}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 341)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 341) is 1.0587\n\n####1.0587", "a": 361, "b": 341, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0587}
{"question": "Solve (724 + 470)", "answer": "The result of (724 + 470) is 1194\n\n####1194", "a": 724, "b": 470, "operator": "+", "result": 1194}
{"question": "Solve (82 - 600)", "answer": "The result of (82 - 600) is -518\n\n####-518", "a": 82, "b": 600, "operator": "-", "result": -518}
{"question": "Solve (10 - 650)", "answer": "The result of (10 - 650) is -640\n\n####-640", "a": 10, "b": 650, "operator": "-", "result": -640}
{"question": "Solve (189 - 962)", "answer": "The result of (189 - 962) is -773\n\n####-773", "a": 189, "b": 962, "operator": "-", "result": -773}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 22)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 22) is 177\n\n####177", "a": 199, "b": 22, "operator": "-", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve (300 * 180)", "answer": "The result of (300 * 180) is 54000\n\n####54000", "a": 300, "b": 180, "operator": "*", "result": 54000}
{"question": "Solve (67 + 336)", "answer": "The result of (67 + 336) is 403\n\n####403", "a": 67, "b": 336, "operator": "+", "result": 403}
{"question": "Solve (781 - 629)", "answer": "The result of (781 - 629) is 152\n\n####152", "a": 781, "b": 629, "operator": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve (678 * 629)", "answer": "The result of (678 * 629) is 426462\n\n####426462", "a": 678, "b": 629, "operator": "*", "result": 426462}
{"question": "Solve (7 - 457)", "answer": "The result of (7 - 457) is -450\n\n####-450", "a": 7, "b": 457, "operator": "-", "result": -450}
{"question": "Solve (759 + 922)", "answer": "The result of (759 + 922) is 1681\n\n####1681", "a": 759, "b": 922, "operator": "+", "result": 1681}
{"question": "Solve (415 + 887)", "answer": "The result of (415 + 887) is 1302\n\n####1302", "a": 415, "b": 887, "operator": "+", "result": 1302}
{"question": "Solve (392 * 770)", "answer": "The result of (392 * 770) is 301840\n\n####301840", "a": 392, "b": 770, "operator": "*", "result": 301840}
{"question": "Solve (426 - 962)", "answer": "The result of (426 - 962) is -536\n\n####-536", "a": 426, "b": 962, "operator": "-", "result": -536}
{"question": "Solve (600 - 124)", "answer": "The result of (600 - 124) is 476\n\n####476", "a": 600, "b": 124, "operator": "-", "result": 476}
{"question": "Solve (447 * 882)", "answer": "The result of (447 * 882) is 394254\n\n####394254", "a": 447, "b": 882, "operator": "*", "result": 394254}
{"question": "Solve (757 * 646)", "answer": "The result of (757 * 646) is 489022\n\n####489022", "a": 757, "b": 646, "operator": "*", "result": 489022}
{"question": "Solve (480 * 908)", "answer": "The result of (480 * 908) is 435840\n\n####435840", "a": 480, "b": 908, "operator": "*", "result": 435840}
{"question": "Solve (498 / 112)", "answer": "The result of (498 / 112) is 4.4464\n\n####4.4464", "a": 498, "b": 112, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4464}
{"question": "Solve (746 / 572)", "answer": "The result of (746 / 572) is 1.3042\n\n####1.3042", "a": 746, "b": 572, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3042}
{"question": "Solve (432 - 979)", "answer": "The result of (432 - 979) is -547\n\n####-547", "a": 432, "b": 979, "operator": "-", "result": -547}
{"question": "Solve (285 - 67)", "answer": "The result of (285 - 67) is 218\n\n####218", "a": 285, "b": 67, "operator": "-", "result": 218}
{"question": "Solve (187 * 340)", "answer": "The result of (187 * 340) is 63580\n\n####63580", "a": 187, "b": 340, "operator": "*", "result": 63580}
{"question": "Solve (627 - 798)", "answer": "The result of (627 - 798) is -171\n\n####-171", "a": 627, "b": 798, "operator": "-", "result": -171}
{"question": "Solve (922 * 541)", "answer": "The result of (922 * 541) is 498802\n\n####498802", "a": 922, "b": 541, "operator": "*", "result": 498802}
{"question": "Solve (418 + 956)", "answer": "The result of (418 + 956) is 1374\n\n####1374", "a": 418, "b": 956, "operator": "+", "result": 1374}
{"question": "Solve (241 * 980)", "answer": "The result of (241 * 980) is 236180\n\n####236180", "a": 241, "b": 980, "operator": "*", "result": 236180}
{"question": "Solve (627 + 373)", "answer": "The result of (627 + 373) is 1000\n\n####1000", "a": 627, "b": 373, "operator": "+", "result": 1000}
{"question": "Solve (649 - 669)", "answer": "The result of (649 - 669) is -20\n\n####-20", "a": 649, "b": 669, "operator": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 98)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 98) is 751\n\n####751", "a": 849, "b": 98, "operator": "-", "result": 751}
{"question": "Solve (138 - 279)", "answer": "The result of (138 - 279) is -141\n\n####-141", "a": 138, "b": 279, "operator": "-", "result": -141}
{"question": "Solve (710 * 193)", "answer": "The result of (710 * 193) is 137030\n\n####137030", "a": 710, "b": 193, "operator": "*", "result": 137030}
{"question": "Solve (869 - 771)", "answer": "The result of (869 - 771) is 98\n\n####98", "a": 869, "b": 771, "operator": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 29)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 29) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 491, "b": 29, "operator": "+", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (677 - 52)", "answer": "The result of (677 - 52) is 625\n\n####625", "a": 677, "b": 52, "operator": "-", "result": 625}
{"question": "Solve (55 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (55 - 825) is -770\n\n####-770", "a": 55, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": -770}
{"question": "Solve (60 / 384)", "answer": "The result of (60 / 384) is 0.1562\n\n####0.1562", "a": 60, "b": 384, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1562}
{"question": "Solve (627 + 39)", "answer": "The result of (627 + 39) is 666\n\n####666", "a": 627, "b": 39, "operator": "+", "result": 666}
{"question": "Solve (617 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (617 - 700) is -83\n\n####-83", "a": 617, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -83}
{"question": "Solve (126 * 453)", "answer": "The result of (126 * 453) is 57078\n\n####57078", "a": 126, "b": 453, "operator": "*", "result": 57078}
{"question": "Solve (584 * 386)", "answer": "The result of (584 * 386) is 225424\n\n####225424", "a": 584, "b": 386, "operator": "*", "result": 225424}
{"question": "Solve (10 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (10 - 822) is -812\n\n####-812", "a": 10, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": -812}
{"question": "Solve (862 / 462)", "answer": "The result of (862 / 462) is 1.8658\n\n####1.8658", "a": 862, "b": 462, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8658}
{"question": "Solve (705 - 821)", "answer": "The result of (705 - 821) is -116\n\n####-116", "a": 705, "b": 821, "operator": "-", "result": -116}
{"question": "Solve (201 * 511)", "answer": "The result of (201 * 511) is 102711\n\n####102711", "a": 201, "b": 511, "operator": "*", "result": 102711}
{"question": "Solve (375 * 890)", "answer": "The result of (375 * 890) is 333750\n\n####333750", "a": 375, "b": 890, "operator": "*", "result": 333750}
{"question": "Solve (279 - 842)", "answer": "The result of (279 - 842) is -563\n\n####-563", "a": 279, "b": 842, "operator": "-", "result": -563}
{"question": "Solve (77 + 719)", "answer": "The result of (77 + 719) is 796\n\n####796", "a": 77, "b": 719, "operator": "+", "result": 796}
{"question": "Solve (256 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (256 * 910) is 232960\n\n####232960", "a": 256, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 232960}
{"question": "Solve (239 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (239 - 184) is 55\n\n####55", "a": 239, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 55}
{"question": "Solve (56 - 723)", "answer": "The result of (56 - 723) is -667\n\n####-667", "a": 56, "b": 723, "operator": "-", "result": -667}
{"question": "Solve (813 / 521)", "answer": "The result of (813 / 521) is 1.5605\n\n####1.5605", "a": 813, "b": 521, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5605}
{"question": "Solve (815 / 34)", "answer": "The result of (815 / 34) is 23.9706\n\n####23.9706", "a": 815, "b": 34, "operator": "/", "result": 23.9706}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 847)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 847) is -523\n\n####-523", "a": 324, "b": 847, "operator": "-", "result": -523}
{"question": "Solve (702 / 948)", "answer": "The result of (702 / 948) is 0.7405\n\n####0.7405", "a": 702, "b": 948, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7405}
{"question": "Solve (851 / 159)", "answer": "The result of (851 / 159) is 5.3522\n\n####5.3522", "a": 851, "b": 159, "operator": "/", "result": 5.3522}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 18)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 18) is 13590\n\n####13590", "a": 755, "b": 18, "operator": "*", "result": 13590}
{"question": "Solve (290 + 778)", "answer": "The result of (290 + 778) is 1068\n\n####1068", "a": 290, "b": 778, "operator": "+", "result": 1068}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 920)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 920) is -333\n\n####-333", "a": 587, "b": 920, "operator": "-", "result": -333}
{"question": "Solve (170 * 12)", "answer": "The result of (170 * 12) is 2040\n\n####2040", "a": 170, "b": 12, "operator": "*", "result": 2040}
{"question": "Solve (243 - 898)", "answer": "The result of (243 - 898) is -655\n\n####-655", "a": 243, "b": 898, "operator": "-", "result": -655}
{"question": "Solve (911 + 637)", "answer": "The result of (911 + 637) is 1548\n\n####1548", "a": 911, "b": 637, "operator": "+", "result": 1548}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 892)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 892) is 0.5706\n\n####0.5706", "a": 509, "b": 892, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5706}
{"question": "Solve (316 * 115)", "answer": "The result of (316 * 115) is 36340\n\n####36340", "a": 316, "b": 115, "operator": "*", "result": 36340}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 246)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 246) is 1132\n\n####1132", "a": 886, "b": 246, "operator": "+", "result": 1132}
{"question": "Solve (449 + 497)", "answer": "The result of (449 + 497) is 946\n\n####946", "a": 449, "b": 497, "operator": "+", "result": 946}
{"question": "Solve (744 - 939)", "answer": "The result of (744 - 939) is -195\n\n####-195", "a": 744, "b": 939, "operator": "-", "result": -195}
{"question": "Solve (210 * 774)", "answer": "The result of (210 * 774) is 162540\n\n####162540", "a": 210, "b": 774, "operator": "*", "result": 162540}
{"question": "Solve (880 / 62)", "answer": "The result of (880 / 62) is 14.1935\n\n####14.1935", "a": 880, "b": 62, "operator": "/", "result": 14.1935}
{"question": "Solve (634 / 355)", "answer": "The result of (634 / 355) is 1.7859\n\n####1.7859", "a": 634, "b": 355, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7859}
{"question": "Solve (317 * 211)", "answer": "The result of (317 * 211) is 66887\n\n####66887", "a": 317, "b": 211, "operator": "*", "result": 66887}
{"question": "Solve (975 - 690)", "answer": "The result of (975 - 690) is 285\n\n####285", "a": 975, "b": 690, "operator": "-", "result": 285}
{"question": "Solve (985 * 896)", "answer": "The result of (985 * 896) is 882560\n\n####882560", "a": 985, "b": 896, "operator": "*", "result": 882560}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 158)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 158) is 1101\n\n####1101", "a": 943, "b": 158, "operator": "+", "result": 1101}
{"question": "Solve (978 / 291)", "answer": "The result of (978 / 291) is 3.3608\n\n####3.3608", "a": 978, "b": 291, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3608}
{"question": "Solve (929 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (929 + 239) is 1168\n\n####1168", "a": 929, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 1168}
{"question": "Solve (428 * 141)", "answer": "The result of (428 * 141) is 60348\n\n####60348", "a": 428, "b": 141, "operator": "*", "result": 60348}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 277)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 277) is 169247\n\n####169247", "a": 611, "b": 277, "operator": "*", "result": 169247}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 299)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 299) is 287638\n\n####287638", "a": 962, "b": 299, "operator": "*", "result": 287638}
{"question": "Solve (382 - 586)", "answer": "The result of (382 - 586) is -204\n\n####-204", "a": 382, "b": 586, "operator": "-", "result": -204}
{"question": "Solve (318 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (318 * 22) is 6996\n\n####6996", "a": 318, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 6996}
{"question": "Solve (118 * 333)", "answer": "The result of (118 * 333) is 39294\n\n####39294", "a": 118, "b": 333, "operator": "*", "result": 39294}
{"question": "Solve (436 / 871)", "answer": "The result of (436 / 871) is 0.5006\n\n####0.5006", "a": 436, "b": 871, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5006}
{"question": "Solve (860 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (860 - 358) is 502\n\n####502", "a": 860, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 502}
{"question": "Solve (276 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (276 + 11) is 287\n\n####287", "a": 276, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 287}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 19)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 19) is 49.0\n\n####49.0", "a": 931, "b": 19, "operator": "/", "result": 49.0}
{"question": "Solve (612 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (612 / 299) is 2.0468\n\n####2.0468", "a": 612, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0468}
{"question": "Solve (534 - 679)", "answer": "The result of (534 - 679) is -145\n\n####-145", "a": 534, "b": 679, "operator": "-", "result": -145}
{"question": "Solve (801 - 108)", "answer": "The result of (801 - 108) is 693\n\n####693", "a": 801, "b": 108, "operator": "-", "result": 693}
{"question": "Solve (198 * 757)", "answer": "The result of (198 * 757) is 149886\n\n####149886", "a": 198, "b": 757, "operator": "*", "result": 149886}
{"question": "Solve (588 + 551)", "answer": "The result of (588 + 551) is 1139\n\n####1139", "a": 588, "b": 551, "operator": "+", "result": 1139}
{"question": "Solve (404 * 116)", "answer": "The result of (404 * 116) is 46864\n\n####46864", "a": 404, "b": 116, "operator": "*", "result": 46864}
{"question": "Solve (545 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (545 * 215) is 117175\n\n####117175", "a": 545, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 117175}
{"question": "Solve (344 + 57)", "answer": "The result of (344 + 57) is 401\n\n####401", "a": 344, "b": 57, "operator": "+", "result": 401}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 399)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 399) is 87\n\n####87", "a": 486, "b": 399, "operator": "-", "result": 87}
{"question": "Solve (25 / 915)", "answer": "The result of (25 / 915) is 0.0273\n\n####0.0273", "a": 25, "b": 915, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0273}
{"question": "Solve (245 - 274)", "answer": "The result of (245 - 274) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 245, "b": 274, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (809 * 236)", "answer": "The result of (809 * 236) is 190924\n\n####190924", "a": 809, "b": 236, "operator": "*", "result": 190924}
{"question": "Solve (186 * 440)", "answer": "The result of (186 * 440) is 81840\n\n####81840", "a": 186, "b": 440, "operator": "*", "result": 81840}
{"question": "Solve (551 + 402)", "answer": "The result of (551 + 402) is 953\n\n####953", "a": 551, "b": 402, "operator": "+", "result": 953}
{"question": "Solve (470 + 332)", "answer": "The result of (470 + 332) is 802\n\n####802", "a": 470, "b": 332, "operator": "+", "result": 802}
{"question": "Solve (970 * 691)", "answer": "The result of (970 * 691) is 670270\n\n####670270", "a": 970, "b": 691, "operator": "*", "result": 670270}
{"question": "Solve (917 - 277)", "answer": "The result of (917 - 277) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 917, "b": 277, "operator": "-", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 977)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 977) is -525\n\n####-525", "a": 452, "b": 977, "operator": "-", "result": -525}
{"question": "Solve (973 - 907)", "answer": "The result of (973 - 907) is 66\n\n####66", "a": 973, "b": 907, "operator": "-", "result": 66}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 143)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 143) is 347\n\n####347", "a": 490, "b": 143, "operator": "-", "result": 347}
{"question": "Solve (778 + 831)", "answer": "The result of (778 + 831) is 1609\n\n####1609", "a": 778, "b": 831, "operator": "+", "result": 1609}
{"question": "Solve (444 - 385)", "answer": "The result of (444 - 385) is 59\n\n####59", "a": 444, "b": 385, "operator": "-", "result": 59}
{"question": "Solve (483 / 834)", "answer": "The result of (483 / 834) is 0.5791\n\n####0.5791", "a": 483, "b": 834, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5791}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 301)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 301) is 1.5282\n\n####1.5282", "a": 460, "b": 301, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5282}
{"question": "Solve (803 * 365)", "answer": "The result of (803 * 365) is 293095\n\n####293095", "a": 803, "b": 365, "operator": "*", "result": 293095}
{"question": "Solve (121 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (121 + 124) is 245\n\n####245", "a": 121, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 245}
{"question": "Solve (282 * 164)", "answer": "The result of (282 * 164) is 46248\n\n####46248", "a": 282, "b": 164, "operator": "*", "result": 46248}
{"question": "Solve (551 * 901)", "answer": "The result of (551 * 901) is 496451\n\n####496451", "a": 551, "b": 901, "operator": "*", "result": 496451}
{"question": "Solve (866 - 580)", "answer": "The result of (866 - 580) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 866, "b": 580, "operator": "-", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (62 / 137)", "answer": "The result of (62 / 137) is 0.4526\n\n####0.4526", "a": 62, "b": 137, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4526}
{"question": "Solve (479 / 928)", "answer": "The result of (479 / 928) is 0.5162\n\n####0.5162", "a": 479, "b": 928, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5162}
{"question": "Solve (644 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (644 - 949) is -305\n\n####-305", "a": 644, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -305}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 226)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 226) is 14916\n\n####14916", "a": 66, "b": 226, "operator": "*", "result": 14916}
{"question": "Solve (376 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (376 - 876) is -500\n\n####-500", "a": 376, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -500}
{"question": "Solve (946 + 961)", "answer": "The result of (946 + 961) is 1907\n\n####1907", "a": 946, "b": 961, "operator": "+", "result": 1907}
{"question": "Solve (248 + 594)", "answer": "The result of (248 + 594) is 842\n\n####842", "a": 248, "b": 594, "operator": "+", "result": 842}
{"question": "Solve (556 * 147)", "answer": "The result of (556 * 147) is 81732\n\n####81732", "a": 556, "b": 147, "operator": "*", "result": 81732}
{"question": "Solve (372 - 433)", "answer": "The result of (372 - 433) is -61\n\n####-61", "a": 372, "b": 433, "operator": "-", "result": -61}
{"question": "Solve (131 / 498)", "answer": "The result of (131 / 498) is 0.2631\n\n####0.2631", "a": 131, "b": 498, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2631}
{"question": "Solve (385 * 263)", "answer": "The result of (385 * 263) is 101255\n\n####101255", "a": 385, "b": 263, "operator": "*", "result": 101255}
{"question": "Solve (188 * 531)", "answer": "The result of (188 * 531) is 99828\n\n####99828", "a": 188, "b": 531, "operator": "*", "result": 99828}
{"question": "Solve (935 / 218)", "answer": "The result of (935 / 218) is 4.289\n\n####4.289", "a": 935, "b": 218, "operator": "/", "result": 4.289}
{"question": "Solve (623 - 201)", "answer": "The result of (623 - 201) is 422\n\n####422", "a": 623, "b": 201, "operator": "-", "result": 422}
{"question": "Solve (230 + 512)", "answer": "The result of (230 + 512) is 742\n\n####742", "a": 230, "b": 512, "operator": "+", "result": 742}
{"question": "Solve (779 / 149)", "answer": "The result of (779 / 149) is 5.2282\n\n####5.2282", "a": 779, "b": 149, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2282}
{"question": "Solve (477 - 191)", "answer": "The result of (477 - 191) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 477, "b": 191, "operator": "-", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (540 * 264)", "answer": "The result of (540 * 264) is 142560\n\n####142560", "a": 540, "b": 264, "operator": "*", "result": 142560}
{"question": "Solve (817 * 220)", "answer": "The result of (817 * 220) is 179740\n\n####179740", "a": 817, "b": 220, "operator": "*", "result": 179740}
{"question": "Solve (714 + 94)", "answer": "The result of (714 + 94) is 808\n\n####808", "a": 714, "b": 94, "operator": "+", "result": 808}
{"question": "Solve (267 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (267 - 321) is -54\n\n####-54", "a": 267, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": -54}
{"question": "Solve (894 * 827)", "answer": "The result of (894 * 827) is 739338\n\n####739338", "a": 894, "b": 827, "operator": "*", "result": 739338}
{"question": "Solve (569 / 378)", "answer": "The result of (569 / 378) is 1.5053\n\n####1.5053", "a": 569, "b": 378, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5053}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 281)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 281) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 127, "b": 281, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 273)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 273) is 665\n\n####665", "a": 938, "b": 273, "operator": "-", "result": 665}
{"question": "Solve (329 / 875)", "answer": "The result of (329 / 875) is 0.376\n\n####0.376", "a": 329, "b": 875, "operator": "/", "result": 0.376}
{"question": "Solve (392 * 238)", "answer": "The result of (392 * 238) is 93296\n\n####93296", "a": 392, "b": 238, "operator": "*", "result": 93296}
{"question": "Solve (321 - 617)", "answer": "The result of (321 - 617) is -296\n\n####-296", "a": 321, "b": 617, "operator": "-", "result": -296}
{"question": "Solve (392 + 90)", "answer": "The result of (392 + 90) is 482\n\n####482", "a": 392, "b": 90, "operator": "+", "result": 482}
{"question": "Solve (660 + 412)", "answer": "The result of (660 + 412) is 1072\n\n####1072", "a": 660, "b": 412, "operator": "+", "result": 1072}
{"question": "Solve (749 * 948)", "answer": "The result of (749 * 948) is 710052\n\n####710052", "a": 749, "b": 948, "operator": "*", "result": 710052}
{"question": "Solve (555 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (555 - 117) is 438\n\n####438", "a": 555, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": 438}
{"question": "Solve (139 - 867)", "answer": "The result of (139 - 867) is -728\n\n####-728", "a": 139, "b": 867, "operator": "-", "result": -728}
{"question": "Solve (451 * 347)", "answer": "The result of (451 * 347) is 156497\n\n####156497", "a": 451, "b": 347, "operator": "*", "result": 156497}
{"question": "Solve (88 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (88 * 102) is 8976\n\n####8976", "a": 88, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 8976}
{"question": "Solve (814 / 349)", "answer": "The result of (814 / 349) is 2.3324\n\n####2.3324", "a": 814, "b": 349, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3324}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 664)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 664) is -77\n\n####-77", "a": 587, "b": 664, "operator": "-", "result": -77}
{"question": "Solve (610 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (610 * 510) is 311100\n\n####311100", "a": 610, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 311100}
{"question": "Solve (593 * 813)", "answer": "The result of (593 * 813) is 482109\n\n####482109", "a": 593, "b": 813, "operator": "*", "result": 482109}
{"question": "Solve (380 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (380 / 230) is 1.6522\n\n####1.6522", "a": 380, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6522}
{"question": "Solve (997 - 133)", "answer": "The result of (997 - 133) is 864\n\n####864", "a": 997, "b": 133, "operator": "-", "result": 864}
{"question": "Solve (71 + 688)", "answer": "The result of (71 + 688) is 759\n\n####759", "a": 71, "b": 688, "operator": "+", "result": 759}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 832)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 832) is -238\n\n####-238", "a": 594, "b": 832, "operator": "-", "result": -238}
{"question": "Solve (285 / 855)", "answer": "The result of (285 / 855) is 0.3333\n\n####0.3333", "a": 285, "b": 855, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3333}
{"question": "Solve (552 * 96)", "answer": "The result of (552 * 96) is 52992\n\n####52992", "a": 552, "b": 96, "operator": "*", "result": 52992}
{"question": "Solve (641 * 794)", "answer": "The result of (641 * 794) is 508954\n\n####508954", "a": 641, "b": 794, "operator": "*", "result": 508954}
{"question": "Solve (533 * 519)", "answer": "The result of (533 * 519) is 276627\n\n####276627", "a": 533, "b": 519, "operator": "*", "result": 276627}
{"question": "Solve (454 / 126)", "answer": "The result of (454 / 126) is 3.6032\n\n####3.6032", "a": 454, "b": 126, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6032}
{"question": "Solve (611 / 16)", "answer": "The result of (611 / 16) is 38.1875\n\n####38.1875", "a": 611, "b": 16, "operator": "/", "result": 38.1875}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 487)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 487) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 351, "b": 487, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (532 + 966)", "answer": "The result of (532 + 966) is 1498\n\n####1498", "a": 532, "b": 966, "operator": "+", "result": 1498}
{"question": "Solve (318 * 467)", "answer": "The result of (318 * 467) is 148506\n\n####148506", "a": 318, "b": 467, "operator": "*", "result": 148506}
{"question": "Solve (486 + 748)", "answer": "The result of (486 + 748) is 1234\n\n####1234", "a": 486, "b": 748, "operator": "+", "result": 1234}
{"question": "Solve (732 - 470)", "answer": "The result of (732 - 470) is 262\n\n####262", "a": 732, "b": 470, "operator": "-", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve (625 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (625 / 289) is 2.1626\n\n####2.1626", "a": 625, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1626}
{"question": "Solve (558 * 860)", "answer": "The result of (558 * 860) is 479880\n\n####479880", "a": 558, "b": 860, "operator": "*", "result": 479880}
{"question": "Solve (889 + 747)", "answer": "The result of (889 + 747) is 1636\n\n####1636", "a": 889, "b": 747, "operator": "+", "result": 1636}
{"question": "Solve (85 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (85 - 384) is -299\n\n####-299", "a": 85, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": -299}
{"question": "Solve (7 - 530)", "answer": "The result of (7 - 530) is -523\n\n####-523", "a": 7, "b": 530, "operator": "-", "result": -523}
{"question": "Solve (917 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (917 - 283) is 634\n\n####634", "a": 917, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 634}
{"question": "Solve (212 + 873)", "answer": "The result of (212 + 873) is 1085\n\n####1085", "a": 212, "b": 873, "operator": "+", "result": 1085}
{"question": "Solve (121 - 467)", "answer": "The result of (121 - 467) is -346\n\n####-346", "a": 121, "b": 467, "operator": "-", "result": -346}
{"question": "Solve (890 + 235)", "answer": "The result of (890 + 235) is 1125\n\n####1125", "a": 890, "b": 235, "operator": "+", "result": 1125}
{"question": "Solve (951 - 102)", "answer": "The result of (951 - 102) is 849\n\n####849", "a": 951, "b": 102, "operator": "-", "result": 849}
{"question": "Solve (959 * 653)", "answer": "The result of (959 * 653) is 626227\n\n####626227", "a": 959, "b": 653, "operator": "*", "result": 626227}
{"question": "Solve (189 + 228)", "answer": "The result of (189 + 228) is 417\n\n####417", "a": 189, "b": 228, "operator": "+", "result": 417}
{"question": "Solve (433 * 832)", "answer": "The result of (433 * 832) is 360256\n\n####360256", "a": 433, "b": 832, "operator": "*", "result": 360256}
{"question": "Solve (456 / 472)", "answer": "The result of (456 / 472) is 0.9661\n\n####0.9661", "a": 456, "b": 472, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9661}
{"question": "Solve (559 / 19)", "answer": "The result of (559 / 19) is 29.4211\n\n####29.4211", "a": 559, "b": 19, "operator": "/", "result": 29.4211}
{"question": "Solve (742 / 739)", "answer": "The result of (742 / 739) is 1.0041\n\n####1.0041", "a": 742, "b": 739, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0041}
{"question": "Solve (967 * 219)", "answer": "The result of (967 * 219) is 211773\n\n####211773", "a": 967, "b": 219, "operator": "*", "result": 211773}
{"question": "Solve (134 - 335)", "answer": "The result of (134 - 335) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 134, "b": 335, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (527 + 6)", "answer": "The result of (527 + 6) is 533\n\n####533", "a": 527, "b": 6, "operator": "+", "result": 533}
{"question": "Solve (877 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (877 - 551) is 326\n\n####326", "a": 877, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 326}
{"question": "Solve (5 - 923)", "answer": "The result of (5 - 923) is -918\n\n####-918", "a": 5, "b": 923, "operator": "-", "result": -918}
{"question": "Solve (952 / 204)", "answer": "The result of (952 / 204) is 4.6667\n\n####4.6667", "a": 952, "b": 204, "operator": "/", "result": 4.6667}
{"question": "Solve (980 * 480)", "answer": "The result of (980 * 480) is 470400\n\n####470400", "a": 980, "b": 480, "operator": "*", "result": 470400}
{"question": "Solve (485 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (485 - 321) is 164\n\n####164", "a": 485, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 164}
{"question": "Solve (114 + 544)", "answer": "The result of (114 + 544) is 658\n\n####658", "a": 114, "b": 544, "operator": "+", "result": 658}
{"question": "Solve (475 * 228)", "answer": "The result of (475 * 228) is 108300\n\n####108300", "a": 475, "b": 228, "operator": "*", "result": 108300}
{"question": "Solve (741 - 793)", "answer": "The result of (741 - 793) is -52\n\n####-52", "a": 741, "b": 793, "operator": "-", "result": -52}
{"question": "Solve (698 + 916)", "answer": "The result of (698 + 916) is 1614\n\n####1614", "a": 698, "b": 916, "operator": "+", "result": 1614}
{"question": "Solve (91 * 826)", "answer": "The result of (91 * 826) is 75166\n\n####75166", "a": 91, "b": 826, "operator": "*", "result": 75166}
{"question": "Solve (243 - 796)", "answer": "The result of (243 - 796) is -553\n\n####-553", "a": 243, "b": 796, "operator": "-", "result": -553}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 283) is 153\n\n####153", "a": 436, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 153}
{"question": "Solve (652 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (652 * 145) is 94540\n\n####94540", "a": 652, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 94540}
{"question": "Solve (276 / 435)", "answer": "The result of (276 / 435) is 0.6345\n\n####0.6345", "a": 276, "b": 435, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6345}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 886)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 886) is 1829\n\n####1829", "a": 943, "b": 886, "operator": "+", "result": 1829}
{"question": "Solve (126 / 748)", "answer": "The result of (126 / 748) is 0.1684\n\n####0.1684", "a": 126, "b": 748, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1684}
{"question": "Solve (166 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (166 * 932) is 154712\n\n####154712", "a": 166, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 154712}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 817)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 817) is 0.8629\n\n####0.8629", "a": 705, "b": 817, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8629}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 199)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 199) is 18\n\n####18", "a": 217, "b": 199, "operator": "-", "result": 18}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 187)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 187) is 0.1123\n\n####0.1123", "a": 21, "b": 187, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1123}
{"question": "Solve (18 * 712)", "answer": "The result of (18 * 712) is 12816\n\n####12816", "a": 18, "b": 712, "operator": "*", "result": 12816}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 159)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 159) is 2.6667\n\n####2.6667", "a": 424, "b": 159, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6667}
{"question": "Solve (913 * 773)", "answer": "The result of (913 * 773) is 705749\n\n####705749", "a": 913, "b": 773, "operator": "*", "result": 705749}
{"question": "Solve (744 * 585)", "answer": "The result of (744 * 585) is 435240\n\n####435240", "a": 744, "b": 585, "operator": "*", "result": 435240}
{"question": "Solve (26 + 928)", "answer": "The result of (26 + 928) is 954\n\n####954", "a": 26, "b": 928, "operator": "+", "result": 954}
{"question": "Solve (436 / 647)", "answer": "The result of (436 / 647) is 0.6739\n\n####0.6739", "a": 436, "b": 647, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6739}
{"question": "Solve (252 - 850)", "answer": "The result of (252 - 850) is -598\n\n####-598", "a": 252, "b": 850, "operator": "-", "result": -598}
{"question": "Solve (979 / 633)", "answer": "The result of (979 / 633) is 1.5466\n\n####1.5466", "a": 979, "b": 633, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5466}
{"question": "Solve (261 + 411)", "answer": "The result of (261 + 411) is 672\n\n####672", "a": 261, "b": 411, "operator": "+", "result": 672}
{"question": "Solve (292 - 119)", "answer": "The result of (292 - 119) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 292, "b": 119, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (151 / 158)", "answer": "The result of (151 / 158) is 0.9557\n\n####0.9557", "a": 151, "b": 158, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9557}
{"question": "Solve (273 - 69)", "answer": "The result of (273 - 69) is 204\n\n####204", "a": 273, "b": 69, "operator": "-", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve (451 - 100)", "answer": "The result of (451 - 100) is 351\n\n####351", "a": 451, "b": 100, "operator": "-", "result": 351}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 961)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 961) is -603\n\n####-603", "a": 358, "b": 961, "operator": "-", "result": -603}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 809)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 809) is 990\n\n####990", "a": 181, "b": 809, "operator": "+", "result": 990}
{"question": "Solve (174 + 30)", "answer": "The result of (174 + 30) is 204\n\n####204", "a": 174, "b": 30, "operator": "+", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve (688 + 866)", "answer": "The result of (688 + 866) is 1554\n\n####1554", "a": 688, "b": 866, "operator": "+", "result": 1554}
{"question": "Solve (195 - 566)", "answer": "The result of (195 - 566) is -371\n\n####-371", "a": 195, "b": 566, "operator": "-", "result": -371}
{"question": "Solve (518 / 182)", "answer": "The result of (518 / 182) is 2.8462\n\n####2.8462", "a": 518, "b": 182, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8462}
{"question": "Solve (634 + 109)", "answer": "The result of (634 + 109) is 743\n\n####743", "a": 634, "b": 109, "operator": "+", "result": 743}
{"question": "Solve (561 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (561 - 777) is -216\n\n####-216", "a": 561, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -216}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 565)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 565) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 512, "b": 565, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (89 + 946)", "answer": "The result of (89 + 946) is 1035\n\n####1035", "a": 89, "b": 946, "operator": "+", "result": 1035}
{"question": "Solve (340 / 601)", "answer": "The result of (340 / 601) is 0.5657\n\n####0.5657", "a": 340, "b": 601, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5657}
{"question": "Solve (473 / 861)", "answer": "The result of (473 / 861) is 0.5494\n\n####0.5494", "a": 473, "b": 861, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5494}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 427)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 427) is 154147\n\n####154147", "a": 361, "b": 427, "operator": "*", "result": 154147}
{"question": "Solve (724 - 54)", "answer": "The result of (724 - 54) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 724, "b": 54, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (442 + 679)", "answer": "The result of (442 + 679) is 1121\n\n####1121", "a": 442, "b": 679, "operator": "+", "result": 1121}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 140)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 140) is 14140\n\n####14140", "a": 101, "b": 140, "operator": "*", "result": 14140}
{"question": "Solve (462 + 488)", "answer": "The result of (462 + 488) is 950\n\n####950", "a": 462, "b": 488, "operator": "+", "result": 950}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 931)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 931) is 1854\n\n####1854", "a": 923, "b": 931, "operator": "+", "result": 1854}
{"question": "Solve (359 * 836)", "answer": "The result of (359 * 836) is 300124\n\n####300124", "a": 359, "b": 836, "operator": "*", "result": 300124}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 294) is 1.0408\n\n####1.0408", "a": 306, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0408}
{"question": "Solve (757 / 590)", "answer": "The result of (757 / 590) is 1.2831\n\n####1.2831", "a": 757, "b": 590, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2831}
{"question": "Solve (75 + 391)", "answer": "The result of (75 + 391) is 466\n\n####466", "a": 75, "b": 391, "operator": "+", "result": 466}
{"question": "Solve (702 / 995)", "answer": "The result of (702 / 995) is 0.7055\n\n####0.7055", "a": 702, "b": 995, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7055}
{"question": "Solve (433 - 629)", "answer": "The result of (433 - 629) is -196\n\n####-196", "a": 433, "b": 629, "operator": "-", "result": -196}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 579)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 579) is 0.3489\n\n####0.3489", "a": 202, "b": 579, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3489}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 648)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 648) is -419\n\n####-419", "a": 229, "b": 648, "operator": "-", "result": -419}
{"question": "Solve (971 / 649)", "answer": "The result of (971 / 649) is 1.4961\n\n####1.4961", "a": 971, "b": 649, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4961}
{"question": "Solve (925 * 744)", "answer": "The result of (925 * 744) is 688200\n\n####688200", "a": 925, "b": 744, "operator": "*", "result": 688200}
{"question": "Solve (786 + 67)", "answer": "The result of (786 + 67) is 853\n\n####853", "a": 786, "b": 67, "operator": "+", "result": 853}
{"question": "Solve (349 - 931)", "answer": "The result of (349 - 931) is -582\n\n####-582", "a": 349, "b": 931, "operator": "-", "result": -582}
{"question": "Solve (203 + 723)", "answer": "The result of (203 + 723) is 926\n\n####926", "a": 203, "b": 723, "operator": "+", "result": 926}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 435)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 435) is -153\n\n####-153", "a": 282, "b": 435, "operator": "-", "result": -153}
{"question": "Solve (787 / 396)", "answer": "The result of (787 / 396) is 1.9874\n\n####1.9874", "a": 787, "b": 396, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9874}
{"question": "Solve (189 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (189 / 686) is 0.2755\n\n####0.2755", "a": 189, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2755}
{"question": "Solve (834 * 549)", "answer": "The result of (834 * 549) is 457866\n\n####457866", "a": 834, "b": 549, "operator": "*", "result": 457866}
{"question": "Solve (234 / 366)", "answer": "The result of (234 / 366) is 0.6393\n\n####0.6393", "a": 234, "b": 366, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6393}
{"question": "Solve (763 + 777)", "answer": "The result of (763 + 777) is 1540\n\n####1540", "a": 763, "b": 777, "operator": "+", "result": 1540}
{"question": "Solve (171 + 34)", "answer": "The result of (171 + 34) is 205\n\n####205", "a": 171, "b": 34, "operator": "+", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve (337 + 349)", "answer": "The result of (337 + 349) is 686\n\n####686", "a": 337, "b": 349, "operator": "+", "result": 686}
{"question": "Solve (504 / 119)", "answer": "The result of (504 / 119) is 4.2353\n\n####4.2353", "a": 504, "b": 119, "operator": "/", "result": 4.2353}
{"question": "Solve (433 + 683)", "answer": "The result of (433 + 683) is 1116\n\n####1116", "a": 433, "b": 683, "operator": "+", "result": 1116}
{"question": "Solve (744 - 947)", "answer": "The result of (744 - 947) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 744, "b": 947, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (843 - 881)", "answer": "The result of (843 - 881) is -38\n\n####-38", "a": 843, "b": 881, "operator": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve (318 * 909)", "answer": "The result of (318 * 909) is 289062\n\n####289062", "a": 318, "b": 909, "operator": "*", "result": 289062}
{"question": "Solve (203 - 848)", "answer": "The result of (203 - 848) is -645\n\n####-645", "a": 203, "b": 848, "operator": "-", "result": -645}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 862)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 862) is 0.3387\n\n####0.3387", "a": 292, "b": 862, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3387}
{"question": "Solve (568 * 203)", "answer": "The result of (568 * 203) is 115304\n\n####115304", "a": 568, "b": 203, "operator": "*", "result": 115304}
{"question": "Solve (19 / 283)", "answer": "The result of (19 / 283) is 0.0671\n\n####0.0671", "a": 19, "b": 283, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0671}
{"question": "Solve (253 - 38)", "answer": "The result of (253 - 38) is 215\n\n####215", "a": 253, "b": 38, "operator": "-", "result": 215}
{"question": "Solve (694 - 592)", "answer": "The result of (694 - 592) is 102\n\n####102", "a": 694, "b": 592, "operator": "-", "result": 102}
{"question": "Solve (660 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (660 + 380) is 1040\n\n####1040", "a": 660, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 1040}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 677)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 677) is -90\n\n####-90", "a": 587, "b": 677, "operator": "-", "result": -90}
{"question": "Solve (397 - 928)", "answer": "The result of (397 - 928) is -531\n\n####-531", "a": 397, "b": 928, "operator": "-", "result": -531}
{"question": "Solve (496 * 775)", "answer": "The result of (496 * 775) is 384400\n\n####384400", "a": 496, "b": 775, "operator": "*", "result": 384400}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 211)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 211) is 711\n\n####711", "a": 922, "b": 211, "operator": "-", "result": 711}
{"question": "Solve (325 * 198)", "answer": "The result of (325 * 198) is 64350\n\n####64350", "a": 325, "b": 198, "operator": "*", "result": 64350}
{"question": "Solve (58 + 109)", "answer": "The result of (58 + 109) is 167\n\n####167", "a": 58, "b": 109, "operator": "+", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve (637 / 786)", "answer": "The result of (637 / 786) is 0.8104\n\n####0.8104", "a": 637, "b": 786, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8104}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 589)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 589) is 220286\n\n####220286", "a": 374, "b": 589, "operator": "*", "result": 220286}
{"question": "Solve (691 / 308)", "answer": "The result of (691 / 308) is 2.2435\n\n####2.2435", "a": 691, "b": 308, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2435}
{"question": "Solve (704 / 644)", "answer": "The result of (704 / 644) is 1.0932\n\n####1.0932", "a": 704, "b": 644, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0932}
{"question": "Solve (126 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (126 + 184) is 310\n\n####310", "a": 126, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 310}
{"question": "Solve (13 * 895)", "answer": "The result of (13 * 895) is 11635\n\n####11635", "a": 13, "b": 895, "operator": "*", "result": 11635}
{"question": "Solve (996 * 573)", "answer": "The result of (996 * 573) is 570708\n\n####570708", "a": 996, "b": 573, "operator": "*", "result": 570708}
{"question": "Solve (864 - 98)", "answer": "The result of (864 - 98) is 766\n\n####766", "a": 864, "b": 98, "operator": "-", "result": 766}
{"question": "Solve (927 * 178)", "answer": "The result of (927 * 178) is 165006\n\n####165006", "a": 927, "b": 178, "operator": "*", "result": 165006}
{"question": "Solve (31 * 746)", "answer": "The result of (31 * 746) is 23126\n\n####23126", "a": 31, "b": 746, "operator": "*", "result": 23126}
{"question": "Solve (857 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (857 * 215) is 184255\n\n####184255", "a": 857, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 184255}
{"question": "Solve (730 + 777)", "answer": "The result of (730 + 777) is 1507\n\n####1507", "a": 730, "b": 777, "operator": "+", "result": 1507}
{"question": "Solve (776 / 123)", "answer": "The result of (776 / 123) is 6.3089\n\n####6.3089", "a": 776, "b": 123, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3089}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 664)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 664) is 0.2289\n\n####0.2289", "a": 152, "b": 664, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2289}
{"question": "Solve (821 + 952)", "answer": "The result of (821 + 952) is 1773\n\n####1773", "a": 821, "b": 952, "operator": "+", "result": 1773}
{"question": "Solve (578 - 613)", "answer": "The result of (578 - 613) is -35\n\n####-35", "a": 578, "b": 613, "operator": "-", "result": -35}
{"question": "Solve (832 * 424)", "answer": "The result of (832 * 424) is 352768\n\n####352768", "a": 832, "b": 424, "operator": "*", "result": 352768}
{"question": "Solve (585 * 122)", "answer": "The result of (585 * 122) is 71370\n\n####71370", "a": 585, "b": 122, "operator": "*", "result": 71370}
{"question": "Solve (169 + 550)", "answer": "The result of (169 + 550) is 719\n\n####719", "a": 169, "b": 550, "operator": "+", "result": 719}
{"question": "Solve (2 * 234)", "answer": "The result of (2 * 234) is 468\n\n####468", "a": 2, "b": 234, "operator": "*", "result": 468}
{"question": "Solve (552 + 894)", "answer": "The result of (552 + 894) is 1446\n\n####1446", "a": 552, "b": 894, "operator": "+", "result": 1446}
{"question": "Solve (324 / 25)", "answer": "The result of (324 / 25) is 12.96\n\n####12.96", "a": 324, "b": 25, "operator": "/", "result": 12.96}
{"question": "Solve (286 / 581)", "answer": "The result of (286 / 581) is 0.4923\n\n####0.4923", "a": 286, "b": 581, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4923}
{"question": "Solve (895 + 623)", "answer": "The result of (895 + 623) is 1518\n\n####1518", "a": 895, "b": 623, "operator": "+", "result": 1518}
{"question": "Solve (314 * 308)", "answer": "The result of (314 * 308) is 96712\n\n####96712", "a": 314, "b": 308, "operator": "*", "result": 96712}
{"question": "Solve (335 / 9)", "answer": "The result of (335 / 9) is 37.2222\n\n####37.2222", "a": 335, "b": 9, "operator": "/", "result": 37.2222}
{"question": "Solve (595 - 286)", "answer": "The result of (595 - 286) is 309\n\n####309", "a": 595, "b": 286, "operator": "-", "result": 309}
{"question": "Solve (588 * 226)", "answer": "The result of (588 * 226) is 132888\n\n####132888", "a": 588, "b": 226, "operator": "*", "result": 132888}
{"question": "Solve (116 * 35)", "answer": "The result of (116 * 35) is 4060\n\n####4060", "a": 116, "b": 35, "operator": "*", "result": 4060}
{"question": "Solve (35 * 895)", "answer": "The result of (35 * 895) is 31325\n\n####31325", "a": 35, "b": 895, "operator": "*", "result": 31325}
{"question": "Solve (357 + 645)", "answer": "The result of (357 + 645) is 1002\n\n####1002", "a": 357, "b": 645, "operator": "+", "result": 1002}
{"question": "Solve (373 - 213)", "answer": "The result of (373 - 213) is 160\n\n####160", "a": 373, "b": 213, "operator": "-", "result": 160}
{"question": "Solve (37 + 515)", "answer": "The result of (37 + 515) is 552\n\n####552", "a": 37, "b": 515, "operator": "+", "result": 552}
{"question": "Solve (368 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (368 - 937) is -569\n\n####-569", "a": 368, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -569}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 74)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 74) is 6586\n\n####6586", "a": 89, "b": 74, "operator": "*", "result": 6586}
{"question": "Solve (370 + 343)", "answer": "The result of (370 + 343) is 713\n\n####713", "a": 370, "b": 343, "operator": "+", "result": 713}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 507)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 507) is 38\n\n####38", "a": 545, "b": 507, "operator": "-", "result": 38}
{"question": "Solve (339 * 178)", "answer": "The result of (339 * 178) is 60342\n\n####60342", "a": 339, "b": 178, "operator": "*", "result": 60342}
{"question": "Solve (489 / 398)", "answer": "The result of (489 / 398) is 1.2286\n\n####1.2286", "a": 489, "b": 398, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2286}
{"question": "Solve (421 / 137)", "answer": "The result of (421 / 137) is 3.073\n\n####3.073", "a": 421, "b": 137, "operator": "/", "result": 3.073}
{"question": "Solve (588 * 872)", "answer": "The result of (588 * 872) is 512736\n\n####512736", "a": 588, "b": 872, "operator": "*", "result": 512736}
{"question": "Solve (44 * 937)", "answer": "The result of (44 * 937) is 41228\n\n####41228", "a": 44, "b": 937, "operator": "*", "result": 41228}
{"question": "Solve (69 - 260)", "answer": "The result of (69 - 260) is -191\n\n####-191", "a": 69, "b": 260, "operator": "-", "result": -191}
{"question": "Solve (725 / 458)", "answer": "The result of (725 / 458) is 1.583\n\n####1.583", "a": 725, "b": 458, "operator": "/", "result": 1.583}
{"question": "Solve (36 - 392)", "answer": "The result of (36 - 392) is -356\n\n####-356", "a": 36, "b": 392, "operator": "-", "result": -356}
{"question": "Solve (551 * 995)", "answer": "The result of (551 * 995) is 548245\n\n####548245", "a": 551, "b": 995, "operator": "*", "result": 548245}
{"question": "Solve (429 * 219)", "answer": "The result of (429 * 219) is 93951\n\n####93951", "a": 429, "b": 219, "operator": "*", "result": 93951}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 449) is 166\n\n####166", "a": 615, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": 166}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 574)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 574) is -144\n\n####-144", "a": 430, "b": 574, "operator": "-", "result": -144}
{"question": "Solve (405 * 73)", "answer": "The result of (405 * 73) is 29565\n\n####29565", "a": 405, "b": 73, "operator": "*", "result": 29565}
{"question": "Solve (731 - 652)", "answer": "The result of (731 - 652) is 79\n\n####79", "a": 731, "b": 652, "operator": "-", "result": 79}
{"question": "Solve (127 / 166)", "answer": "The result of (127 / 166) is 0.7651\n\n####0.7651", "a": 127, "b": 166, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7651}
{"question": "Solve (372 / 932)", "answer": "The result of (372 / 932) is 0.3991\n\n####0.3991", "a": 372, "b": 932, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3991}
{"question": "Solve (30 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (30 * 932) is 27960\n\n####27960", "a": 30, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 27960}
{"question": "Solve (408 * 809)", "answer": "The result of (408 * 809) is 330072\n\n####330072", "a": 408, "b": 809, "operator": "*", "result": 330072}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 217)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 217) is 4.2903\n\n####4.2903", "a": 931, "b": 217, "operator": "/", "result": 4.2903}
{"question": "Solve (986 * 105)", "answer": "The result of (986 * 105) is 103530\n\n####103530", "a": 986, "b": 105, "operator": "*", "result": 103530}
{"question": "Solve (645 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (645 - 846) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 645, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (743 * 276)", "answer": "The result of (743 * 276) is 205068\n\n####205068", "a": 743, "b": 276, "operator": "*", "result": 205068}
{"question": "Solve (354 - 834)", "answer": "The result of (354 - 834) is -480\n\n####-480", "a": 354, "b": 834, "operator": "-", "result": -480}
{"question": "Solve (981 * 72)", "answer": "The result of (981 * 72) is 70632\n\n####70632", "a": 981, "b": 72, "operator": "*", "result": 70632}
{"question": "Solve (626 - 482)", "answer": "The result of (626 - 482) is 144\n\n####144", "a": 626, "b": 482, "operator": "-", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve (216 * 580)", "answer": "The result of (216 * 580) is 125280\n\n####125280", "a": 216, "b": 580, "operator": "*", "result": 125280}
{"question": "Solve (359 * 34)", "answer": "The result of (359 * 34) is 12206\n\n####12206", "a": 359, "b": 34, "operator": "*", "result": 12206}
{"question": "Solve (175 * 654)", "answer": "The result of (175 * 654) is 114450\n\n####114450", "a": 175, "b": 654, "operator": "*", "result": 114450}
{"question": "Solve (739 / 193)", "answer": "The result of (739 / 193) is 3.829\n\n####3.829", "a": 739, "b": 193, "operator": "/", "result": 3.829}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 985)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 985) is -945\n\n####-945", "a": 40, "b": 985, "operator": "-", "result": -945}
{"question": "Solve (994 + 580)", "answer": "The result of (994 + 580) is 1574\n\n####1574", "a": 994, "b": 580, "operator": "+", "result": 1574}
{"question": "Solve (533 - 683)", "answer": "The result of (533 - 683) is -150\n\n####-150", "a": 533, "b": 683, "operator": "-", "result": -150}
{"question": "Solve (608 + 708)", "answer": "The result of (608 + 708) is 1316\n\n####1316", "a": 608, "b": 708, "operator": "+", "result": 1316}
{"question": "Solve (39 * 704)", "answer": "The result of (39 * 704) is 27456\n\n####27456", "a": 39, "b": 704, "operator": "*", "result": 27456}
{"question": "Solve (984 / 319)", "answer": "The result of (984 / 319) is 3.0846\n\n####3.0846", "a": 984, "b": 319, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0846}
{"question": "Solve (182 + 740)", "answer": "The result of (182 + 740) is 922\n\n####922", "a": 182, "b": 740, "operator": "+", "result": 922}
{"question": "Solve (88 * 272)", "answer": "The result of (88 * 272) is 23936\n\n####23936", "a": 88, "b": 272, "operator": "*", "result": 23936}
{"question": "Solve (863 * 905)", "answer": "The result of (863 * 905) is 781015\n\n####781015", "a": 863, "b": 905, "operator": "*", "result": 781015}
{"question": "Solve (963 + 918)", "answer": "The result of (963 + 918) is 1881\n\n####1881", "a": 963, "b": 918, "operator": "+", "result": 1881}
{"question": "Solve (35 - 727)", "answer": "The result of (35 - 727) is -692\n\n####-692", "a": 35, "b": 727, "operator": "-", "result": -692}
{"question": "Solve (275 + 636)", "answer": "The result of (275 + 636) is 911\n\n####911", "a": 275, "b": 636, "operator": "+", "result": 911}
{"question": "Solve (184 + 628)", "answer": "The result of (184 + 628) is 812\n\n####812", "a": 184, "b": 628, "operator": "+", "result": 812}
{"question": "Solve (986 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (986 / 815) is 1.2098\n\n####1.2098", "a": 986, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2098}
{"question": "Solve (29 - 316)", "answer": "The result of (29 - 316) is -287\n\n####-287", "a": 29, "b": 316, "operator": "-", "result": -287}
{"question": "Solve (874 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (874 - 918) is -44\n\n####-44", "a": 874, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -44}
{"question": "Solve (2 + 697)", "answer": "The result of (2 + 697) is 699\n\n####699", "a": 2, "b": 697, "operator": "+", "result": 699}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 609)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 609) is 887\n\n####887", "a": 278, "b": 609, "operator": "+", "result": 887}
{"question": "Solve (662 * 989)", "answer": "The result of (662 * 989) is 654718\n\n####654718", "a": 662, "b": 989, "operator": "*", "result": 654718}
{"question": "Solve (411 * 945)", "answer": "The result of (411 * 945) is 388395\n\n####388395", "a": 411, "b": 945, "operator": "*", "result": 388395}
{"question": "Solve (378 + 758)", "answer": "The result of (378 + 758) is 1136\n\n####1136", "a": 378, "b": 758, "operator": "+", "result": 1136}
{"question": "Solve (746 * 2)", "answer": "The result of (746 * 2) is 1492\n\n####1492", "a": 746, "b": 2, "operator": "*", "result": 1492}
{"question": "Solve (41 / 712)", "answer": "The result of (41 / 712) is 0.0576\n\n####0.0576", "a": 41, "b": 712, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0576}
{"question": "Solve (103 - 376)", "answer": "The result of (103 - 376) is -273\n\n####-273", "a": 103, "b": 376, "operator": "-", "result": -273}
{"question": "Solve (666 - 208)", "answer": "The result of (666 - 208) is 458\n\n####458", "a": 666, "b": 208, "operator": "-", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 874)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 874) is 804080\n\n####804080", "a": 920, "b": 874, "operator": "*", "result": 804080}
{"question": "Solve (557 + 719)", "answer": "The result of (557 + 719) is 1276\n\n####1276", "a": 557, "b": 719, "operator": "+", "result": 1276}
{"question": "Solve (28 - 246)", "answer": "The result of (28 - 246) is -218\n\n####-218", "a": 28, "b": 246, "operator": "-", "result": -218}
{"question": "Solve (492 + 457)", "answer": "The result of (492 + 457) is 949\n\n####949", "a": 492, "b": 457, "operator": "+", "result": 949}
{"question": "Solve (62 / 386)", "answer": "The result of (62 / 386) is 0.1606\n\n####0.1606", "a": 62, "b": 386, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1606}
{"question": "Solve (825 * 503)", "answer": "The result of (825 * 503) is 414975\n\n####414975", "a": 825, "b": 503, "operator": "*", "result": 414975}
{"question": "Solve (932 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (932 + 259) is 1191\n\n####1191", "a": 932, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 1191}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 62)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 62) is 14.5806\n\n####14.5806", "a": 904, "b": 62, "operator": "/", "result": 14.5806}
{"question": "Solve (778 * 202)", "answer": "The result of (778 * 202) is 157156\n\n####157156", "a": 778, "b": 202, "operator": "*", "result": 157156}
{"question": "Solve (156 * 298)", "answer": "The result of (156 * 298) is 46488\n\n####46488", "a": 156, "b": 298, "operator": "*", "result": 46488}
{"question": "Solve (211 / 179)", "answer": "The result of (211 / 179) is 1.1788\n\n####1.1788", "a": 211, "b": 179, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1788}
{"question": "Solve (47 * 174)", "answer": "The result of (47 * 174) is 8178\n\n####8178", "a": 47, "b": 174, "operator": "*", "result": 8178}
{"question": "Solve (664 / 264)", "answer": "The result of (664 / 264) is 2.5152\n\n####2.5152", "a": 664, "b": 264, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5152}
{"question": "Solve (327 / 284)", "answer": "The result of (327 / 284) is 1.1514\n\n####1.1514", "a": 327, "b": 284, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1514}
{"question": "Solve (296 * 335)", "answer": "The result of (296 * 335) is 99160\n\n####99160", "a": 296, "b": 335, "operator": "*", "result": 99160}
{"question": "Solve (464 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (464 - 162) is 302\n\n####302", "a": 464, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 302}
{"question": "Solve (868 * 222)", "answer": "The result of (868 * 222) is 192696\n\n####192696", "a": 868, "b": 222, "operator": "*", "result": 192696}
{"question": "Solve (585 / 640)", "answer": "The result of (585 / 640) is 0.9141\n\n####0.9141", "a": 585, "b": 640, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9141}
{"question": "Solve (615 * 349)", "answer": "The result of (615 * 349) is 214635\n\n####214635", "a": 615, "b": 349, "operator": "*", "result": 214635}
{"question": "Solve (786 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (786 - 945) is -159\n\n####-159", "a": 786, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -159}
{"question": "Solve (283 * 929)", "answer": "The result of (283 * 929) is 262907\n\n####262907", "a": 283, "b": 929, "operator": "*", "result": 262907}
{"question": "Solve (342 + 58)", "answer": "The result of (342 + 58) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 342, "b": 58, "operator": "+", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (526 * 194)", "answer": "The result of (526 * 194) is 102044\n\n####102044", "a": 526, "b": 194, "operator": "*", "result": 102044}
{"question": "Solve (544 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (544 - 579) is -35\n\n####-35", "a": 544, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": -35}
{"question": "Solve (439 / 581)", "answer": "The result of (439 / 581) is 0.7556\n\n####0.7556", "a": 439, "b": 581, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7556}
{"question": "Solve (51 / 27)", "answer": "The result of (51 / 27) is 1.8889\n\n####1.8889", "a": 51, "b": 27, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8889}
{"question": "Solve (616 - 3)", "answer": "The result of (616 - 3) is 613\n\n####613", "a": 616, "b": 3, "operator": "-", "result": 613}
{"question": "Solve (834 * 859)", "answer": "The result of (834 * 859) is 716406\n\n####716406", "a": 834, "b": 859, "operator": "*", "result": 716406}
{"question": "Solve (527 / 603)", "answer": "The result of (527 / 603) is 0.874\n\n####0.874", "a": 527, "b": 603, "operator": "/", "result": 0.874}
{"question": "Solve (24 / 354)", "answer": "The result of (24 / 354) is 0.0678\n\n####0.0678", "a": 24, "b": 354, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0678}
{"question": "Solve (415 - 323)", "answer": "The result of (415 - 323) is 92\n\n####92", "a": 415, "b": 323, "operator": "-", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve (226 - 155)", "answer": "The result of (226 - 155) is 71\n\n####71", "a": 226, "b": 155, "operator": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve (93 * 111)", "answer": "The result of (93 * 111) is 10323\n\n####10323", "a": 93, "b": 111, "operator": "*", "result": 10323}
{"question": "Solve (968 / 152)", "answer": "The result of (968 / 152) is 6.3684\n\n####6.3684", "a": 968, "b": 152, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3684}
{"question": "Solve (960 / 117)", "answer": "The result of (960 / 117) is 8.2051\n\n####8.2051", "a": 960, "b": 117, "operator": "/", "result": 8.2051}
{"question": "Solve (474 / 464)", "answer": "The result of (474 / 464) is 1.0216\n\n####1.0216", "a": 474, "b": 464, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0216}
{"question": "Solve (489 * 843)", "answer": "The result of (489 * 843) is 412227\n\n####412227", "a": 489, "b": 843, "operator": "*", "result": 412227}
{"question": "Solve (529 - 326)", "answer": "The result of (529 - 326) is 203\n\n####203", "a": 529, "b": 326, "operator": "-", "result": 203}
{"question": "Solve (430 / 940)", "answer": "The result of (430 / 940) is 0.4574\n\n####0.4574", "a": 430, "b": 940, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4574}
{"question": "Solve (155 * 144)", "answer": "The result of (155 * 144) is 22320\n\n####22320", "a": 155, "b": 144, "operator": "*", "result": 22320}
{"question": "Solve (748 * 25)", "answer": "The result of (748 * 25) is 18700\n\n####18700", "a": 748, "b": 25, "operator": "*", "result": 18700}
{"question": "Solve (969 / 193)", "answer": "The result of (969 / 193) is 5.0207\n\n####5.0207", "a": 969, "b": 193, "operator": "/", "result": 5.0207}
{"question": "Solve (420 / 479)", "answer": "The result of (420 / 479) is 0.8768\n\n####0.8768", "a": 420, "b": 479, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8768}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 825) is 97\n\n####97", "a": 922, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": 97}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 475)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 475) is 285950\n\n####285950", "a": 602, "b": 475, "operator": "*", "result": 285950}
{"question": "Solve (197 / 301)", "answer": "The result of (197 / 301) is 0.6545\n\n####0.6545", "a": 197, "b": 301, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6545}
{"question": "Solve (730 + 847)", "answer": "The result of (730 + 847) is 1577\n\n####1577", "a": 730, "b": 847, "operator": "+", "result": 1577}
{"question": "Solve (308 * 696)", "answer": "The result of (308 * 696) is 214368\n\n####214368", "a": 308, "b": 696, "operator": "*", "result": 214368}
{"question": "Solve (683 / 668)", "answer": "The result of (683 / 668) is 1.0225\n\n####1.0225", "a": 683, "b": 668, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0225}
{"question": "Solve (64 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (64 / 240) is 0.2667\n\n####0.2667", "a": 64, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2667}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 460)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 460) is 2.1087\n\n####2.1087", "a": 970, "b": 460, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1087}
{"question": "Solve (961 / 156)", "answer": "The result of (961 / 156) is 6.1603\n\n####6.1603", "a": 961, "b": 156, "operator": "/", "result": 6.1603}
{"question": "Solve (899 / 824)", "answer": "The result of (899 / 824) is 1.091\n\n####1.091", "a": 899, "b": 824, "operator": "/", "result": 1.091}
{"question": "Solve (685 / 866)", "answer": "The result of (685 / 866) is 0.791\n\n####0.791", "a": 685, "b": 866, "operator": "/", "result": 0.791}
{"question": "Solve (144 / 761)", "answer": "The result of (144 / 761) is 0.1892\n\n####0.1892", "a": 144, "b": 761, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1892}
{"question": "Solve (978 + 746)", "answer": "The result of (978 + 746) is 1724\n\n####1724", "a": 978, "b": 746, "operator": "+", "result": 1724}
{"question": "Solve (515 / 325)", "answer": "The result of (515 / 325) is 1.5846\n\n####1.5846", "a": 515, "b": 325, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5846}
{"question": "Solve (843 / 826)", "answer": "The result of (843 / 826) is 1.0206\n\n####1.0206", "a": 843, "b": 826, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0206}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 835)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 835) is 1.1425\n\n####1.1425", "a": 954, "b": 835, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1425}
{"question": "Solve (665 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (665 - 245) is 420\n\n####420", "a": 665, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 420}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 157)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 157) is 1.8599\n\n####1.8599", "a": 292, "b": 157, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8599}
{"question": "Solve (141 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (141 - 992) is -851\n\n####-851", "a": 141, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -851}
{"question": "Solve (500 / 295)", "answer": "The result of (500 / 295) is 1.6949\n\n####1.6949", "a": 500, "b": 295, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6949}
{"question": "Solve (188 - 575)", "answer": "The result of (188 - 575) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 188, "b": 575, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (524 + 465)", "answer": "The result of (524 + 465) is 989\n\n####989", "a": 524, "b": 465, "operator": "+", "result": 989}
{"question": "Solve (398 / 613)", "answer": "The result of (398 / 613) is 0.6493\n\n####0.6493", "a": 398, "b": 613, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6493}
{"question": "Solve (160 / 97)", "answer": "The result of (160 / 97) is 1.6495\n\n####1.6495", "a": 160, "b": 97, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6495}
{"question": "Solve (631 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (631 - 283) is 348\n\n####348", "a": 631, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 348}
{"question": "Solve (413 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (413 - 27) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 413, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (709 + 757)", "answer": "The result of (709 + 757) is 1466\n\n####1466", "a": 709, "b": 757, "operator": "+", "result": 1466}
{"question": "Solve (453 + 651)", "answer": "The result of (453 + 651) is 1104\n\n####1104", "a": 453, "b": 651, "operator": "+", "result": 1104}
{"question": "Solve (12 / 460)", "answer": "The result of (12 / 460) is 0.0261\n\n####0.0261", "a": 12, "b": 460, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0261}
{"question": "Solve (640 + 835)", "answer": "The result of (640 + 835) is 1475\n\n####1475", "a": 640, "b": 835, "operator": "+", "result": 1475}
{"question": "Solve (795 * 709)", "answer": "The result of (795 * 709) is 563655\n\n####563655", "a": 795, "b": 709, "operator": "*", "result": 563655}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 427)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 427) is 1313\n\n####1313", "a": 886, "b": 427, "operator": "+", "result": 1313}
{"question": "Solve (855 * 878)", "answer": "The result of (855 * 878) is 750690\n\n####750690", "a": 855, "b": 878, "operator": "*", "result": 750690}
{"question": "Solve (857 - 502)", "answer": "The result of (857 - 502) is 355\n\n####355", "a": 857, "b": 502, "operator": "-", "result": 355}
{"question": "Solve (482 - 883)", "answer": "The result of (482 - 883) is -401\n\n####-401", "a": 482, "b": 883, "operator": "-", "result": -401}
{"question": "Solve (725 * 650)", "answer": "The result of (725 * 650) is 471250\n\n####471250", "a": 725, "b": 650, "operator": "*", "result": 471250}
{"question": "Solve (745 / 72)", "answer": "The result of (745 / 72) is 10.3472\n\n####10.3472", "a": 745, "b": 72, "operator": "/", "result": 10.3472}
{"question": "Solve (789 + 427)", "answer": "The result of (789 + 427) is 1216\n\n####1216", "a": 789, "b": 427, "operator": "+", "result": 1216}
{"question": "Solve (398 - 964)", "answer": "The result of (398 - 964) is -566\n\n####-566", "a": 398, "b": 964, "operator": "-", "result": -566}
{"question": "Solve (200 * 491)", "answer": "The result of (200 * 491) is 98200\n\n####98200", "a": 200, "b": 491, "operator": "*", "result": 98200}
{"question": "Solve (843 * 922)", "answer": "The result of (843 * 922) is 777246\n\n####777246", "a": 843, "b": 922, "operator": "*", "result": 777246}
{"question": "Solve (399 / 639)", "answer": "The result of (399 / 639) is 0.6244\n\n####0.6244", "a": 399, "b": 639, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6244}
{"question": "Solve (779 / 574)", "answer": "The result of (779 / 574) is 1.3571\n\n####1.3571", "a": 779, "b": 574, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3571}
{"question": "Solve (205 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (205 / 984) is 0.2083\n\n####0.2083", "a": 205, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2083}
{"question": "Solve (556 - 49)", "answer": "The result of (556 - 49) is 507\n\n####507", "a": 556, "b": 49, "operator": "-", "result": 507}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 502)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 502) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 436, "b": 502, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 547)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 547) is 247244\n\n####247244", "a": 452, "b": 547, "operator": "*", "result": 247244}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 485) is -120\n\n####-120", "a": 365, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 350)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 350) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 130, "b": 350, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (131 * 928)", "answer": "The result of (131 * 928) is 121568\n\n####121568", "a": 131, "b": 928, "operator": "*", "result": 121568}
{"question": "Solve (661 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (661 / 852) is 0.7758\n\n####0.7758", "a": 661, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7758}
{"question": "Solve (687 - 32)", "answer": "The result of (687 - 32) is 655\n\n####655", "a": 687, "b": 32, "operator": "-", "result": 655}
{"question": "Solve (805 * 643)", "answer": "The result of (805 * 643) is 517615\n\n####517615", "a": 805, "b": 643, "operator": "*", "result": 517615}
{"question": "Solve (862 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (862 - 701) is 161\n\n####161", "a": 862, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": 161}
{"question": "Solve (393 + 782)", "answer": "The result of (393 + 782) is 1175\n\n####1175", "a": 393, "b": 782, "operator": "+", "result": 1175}
{"question": "Solve (109 - 382)", "answer": "The result of (109 - 382) is -273\n\n####-273", "a": 109, "b": 382, "operator": "-", "result": -273}
{"question": "Solve (677 * 43)", "answer": "The result of (677 * 43) is 29111\n\n####29111", "a": 677, "b": 43, "operator": "*", "result": 29111}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 110)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 110) is 977\n\n####977", "a": 867, "b": 110, "operator": "+", "result": 977}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 911)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 911) is -78\n\n####-78", "a": 833, "b": 911, "operator": "-", "result": -78}
{"question": "Solve (576 - 588)", "answer": "The result of (576 - 588) is -12\n\n####-12", "a": 576, "b": 588, "operator": "-", "result": -12}
{"question": "Solve (156 / 980)", "answer": "The result of (156 / 980) is 0.1592\n\n####0.1592", "a": 156, "b": 980, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1592}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 725)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 725) is 379900\n\n####379900", "a": 524, "b": 725, "operator": "*", "result": 379900}
{"question": "Solve (541 * 943)", "answer": "The result of (541 * 943) is 510163\n\n####510163", "a": 541, "b": 943, "operator": "*", "result": 510163}
{"question": "Solve (59 + 169)", "answer": "The result of (59 + 169) is 228\n\n####228", "a": 59, "b": 169, "operator": "+", "result": 228}
{"question": "Solve (33 * 711)", "answer": "The result of (33 * 711) is 23463\n\n####23463", "a": 33, "b": 711, "operator": "*", "result": 23463}
{"question": "Solve (918 * 656)", "answer": "The result of (918 * 656) is 602208\n\n####602208", "a": 918, "b": 656, "operator": "*", "result": 602208}
{"question": "Solve (328 * 874)", "answer": "The result of (328 * 874) is 286672\n\n####286672", "a": 328, "b": 874, "operator": "*", "result": 286672}
{"question": "Solve (857 / 286)", "answer": "The result of (857 / 286) is 2.9965\n\n####2.9965", "a": 857, "b": 286, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9965}
{"question": "Solve (355 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (355 + 184) is 539\n\n####539", "a": 355, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 539}
{"question": "Solve (248 + 890)", "answer": "The result of (248 + 890) is 1138\n\n####1138", "a": 248, "b": 890, "operator": "+", "result": 1138}
{"question": "Solve (220 / 72)", "answer": "The result of (220 / 72) is 3.0556\n\n####3.0556", "a": 220, "b": 72, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0556}
{"question": "Solve (203 + 38)", "answer": "The result of (203 + 38) is 241\n\n####241", "a": 203, "b": 38, "operator": "+", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve (584 - 993)", "answer": "The result of (584 - 993) is -409\n\n####-409", "a": 584, "b": 993, "operator": "-", "result": -409}
{"question": "Solve (437 / 394)", "answer": "The result of (437 / 394) is 1.1091\n\n####1.1091", "a": 437, "b": 394, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1091}
{"question": "Solve (361 + 685)", "answer": "The result of (361 + 685) is 1046\n\n####1046", "a": 361, "b": 685, "operator": "+", "result": 1046}
{"question": "Solve (202 - 968)", "answer": "The result of (202 - 968) is -766\n\n####-766", "a": 202, "b": 968, "operator": "-", "result": -766}
{"question": "Solve (466 / 326)", "answer": "The result of (466 / 326) is 1.4294\n\n####1.4294", "a": 466, "b": 326, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4294}
{"question": "Solve (777 * 427)", "answer": "The result of (777 * 427) is 331779\n\n####331779", "a": 777, "b": 427, "operator": "*", "result": 331779}
{"question": "Solve (218 / 212)", "answer": "The result of (218 / 212) is 1.0283\n\n####1.0283", "a": 218, "b": 212, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0283}
{"question": "Solve (868 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (868 / 236) is 3.678\n\n####3.678", "a": 868, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 3.678}
{"question": "Solve (630 * 726)", "answer": "The result of (630 * 726) is 457380\n\n####457380", "a": 630, "b": 726, "operator": "*", "result": 457380}
{"question": "Solve (162 - 414)", "answer": "The result of (162 - 414) is -252\n\n####-252", "a": 162, "b": 414, "operator": "-", "result": -252}
{"question": "Solve (154 * 937)", "answer": "The result of (154 * 937) is 144298\n\n####144298", "a": 154, "b": 937, "operator": "*", "result": 144298}
{"question": "Solve (352 - 297)", "answer": "The result of (352 - 297) is 55\n\n####55", "a": 352, "b": 297, "operator": "-", "result": 55}
{"question": "Solve (900 + 553)", "answer": "The result of (900 + 553) is 1453\n\n####1453", "a": 900, "b": 553, "operator": "+", "result": 1453}
{"question": "Solve (136 * 850)", "answer": "The result of (136 * 850) is 115600\n\n####115600", "a": 136, "b": 850, "operator": "*", "result": 115600}
{"question": "Solve (818 + 905)", "answer": "The result of (818 + 905) is 1723\n\n####1723", "a": 818, "b": 905, "operator": "+", "result": 1723}
{"question": "Solve (577 / 221)", "answer": "The result of (577 / 221) is 2.6109\n\n####2.6109", "a": 577, "b": 221, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6109}
{"question": "Solve (636 + 612)", "answer": "The result of (636 + 612) is 1248\n\n####1248", "a": 636, "b": 612, "operator": "+", "result": 1248}
{"question": "Solve (546 / 326)", "answer": "The result of (546 / 326) is 1.6748\n\n####1.6748", "a": 546, "b": 326, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6748}
{"question": "Solve (568 * 8)", "answer": "The result of (568 * 8) is 4544\n\n####4544", "a": 568, "b": 8, "operator": "*", "result": 4544}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 835)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 835) is 502670\n\n####502670", "a": 602, "b": 835, "operator": "*", "result": 502670}
{"question": "Solve (353 - 442)", "answer": "The result of (353 - 442) is -89\n\n####-89", "a": 353, "b": 442, "operator": "-", "result": -89}
{"question": "Solve (97 / 497)", "answer": "The result of (97 / 497) is 0.1952\n\n####0.1952", "a": 97, "b": 497, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1952}
{"question": "Solve (281 + 391)", "answer": "The result of (281 + 391) is 672\n\n####672", "a": 281, "b": 391, "operator": "+", "result": 672}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 261)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 261) is 2.7663\n\n####2.7663", "a": 722, "b": 261, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7663}
{"question": "Solve (8 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (8 * 958) is 7664\n\n####7664", "a": 8, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 7664}
{"question": "Solve (601 / 972)", "answer": "The result of (601 / 972) is 0.6183\n\n####0.6183", "a": 601, "b": 972, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6183}
{"question": "Solve (879 / 468)", "answer": "The result of (879 / 468) is 1.8782\n\n####1.8782", "a": 879, "b": 468, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8782}
{"question": "Solve (742 - 983)", "answer": "The result of (742 - 983) is -241\n\n####-241", "a": 742, "b": 983, "operator": "-", "result": -241}
{"question": "Solve (664 / 536)", "answer": "The result of (664 / 536) is 1.2388\n\n####1.2388", "a": 664, "b": 536, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2388}
{"question": "Solve (368 * 677)", "answer": "The result of (368 * 677) is 249136\n\n####249136", "a": 368, "b": 677, "operator": "*", "result": 249136}
{"question": "Solve (817 - 468)", "answer": "The result of (817 - 468) is 349\n\n####349", "a": 817, "b": 468, "operator": "-", "result": 349}
{"question": "Solve (871 - 683)", "answer": "The result of (871 - 683) is 188\n\n####188", "a": 871, "b": 683, "operator": "-", "result": 188}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 624)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 624) is -315\n\n####-315", "a": 309, "b": 624, "operator": "-", "result": -315}
{"question": "Solve (744 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (744 * 596) is 443424\n\n####443424", "a": 744, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 443424}
{"question": "Solve (992 * 836)", "answer": "The result of (992 * 836) is 829312\n\n####829312", "a": 992, "b": 836, "operator": "*", "result": 829312}
{"question": "Solve (455 - 329)", "answer": "The result of (455 - 329) is 126\n\n####126", "a": 455, "b": 329, "operator": "-", "result": 126}
{"question": "Solve (865 / 522)", "answer": "The result of (865 / 522) is 1.6571\n\n####1.6571", "a": 865, "b": 522, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6571}
{"question": "Solve (200 - 717)", "answer": "The result of (200 - 717) is -517\n\n####-517", "a": 200, "b": 717, "operator": "-", "result": -517}
{"question": "Solve (230 + 159)", "answer": "The result of (230 + 159) is 389\n\n####389", "a": 230, "b": 159, "operator": "+", "result": 389}
{"question": "Solve (518 - 923)", "answer": "The result of (518 - 923) is -405\n\n####-405", "a": 518, "b": 923, "operator": "-", "result": -405}
{"question": "Solve (822 - 568)", "answer": "The result of (822 - 568) is 254\n\n####254", "a": 822, "b": 568, "operator": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve (266 - 842)", "answer": "The result of (266 - 842) is -576\n\n####-576", "a": 266, "b": 842, "operator": "-", "result": -576}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 340)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 340) is 611\n\n####611", "a": 271, "b": 340, "operator": "+", "result": 611}
{"question": "Solve (305 - 264)", "answer": "The result of (305 - 264) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 305, "b": 264, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (276 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (276 + 31) is 307\n\n####307", "a": 276, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve (477 * 126)", "answer": "The result of (477 * 126) is 60102\n\n####60102", "a": 477, "b": 126, "operator": "*", "result": 60102}
{"question": "Solve (7 / 261)", "answer": "The result of (7 / 261) is 0.0268\n\n####0.0268", "a": 7, "b": 261, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0268}
{"question": "Solve (222 * 120)", "answer": "The result of (222 * 120) is 26640\n\n####26640", "a": 222, "b": 120, "operator": "*", "result": 26640}
{"question": "Solve (404 * 976)", "answer": "The result of (404 * 976) is 394304\n\n####394304", "a": 404, "b": 976, "operator": "*", "result": 394304}
{"question": "Solve (251 + 46)", "answer": "The result of (251 + 46) is 297\n\n####297", "a": 251, "b": 46, "operator": "+", "result": 297}
{"question": "Solve (370 - 990)", "answer": "The result of (370 - 990) is -620\n\n####-620", "a": 370, "b": 990, "operator": "-", "result": -620}
{"question": "Solve (210 - 488)", "answer": "The result of (210 - 488) is -278\n\n####-278", "a": 210, "b": 488, "operator": "-", "result": -278}
{"question": "Solve (743 * 194)", "answer": "The result of (743 * 194) is 144142\n\n####144142", "a": 743, "b": 194, "operator": "*", "result": 144142}
{"question": "Solve (253 / 877)", "answer": "The result of (253 / 877) is 0.2885\n\n####0.2885", "a": 253, "b": 877, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2885}
{"question": "Solve (464 - 333)", "answer": "The result of (464 - 333) is 131\n\n####131", "a": 464, "b": 333, "operator": "-", "result": 131}
{"question": "Solve (932 + 580)", "answer": "The result of (932 + 580) is 1512\n\n####1512", "a": 932, "b": 580, "operator": "+", "result": 1512}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 857)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 857) is 123408\n\n####123408", "a": 144, "b": 857, "operator": "*", "result": 123408}
{"question": "Solve (804 * 717)", "answer": "The result of (804 * 717) is 576468\n\n####576468", "a": 804, "b": 717, "operator": "*", "result": 576468}
{"question": "Solve (643 - 30)", "answer": "The result of (643 - 30) is 613\n\n####613", "a": 643, "b": 30, "operator": "-", "result": 613}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 115)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 115) is 60835\n\n####60835", "a": 529, "b": 115, "operator": "*", "result": 60835}
{"question": "Solve (139 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (139 + 245) is 384\n\n####384", "a": 139, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 384}
{"question": "Solve (72 * 623)", "answer": "The result of (72 * 623) is 44856\n\n####44856", "a": 72, "b": 623, "operator": "*", "result": 44856}
{"question": "Solve (218 + 586)", "answer": "The result of (218 + 586) is 804\n\n####804", "a": 218, "b": 586, "operator": "+", "result": 804}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 122)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 122) is -70\n\n####-70", "a": 52, "b": 122, "operator": "-", "result": -70}
{"question": "Solve (114 * 972)", "answer": "The result of (114 * 972) is 110808\n\n####110808", "a": 114, "b": 972, "operator": "*", "result": 110808}
{"question": "Solve (609 * 80)", "answer": "The result of (609 * 80) is 48720\n\n####48720", "a": 609, "b": 80, "operator": "*", "result": 48720}
{"question": "Solve (284 * 118)", "answer": "The result of (284 * 118) is 33512\n\n####33512", "a": 284, "b": 118, "operator": "*", "result": 33512}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 144) is 0.0694\n\n####0.0694", "a": 10, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0694}
{"question": "Solve (317 + 422)", "answer": "The result of (317 + 422) is 739\n\n####739", "a": 317, "b": 422, "operator": "+", "result": 739}
{"question": "Solve (983 / 564)", "answer": "The result of (983 / 564) is 1.7429\n\n####1.7429", "a": 983, "b": 564, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7429}
{"question": "Solve (559 * 52)", "answer": "The result of (559 * 52) is 29068\n\n####29068", "a": 559, "b": 52, "operator": "*", "result": 29068}
{"question": "Solve (533 * 237)", "answer": "The result of (533 * 237) is 126321\n\n####126321", "a": 533, "b": 237, "operator": "*", "result": 126321}
{"question": "Solve (834 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (834 - 408) is 426\n\n####426", "a": 834, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 426}
{"question": "Solve (626 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (626 / 43) is 14.5581\n\n####14.5581", "a": 626, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 14.5581}
{"question": "Solve (557 * 917)", "answer": "The result of (557 * 917) is 510769\n\n####510769", "a": 557, "b": 917, "operator": "*", "result": 510769}
{"question": "Solve (610 + 461)", "answer": "The result of (610 + 461) is 1071\n\n####1071", "a": 610, "b": 461, "operator": "+", "result": 1071}
{"question": "Solve (321 - 379)", "answer": "The result of (321 - 379) is -58\n\n####-58", "a": 321, "b": 379, "operator": "-", "result": -58}
{"question": "Solve (313 * 325)", "answer": "The result of (313 * 325) is 101725\n\n####101725", "a": 313, "b": 325, "operator": "*", "result": 101725}
{"question": "Solve (106 / 50)", "answer": "The result of (106 / 50) is 2.12\n\n####2.12", "a": 106, "b": 50, "operator": "/", "result": 2.12}
{"question": "Solve (890 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (890 - 849) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 890, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (916 + 41)", "answer": "The result of (916 + 41) is 957\n\n####957", "a": 916, "b": 41, "operator": "+", "result": 957}
{"question": "Solve (386 / 369)", "answer": "The result of (386 / 369) is 1.0461\n\n####1.0461", "a": 386, "b": 369, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0461}
{"question": "Solve (413 - 625)", "answer": "The result of (413 - 625) is -212\n\n####-212", "a": 413, "b": 625, "operator": "-", "result": -212}
{"question": "Solve (876 - 488)", "answer": "The result of (876 - 488) is 388\n\n####388", "a": 876, "b": 488, "operator": "-", "result": 388}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 167)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 167) is 1.8323\n\n####1.8323", "a": 306, "b": 167, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8323}
{"question": "Solve (990 - 448)", "answer": "The result of (990 - 448) is 542\n\n####542", "a": 990, "b": 448, "operator": "-", "result": 542}
{"question": "Solve (651 - 812)", "answer": "The result of (651 - 812) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 651, "b": 812, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (111 + 316)", "answer": "The result of (111 + 316) is 427\n\n####427", "a": 111, "b": 316, "operator": "+", "result": 427}
{"question": "Solve (128 * 8)", "answer": "The result of (128 * 8) is 1024\n\n####1024", "a": 128, "b": 8, "operator": "*", "result": 1024}
{"question": "Solve (830 + 737)", "answer": "The result of (830 + 737) is 1567\n\n####1567", "a": 830, "b": 737, "operator": "+", "result": 1567}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 254)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 254) is 159004\n\n####159004", "a": 626, "b": 254, "operator": "*", "result": 159004}
{"question": "Solve (392 * 890)", "answer": "The result of (392 * 890) is 348880\n\n####348880", "a": 392, "b": 890, "operator": "*", "result": 348880}
{"question": "Solve (764 - 134)", "answer": "The result of (764 - 134) is 630\n\n####630", "a": 764, "b": 134, "operator": "-", "result": 630}
{"question": "Solve (87 / 179)", "answer": "The result of (87 / 179) is 0.486\n\n####0.486", "a": 87, "b": 179, "operator": "/", "result": 0.486}
{"question": "Solve (508 / 894)", "answer": "The result of (508 / 894) is 0.5682\n\n####0.5682", "a": 508, "b": 894, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5682}
{"question": "Solve (94 + 17)", "answer": "The result of (94 + 17) is 111\n\n####111", "a": 94, "b": 17, "operator": "+", "result": 111}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 27)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 27) is 20.0741\n\n####20.0741", "a": 542, "b": 27, "operator": "/", "result": 20.0741}
{"question": "Solve (144 - 531)", "answer": "The result of (144 - 531) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 144, "b": 531, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (432 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (432 / 560) is 0.7714\n\n####0.7714", "a": 432, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7714}
{"question": "Solve (74 / 583)", "answer": "The result of (74 / 583) is 0.1269\n\n####0.1269", "a": 74, "b": 583, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1269}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 154)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 154) is 787\n\n####787", "a": 941, "b": 154, "operator": "-", "result": 787}
{"question": "Solve (704 + 926)", "answer": "The result of (704 + 926) is 1630\n\n####1630", "a": 704, "b": 926, "operator": "+", "result": 1630}
{"question": "Solve (965 / 223)", "answer": "The result of (965 / 223) is 4.3274\n\n####4.3274", "a": 965, "b": 223, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3274}
{"question": "Solve (661 - 455)", "answer": "The result of (661 - 455) is 206\n\n####206", "a": 661, "b": 455, "operator": "-", "result": 206}
{"question": "Solve (417 * 425)", "answer": "The result of (417 * 425) is 177225\n\n####177225", "a": 417, "b": 425, "operator": "*", "result": 177225}
{"question": "Solve (292 - 568)", "answer": "The result of (292 - 568) is -276\n\n####-276", "a": 292, "b": 568, "operator": "-", "result": -276}
{"question": "Solve (625 / 724)", "answer": "The result of (625 / 724) is 0.8633\n\n####0.8633", "a": 625, "b": 724, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8633}
{"question": "Solve (259 * 544)", "answer": "The result of (259 * 544) is 140896\n\n####140896", "a": 259, "b": 544, "operator": "*", "result": 140896}
{"question": "Solve (116 + 364)", "answer": "The result of (116 + 364) is 480\n\n####480", "a": 116, "b": 364, "operator": "+", "result": 480}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 38)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 38) is 18.1316\n\n####18.1316", "a": 689, "b": 38, "operator": "/", "result": 18.1316}
{"question": "Solve (718 * 563)", "answer": "The result of (718 * 563) is 404234\n\n####404234", "a": 718, "b": 563, "operator": "*", "result": 404234}
{"question": "Solve (602 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (602 - 492) is 110\n\n####110", "a": 602, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve (743 - 944)", "answer": "The result of (743 - 944) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 743, "b": 944, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 332) is 194552\n\n####194552", "a": 586, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 194552}
{"question": "Solve (118 - 227)", "answer": "The result of (118 - 227) is -109\n\n####-109", "a": 118, "b": 227, "operator": "-", "result": -109}
{"question": "Solve (502 - 693)", "answer": "The result of (502 - 693) is -191\n\n####-191", "a": 502, "b": 693, "operator": "-", "result": -191}
{"question": "Solve (468 * 719)", "answer": "The result of (468 * 719) is 336492\n\n####336492", "a": 468, "b": 719, "operator": "*", "result": 336492}
{"question": "Solve (992 + 975)", "answer": "The result of (992 + 975) is 1967\n\n####1967", "a": 992, "b": 975, "operator": "+", "result": 1967}
{"question": "Solve (674 + 810)", "answer": "The result of (674 + 810) is 1484\n\n####1484", "a": 674, "b": 810, "operator": "+", "result": 1484}
{"question": "Solve (983 / 572)", "answer": "The result of (983 / 572) is 1.7185\n\n####1.7185", "a": 983, "b": 572, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7185}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 331)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 331) is 304520\n\n####304520", "a": 920, "b": 331, "operator": "*", "result": 304520}
{"question": "Solve (305 - 696)", "answer": "The result of (305 - 696) is -391\n\n####-391", "a": 305, "b": 696, "operator": "-", "result": -391}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 805)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 805) is -353\n\n####-353", "a": 452, "b": 805, "operator": "-", "result": -353}
{"question": "Solve (420 * 669)", "answer": "The result of (420 * 669) is 280980\n\n####280980", "a": 420, "b": 669, "operator": "*", "result": 280980}
{"question": "Solve (720 * 766)", "answer": "The result of (720 * 766) is 551520\n\n####551520", "a": 720, "b": 766, "operator": "*", "result": 551520}
{"question": "Solve (124 * 849)", "answer": "The result of (124 * 849) is 105276\n\n####105276", "a": 124, "b": 849, "operator": "*", "result": 105276}
{"question": "Solve (421 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (421 / 852) is 0.4941\n\n####0.4941", "a": 421, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4941}
{"question": "Solve (75 - 818)", "answer": "The result of (75 - 818) is -743\n\n####-743", "a": 75, "b": 818, "operator": "-", "result": -743}
{"question": "Solve (127 * 54)", "answer": "The result of (127 * 54) is 6858\n\n####6858", "a": 127, "b": 54, "operator": "*", "result": 6858}
{"question": "Solve (929 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (929 - 579) is 350\n\n####350", "a": 929, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": 350}
{"question": "Solve (236 - 95)", "answer": "The result of (236 - 95) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 236, "b": 95, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (852 - 277)", "answer": "The result of (852 - 277) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 852, "b": 277, "operator": "-", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (646 + 170)", "answer": "The result of (646 + 170) is 816\n\n####816", "a": 646, "b": 170, "operator": "+", "result": 816}
{"question": "Solve (138 - 167)", "answer": "The result of (138 - 167) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 138, "b": 167, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (194 - 11)", "answer": "The result of (194 - 11) is 183\n\n####183", "a": 194, "b": 11, "operator": "-", "result": 183}
{"question": "Solve (314 / 996)", "answer": "The result of (314 / 996) is 0.3153\n\n####0.3153", "a": 314, "b": 996, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3153}
{"question": "Solve (742 + 800)", "answer": "The result of (742 + 800) is 1542\n\n####1542", "a": 742, "b": 800, "operator": "+", "result": 1542}
{"question": "Solve (593 - 940)", "answer": "The result of (593 - 940) is -347\n\n####-347", "a": 593, "b": 940, "operator": "-", "result": -347}
{"question": "Solve (881 + 700)", "answer": "The result of (881 + 700) is 1581\n\n####1581", "a": 881, "b": 700, "operator": "+", "result": 1581}
{"question": "Solve (792 * 788)", "answer": "The result of (792 * 788) is 624096\n\n####624096", "a": 792, "b": 788, "operator": "*", "result": 624096}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 61) is 21655\n\n####21655", "a": 355, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 21655}
{"question": "Solve (718 * 651)", "answer": "The result of (718 * 651) is 467418\n\n####467418", "a": 718, "b": 651, "operator": "*", "result": 467418}
{"question": "Solve (753 * 644)", "answer": "The result of (753 * 644) is 484932\n\n####484932", "a": 753, "b": 644, "operator": "*", "result": 484932}
{"question": "Solve (706 / 235)", "answer": "The result of (706 / 235) is 3.0043\n\n####3.0043", "a": 706, "b": 235, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0043}
{"question": "Solve (362 + 99)", "answer": "The result of (362 + 99) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 362, "b": 99, "operator": "+", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (826 * 237)", "answer": "The result of (826 * 237) is 195762\n\n####195762", "a": 826, "b": 237, "operator": "*", "result": 195762}
{"question": "Solve (120 * 12)", "answer": "The result of (120 * 12) is 1440\n\n####1440", "a": 120, "b": 12, "operator": "*", "result": 1440}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 122)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 122) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 94, "b": 122, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (215 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (215 - 409) is -194\n\n####-194", "a": 215, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": -194}
{"question": "Solve (955 / 840)", "answer": "The result of (955 / 840) is 1.1369\n\n####1.1369", "a": 955, "b": 840, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1369}
{"question": "Solve (680 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (680 * 861) is 585480\n\n####585480", "a": 680, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 585480}
{"question": "Solve (470 + 76)", "answer": "The result of (470 + 76) is 546\n\n####546", "a": 470, "b": 76, "operator": "+", "result": 546}
{"question": "Solve (148 + 163)", "answer": "The result of (148 + 163) is 311\n\n####311", "a": 148, "b": 163, "operator": "+", "result": 311}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 830)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 830) is 1036\n\n####1036", "a": 206, "b": 830, "operator": "+", "result": 1036}
{"question": "Solve (780 - 51)", "answer": "The result of (780 - 51) is 729\n\n####729", "a": 780, "b": 51, "operator": "-", "result": 729}
{"question": "Solve (779 * 125)", "answer": "The result of (779 * 125) is 97375\n\n####97375", "a": 779, "b": 125, "operator": "*", "result": 97375}
{"question": "Solve (111 + 474)", "answer": "The result of (111 + 474) is 585\n\n####585", "a": 111, "b": 474, "operator": "+", "result": 585}
{"question": "Solve (765 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (765 * 22) is 16830\n\n####16830", "a": 765, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 16830}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 614)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 614) is 362\n\n####362", "a": 976, "b": 614, "operator": "-", "result": 362}
{"question": "Solve (526 + 910)", "answer": "The result of (526 + 910) is 1436\n\n####1436", "a": 526, "b": 910, "operator": "+", "result": 1436}
{"question": "Solve (546 - 192)", "answer": "The result of (546 - 192) is 354\n\n####354", "a": 546, "b": 192, "operator": "-", "result": 354}
{"question": "Solve (821 / 822)", "answer": "The result of (821 / 822) is 0.9988\n\n####0.9988", "a": 821, "b": 822, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9988}
{"question": "Solve (218 + 836)", "answer": "The result of (218 + 836) is 1054\n\n####1054", "a": 218, "b": 836, "operator": "+", "result": 1054}
{"question": "Solve (120 * 244)", "answer": "The result of (120 * 244) is 29280\n\n####29280", "a": 120, "b": 244, "operator": "*", "result": 29280}
{"question": "Solve (83 / 98)", "answer": "The result of (83 / 98) is 0.8469\n\n####0.8469", "a": 83, "b": 98, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8469}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 371)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 371) is 0.097\n\n####0.097", "a": 36, "b": 371, "operator": "/", "result": 0.097}
{"question": "Solve (370 - 107)", "answer": "The result of (370 - 107) is 263\n\n####263", "a": 370, "b": 107, "operator": "-", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve (607 / 533)", "answer": "The result of (607 / 533) is 1.1388\n\n####1.1388", "a": 607, "b": 533, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1388}
{"question": "Solve (920 + 401)", "answer": "The result of (920 + 401) is 1321\n\n####1321", "a": 920, "b": 401, "operator": "+", "result": 1321}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 105)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 105) is -12\n\n####-12", "a": 93, "b": 105, "operator": "-", "result": -12}
{"question": "Solve (700 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (700 / 695) is 1.0072\n\n####1.0072", "a": 700, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0072}
{"question": "Solve (992 / 769)", "answer": "The result of (992 / 769) is 1.29\n\n####1.29", "a": 992, "b": 769, "operator": "/", "result": 1.29}
{"question": "Solve (208 - 469)", "answer": "The result of (208 - 469) is -261\n\n####-261", "a": 208, "b": 469, "operator": "-", "result": -261}
{"question": "Solve (484 + 133)", "answer": "The result of (484 + 133) is 617\n\n####617", "a": 484, "b": 133, "operator": "+", "result": 617}
{"question": "Solve (51 - 684)", "answer": "The result of (51 - 684) is -633\n\n####-633", "a": 51, "b": 684, "operator": "-", "result": -633}
{"question": "Solve (956 - 694)", "answer": "The result of (956 - 694) is 262\n\n####262", "a": 956, "b": 694, "operator": "-", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 409)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 409) is 1352\n\n####1352", "a": 943, "b": 409, "operator": "+", "result": 1352}
{"question": "Solve (829 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (829 * 175) is 145075\n\n####145075", "a": 829, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 145075}
{"question": "Solve (494 / 803)", "answer": "The result of (494 / 803) is 0.6152\n\n####0.6152", "a": 494, "b": 803, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6152}
{"question": "Solve (820 + 850)", "answer": "The result of (820 + 850) is 1670\n\n####1670", "a": 820, "b": 850, "operator": "+", "result": 1670}
{"question": "Solve (326 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (326 * 332) is 108232\n\n####108232", "a": 326, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 108232}
{"question": "Solve (527 + 132)", "answer": "The result of (527 + 132) is 659\n\n####659", "a": 527, "b": 132, "operator": "+", "result": 659}
{"question": "Solve (748 + 647)", "answer": "The result of (748 + 647) is 1395\n\n####1395", "a": 748, "b": 647, "operator": "+", "result": 1395}
{"question": "Solve (3 * 392)", "answer": "The result of (3 * 392) is 1176\n\n####1176", "a": 3, "b": 392, "operator": "*", "result": 1176}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 983)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 983) is -674\n\n####-674", "a": 309, "b": 983, "operator": "-", "result": -674}
{"question": "Solve (641 / 772)", "answer": "The result of (641 / 772) is 0.8303\n\n####0.8303", "a": 641, "b": 772, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8303}
{"question": "Solve (450 - 589)", "answer": "The result of (450 - 589) is -139\n\n####-139", "a": 450, "b": 589, "operator": "-", "result": -139}
{"question": "Solve (83 + 908)", "answer": "The result of (83 + 908) is 991\n\n####991", "a": 83, "b": 908, "operator": "+", "result": 991}
{"question": "Solve (815 / 972)", "answer": "The result of (815 / 972) is 0.8385\n\n####0.8385", "a": 815, "b": 972, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8385}
{"question": "Solve (371 / 575)", "answer": "The result of (371 / 575) is 0.6452\n\n####0.6452", "a": 371, "b": 575, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6452}
{"question": "Solve (314 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (314 - 932) is -618\n\n####-618", "a": 314, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": -618}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 103)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 103) is 730\n\n####730", "a": 833, "b": 103, "operator": "-", "result": 730}
{"question": "Solve (287 / 479)", "answer": "The result of (287 / 479) is 0.5992\n\n####0.5992", "a": 287, "b": 479, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5992}
{"question": "Solve (43 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (43 - 238) is -195\n\n####-195", "a": 43, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": -195}
{"question": "Solve (194 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (194 + 245) is 439\n\n####439", "a": 194, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 439}
{"question": "Solve (782 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (782 / 289) is 2.7059\n\n####2.7059", "a": 782, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7059}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 649)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 649) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 365, "b": 649, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (627 - 392)", "answer": "The result of (627 - 392) is 235\n\n####235", "a": 627, "b": 392, "operator": "-", "result": 235}
{"question": "Solve (613 / 872)", "answer": "The result of (613 / 872) is 0.703\n\n####0.703", "a": 613, "b": 872, "operator": "/", "result": 0.703}
{"question": "Solve (327 + 252)", "answer": "The result of (327 + 252) is 579\n\n####579", "a": 327, "b": 252, "operator": "+", "result": 579}
{"question": "Solve (611 - 437)", "answer": "The result of (611 - 437) is 174\n\n####174", "a": 611, "b": 437, "operator": "-", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve (273 / 622)", "answer": "The result of (273 / 622) is 0.4389\n\n####0.4389", "a": 273, "b": 622, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4389}
{"question": "Solve (701 + 895)", "answer": "The result of (701 + 895) is 1596\n\n####1596", "a": 701, "b": 895, "operator": "+", "result": 1596}
{"question": "Solve (840 - 994)", "answer": "The result of (840 - 994) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 840, "b": 994, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (31 * 675)", "answer": "The result of (31 * 675) is 20925\n\n####20925", "a": 31, "b": 675, "operator": "*", "result": 20925}
{"question": "Solve (618 - 800)", "answer": "The result of (618 - 800) is -182\n\n####-182", "a": 618, "b": 800, "operator": "-", "result": -182}
{"question": "Solve (632 * 330)", "answer": "The result of (632 * 330) is 208560\n\n####208560", "a": 632, "b": 330, "operator": "*", "result": 208560}
{"question": "Solve (436 * 961)", "answer": "The result of (436 * 961) is 418996\n\n####418996", "a": 436, "b": 961, "operator": "*", "result": 418996}
{"question": "Solve (521 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (521 - 295) is 226\n\n####226", "a": 521, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": 226}
{"question": "Solve (511 / 172)", "answer": "The result of (511 / 172) is 2.9709\n\n####2.9709", "a": 511, "b": 172, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9709}
{"question": "Solve (321 * 546)", "answer": "The result of (321 * 546) is 175266\n\n####175266", "a": 321, "b": 546, "operator": "*", "result": 175266}
{"question": "Solve (166 + 370)", "answer": "The result of (166 + 370) is 536\n\n####536", "a": 166, "b": 370, "operator": "+", "result": 536}
{"question": "Solve (192 / 681)", "answer": "The result of (192 / 681) is 0.2819\n\n####0.2819", "a": 192, "b": 681, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2819}
{"question": "Solve (326 + 909)", "answer": "The result of (326 + 909) is 1235\n\n####1235", "a": 326, "b": 909, "operator": "+", "result": 1235}
{"question": "Solve (229 * 81)", "answer": "The result of (229 * 81) is 18549\n\n####18549", "a": 229, "b": 81, "operator": "*", "result": 18549}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 690) is 431940\n\n####431940", "a": 626, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 431940}
{"question": "Solve (426 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (426 - 998) is -572\n\n####-572", "a": 426, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -572}
{"question": "Solve (210 * 847)", "answer": "The result of (210 * 847) is 177870\n\n####177870", "a": 210, "b": 847, "operator": "*", "result": 177870}
{"question": "Solve (67 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (67 - 634) is -567\n\n####-567", "a": 67, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": -567}
{"question": "Solve (976 / 678)", "answer": "The result of (976 / 678) is 1.4395\n\n####1.4395", "a": 976, "b": 678, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4395}
{"question": "Solve (267 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (267 * 958) is 255786\n\n####255786", "a": 267, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 255786}
{"question": "Solve (44 / 860)", "answer": "The result of (44 / 860) is 0.0512\n\n####0.0512", "a": 44, "b": 860, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0512}
{"question": "Solve (447 / 683)", "answer": "The result of (447 / 683) is 0.6545\n\n####0.6545", "a": 447, "b": 683, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6545}
{"question": "Solve (25 * 901)", "answer": "The result of (25 * 901) is 22525\n\n####22525", "a": 25, "b": 901, "operator": "*", "result": 22525}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 640)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 640) is 110\n\n####110", "a": 750, "b": 640, "operator": "-", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve (899 + 798)", "answer": "The result of (899 + 798) is 1697\n\n####1697", "a": 899, "b": 798, "operator": "+", "result": 1697}
{"question": "Solve (165 - 434)", "answer": "The result of (165 - 434) is -269\n\n####-269", "a": 165, "b": 434, "operator": "-", "result": -269}
{"question": "Solve (680 - 882)", "answer": "The result of (680 - 882) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 680, "b": 882, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 671)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 671) is 1.3711\n\n####1.3711", "a": 920, "b": 671, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3711}
{"question": "Solve (922 + 33)", "answer": "The result of (922 + 33) is 955\n\n####955", "a": 922, "b": 33, "operator": "+", "result": 955}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 587)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 587) is -563\n\n####-563", "a": 24, "b": 587, "operator": "-", "result": -563}
{"question": "Solve (702 / 554)", "answer": "The result of (702 / 554) is 1.2671\n\n####1.2671", "a": 702, "b": 554, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2671}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 486)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 486) is 757\n\n####757", "a": 271, "b": 486, "operator": "+", "result": 757}
{"question": "Solve (345 / 19)", "answer": "The result of (345 / 19) is 18.1579\n\n####18.1579", "a": 345, "b": 19, "operator": "/", "result": 18.1579}
{"question": "Solve (34 - 433)", "answer": "The result of (34 - 433) is -399\n\n####-399", "a": 34, "b": 433, "operator": "-", "result": -399}
{"question": "Solve (994 / 774)", "answer": "The result of (994 / 774) is 1.2842\n\n####1.2842", "a": 994, "b": 774, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2842}
{"question": "Solve (524 - 336)", "answer": "The result of (524 - 336) is 188\n\n####188", "a": 524, "b": 336, "operator": "-", "result": 188}
{"question": "Solve (729 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (729 - 431) is 298\n\n####298", "a": 729, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": 298}
{"question": "Solve (252 / 369)", "answer": "The result of (252 / 369) is 0.6829\n\n####0.6829", "a": 252, "b": 369, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6829}
{"question": "Solve (655 + 330)", "answer": "The result of (655 + 330) is 985\n\n####985", "a": 655, "b": 330, "operator": "+", "result": 985}
{"question": "Solve (820 * 703)", "answer": "The result of (820 * 703) is 576460\n\n####576460", "a": 820, "b": 703, "operator": "*", "result": 576460}
{"question": "Solve (996 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (996 * 357) is 355572\n\n####355572", "a": 996, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 355572}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 311)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 311) is 2.2669\n\n####2.2669", "a": 705, "b": 311, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2669}
{"question": "Solve (13 * 959)", "answer": "The result of (13 * 959) is 12467\n\n####12467", "a": 13, "b": 959, "operator": "*", "result": 12467}
{"question": "Solve (828 + 260)", "answer": "The result of (828 + 260) is 1088\n\n####1088", "a": 828, "b": 260, "operator": "+", "result": 1088}
{"question": "Solve (384 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (384 / 453) is 0.8477\n\n####0.8477", "a": 384, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8477}
{"question": "Solve (453 / 522)", "answer": "The result of (453 / 522) is 0.8678\n\n####0.8678", "a": 453, "b": 522, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8678}
{"question": "Solve (617 * 798)", "answer": "The result of (617 * 798) is 492366\n\n####492366", "a": 617, "b": 798, "operator": "*", "result": 492366}
{"question": "Solve (252 * 863)", "answer": "The result of (252 * 863) is 217476\n\n####217476", "a": 252, "b": 863, "operator": "*", "result": 217476}
{"question": "Solve (433 + 863)", "answer": "The result of (433 + 863) is 1296\n\n####1296", "a": 433, "b": 863, "operator": "+", "result": 1296}
{"question": "Solve (874 + 117)", "answer": "The result of (874 + 117) is 991\n\n####991", "a": 874, "b": 117, "operator": "+", "result": 991}
{"question": "Solve (748 * 475)", "answer": "The result of (748 * 475) is 355300\n\n####355300", "a": 748, "b": 475, "operator": "*", "result": 355300}
{"question": "Solve (630 - 382)", "answer": "The result of (630 - 382) is 248\n\n####248", "a": 630, "b": 382, "operator": "-", "result": 248}
{"question": "Solve (927 - 947)", "answer": "The result of (927 - 947) is -20\n\n####-20", "a": 927, "b": 947, "operator": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve (482 + 263)", "answer": "The result of (482 + 263) is 745\n\n####745", "a": 482, "b": 263, "operator": "+", "result": 745}
{"question": "Solve (231 + 374)", "answer": "The result of (231 + 374) is 605\n\n####605", "a": 231, "b": 374, "operator": "+", "result": 605}
{"question": "Solve (974 / 917)", "answer": "The result of (974 / 917) is 1.0622\n\n####1.0622", "a": 974, "b": 917, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0622}
{"question": "Solve (434 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (434 / 852) is 0.5094\n\n####0.5094", "a": 434, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5094}
{"question": "Solve (119 / 224)", "answer": "The result of (119 / 224) is 0.5312\n\n####0.5312", "a": 119, "b": 224, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5312}
{"question": "Solve (220 * 279)", "answer": "The result of (220 * 279) is 61380\n\n####61380", "a": 220, "b": 279, "operator": "*", "result": 61380}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 26)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 26) is 37.3077\n\n####37.3077", "a": 970, "b": 26, "operator": "/", "result": 37.3077}
{"question": "Solve (713 / 682)", "answer": "The result of (713 / 682) is 1.0455\n\n####1.0455", "a": 713, "b": 682, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0455}
{"question": "Solve (171 + 437)", "answer": "The result of (171 + 437) is 608\n\n####608", "a": 171, "b": 437, "operator": "+", "result": 608}
{"question": "Solve (516 / 957)", "answer": "The result of (516 / 957) is 0.5392\n\n####0.5392", "a": 516, "b": 957, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5392}
{"question": "Solve (329 * 465)", "answer": "The result of (329 * 465) is 152985\n\n####152985", "a": 329, "b": 465, "operator": "*", "result": 152985}
{"question": "Solve (802 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (802 / 891) is 0.9001\n\n####0.9001", "a": 802, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9001}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 138)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 138) is 73002\n\n####73002", "a": 529, "b": 138, "operator": "*", "result": 73002}
{"question": "Solve (180 - 874)", "answer": "The result of (180 - 874) is -694\n\n####-694", "a": 180, "b": 874, "operator": "-", "result": -694}
{"question": "Solve (623 * 946)", "answer": "The result of (623 * 946) is 589358\n\n####589358", "a": 623, "b": 946, "operator": "*", "result": 589358}
{"question": "Solve (886 * 942)", "answer": "The result of (886 * 942) is 834612\n\n####834612", "a": 886, "b": 942, "operator": "*", "result": 834612}
{"question": "Solve (625 / 859)", "answer": "The result of (625 / 859) is 0.7276\n\n####0.7276", "a": 625, "b": 859, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7276}
{"question": "Solve (745 - 556)", "answer": "The result of (745 - 556) is 189\n\n####189", "a": 745, "b": 556, "operator": "-", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve (507 * 779)", "answer": "The result of (507 * 779) is 394953\n\n####394953", "a": 507, "b": 779, "operator": "*", "result": 394953}
{"question": "Solve (611 + 181)", "answer": "The result of (611 + 181) is 792\n\n####792", "a": 611, "b": 181, "operator": "+", "result": 792}
{"question": "Solve (726 * 622)", "answer": "The result of (726 * 622) is 451572\n\n####451572", "a": 726, "b": 622, "operator": "*", "result": 451572}
{"question": "Solve (362 - 966)", "answer": "The result of (362 - 966) is -604\n\n####-604", "a": 362, "b": 966, "operator": "-", "result": -604}
{"question": "Solve (618 / 549)", "answer": "The result of (618 / 549) is 1.1257\n\n####1.1257", "a": 618, "b": 549, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1257}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 534)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 534) is 33642\n\n####33642", "a": 63, "b": 534, "operator": "*", "result": 33642}
{"question": "Solve (730 + 804)", "answer": "The result of (730 + 804) is 1534\n\n####1534", "a": 730, "b": 804, "operator": "+", "result": 1534}
{"question": "Solve (979 * 758)", "answer": "The result of (979 * 758) is 742082\n\n####742082", "a": 979, "b": 758, "operator": "*", "result": 742082}
{"question": "Solve (906 - 200)", "answer": "The result of (906 - 200) is 706\n\n####706", "a": 906, "b": 200, "operator": "-", "result": 706}
{"question": "Solve (515 / 619)", "answer": "The result of (515 / 619) is 0.832\n\n####0.832", "a": 515, "b": 619, "operator": "/", "result": 0.832}
{"question": "Solve (549 * 727)", "answer": "The result of (549 * 727) is 399123\n\n####399123", "a": 549, "b": 727, "operator": "*", "result": 399123}
{"question": "Solve (232 - 762)", "answer": "The result of (232 - 762) is -530\n\n####-530", "a": 232, "b": 762, "operator": "-", "result": -530}
{"question": "Solve (357 / 417)", "answer": "The result of (357 / 417) is 0.8561\n\n####0.8561", "a": 357, "b": 417, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8561}
{"question": "Solve (384 * 371)", "answer": "The result of (384 * 371) is 142464\n\n####142464", "a": 384, "b": 371, "operator": "*", "result": 142464}
{"question": "Solve (528 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (528 - 496) is 32\n\n####32", "a": 528, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": 32}
{"question": "Solve (572 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (572 / 327) is 1.7492\n\n####1.7492", "a": 572, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7492}
{"question": "Solve (589 / 869)", "answer": "The result of (589 / 869) is 0.6778\n\n####0.6778", "a": 589, "b": 869, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6778}
{"question": "Solve (400 - 53)", "answer": "The result of (400 - 53) is 347\n\n####347", "a": 400, "b": 53, "operator": "-", "result": 347}
{"question": "Solve (241 - 427)", "answer": "The result of (241 - 427) is -186\n\n####-186", "a": 241, "b": 427, "operator": "-", "result": -186}
{"question": "Solve (311 - 330)", "answer": "The result of (311 - 330) is -19\n\n####-19", "a": 311, "b": 330, "operator": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve (350 / 890)", "answer": "The result of (350 / 890) is 0.3933\n\n####0.3933", "a": 350, "b": 890, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3933}
{"question": "Solve (957 * 38)", "answer": "The result of (957 * 38) is 36366\n\n####36366", "a": 957, "b": 38, "operator": "*", "result": 36366}
{"question": "Solve (144 - 999)", "answer": "The result of (144 - 999) is -855\n\n####-855", "a": 144, "b": 999, "operator": "-", "result": -855}
{"question": "Solve (64 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (64 - 498) is -434\n\n####-434", "a": 64, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": -434}
{"question": "Solve (811 + 227)", "answer": "The result of (811 + 227) is 1038\n\n####1038", "a": 811, "b": 227, "operator": "+", "result": 1038}
{"question": "Solve (886 + 909)", "answer": "The result of (886 + 909) is 1795\n\n####1795", "a": 886, "b": 909, "operator": "+", "result": 1795}
{"question": "Solve (56 / 483)", "answer": "The result of (56 / 483) is 0.1159\n\n####0.1159", "a": 56, "b": 483, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1159}
{"question": "Solve (729 - 856)", "answer": "The result of (729 - 856) is -127\n\n####-127", "a": 729, "b": 856, "operator": "-", "result": -127}
{"question": "Solve (160 / 762)", "answer": "The result of (160 / 762) is 0.21\n\n####0.21", "a": 160, "b": 762, "operator": "/", "result": 0.21}
{"question": "Solve (443 + 374)", "answer": "The result of (443 + 374) is 817\n\n####817", "a": 443, "b": 374, "operator": "+", "result": 817}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 537)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 537) is 0.5531\n\n####0.5531", "a": 297, "b": 537, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5531}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 427) is 2.2717\n\n####2.2717", "a": 970, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2717}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 128)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 128) is 334\n\n####334", "a": 206, "b": 128, "operator": "+", "result": 334}
{"question": "Solve (211 - 536)", "answer": "The result of (211 - 536) is -325\n\n####-325", "a": 211, "b": 536, "operator": "-", "result": -325}
{"question": "Solve (263 / 760)", "answer": "The result of (263 / 760) is 0.3461\n\n####0.3461", "a": 263, "b": 760, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3461}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 411) is 0.0876\n\n####0.0876", "a": 36, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0876}
{"question": "Solve (750 + 336)", "answer": "The result of (750 + 336) is 1086\n\n####1086", "a": 750, "b": 336, "operator": "+", "result": 1086}
{"question": "Solve (353 / 799)", "answer": "The result of (353 / 799) is 0.4418\n\n####0.4418", "a": 353, "b": 799, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4418}
{"question": "Solve (520 + 351)", "answer": "The result of (520 + 351) is 871\n\n####871", "a": 520, "b": 351, "operator": "+", "result": 871}
{"question": "Solve (496 + 191)", "answer": "The result of (496 + 191) is 687\n\n####687", "a": 496, "b": 191, "operator": "+", "result": 687}
{"question": "Solve (283 * 867)", "answer": "The result of (283 * 867) is 245361\n\n####245361", "a": 283, "b": 867, "operator": "*", "result": 245361}
{"question": "Solve (182 + 822)", "answer": "The result of (182 + 822) is 1004\n\n####1004", "a": 182, "b": 822, "operator": "+", "result": 1004}
{"question": "Solve (370 - 524)", "answer": "The result of (370 - 524) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 370, "b": 524, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (29 + 390)", "answer": "The result of (29 + 390) is 419\n\n####419", "a": 29, "b": 390, "operator": "+", "result": 419}
{"question": "Solve (595 + 230)", "answer": "The result of (595 + 230) is 825\n\n####825", "a": 595, "b": 230, "operator": "+", "result": 825}
{"question": "Solve (345 - 774)", "answer": "The result of (345 - 774) is -429\n\n####-429", "a": 345, "b": 774, "operator": "-", "result": -429}
{"question": "Solve (11 - 624)", "answer": "The result of (11 - 624) is -613\n\n####-613", "a": 11, "b": 624, "operator": "-", "result": -613}
{"question": "Solve (84 - 208)", "answer": "The result of (84 - 208) is -124\n\n####-124", "a": 84, "b": 208, "operator": "-", "result": -124}
{"question": "Solve (545 + 930)", "answer": "The result of (545 + 930) is 1475\n\n####1475", "a": 545, "b": 930, "operator": "+", "result": 1475}
{"question": "Solve (558 / 209)", "answer": "The result of (558 / 209) is 2.6699\n\n####2.6699", "a": 558, "b": 209, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6699}
{"question": "Solve (350 - 993)", "answer": "The result of (350 - 993) is -643\n\n####-643", "a": 350, "b": 993, "operator": "-", "result": -643}
{"question": "Solve (795 / 857)", "answer": "The result of (795 / 857) is 0.9277\n\n####0.9277", "a": 795, "b": 857, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9277}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 108)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 108) is 54864\n\n####54864", "a": 508, "b": 108, "operator": "*", "result": 54864}
{"question": "Solve (253 * 801)", "answer": "The result of (253 * 801) is 202653\n\n####202653", "a": 253, "b": 801, "operator": "*", "result": 202653}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 324)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 324) is 294840\n\n####294840", "a": 910, "b": 324, "operator": "*", "result": 294840}
{"question": "Solve (378 * 678)", "answer": "The result of (378 * 678) is 256284\n\n####256284", "a": 378, "b": 678, "operator": "*", "result": 256284}
{"question": "Solve (906 / 537)", "answer": "The result of (906 / 537) is 1.6872\n\n####1.6872", "a": 906, "b": 537, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6872}
{"question": "Solve (405 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (405 - 184) is 221\n\n####221", "a": 405, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve (504 / 73)", "answer": "The result of (504 / 73) is 6.9041\n\n####6.9041", "a": 504, "b": 73, "operator": "/", "result": 6.9041}
{"question": "Solve (579 * 307)", "answer": "The result of (579 * 307) is 177753\n\n####177753", "a": 579, "b": 307, "operator": "*", "result": 177753}
{"question": "Solve (664 - 880)", "answer": "The result of (664 - 880) is -216\n\n####-216", "a": 664, "b": 880, "operator": "-", "result": -216}
{"question": "Solve (100 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (100 / 984) is 0.1016\n\n####0.1016", "a": 100, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1016}
{"question": "Solve (4 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (4 + 868) is 872\n\n####872", "a": 4, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 872}
{"question": "Solve (140 / 84)", "answer": "The result of (140 / 84) is 1.6667\n\n####1.6667", "a": 140, "b": 84, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6667}
{"question": "Solve (642 - 941)", "answer": "The result of (642 - 941) is -299\n\n####-299", "a": 642, "b": 941, "operator": "-", "result": -299}
{"question": "Solve (367 + 759)", "answer": "The result of (367 + 759) is 1126\n\n####1126", "a": 367, "b": 759, "operator": "+", "result": 1126}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 255)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 255) is 34425\n\n####34425", "a": 135, "b": 255, "operator": "*", "result": 34425}
{"question": "Solve (834 / 466)", "answer": "The result of (834 / 466) is 1.7897\n\n####1.7897", "a": 834, "b": 466, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7897}
{"question": "Solve (492 * 604)", "answer": "The result of (492 * 604) is 297168\n\n####297168", "a": 492, "b": 604, "operator": "*", "result": 297168}
{"question": "Solve (550 * 480)", "answer": "The result of (550 * 480) is 264000\n\n####264000", "a": 550, "b": 480, "operator": "*", "result": 264000}
{"question": "Solve (772 / 148)", "answer": "The result of (772 / 148) is 5.2162\n\n####5.2162", "a": 772, "b": 148, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2162}
{"question": "Solve (931 * 662)", "answer": "The result of (931 * 662) is 616322\n\n####616322", "a": 931, "b": 662, "operator": "*", "result": 616322}
{"question": "Solve (876 / 585)", "answer": "The result of (876 / 585) is 1.4974\n\n####1.4974", "a": 876, "b": 585, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4974}
{"question": "Solve (686 + 836)", "answer": "The result of (686 + 836) is 1522\n\n####1522", "a": 686, "b": 836, "operator": "+", "result": 1522}
{"question": "Solve (896 / 347)", "answer": "The result of (896 / 347) is 2.5821\n\n####2.5821", "a": 896, "b": 347, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5821}
{"question": "Solve (383 - 121)", "answer": "The result of (383 - 121) is 262\n\n####262", "a": 383, "b": 121, "operator": "-", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve (733 - 892)", "answer": "The result of (733 - 892) is -159\n\n####-159", "a": 733, "b": 892, "operator": "-", "result": -159}
{"question": "Solve (830 * 969)", "answer": "The result of (830 * 969) is 804270\n\n####804270", "a": 830, "b": 969, "operator": "*", "result": 804270}
{"question": "Solve (284 - 332)", "answer": "The result of (284 - 332) is -48\n\n####-48", "a": 284, "b": 332, "operator": "-", "result": -48}
{"question": "Solve (10 - 633)", "answer": "The result of (10 - 633) is -623\n\n####-623", "a": 10, "b": 633, "operator": "-", "result": -623}
{"question": "Solve (856 * 5)", "answer": "The result of (856 * 5) is 4280\n\n####4280", "a": 856, "b": 5, "operator": "*", "result": 4280}
{"question": "Solve (411 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (411 + 211) is 622\n\n####622", "a": 411, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 622}
{"question": "Solve (462 - 161)", "answer": "The result of (462 - 161) is 301\n\n####301", "a": 462, "b": 161, "operator": "-", "result": 301}
{"question": "Solve (625 / 4)", "answer": "The result of (625 / 4) is 156.25\n\n####156.25", "a": 625, "b": 4, "operator": "/", "result": 156.25}
{"question": "Solve (449 * 181)", "answer": "The result of (449 * 181) is 81269\n\n####81269", "a": 449, "b": 181, "operator": "*", "result": 81269}
{"question": "Solve (260 * 493)", "answer": "The result of (260 * 493) is 128180\n\n####128180", "a": 260, "b": 493, "operator": "*", "result": 128180}
{"question": "Solve (970 - 707)", "answer": "The result of (970 - 707) is 263\n\n####263", "a": 970, "b": 707, "operator": "-", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve (413 * 99)", "answer": "The result of (413 * 99) is 40887\n\n####40887", "a": 413, "b": 99, "operator": "*", "result": 40887}
{"question": "Solve (541 * 839)", "answer": "The result of (541 * 839) is 453899\n\n####453899", "a": 541, "b": 839, "operator": "*", "result": 453899}
{"question": "Solve (735 / 607)", "answer": "The result of (735 / 607) is 1.2109\n\n####1.2109", "a": 735, "b": 607, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2109}
{"question": "Solve (195 + 559)", "answer": "The result of (195 + 559) is 754\n\n####754", "a": 195, "b": 559, "operator": "+", "result": 754}
{"question": "Solve (485 * 557)", "answer": "The result of (485 * 557) is 270145\n\n####270145", "a": 485, "b": 557, "operator": "*", "result": 270145}
{"question": "Solve (778 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (778 * 439) is 341542\n\n####341542", "a": 778, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 341542}
{"question": "Solve (438 - 851)", "answer": "The result of (438 - 851) is -413\n\n####-413", "a": 438, "b": 851, "operator": "-", "result": -413}
{"question": "Solve (599 - 874)", "answer": "The result of (599 - 874) is -275\n\n####-275", "a": 599, "b": 874, "operator": "-", "result": -275}
{"question": "Solve (183 / 779)", "answer": "The result of (183 / 779) is 0.2349\n\n####0.2349", "a": 183, "b": 779, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2349}
{"question": "Solve (848 * 317)", "answer": "The result of (848 * 317) is 268816\n\n####268816", "a": 848, "b": 317, "operator": "*", "result": 268816}
{"question": "Solve (868 - 897)", "answer": "The result of (868 - 897) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 868, "b": 897, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (17 / 357)", "answer": "The result of (17 / 357) is 0.0476\n\n####0.0476", "a": 17, "b": 357, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0476}
{"question": "Solve (692 + 762)", "answer": "The result of (692 + 762) is 1454\n\n####1454", "a": 692, "b": 762, "operator": "+", "result": 1454}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 124) is 305\n\n####305", "a": 181, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 305}
{"question": "Solve (798 - 480)", "answer": "The result of (798 - 480) is 318\n\n####318", "a": 798, "b": 480, "operator": "-", "result": 318}
{"question": "Solve (658 - 454)", "answer": "The result of (658 - 454) is 204\n\n####204", "a": 658, "b": 454, "operator": "-", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve (263 / 574)", "answer": "The result of (263 / 574) is 0.4582\n\n####0.4582", "a": 263, "b": 574, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4582}
{"question": "Solve (725 - 864)", "answer": "The result of (725 - 864) is -139\n\n####-139", "a": 725, "b": 864, "operator": "-", "result": -139}
{"question": "Solve (207 + 237)", "answer": "The result of (207 + 237) is 444\n\n####444", "a": 207, "b": 237, "operator": "+", "result": 444}
{"question": "Solve (208 * 609)", "answer": "The result of (208 * 609) is 126672\n\n####126672", "a": 208, "b": 609, "operator": "*", "result": 126672}
{"question": "Solve (241 - 155)", "answer": "The result of (241 - 155) is 86\n\n####86", "a": 241, "b": 155, "operator": "-", "result": 86}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 102)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 102) is 618\n\n####618", "a": 720, "b": 102, "operator": "-", "result": 618}
{"question": "Solve (844 + 326)", "answer": "The result of (844 + 326) is 1170\n\n####1170", "a": 844, "b": 326, "operator": "+", "result": 1170}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 487)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 487) is 64771\n\n####64771", "a": 133, "b": 487, "operator": "*", "result": 64771}
{"question": "Solve (941 + 125)", "answer": "The result of (941 + 125) is 1066\n\n####1066", "a": 941, "b": 125, "operator": "+", "result": 1066}
{"question": "Solve (737 + 907)", "answer": "The result of (737 + 907) is 1644\n\n####1644", "a": 737, "b": 907, "operator": "+", "result": 1644}
{"question": "Solve (394 / 222)", "answer": "The result of (394 / 222) is 1.7748\n\n####1.7748", "a": 394, "b": 222, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7748}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 612)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 612) is 0.165\n\n####0.165", "a": 101, "b": 612, "operator": "/", "result": 0.165}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 839)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 839) is -245\n\n####-245", "a": 594, "b": 839, "operator": "-", "result": -245}
{"question": "Solve (164 / 201)", "answer": "The result of (164 / 201) is 0.8159\n\n####0.8159", "a": 164, "b": 201, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8159}
{"question": "Solve (828 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (828 / 873) is 0.9485\n\n####0.9485", "a": 828, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9485}
{"question": "Solve (672 / 32)", "answer": "The result of (672 / 32) is 21.0\n\n####21.0", "a": 672, "b": 32, "operator": "/", "result": 21.0}
{"question": "Solve (626 - 732)", "answer": "The result of (626 - 732) is -106\n\n####-106", "a": 626, "b": 732, "operator": "-", "result": -106}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 930)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 930) is 687270\n\n####687270", "a": 739, "b": 930, "operator": "*", "result": 687270}
{"question": "Solve (378 / 281)", "answer": "The result of (378 / 281) is 1.3452\n\n####1.3452", "a": 378, "b": 281, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3452}
{"question": "Solve (866 / 338)", "answer": "The result of (866 / 338) is 2.5621\n\n####2.5621", "a": 866, "b": 338, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5621}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 895)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 895) is -219\n\n####-219", "a": 676, "b": 895, "operator": "-", "result": -219}
{"question": "Solve (537 / 444)", "answer": "The result of (537 / 444) is 1.2095\n\n####1.2095", "a": 537, "b": 444, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2095}
{"question": "Solve (552 / 207)", "answer": "The result of (552 / 207) is 2.6667\n\n####2.6667", "a": 552, "b": 207, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6667}
{"question": "Solve (574 - 106)", "answer": "The result of (574 - 106) is 468\n\n####468", "a": 574, "b": 106, "operator": "-", "result": 468}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 434)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 434) is -185\n\n####-185", "a": 249, "b": 434, "operator": "-", "result": -185}
{"question": "Solve (919 * 296)", "answer": "The result of (919 * 296) is 272024\n\n####272024", "a": 919, "b": 296, "operator": "*", "result": 272024}
{"question": "Solve (877 / 417)", "answer": "The result of (877 / 417) is 2.1031\n\n####2.1031", "a": 877, "b": 417, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1031}
{"question": "Solve (902 * 375)", "answer": "The result of (902 * 375) is 338250\n\n####338250", "a": 902, "b": 375, "operator": "*", "result": 338250}
{"question": "Solve (739 - 474)", "answer": "The result of (739 - 474) is 265\n\n####265", "a": 739, "b": 474, "operator": "-", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve (930 * 568)", "answer": "The result of (930 * 568) is 528240\n\n####528240", "a": 930, "b": 568, "operator": "*", "result": 528240}
{"question": "Solve (335 * 765)", "answer": "The result of (335 * 765) is 256275\n\n####256275", "a": 335, "b": 765, "operator": "*", "result": 256275}
{"question": "Solve (112 / 459)", "answer": "The result of (112 / 459) is 0.244\n\n####0.244", "a": 112, "b": 459, "operator": "/", "result": 0.244}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 178)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 178) is 430\n\n####430", "a": 608, "b": 178, "operator": "-", "result": 430}
{"question": "Solve (316 * 54)", "answer": "The result of (316 * 54) is 17064\n\n####17064", "a": 316, "b": 54, "operator": "*", "result": 17064}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 351)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 351) is 0.0598\n\n####0.0598", "a": 21, "b": 351, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0598}
{"question": "Solve (380 * 143)", "answer": "The result of (380 * 143) is 54340\n\n####54340", "a": 380, "b": 143, "operator": "*", "result": 54340}
{"question": "Solve (396 * 704)", "answer": "The result of (396 * 704) is 278784\n\n####278784", "a": 396, "b": 704, "operator": "*", "result": 278784}
{"question": "Solve (777 - 815)", "answer": "The result of (777 - 815) is -38\n\n####-38", "a": 777, "b": 815, "operator": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve (254 * 220)", "answer": "The result of (254 * 220) is 55880\n\n####55880", "a": 254, "b": 220, "operator": "*", "result": 55880}
{"question": "Solve (219 + 750)", "answer": "The result of (219 + 750) is 969\n\n####969", "a": 219, "b": 750, "operator": "+", "result": 969}
{"question": "Solve (679 + 842)", "answer": "The result of (679 + 842) is 1521\n\n####1521", "a": 679, "b": 842, "operator": "+", "result": 1521}
{"question": "Solve (278 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (278 * 390) is 108420\n\n####108420", "a": 278, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 108420}
{"question": "Solve (147 - 322)", "answer": "The result of (147 - 322) is -175\n\n####-175", "a": 147, "b": 322, "operator": "-", "result": -175}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 739)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 739) is -421\n\n####-421", "a": 318, "b": 739, "operator": "-", "result": -421}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 904)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 904) is 0.3595\n\n####0.3595", "a": 325, "b": 904, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3595}
{"question": "Solve (581 / 788)", "answer": "The result of (581 / 788) is 0.7373\n\n####0.7373", "a": 581, "b": 788, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7373}
{"question": "Solve (372 / 14)", "answer": "The result of (372 / 14) is 26.5714\n\n####26.5714", "a": 372, "b": 14, "operator": "/", "result": 26.5714}
{"question": "Solve (655 / 520)", "answer": "The result of (655 / 520) is 1.2596\n\n####1.2596", "a": 655, "b": 520, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2596}
{"question": "Solve (987 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (987 / 327) is 3.0183\n\n####3.0183", "a": 987, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0183}
{"question": "Solve (967 - 904)", "answer": "The result of (967 - 904) is 63\n\n####63", "a": 967, "b": 904, "operator": "-", "result": 63}
{"question": "Solve (546 / 47)", "answer": "The result of (546 / 47) is 11.617\n\n####11.617", "a": 546, "b": 47, "operator": "/", "result": 11.617}
{"question": "Solve (622 / 150)", "answer": "The result of (622 / 150) is 4.1467\n\n####4.1467", "a": 622, "b": 150, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1467}
{"question": "Solve (320 / 347)", "answer": "The result of (320 / 347) is 0.9222\n\n####0.9222", "a": 320, "b": 347, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9222}
{"question": "Solve (524 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (524 / 390) is 1.3436\n\n####1.3436", "a": 524, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3436}
{"question": "Solve (501 - 959)", "answer": "The result of (501 - 959) is -458\n\n####-458", "a": 501, "b": 959, "operator": "-", "result": -458}
{"question": "Solve (961 - 193)", "answer": "The result of (961 - 193) is 768\n\n####768", "a": 961, "b": 193, "operator": "-", "result": 768}
{"question": "Solve (36 + 740)", "answer": "The result of (36 + 740) is 776\n\n####776", "a": 36, "b": 740, "operator": "+", "result": 776}
{"question": "Solve (745 + 871)", "answer": "The result of (745 + 871) is 1616\n\n####1616", "a": 745, "b": 871, "operator": "+", "result": 1616}
{"question": "Solve (980 + 911)", "answer": "The result of (980 + 911) is 1891\n\n####1891", "a": 980, "b": 911, "operator": "+", "result": 1891}
{"question": "Solve (815 - 740)", "answer": "The result of (815 - 740) is 75\n\n####75", "a": 815, "b": 740, "operator": "-", "result": 75}
{"question": "Solve (544 / 126)", "answer": "The result of (544 / 126) is 4.3175\n\n####4.3175", "a": 544, "b": 126, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3175}
{"question": "Solve (530 + 518)", "answer": "The result of (530 + 518) is 1048\n\n####1048", "a": 530, "b": 518, "operator": "+", "result": 1048}
{"question": "Solve (189 - 619)", "answer": "The result of (189 - 619) is -430\n\n####-430", "a": 189, "b": 619, "operator": "-", "result": -430}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 318)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 318) is 305916\n\n####305916", "a": 962, "b": 318, "operator": "*", "result": 305916}
{"question": "Solve (982 / 365)", "answer": "The result of (982 / 365) is 2.6904\n\n####2.6904", "a": 982, "b": 365, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6904}
{"question": "Solve (481 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (481 - 706) is -225\n\n####-225", "a": 481, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -225}
{"question": "Solve (427 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (427 - 700) is -273\n\n####-273", "a": 427, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -273}
{"question": "Solve (547 / 501)", "answer": "The result of (547 / 501) is 1.0918\n\n####1.0918", "a": 547, "b": 501, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0918}
{"question": "Solve (848 * 789)", "answer": "The result of (848 * 789) is 669072\n\n####669072", "a": 848, "b": 789, "operator": "*", "result": 669072}
{"question": "Solve (166 / 210)", "answer": "The result of (166 / 210) is 0.7905\n\n####0.7905", "a": 166, "b": 210, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7905}
{"question": "Solve (458 * 393)", "answer": "The result of (458 * 393) is 179994\n\n####179994", "a": 458, "b": 393, "operator": "*", "result": 179994}
{"question": "Solve (573 / 840)", "answer": "The result of (573 / 840) is 0.6821\n\n####0.6821", "a": 573, "b": 840, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6821}
{"question": "Solve (916 * 718)", "answer": "The result of (916 * 718) is 657688\n\n####657688", "a": 916, "b": 718, "operator": "*", "result": 657688}
{"question": "Solve (398 / 191)", "answer": "The result of (398 / 191) is 2.0838\n\n####2.0838", "a": 398, "b": 191, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0838}
{"question": "Solve (305 / 795)", "answer": "The result of (305 / 795) is 0.3836\n\n####0.3836", "a": 305, "b": 795, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3836}
{"question": "Solve (820 * 214)", "answer": "The result of (820 * 214) is 175480\n\n####175480", "a": 820, "b": 214, "operator": "*", "result": 175480}
{"question": "Solve (38 / 374)", "answer": "The result of (38 / 374) is 0.1016\n\n####0.1016", "a": 38, "b": 374, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1016}
{"question": "Solve (551 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (551 - 756) is -205\n\n####-205", "a": 551, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve (481 + 537)", "answer": "The result of (481 + 537) is 1018\n\n####1018", "a": 481, "b": 537, "operator": "+", "result": 1018}
{"question": "Solve (13 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (13 + 19) is 32\n\n####32", "a": 13, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 32}
{"question": "Solve (496 - 263)", "answer": "The result of (496 - 263) is 233\n\n####233", "a": 496, "b": 263, "operator": "-", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve (643 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (643 - 927) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 643, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (19 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (19 - 945) is -926\n\n####-926", "a": 19, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -926}
{"question": "Solve (884 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (884 - 175) is 709\n\n####709", "a": 884, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 709}
{"question": "Solve (294 / 999)", "answer": "The result of (294 / 999) is 0.2943\n\n####0.2943", "a": 294, "b": 999, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2943}
{"question": "Solve (529 / 168)", "answer": "The result of (529 / 168) is 3.1488\n\n####3.1488", "a": 529, "b": 168, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1488}
{"question": "Solve (705 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (705 - 551) is 154\n\n####154", "a": 705, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 154}
{"question": "Solve (799 - 784)", "answer": "The result of (799 - 784) is 15\n\n####15", "a": 799, "b": 784, "operator": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve (47 / 728)", "answer": "The result of (47 / 728) is 0.0646\n\n####0.0646", "a": 47, "b": 728, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0646}
{"question": "Solve (725 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (725 * 142) is 102950\n\n####102950", "a": 725, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 102950}
{"question": "Solve (10 + 531)", "answer": "The result of (10 + 531) is 541\n\n####541", "a": 10, "b": 531, "operator": "+", "result": 541}
{"question": "Solve (394 * 359)", "answer": "The result of (394 * 359) is 141446\n\n####141446", "a": 394, "b": 359, "operator": "*", "result": 141446}
{"question": "Solve (991 / 890)", "answer": "The result of (991 / 890) is 1.1135\n\n####1.1135", "a": 991, "b": 890, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1135}
{"question": "Solve (853 - 182)", "answer": "The result of (853 - 182) is 671\n\n####671", "a": 853, "b": 182, "operator": "-", "result": 671}
{"question": "Solve (486 / 221)", "answer": "The result of (486 / 221) is 2.1991\n\n####2.1991", "a": 486, "b": 221, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1991}
{"question": "Solve (773 * 372)", "answer": "The result of (773 * 372) is 287556\n\n####287556", "a": 773, "b": 372, "operator": "*", "result": 287556}
{"question": "Solve (592 - 226)", "answer": "The result of (592 - 226) is 366\n\n####366", "a": 592, "b": 226, "operator": "-", "result": 366}
{"question": "Solve (503 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (503 / 206) is 2.4417\n\n####2.4417", "a": 503, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4417}
{"question": "Solve (538 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (538 / 567) is 0.9489\n\n####0.9489", "a": 538, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9489}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 61) is 37088\n\n####37088", "a": 608, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 37088}
{"question": "Solve (538 - 646)", "answer": "The result of (538 - 646) is -108\n\n####-108", "a": 538, "b": 646, "operator": "-", "result": -108}
{"question": "Solve (622 * 17)", "answer": "The result of (622 * 17) is 10574\n\n####10574", "a": 622, "b": 17, "operator": "*", "result": 10574}
{"question": "Solve (393 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (393 / 385) is 1.0208\n\n####1.0208", "a": 393, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0208}
{"question": "Solve (162 / 714)", "answer": "The result of (162 / 714) is 0.2269\n\n####0.2269", "a": 162, "b": 714, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2269}
{"question": "Solve (503 * 793)", "answer": "The result of (503 * 793) is 398879\n\n####398879", "a": 503, "b": 793, "operator": "*", "result": 398879}
{"question": "Solve (623 - 841)", "answer": "The result of (623 - 841) is -218\n\n####-218", "a": 623, "b": 841, "operator": "-", "result": -218}
{"question": "Solve (273 / 387)", "answer": "The result of (273 / 387) is 0.7054\n\n####0.7054", "a": 273, "b": 387, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7054}
{"question": "Solve (139 - 944)", "answer": "The result of (139 - 944) is -805\n\n####-805", "a": 139, "b": 944, "operator": "-", "result": -805}
{"question": "Solve (134 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (134 + 487) is 621\n\n####621", "a": 134, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 621}
{"question": "Solve (332 - 118)", "answer": "The result of (332 - 118) is 214\n\n####214", "a": 332, "b": 118, "operator": "-", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve (44 / 338)", "answer": "The result of (44 / 338) is 0.1302\n\n####0.1302", "a": 44, "b": 338, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1302}
{"question": "Solve (779 * 566)", "answer": "The result of (779 * 566) is 440914\n\n####440914", "a": 779, "b": 566, "operator": "*", "result": 440914}
{"question": "Solve (427 / 400)", "answer": "The result of (427 / 400) is 1.0675\n\n####1.0675", "a": 427, "b": 400, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0675}
{"question": "Solve (630 * 27)", "answer": "The result of (630 * 27) is 17010\n\n####17010", "a": 630, "b": 27, "operator": "*", "result": 17010}
{"question": "Solve (145 - 906)", "answer": "The result of (145 - 906) is -761\n\n####-761", "a": 145, "b": 906, "operator": "-", "result": -761}
{"question": "Solve (440 * 69)", "answer": "The result of (440 * 69) is 30360\n\n####30360", "a": 440, "b": 69, "operator": "*", "result": 30360}
{"question": "Solve (898 / 771)", "answer": "The result of (898 / 771) is 1.1647\n\n####1.1647", "a": 898, "b": 771, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1647}
{"question": "Solve (992 + 500)", "answer": "The result of (992 + 500) is 1492\n\n####1492", "a": 992, "b": 500, "operator": "+", "result": 1492}
{"question": "Solve (694 + 912)", "answer": "The result of (694 + 912) is 1606\n\n####1606", "a": 694, "b": 912, "operator": "+", "result": 1606}
{"question": "Solve (619 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (619 - 992) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 619, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (550 + 167)", "answer": "The result of (550 + 167) is 717\n\n####717", "a": 550, "b": 167, "operator": "+", "result": 717}
{"question": "Solve (660 - 446)", "answer": "The result of (660 - 446) is 214\n\n####214", "a": 660, "b": 446, "operator": "-", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve (137 - 711)", "answer": "The result of (137 - 711) is -574\n\n####-574", "a": 137, "b": 711, "operator": "-", "result": -574}
{"question": "Solve (53 / 145)", "answer": "The result of (53 / 145) is 0.3655\n\n####0.3655", "a": 53, "b": 145, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3655}
{"question": "Solve (424 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (424 * 524) is 222176\n\n####222176", "a": 424, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 222176}
{"question": "Solve (759 * 956)", "answer": "The result of (759 * 956) is 725604\n\n####725604", "a": 759, "b": 956, "operator": "*", "result": 725604}
{"question": "Solve (605 + 42)", "answer": "The result of (605 + 42) is 647\n\n####647", "a": 605, "b": 42, "operator": "+", "result": 647}
{"question": "Solve (368 - 234)", "answer": "The result of (368 - 234) is 134\n\n####134", "a": 368, "b": 234, "operator": "-", "result": 134}
{"question": "Solve (582 * 883)", "answer": "The result of (582 * 883) is 513906\n\n####513906", "a": 582, "b": 883, "operator": "*", "result": 513906}
{"question": "Solve (872 * 743)", "answer": "The result of (872 * 743) is 647896\n\n####647896", "a": 872, "b": 743, "operator": "*", "result": 647896}
{"question": "Solve (44 * 44)", "answer": "The result of (44 * 44) is 1936\n\n####1936", "a": 44, "b": 44, "operator": "*", "result": 1936}
{"question": "Solve (254 + 799)", "answer": "The result of (254 + 799) is 1053\n\n####1053", "a": 254, "b": 799, "operator": "+", "result": 1053}
{"question": "Solve (487 * 597)", "answer": "The result of (487 * 597) is 290739\n\n####290739", "a": 487, "b": 597, "operator": "*", "result": 290739}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 661)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 661) is 247214\n\n####247214", "a": 374, "b": 661, "operator": "*", "result": 247214}
{"question": "Solve (776 * 468)", "answer": "The result of (776 * 468) is 363168\n\n####363168", "a": 776, "b": 468, "operator": "*", "result": 363168}
{"question": "Solve (781 + 829)", "answer": "The result of (781 + 829) is 1610\n\n####1610", "a": 781, "b": 829, "operator": "+", "result": 1610}
{"question": "Solve (878 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (878 - 609) is 269\n\n####269", "a": 878, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": 269}
{"question": "Solve (991 / 610)", "answer": "The result of (991 / 610) is 1.6246\n\n####1.6246", "a": 991, "b": 610, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6246}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 204)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 204) is -7\n\n####-7", "a": 197, "b": 204, "operator": "-", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve (380 - 903)", "answer": "The result of (380 - 903) is -523\n\n####-523", "a": 380, "b": 903, "operator": "-", "result": -523}
{"question": "Solve (66 + 563)", "answer": "The result of (66 + 563) is 629\n\n####629", "a": 66, "b": 563, "operator": "+", "result": 629}
{"question": "Solve (556 - 318)", "answer": "The result of (556 - 318) is 238\n\n####238", "a": 556, "b": 318, "operator": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 46)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 46) is 669\n\n####669", "a": 715, "b": 46, "operator": "-", "result": 669}
{"question": "Solve (700 + 649)", "answer": "The result of (700 + 649) is 1349\n\n####1349", "a": 700, "b": 649, "operator": "+", "result": 1349}
{"question": "Solve (985 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (985 - 520) is 465\n\n####465", "a": 985, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": 465}
{"question": "Solve (262 + 833)", "answer": "The result of (262 + 833) is 1095\n\n####1095", "a": 262, "b": 833, "operator": "+", "result": 1095}
{"question": "Solve (199 / 384)", "answer": "The result of (199 / 384) is 0.5182\n\n####0.5182", "a": 199, "b": 384, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5182}
{"question": "Solve (898 - 214)", "answer": "The result of (898 - 214) is 684\n\n####684", "a": 898, "b": 214, "operator": "-", "result": 684}
{"question": "Solve (723 - 194)", "answer": "The result of (723 - 194) is 529\n\n####529", "a": 723, "b": 194, "operator": "-", "result": 529}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 283)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 283) is 1.9152\n\n####1.9152", "a": 542, "b": 283, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9152}
{"question": "Solve (374 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (374 / 411) is 0.91\n\n####0.91", "a": 374, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 0.91}
{"question": "Solve (559 * 488)", "answer": "The result of (559 * 488) is 272792\n\n####272792", "a": 559, "b": 488, "operator": "*", "result": 272792}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 244)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 244) is 35136\n\n####35136", "a": 144, "b": 244, "operator": "*", "result": 35136}
{"question": "Solve (154 - 174)", "answer": "The result of (154 - 174) is -20\n\n####-20", "a": 154, "b": 174, "operator": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 265)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 265) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 199, "b": 265, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (345 + 798)", "answer": "The result of (345 + 798) is 1143\n\n####1143", "a": 345, "b": 798, "operator": "+", "result": 1143}
{"question": "Solve (266 * 36)", "answer": "The result of (266 * 36) is 9576\n\n####9576", "a": 266, "b": 36, "operator": "*", "result": 9576}
{"question": "Solve (154 / 38)", "answer": "The result of (154 / 38) is 4.0526\n\n####4.0526", "a": 154, "b": 38, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0526}
{"question": "Solve (896 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (896 - 408) is 488\n\n####488", "a": 896, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 488}
{"question": "Solve (423 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (423 * 861) is 364203\n\n####364203", "a": 423, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 364203}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 118)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 118) is 72098\n\n####72098", "a": 611, "b": 118, "operator": "*", "result": 72098}
{"question": "Solve (351 / 503)", "answer": "The result of (351 / 503) is 0.6978\n\n####0.6978", "a": 351, "b": 503, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6978}
{"question": "Solve (402 / 70)", "answer": "The result of (402 / 70) is 5.7429\n\n####5.7429", "a": 402, "b": 70, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7429}
{"question": "Solve (756 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (756 / 276) is 2.7391\n\n####2.7391", "a": 756, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7391}
{"question": "Solve (287 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (287 / 686) is 0.4184\n\n####0.4184", "a": 287, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4184}
{"question": "Solve (682 + 860)", "answer": "The result of (682 + 860) is 1542\n\n####1542", "a": 682, "b": 860, "operator": "+", "result": 1542}
{"question": "Solve (185 * 988)", "answer": "The result of (185 * 988) is 182780\n\n####182780", "a": 185, "b": 988, "operator": "*", "result": 182780}
{"question": "Solve (264 + 747)", "answer": "The result of (264 + 747) is 1011\n\n####1011", "a": 264, "b": 747, "operator": "+", "result": 1011}
{"question": "Solve (370 / 381)", "answer": "The result of (370 / 381) is 0.9711\n\n####0.9711", "a": 370, "b": 381, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9711}
{"question": "Solve (985 * 172)", "answer": "The result of (985 * 172) is 169420\n\n####169420", "a": 985, "b": 172, "operator": "*", "result": 169420}
{"question": "Solve (341 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (341 - 756) is -415\n\n####-415", "a": 341, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -415}
{"question": "Solve (480 - 603)", "answer": "The result of (480 - 603) is -123\n\n####-123", "a": 480, "b": 603, "operator": "-", "result": -123}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 82)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 82) is 50102\n\n####50102", "a": 611, "b": 82, "operator": "*", "result": 50102}
{"question": "Solve (808 - 204)", "answer": "The result of (808 - 204) is 604\n\n####604", "a": 808, "b": 204, "operator": "-", "result": 604}
{"question": "Solve (548 + 472)", "answer": "The result of (548 + 472) is 1020\n\n####1020", "a": 548, "b": 472, "operator": "+", "result": 1020}
{"question": "Solve (61 / 930)", "answer": "The result of (61 / 930) is 0.0656\n\n####0.0656", "a": 61, "b": 930, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0656}
{"question": "Solve (958 / 387)", "answer": "The result of (958 / 387) is 2.4755\n\n####2.4755", "a": 958, "b": 387, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4755}
{"question": "Solve (495 - 29)", "answer": "The result of (495 - 29) is 466\n\n####466", "a": 495, "b": 29, "operator": "-", "result": 466}
{"question": "Solve (342 - 236)", "answer": "The result of (342 - 236) is 106\n\n####106", "a": 342, "b": 236, "operator": "-", "result": 106}
{"question": "Solve (649 + 59)", "answer": "The result of (649 + 59) is 708\n\n####708", "a": 649, "b": 59, "operator": "+", "result": 708}
{"question": "Solve (568 / 859)", "answer": "The result of (568 / 859) is 0.6612\n\n####0.6612", "a": 568, "b": 859, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6612}
{"question": "Solve (367 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (367 - 321) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 367, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (433 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (433 - 810) is -377\n\n####-377", "a": 433, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": -377}
{"question": "Solve (755 / 610)", "answer": "The result of (755 / 610) is 1.2377\n\n####1.2377", "a": 755, "b": 610, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2377}
{"question": "Solve (140 - 613)", "answer": "The result of (140 - 613) is -473\n\n####-473", "a": 140, "b": 613, "operator": "-", "result": -473}
{"question": "Solve (942 / 763)", "answer": "The result of (942 / 763) is 1.2346\n\n####1.2346", "a": 942, "b": 763, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2346}
{"question": "Solve (139 * 989)", "answer": "The result of (139 * 989) is 137471\n\n####137471", "a": 139, "b": 989, "operator": "*", "result": 137471}
{"question": "Solve (790 + 990)", "answer": "The result of (790 + 990) is 1780\n\n####1780", "a": 790, "b": 990, "operator": "+", "result": 1780}
{"question": "Solve (973 - 88)", "answer": "The result of (973 - 88) is 885\n\n####885", "a": 973, "b": 88, "operator": "-", "result": 885}
{"question": "Solve (124 + 113)", "answer": "The result of (124 + 113) is 237\n\n####237", "a": 124, "b": 113, "operator": "+", "result": 237}
{"question": "Solve (875 * 571)", "answer": "The result of (875 * 571) is 499625\n\n####499625", "a": 875, "b": 571, "operator": "*", "result": 499625}
{"question": "Solve (439 * 521)", "answer": "The result of (439 * 521) is 228719\n\n####228719", "a": 439, "b": 521, "operator": "*", "result": 228719}
{"question": "Solve (657 - 793)", "answer": "The result of (657 - 793) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 657, "b": 793, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (955 * 645)", "answer": "The result of (955 * 645) is 615975\n\n####615975", "a": 955, "b": 645, "operator": "*", "result": 615975}
{"question": "Solve (67 * 875)", "answer": "The result of (67 * 875) is 58625\n\n####58625", "a": 67, "b": 875, "operator": "*", "result": 58625}
{"question": "Solve (976 + 175)", "answer": "The result of (976 + 175) is 1151\n\n####1151", "a": 976, "b": 175, "operator": "+", "result": 1151}
{"question": "Solve (556 * 634)", "answer": "The result of (556 * 634) is 352504\n\n####352504", "a": 556, "b": 634, "operator": "*", "result": 352504}
{"question": "Solve (884 - 674)", "answer": "The result of (884 - 674) is 210\n\n####210", "a": 884, "b": 674, "operator": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve (935 - 583)", "answer": "The result of (935 - 583) is 352\n\n####352", "a": 935, "b": 583, "operator": "-", "result": 352}
{"question": "Solve (803 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (803 - 238) is 565\n\n####565", "a": 803, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 565}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 787)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 787) is -24\n\n####-24", "a": 763, "b": 787, "operator": "-", "result": -24}
{"question": "Solve (110 * 864)", "answer": "The result of (110 * 864) is 95040\n\n####95040", "a": 110, "b": 864, "operator": "*", "result": 95040}
{"question": "Solve (476 + 154)", "answer": "The result of (476 + 154) is 630\n\n####630", "a": 476, "b": 154, "operator": "+", "result": 630}
{"question": "Solve (408 / 114)", "answer": "The result of (408 / 114) is 3.5789\n\n####3.5789", "a": 408, "b": 114, "operator": "/", "result": 3.5789}
{"question": "Solve (612 * 358)", "answer": "The result of (612 * 358) is 219096\n\n####219096", "a": 612, "b": 358, "operator": "*", "result": 219096}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 36)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 36) is 4.5833\n\n####4.5833", "a": 165, "b": 36, "operator": "/", "result": 4.5833}
{"question": "Solve (9 * 404)", "answer": "The result of (9 * 404) is 3636\n\n####3636", "a": 9, "b": 404, "operator": "*", "result": 3636}
{"question": "Solve (239 + 157)", "answer": "The result of (239 + 157) is 396\n\n####396", "a": 239, "b": 157, "operator": "+", "result": 396}
{"question": "Solve (925 + 682)", "answer": "The result of (925 + 682) is 1607\n\n####1607", "a": 925, "b": 682, "operator": "+", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 131)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 131) is -91\n\n####-91", "a": 40, "b": 131, "operator": "-", "result": -91}
{"question": "Solve (517 / 142)", "answer": "The result of (517 / 142) is 3.6408\n\n####3.6408", "a": 517, "b": 142, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6408}
{"question": "Solve (341 / 661)", "answer": "The result of (341 / 661) is 0.5159\n\n####0.5159", "a": 341, "b": 661, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5159}
{"question": "Solve (141 * 157)", "answer": "The result of (141 * 157) is 22137\n\n####22137", "a": 141, "b": 157, "operator": "*", "result": 22137}
{"question": "Solve (630 / 939)", "answer": "The result of (630 / 939) is 0.6709\n\n####0.6709", "a": 630, "b": 939, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6709}
{"question": "Solve (699 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (699 - 210) is 489\n\n####489", "a": 699, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": 489}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 816)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 816) is 1683\n\n####1683", "a": 867, "b": 816, "operator": "+", "result": 1683}
{"question": "Solve (497 / 955)", "answer": "The result of (497 / 955) is 0.5204\n\n####0.5204", "a": 497, "b": 955, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5204}
{"question": "Solve (680 / 211)", "answer": "The result of (680 / 211) is 3.2227\n\n####3.2227", "a": 680, "b": 211, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2227}
{"question": "Solve (231 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (231 - 849) is -618\n\n####-618", "a": 231, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -618}
{"question": "Solve (138 / 872)", "answer": "The result of (138 / 872) is 0.1583\n\n####0.1583", "a": 138, "b": 872, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1583}
{"question": "Solve (389 - 757)", "answer": "The result of (389 - 757) is -368\n\n####-368", "a": 389, "b": 757, "operator": "-", "result": -368}
{"question": "Solve (736 / 377)", "answer": "The result of (736 / 377) is 1.9523\n\n####1.9523", "a": 736, "b": 377, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9523}
{"question": "Solve (152 - 678)", "answer": "The result of (152 - 678) is -526\n\n####-526", "a": 152, "b": 678, "operator": "-", "result": -526}
{"question": "Solve (591 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (591 - 745) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 591, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (432 + 133)", "answer": "The result of (432 + 133) is 565\n\n####565", "a": 432, "b": 133, "operator": "+", "result": 565}
{"question": "Solve (742 - 241)", "answer": "The result of (742 - 241) is 501\n\n####501", "a": 742, "b": 241, "operator": "-", "result": 501}
{"question": "Solve (9 / 54)", "answer": "The result of (9 / 54) is 0.1667\n\n####0.1667", "a": 9, "b": 54, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1667}
{"question": "Solve (742 * 735)", "answer": "The result of (742 * 735) is 545370\n\n####545370", "a": 742, "b": 735, "operator": "*", "result": 545370}
{"question": "Solve (802 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (802 - 537) is 265\n\n####265", "a": 802, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve (268 + 402)", "answer": "The result of (268 + 402) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 268, "b": 402, "operator": "+", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (49 * 454)", "answer": "The result of (49 * 454) is 22246\n\n####22246", "a": 49, "b": 454, "operator": "*", "result": 22246}
{"question": "Solve (427 / 128)", "answer": "The result of (427 / 128) is 3.3359\n\n####3.3359", "a": 427, "b": 128, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3359}
{"question": "Solve (581 * 298)", "answer": "The result of (581 * 298) is 173138\n\n####173138", "a": 581, "b": 298, "operator": "*", "result": 173138}
{"question": "Solve (283 + 294)", "answer": "The result of (283 + 294) is 577\n\n####577", "a": 283, "b": 294, "operator": "+", "result": 577}
{"question": "Solve (514 / 699)", "answer": "The result of (514 / 699) is 0.7353\n\n####0.7353", "a": 514, "b": 699, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7353}
{"question": "Solve (587 * 685)", "answer": "The result of (587 * 685) is 402095\n\n####402095", "a": 587, "b": 685, "operator": "*", "result": 402095}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 492)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 492) is 56580\n\n####56580", "a": 115, "b": 492, "operator": "*", "result": 56580}
{"question": "Solve (709 / 105)", "answer": "The result of (709 / 105) is 6.7524\n\n####6.7524", "a": 709, "b": 105, "operator": "/", "result": 6.7524}
{"question": "Solve (317 - 694)", "answer": "The result of (317 - 694) is -377\n\n####-377", "a": 317, "b": 694, "operator": "-", "result": -377}
{"question": "Solve (17 + 984)", "answer": "The result of (17 + 984) is 1001\n\n####1001", "a": 17, "b": 984, "operator": "+", "result": 1001}
{"question": "Solve (911 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (911 - 949) is -38\n\n####-38", "a": 911, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve (687 - 955)", "answer": "The result of (687 - 955) is -268\n\n####-268", "a": 687, "b": 955, "operator": "-", "result": -268}
{"question": "Solve (278 / 601)", "answer": "The result of (278 / 601) is 0.4626\n\n####0.4626", "a": 278, "b": 601, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4626}
{"question": "Solve (678 + 984)", "answer": "The result of (678 + 984) is 1662\n\n####1662", "a": 678, "b": 984, "operator": "+", "result": 1662}
{"question": "Solve (634 + 252)", "answer": "The result of (634 + 252) is 886\n\n####886", "a": 634, "b": 252, "operator": "+", "result": 886}
{"question": "Solve (839 * 224)", "answer": "The result of (839 * 224) is 187936\n\n####187936", "a": 839, "b": 224, "operator": "*", "result": 187936}
{"question": "Solve (845 / 766)", "answer": "The result of (845 / 766) is 1.1031\n\n####1.1031", "a": 845, "b": 766, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1031}
{"question": "Solve (465 / 348)", "answer": "The result of (465 / 348) is 1.3362\n\n####1.3362", "a": 465, "b": 348, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3362}
{"question": "Solve (143 * 652)", "answer": "The result of (143 * 652) is 93236\n\n####93236", "a": 143, "b": 652, "operator": "*", "result": 93236}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 468)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 468) is 0.188\n\n####0.188", "a": 88, "b": 468, "operator": "/", "result": 0.188}
{"question": "Solve (634 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (634 / 669) is 0.9477\n\n####0.9477", "a": 634, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9477}
{"question": "Solve (683 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (683 - 384) is 299\n\n####299", "a": 683, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": 299}
{"question": "Solve (284 / 23)", "answer": "The result of (284 / 23) is 12.3478\n\n####12.3478", "a": 284, "b": 23, "operator": "/", "result": 12.3478}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 522)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 522) is -2\n\n####-2", "a": 520, "b": 522, "operator": "-", "result": -2}
{"question": "Solve (142 / 949)", "answer": "The result of (142 / 949) is 0.1496\n\n####0.1496", "a": 142, "b": 949, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1496}
{"question": "Solve (77 / 541)", "answer": "The result of (77 / 541) is 0.1423\n\n####0.1423", "a": 77, "b": 541, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1423}
{"question": "Solve (345 * 23)", "answer": "The result of (345 * 23) is 7935\n\n####7935", "a": 345, "b": 23, "operator": "*", "result": 7935}
{"question": "Solve (248 * 735)", "answer": "The result of (248 * 735) is 182280\n\n####182280", "a": 248, "b": 735, "operator": "*", "result": 182280}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 637) is 333151\n\n####333151", "a": 523, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 333151}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 296)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 296) is 634\n\n####634", "a": 930, "b": 296, "operator": "-", "result": 634}
{"question": "Solve (808 * 403)", "answer": "The result of (808 * 403) is 325624\n\n####325624", "a": 808, "b": 403, "operator": "*", "result": 325624}
{"question": "Solve (425 * 916)", "answer": "The result of (425 * 916) is 389300\n\n####389300", "a": 425, "b": 916, "operator": "*", "result": 389300}
{"question": "Solve (442 + 491)", "answer": "The result of (442 + 491) is 933\n\n####933", "a": 442, "b": 491, "operator": "+", "result": 933}
{"question": "Solve (23 - 952)", "answer": "The result of (23 - 952) is -929\n\n####-929", "a": 23, "b": 952, "operator": "-", "result": -929}
{"question": "Solve (727 - 982)", "answer": "The result of (727 - 982) is -255\n\n####-255", "a": 727, "b": 982, "operator": "-", "result": -255}
{"question": "Solve (952 + 517)", "answer": "The result of (952 + 517) is 1469\n\n####1469", "a": 952, "b": 517, "operator": "+", "result": 1469}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 777) is -737\n\n####-737", "a": 40, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -737}
{"question": "Solve (86 + 324)", "answer": "The result of (86 + 324) is 410\n\n####410", "a": 86, "b": 324, "operator": "+", "result": 410}
{"question": "Solve (919 + 565)", "answer": "The result of (919 + 565) is 1484\n\n####1484", "a": 919, "b": 565, "operator": "+", "result": 1484}
{"question": "Solve (832 + 752)", "answer": "The result of (832 + 752) is 1584\n\n####1584", "a": 832, "b": 752, "operator": "+", "result": 1584}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 40)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 40) is 221\n\n####221", "a": 181, "b": 40, "operator": "+", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve (767 - 739)", "answer": "The result of (767 - 739) is 28\n\n####28", "a": 767, "b": 739, "operator": "-", "result": 28}
{"question": "Solve (986 - 869)", "answer": "The result of (986 - 869) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 986, "b": 869, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (101 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (101 - 945) is -844\n\n####-844", "a": 101, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -844}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 745) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 358, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (544 - 575)", "answer": "The result of (544 - 575) is -31\n\n####-31", "a": 544, "b": 575, "operator": "-", "result": -31}
{"question": "Solve (226 * 217)", "answer": "The result of (226 * 217) is 49042\n\n####49042", "a": 226, "b": 217, "operator": "*", "result": 49042}
{"question": "Solve (669 + 301)", "answer": "The result of (669 + 301) is 970\n\n####970", "a": 669, "b": 301, "operator": "+", "result": 970}
{"question": "Solve (672 / 499)", "answer": "The result of (672 / 499) is 1.3467\n\n####1.3467", "a": 672, "b": 499, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3467}
{"question": "Solve (78 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (78 - 408) is -330\n\n####-330", "a": 78, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": -330}
{"question": "Solve (597 * 835)", "answer": "The result of (597 * 835) is 498495\n\n####498495", "a": 597, "b": 835, "operator": "*", "result": 498495}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 554)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 554) is 0.2455\n\n####0.2455", "a": 136, "b": 554, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2455}
{"question": "Solve (238 - 677)", "answer": "The result of (238 - 677) is -439\n\n####-439", "a": 238, "b": 677, "operator": "-", "result": -439}
{"question": "Solve (29 / 828)", "answer": "The result of (29 / 828) is 0.035\n\n####0.035", "a": 29, "b": 828, "operator": "/", "result": 0.035}
{"question": "Solve (665 + 388)", "answer": "The result of (665 + 388) is 1053\n\n####1053", "a": 665, "b": 388, "operator": "+", "result": 1053}
{"question": "Solve (320 - 975)", "answer": "The result of (320 - 975) is -655\n\n####-655", "a": 320, "b": 975, "operator": "-", "result": -655}
{"question": "Solve (695 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (695 / 623) is 1.1156\n\n####1.1156", "a": 695, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1156}
{"question": "Solve (601 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (601 / 322) is 1.8665\n\n####1.8665", "a": 601, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8665}
{"question": "Solve (787 + 431)", "answer": "The result of (787 + 431) is 1218\n\n####1218", "a": 787, "b": 431, "operator": "+", "result": 1218}
{"question": "Solve (488 / 906)", "answer": "The result of (488 / 906) is 0.5386\n\n####0.5386", "a": 488, "b": 906, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5386}
{"question": "Solve (953 + 439)", "answer": "The result of (953 + 439) is 1392\n\n####1392", "a": 953, "b": 439, "operator": "+", "result": 1392}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 754)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 754) is -446\n\n####-446", "a": 308, "b": 754, "operator": "-", "result": -446}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 434)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 434) is 2.1152\n\n####2.1152", "a": 918, "b": 434, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1152}
{"question": "Solve (546 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (546 * 861) is 470106\n\n####470106", "a": 546, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 470106}
{"question": "Solve (126 / 892)", "answer": "The result of (126 / 892) is 0.1413\n\n####0.1413", "a": 126, "b": 892, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1413}
{"question": "Solve (239 * 811)", "answer": "The result of (239 * 811) is 193829\n\n####193829", "a": 239, "b": 811, "operator": "*", "result": 193829}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 146)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 146) is 110230\n\n####110230", "a": 755, "b": 146, "operator": "*", "result": 110230}
{"question": "Solve (939 * 672)", "answer": "The result of (939 * 672) is 631008\n\n####631008", "a": 939, "b": 672, "operator": "*", "result": 631008}
{"question": "Solve (221 / 770)", "answer": "The result of (221 / 770) is 0.287\n\n####0.287", "a": 221, "b": 770, "operator": "/", "result": 0.287}
{"question": "Solve (567 * 889)", "answer": "The result of (567 * 889) is 504063\n\n####504063", "a": 567, "b": 889, "operator": "*", "result": 504063}
{"question": "Solve (878 - 128)", "answer": "The result of (878 - 128) is 750\n\n####750", "a": 878, "b": 128, "operator": "-", "result": 750}
{"question": "Solve (188 / 57)", "answer": "The result of (188 / 57) is 3.2982\n\n####3.2982", "a": 188, "b": 57, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2982}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 741)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 741) is -133\n\n####-133", "a": 608, "b": 741, "operator": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve (45 / 495)", "answer": "The result of (45 / 495) is 0.0909\n\n####0.0909", "a": 45, "b": 495, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0909}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 855)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 855) is 1516\n\n####1516", "a": 661, "b": 855, "operator": "+", "result": 1516}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 797)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 797) is 1.197\n\n####1.197", "a": 954, "b": 797, "operator": "/", "result": 1.197}
{"question": "Solve (31 - 104)", "answer": "The result of (31 - 104) is -73\n\n####-73", "a": 31, "b": 104, "operator": "-", "result": -73}
{"question": "Solve (69 + 530)", "answer": "The result of (69 + 530) is 599\n\n####599", "a": 69, "b": 530, "operator": "+", "result": 599}
{"question": "Solve (800 + 505)", "answer": "The result of (800 + 505) is 1305\n\n####1305", "a": 800, "b": 505, "operator": "+", "result": 1305}
{"question": "Solve (198 - 728)", "answer": "The result of (198 - 728) is -530\n\n####-530", "a": 198, "b": 728, "operator": "-", "result": -530}
{"question": "Solve (535 / 104)", "answer": "The result of (535 / 104) is 5.1442\n\n####5.1442", "a": 535, "b": 104, "operator": "/", "result": 5.1442}
{"question": "Solve (352 + 677)", "answer": "The result of (352 + 677) is 1029\n\n####1029", "a": 352, "b": 677, "operator": "+", "result": 1029}
{"question": "Solve (775 - 116)", "answer": "The result of (775 - 116) is 659\n\n####659", "a": 775, "b": 116, "operator": "-", "result": 659}
{"question": "Solve (109 - 225)", "answer": "The result of (109 - 225) is -116\n\n####-116", "a": 109, "b": 225, "operator": "-", "result": -116}
{"question": "Solve (469 - 606)", "answer": "The result of (469 - 606) is -137\n\n####-137", "a": 469, "b": 606, "operator": "-", "result": -137}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 34)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 34) is 13.5294\n\n####13.5294", "a": 460, "b": 34, "operator": "/", "result": 13.5294}
{"question": "Solve (948 * 970)", "answer": "The result of (948 * 970) is 919560\n\n####919560", "a": 948, "b": 970, "operator": "*", "result": 919560}
{"question": "Solve (776 - 995)", "answer": "The result of (776 - 995) is -219\n\n####-219", "a": 776, "b": 995, "operator": "-", "result": -219}
{"question": "Solve (972 * 290)", "answer": "The result of (972 * 290) is 281880\n\n####281880", "a": 972, "b": 290, "operator": "*", "result": 281880}
{"question": "Solve (31 * 421)", "answer": "The result of (31 * 421) is 13051\n\n####13051", "a": 31, "b": 421, "operator": "*", "result": 13051}
{"question": "Solve (736 + 947)", "answer": "The result of (736 + 947) is 1683\n\n####1683", "a": 736, "b": 947, "operator": "+", "result": 1683}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 528)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 528) is 60720\n\n####60720", "a": 115, "b": 528, "operator": "*", "result": 60720}
{"question": "Solve (807 / 106)", "answer": "The result of (807 / 106) is 7.6132\n\n####7.6132", "a": 807, "b": 106, "operator": "/", "result": 7.6132}
{"question": "Solve (373 * 433)", "answer": "The result of (373 * 433) is 161509\n\n####161509", "a": 373, "b": 433, "operator": "*", "result": 161509}
{"question": "Solve (436 * 706)", "answer": "The result of (436 * 706) is 307816\n\n####307816", "a": 436, "b": 706, "operator": "*", "result": 307816}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 376) is 1.8298\n\n####1.8298", "a": 688, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8298}
{"question": "Solve (162 / 682)", "answer": "The result of (162 / 682) is 0.2375\n\n####0.2375", "a": 162, "b": 682, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2375}
{"question": "Solve (588 + 562)", "answer": "The result of (588 + 562) is 1150\n\n####1150", "a": 588, "b": 562, "operator": "+", "result": 1150}
{"question": "Solve (896 / 62)", "answer": "The result of (896 / 62) is 14.4516\n\n####14.4516", "a": 896, "b": 62, "operator": "/", "result": 14.4516}
{"question": "Solve (172 * 577)", "answer": "The result of (172 * 577) is 99244\n\n####99244", "a": 172, "b": 577, "operator": "*", "result": 99244}
{"question": "Solve (176 / 666)", "answer": "The result of (176 / 666) is 0.2643\n\n####0.2643", "a": 176, "b": 666, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2643}
{"question": "Solve (436 / 268)", "answer": "The result of (436 / 268) is 1.6269\n\n####1.6269", "a": 436, "b": 268, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6269}
{"question": "Solve (264 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (264 - 117) is 147\n\n####147", "a": 264, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve (156 * 426)", "answer": "The result of (156 * 426) is 66456\n\n####66456", "a": 156, "b": 426, "operator": "*", "result": 66456}
{"question": "Solve (121 / 923)", "answer": "The result of (121 / 923) is 0.1311\n\n####0.1311", "a": 121, "b": 923, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1311}
{"question": "Solve (121 + 815)", "answer": "The result of (121 + 815) is 936\n\n####936", "a": 121, "b": 815, "operator": "+", "result": 936}
{"question": "Solve (897 + 93)", "answer": "The result of (897 + 93) is 990\n\n####990", "a": 897, "b": 93, "operator": "+", "result": 990}
{"question": "Solve (877 + 592)", "answer": "The result of (877 + 592) is 1469\n\n####1469", "a": 877, "b": 592, "operator": "+", "result": 1469}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 825)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 825) is 483450\n\n####483450", "a": 586, "b": 825, "operator": "*", "result": 483450}
{"question": "Solve (455 + 650)", "answer": "The result of (455 + 650) is 1105\n\n####1105", "a": 455, "b": 650, "operator": "+", "result": 1105}
{"question": "Solve (93 + 368)", "answer": "The result of (93 + 368) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 93, "b": 368, "operator": "+", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (558 / 989)", "answer": "The result of (558 / 989) is 0.5642\n\n####0.5642", "a": 558, "b": 989, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5642}
{"question": "Solve (749 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (749 - 233) is 516\n\n####516", "a": 749, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": 516}
{"question": "Solve (479 / 246)", "answer": "The result of (479 / 246) is 1.9472\n\n####1.9472", "a": 479, "b": 246, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9472}
{"question": "Solve (49 + 135)", "answer": "The result of (49 + 135) is 184\n\n####184", "a": 49, "b": 135, "operator": "+", "result": 184}
{"question": "Solve (779 * 615)", "answer": "The result of (779 * 615) is 479085\n\n####479085", "a": 779, "b": 615, "operator": "*", "result": 479085}
{"question": "Solve (492 / 337)", "answer": "The result of (492 / 337) is 1.4599\n\n####1.4599", "a": 492, "b": 337, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4599}
{"question": "Solve (53 * 113)", "answer": "The result of (53 * 113) is 5989\n\n####5989", "a": 53, "b": 113, "operator": "*", "result": 5989}
{"question": "Solve (17 + 279)", "answer": "The result of (17 + 279) is 296\n\n####296", "a": 17, "b": 279, "operator": "+", "result": 296}
{"question": "Solve (411 / 846)", "answer": "The result of (411 / 846) is 0.4858\n\n####0.4858", "a": 411, "b": 846, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4858}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 583)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 583) is 15\n\n####15", "a": 598, "b": 583, "operator": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 41)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 41) is 28372\n\n####28372", "a": 692, "b": 41, "operator": "*", "result": 28372}
{"question": "Solve (131 / 428)", "answer": "The result of (131 / 428) is 0.3061\n\n####0.3061", "a": 131, "b": 428, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3061}
{"question": "Solve (573 - 187)", "answer": "The result of (573 - 187) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 573, "b": 187, "operator": "-", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (220 / 540)", "answer": "The result of (220 / 540) is 0.4074\n\n####0.4074", "a": 220, "b": 540, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4074}
{"question": "Solve (503 - 521)", "answer": "The result of (503 - 521) is -18\n\n####-18", "a": 503, "b": 521, "operator": "-", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve (346 + 278)", "answer": "The result of (346 + 278) is 624\n\n####624", "a": 346, "b": 278, "operator": "+", "result": 624}
{"question": "Solve (938 * 625)", "answer": "The result of (938 * 625) is 586250\n\n####586250", "a": 938, "b": 625, "operator": "*", "result": 586250}
{"question": "Solve (691 / 147)", "answer": "The result of (691 / 147) is 4.7007\n\n####4.7007", "a": 691, "b": 147, "operator": "/", "result": 4.7007}
{"question": "Solve (765 / 963)", "answer": "The result of (765 / 963) is 0.7944\n\n####0.7944", "a": 765, "b": 963, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7944}
{"question": "Solve (73 - 534)", "answer": "The result of (73 - 534) is -461\n\n####-461", "a": 73, "b": 534, "operator": "-", "result": -461}
{"question": "Solve (549 + 724)", "answer": "The result of (549 + 724) is 1273\n\n####1273", "a": 549, "b": 724, "operator": "+", "result": 1273}
{"question": "Solve (135 - 258)", "answer": "The result of (135 - 258) is -123\n\n####-123", "a": 135, "b": 258, "operator": "-", "result": -123}
{"question": "Solve (529 / 254)", "answer": "The result of (529 / 254) is 2.0827\n\n####2.0827", "a": 529, "b": 254, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0827}
{"question": "Solve (678 - 73)", "answer": "The result of (678 - 73) is 605\n\n####605", "a": 678, "b": 73, "operator": "-", "result": 605}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 586)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 586) is 1.2969\n\n####1.2969", "a": 760, "b": 586, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2969}
{"question": "Solve (779 * 24)", "answer": "The result of (779 * 24) is 18696\n\n####18696", "a": 779, "b": 24, "operator": "*", "result": 18696}
{"question": "Solve (397 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (397 + 31) is 428\n\n####428", "a": 397, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 428}
{"question": "Solve (278 - 102)", "answer": "The result of (278 - 102) is 176\n\n####176", "a": 278, "b": 102, "operator": "-", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve (794 * 278)", "answer": "The result of (794 * 278) is 220732\n\n####220732", "a": 794, "b": 278, "operator": "*", "result": 220732}
{"question": "Solve (195 / 632)", "answer": "The result of (195 / 632) is 0.3085\n\n####0.3085", "a": 195, "b": 632, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3085}
{"question": "Solve (298 + 423)", "answer": "The result of (298 + 423) is 721\n\n####721", "a": 298, "b": 423, "operator": "+", "result": 721}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 267)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 267) is 496\n\n####496", "a": 763, "b": 267, "operator": "-", "result": 496}
{"question": "Solve (385 + 652)", "answer": "The result of (385 + 652) is 1037\n\n####1037", "a": 385, "b": 652, "operator": "+", "result": 1037}
{"question": "Solve (945 / 966)", "answer": "The result of (945 / 966) is 0.9783\n\n####0.9783", "a": 945, "b": 966, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9783}
{"question": "Solve (323 * 237)", "answer": "The result of (323 * 237) is 76551\n\n####76551", "a": 323, "b": 237, "operator": "*", "result": 76551}
{"question": "Solve (53 / 833)", "answer": "The result of (53 / 833) is 0.0636\n\n####0.0636", "a": 53, "b": 833, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0636}
{"question": "Solve (715 + 975)", "answer": "The result of (715 + 975) is 1690\n\n####1690", "a": 715, "b": 975, "operator": "+", "result": 1690}
{"question": "Solve (428 + 906)", "answer": "The result of (428 + 906) is 1334\n\n####1334", "a": 428, "b": 906, "operator": "+", "result": 1334}
{"question": "Solve (418 / 103)", "answer": "The result of (418 / 103) is 4.0583\n\n####4.0583", "a": 418, "b": 103, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0583}
{"question": "Solve (894 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (894 / 230) is 3.887\n\n####3.887", "a": 894, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 3.887}
{"question": "Solve (108 / 709)", "answer": "The result of (108 / 709) is 0.1523\n\n####0.1523", "a": 108, "b": 709, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1523}
{"question": "Solve (561 - 970)", "answer": "The result of (561 - 970) is -409\n\n####-409", "a": 561, "b": 970, "operator": "-", "result": -409}
{"question": "Solve (970 + 915)", "answer": "The result of (970 + 915) is 1885\n\n####1885", "a": 970, "b": 915, "operator": "+", "result": 1885}
{"question": "Solve (632 / 22)", "answer": "The result of (632 / 22) is 28.7273\n\n####28.7273", "a": 632, "b": 22, "operator": "/", "result": 28.7273}
{"question": "Solve (673 * 161)", "answer": "The result of (673 * 161) is 108353\n\n####108353", "a": 673, "b": 161, "operator": "*", "result": 108353}
{"question": "Solve (816 - 351)", "answer": "The result of (816 - 351) is 465\n\n####465", "a": 816, "b": 351, "operator": "-", "result": 465}
{"question": "Solve (464 - 401)", "answer": "The result of (464 - 401) is 63\n\n####63", "a": 464, "b": 401, "operator": "-", "result": 63}
{"question": "Solve (463 - 267)", "answer": "The result of (463 - 267) is 196\n\n####196", "a": 463, "b": 267, "operator": "-", "result": 196}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 892)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 892) is 811720\n\n####811720", "a": 910, "b": 892, "operator": "*", "result": 811720}
{"question": "Solve (764 + 319)", "answer": "The result of (764 + 319) is 1083\n\n####1083", "a": 764, "b": 319, "operator": "+", "result": 1083}
{"question": "Solve (871 / 962)", "answer": "The result of (871 / 962) is 0.9054\n\n####0.9054", "a": 871, "b": 962, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9054}
{"question": "Solve (793 / 941)", "answer": "The result of (793 / 941) is 0.8427\n\n####0.8427", "a": 793, "b": 941, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8427}
{"question": "Solve (963 / 722)", "answer": "The result of (963 / 722) is 1.3338\n\n####1.3338", "a": 963, "b": 722, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3338}
{"question": "Solve (147 / 639)", "answer": "The result of (147 / 639) is 0.23\n\n####0.23", "a": 147, "b": 639, "operator": "/", "result": 0.23}
{"question": "Solve (330 - 188)", "answer": "The result of (330 - 188) is 142\n\n####142", "a": 330, "b": 188, "operator": "-", "result": 142}
{"question": "Solve (34 - 511)", "answer": "The result of (34 - 511) is -477\n\n####-477", "a": 34, "b": 511, "operator": "-", "result": -477}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 713)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 713) is 115\n\n####115", "a": 828, "b": 713, "operator": "-", "result": 115}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 673)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 673) is 249\n\n####249", "a": 922, "b": 673, "operator": "-", "result": 249}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 288)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 288) is 0.4722\n\n####0.4722", "a": 136, "b": 288, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4722}
{"question": "Solve (871 * 907)", "answer": "The result of (871 * 907) is 789997\n\n####789997", "a": 871, "b": 907, "operator": "*", "result": 789997}
{"question": "Solve (444 * 734)", "answer": "The result of (444 * 734) is 325896\n\n####325896", "a": 444, "b": 734, "operator": "*", "result": 325896}
{"question": "Solve (460 - 54)", "answer": "The result of (460 - 54) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 460, "b": 54, "operator": "-", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (218 + 407)", "answer": "The result of (218 + 407) is 625\n\n####625", "a": 218, "b": 407, "operator": "+", "result": 625}
{"question": "Solve (696 / 404)", "answer": "The result of (696 / 404) is 1.7228\n\n####1.7228", "a": 696, "b": 404, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7228}
{"question": "Solve (923 / 748)", "answer": "The result of (923 / 748) is 1.234\n\n####1.234", "a": 923, "b": 748, "operator": "/", "result": 1.234}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 215)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 215) is 1.2512\n\n####1.2512", "a": 269, "b": 215, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2512}
{"question": "Solve (611 - 956)", "answer": "The result of (611 - 956) is -345\n\n####-345", "a": 611, "b": 956, "operator": "-", "result": -345}
{"question": "Solve (28 / 364)", "answer": "The result of (28 / 364) is 0.0769\n\n####0.0769", "a": 28, "b": 364, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0769}
{"question": "Solve (687 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (687 / 475) is 1.4463\n\n####1.4463", "a": 687, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4463}
{"question": "Solve (154 * 111)", "answer": "The result of (154 * 111) is 17094\n\n####17094", "a": 154, "b": 111, "operator": "*", "result": 17094}
{"question": "Solve (385 * 856)", "answer": "The result of (385 * 856) is 329560\n\n####329560", "a": 385, "b": 856, "operator": "*", "result": 329560}
{"question": "Solve (88 - 214)", "answer": "The result of (88 - 214) is -126\n\n####-126", "a": 88, "b": 214, "operator": "-", "result": -126}
{"question": "Solve (930 / 461)", "answer": "The result of (930 / 461) is 2.0174\n\n####2.0174", "a": 930, "b": 461, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0174}
{"question": "Solve (324 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (324 + 487) is 811\n\n####811", "a": 324, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 811}
{"question": "Solve (334 * 569)", "answer": "The result of (334 * 569) is 190046\n\n####190046", "a": 334, "b": 569, "operator": "*", "result": 190046}
{"question": "Solve (80 - 633)", "answer": "The result of (80 - 633) is -553\n\n####-553", "a": 80, "b": 633, "operator": "-", "result": -553}
{"question": "Solve (52 + 540)", "answer": "The result of (52 + 540) is 592\n\n####592", "a": 52, "b": 540, "operator": "+", "result": 592}
{"question": "Solve (256 * 120)", "answer": "The result of (256 * 120) is 30720\n\n####30720", "a": 256, "b": 120, "operator": "*", "result": 30720}
{"question": "Solve (377 - 631)", "answer": "The result of (377 - 631) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 377, "b": 631, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (318 * 709)", "answer": "The result of (318 * 709) is 225462\n\n####225462", "a": 318, "b": 709, "operator": "*", "result": 225462}
{"question": "Solve (125 / 422)", "answer": "The result of (125 / 422) is 0.2962\n\n####0.2962", "a": 125, "b": 422, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2962}
{"question": "Solve (888 + 337)", "answer": "The result of (888 + 337) is 1225\n\n####1225", "a": 888, "b": 337, "operator": "+", "result": 1225}
{"question": "Solve (875 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (875 * 698) is 610750\n\n####610750", "a": 875, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 610750}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 501)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 501) is 220\n\n####220", "a": 721, "b": 501, "operator": "-", "result": 220}
{"question": "Solve (221 / 599)", "answer": "The result of (221 / 599) is 0.3689\n\n####0.3689", "a": 221, "b": 599, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3689}
{"question": "Solve (427 - 432)", "answer": "The result of (427 - 432) is -5\n\n####-5", "a": 427, "b": 432, "operator": "-", "result": -5}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 944) is 539024\n\n####539024", "a": 571, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 539024}
{"question": "Solve (115 / 92)", "answer": "The result of (115 / 92) is 1.25\n\n####1.25", "a": 115, "b": 92, "operator": "/", "result": 1.25}
{"question": "Solve (615 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (615 / 504) is 1.2202\n\n####1.2202", "a": 615, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2202}
{"question": "Solve (699 - 315)", "answer": "The result of (699 - 315) is 384\n\n####384", "a": 699, "b": 315, "operator": "-", "result": 384}
{"question": "Solve (472 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (472 - 409) is 63\n\n####63", "a": 472, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": 63}
{"question": "Solve (654 + 582)", "answer": "The result of (654 + 582) is 1236\n\n####1236", "a": 654, "b": 582, "operator": "+", "result": 1236}
{"question": "Solve (765 + 696)", "answer": "The result of (765 + 696) is 1461\n\n####1461", "a": 765, "b": 696, "operator": "+", "result": 1461}
{"question": "Solve (721 + 778)", "answer": "The result of (721 + 778) is 1499\n\n####1499", "a": 721, "b": 778, "operator": "+", "result": 1499}
{"question": "Solve (794 - 991)", "answer": "The result of (794 - 991) is -197\n\n####-197", "a": 794, "b": 991, "operator": "-", "result": -197}
{"question": "Solve (410 - 361)", "answer": "The result of (410 - 361) is 49\n\n####49", "a": 410, "b": 361, "operator": "-", "result": 49}
{"question": "Solve (851 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (851 + 245) is 1096\n\n####1096", "a": 851, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 1096}
{"question": "Solve (75 - 181)", "answer": "The result of (75 - 181) is -106\n\n####-106", "a": 75, "b": 181, "operator": "-", "result": -106}
{"question": "Solve (834 / 716)", "answer": "The result of (834 / 716) is 1.1648\n\n####1.1648", "a": 834, "b": 716, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1648}
{"question": "Solve (687 / 527)", "answer": "The result of (687 / 527) is 1.3036\n\n####1.3036", "a": 687, "b": 527, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3036}
{"question": "Solve (751 / 446)", "answer": "The result of (751 / 446) is 1.6839\n\n####1.6839", "a": 751, "b": 446, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6839}
{"question": "Solve (440 * 766)", "answer": "The result of (440 * 766) is 337040\n\n####337040", "a": 440, "b": 766, "operator": "*", "result": 337040}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 48)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 48) is 27072\n\n####27072", "a": 564, "b": 48, "operator": "*", "result": 27072}
{"question": "Solve (562 - 645)", "answer": "The result of (562 - 645) is -83\n\n####-83", "a": 562, "b": 645, "operator": "-", "result": -83}
{"question": "Solve (26 - 699)", "answer": "The result of (26 - 699) is -673\n\n####-673", "a": 26, "b": 699, "operator": "-", "result": -673}
{"question": "Solve (532 * 95)", "answer": "The result of (532 * 95) is 50540\n\n####50540", "a": 532, "b": 95, "operator": "*", "result": 50540}
{"question": "Solve (342 / 590)", "answer": "The result of (342 / 590) is 0.5797\n\n####0.5797", "a": 342, "b": 590, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5797}
{"question": "Solve (391 + 828)", "answer": "The result of (391 + 828) is 1219\n\n####1219", "a": 391, "b": 828, "operator": "+", "result": 1219}
{"question": "Solve (189 - 376)", "answer": "The result of (189 - 376) is -187\n\n####-187", "a": 189, "b": 376, "operator": "-", "result": -187}
{"question": "Solve (146 - 73)", "answer": "The result of (146 - 73) is 73\n\n####73", "a": 146, "b": 73, "operator": "-", "result": 73}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 23)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 23) is 8303\n\n####8303", "a": 361, "b": 23, "operator": "*", "result": 8303}
{"question": "Solve (859 * 909)", "answer": "The result of (859 * 909) is 780831\n\n####780831", "a": 859, "b": 909, "operator": "*", "result": 780831}
{"question": "Solve (520 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (520 * 939) is 488280\n\n####488280", "a": 520, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 488280}
{"question": "Solve (155 - 146)", "answer": "The result of (155 - 146) is 9\n\n####9", "a": 155, "b": 146, "operator": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve (691 + 800)", "answer": "The result of (691 + 800) is 1491\n\n####1491", "a": 691, "b": 800, "operator": "+", "result": 1491}
{"question": "Solve (4 / 383)", "answer": "The result of (4 / 383) is 0.0104\n\n####0.0104", "a": 4, "b": 383, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0104}
{"question": "Solve (536 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (536 - 937) is -401\n\n####-401", "a": 536, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -401}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 55)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 55) is 665\n\n####665", "a": 720, "b": 55, "operator": "-", "result": 665}
{"question": "Solve (22 / 958)", "answer": "The result of (22 / 958) is 0.023\n\n####0.023", "a": 22, "b": 958, "operator": "/", "result": 0.023}
{"question": "Solve (895 + 250)", "answer": "The result of (895 + 250) is 1145\n\n####1145", "a": 895, "b": 250, "operator": "+", "result": 1145}
{"question": "Solve (545 - 767)", "answer": "The result of (545 - 767) is -222\n\n####-222", "a": 545, "b": 767, "operator": "-", "result": -222}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 613)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 613) is -82\n\n####-82", "a": 531, "b": 613, "operator": "-", "result": -82}
{"question": "Solve (223 - 896)", "answer": "The result of (223 - 896) is -673\n\n####-673", "a": 223, "b": 896, "operator": "-", "result": -673}
{"question": "Solve (525 + 973)", "answer": "The result of (525 + 973) is 1498\n\n####1498", "a": 525, "b": 973, "operator": "+", "result": 1498}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 751) is -143\n\n####-143", "a": 608, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": -143}
{"question": "Solve (244 / 459)", "answer": "The result of (244 / 459) is 0.5316\n\n####0.5316", "a": 244, "b": 459, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5316}
{"question": "Solve (708 - 351)", "answer": "The result of (708 - 351) is 357\n\n####357", "a": 708, "b": 351, "operator": "-", "result": 357}
{"question": "Solve (593 * 3)", "answer": "The result of (593 * 3) is 1779\n\n####1779", "a": 593, "b": 3, "operator": "*", "result": 1779}
{"question": "Solve (19 - 864)", "answer": "The result of (19 - 864) is -845\n\n####-845", "a": 19, "b": 864, "operator": "-", "result": -845}
{"question": "Solve (111 / 742)", "answer": "The result of (111 / 742) is 0.1496\n\n####0.1496", "a": 111, "b": 742, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1496}
{"question": "Solve (363 + 439)", "answer": "The result of (363 + 439) is 802\n\n####802", "a": 363, "b": 439, "operator": "+", "result": 802}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 703)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 703) is 0.7923\n\n####0.7923", "a": 557, "b": 703, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7923}
{"question": "Solve (120 * 455)", "answer": "The result of (120 * 455) is 54600\n\n####54600", "a": 120, "b": 455, "operator": "*", "result": 54600}
{"question": "Solve (493 + 100)", "answer": "The result of (493 + 100) is 593\n\n####593", "a": 493, "b": 100, "operator": "+", "result": 593}
{"question": "Solve (430 + 787)", "answer": "The result of (430 + 787) is 1217\n\n####1217", "a": 430, "b": 787, "operator": "+", "result": 1217}
{"question": "Solve (967 - 889)", "answer": "The result of (967 - 889) is 78\n\n####78", "a": 967, "b": 889, "operator": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve (45 * 106)", "answer": "The result of (45 * 106) is 4770\n\n####4770", "a": 45, "b": 106, "operator": "*", "result": 4770}
{"question": "Solve (126 * 152)", "answer": "The result of (126 * 152) is 19152\n\n####19152", "a": 126, "b": 152, "operator": "*", "result": 19152}
{"question": "Solve (490 + 470)", "answer": "The result of (490 + 470) is 960\n\n####960", "a": 490, "b": 470, "operator": "+", "result": 960}
{"question": "Solve (688 - 847)", "answer": "The result of (688 - 847) is -159\n\n####-159", "a": 688, "b": 847, "operator": "-", "result": -159}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 550)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 550) is 1.6436\n\n####1.6436", "a": 904, "b": 550, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6436}
{"question": "Solve (709 - 781)", "answer": "The result of (709 - 781) is -72\n\n####-72", "a": 709, "b": 781, "operator": "-", "result": -72}
{"question": "Solve (91 * 847)", "answer": "The result of (91 * 847) is 77077\n\n####77077", "a": 91, "b": 847, "operator": "*", "result": 77077}
{"question": "Solve (364 - 618)", "answer": "The result of (364 - 618) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 364, "b": 618, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (968 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (968 - 471) is 497\n\n####497", "a": 968, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": 497}
{"question": "Solve (17 - 474)", "answer": "The result of (17 - 474) is -457\n\n####-457", "a": 17, "b": 474, "operator": "-", "result": -457}
{"question": "Solve (111 - 186)", "answer": "The result of (111 - 186) is -75\n\n####-75", "a": 111, "b": 186, "operator": "-", "result": -75}
{"question": "Solve (744 - 454)", "answer": "The result of (744 - 454) is 290\n\n####290", "a": 744, "b": 454, "operator": "-", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve (222 * 469)", "answer": "The result of (222 * 469) is 104118\n\n####104118", "a": 222, "b": 469, "operator": "*", "result": 104118}
{"question": "Solve (744 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (744 / 873) is 0.8522\n\n####0.8522", "a": 744, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8522}
{"question": "Solve (658 - 376)", "answer": "The result of (658 - 376) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 658, "b": 376, "operator": "-", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (356 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (356 + 239) is 595\n\n####595", "a": 356, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 595}
{"question": "Solve (323 / 830)", "answer": "The result of (323 / 830) is 0.3892\n\n####0.3892", "a": 323, "b": 830, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3892}
{"question": "Solve (694 / 684)", "answer": "The result of (694 / 684) is 1.0146\n\n####1.0146", "a": 694, "b": 684, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0146}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 586)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 586) is 1554\n\n####1554", "a": 968, "b": 586, "operator": "+", "result": 1554}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 240)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 240) is 126960\n\n####126960", "a": 529, "b": 240, "operator": "*", "result": 126960}
{"question": "Solve (572 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (572 / 701) is 0.816\n\n####0.816", "a": 572, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 0.816}
{"question": "Solve (213 / 658)", "answer": "The result of (213 / 658) is 0.3237\n\n####0.3237", "a": 213, "b": 658, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3237}
{"question": "Solve (32 + 970)", "answer": "The result of (32 + 970) is 1002\n\n####1002", "a": 32, "b": 970, "operator": "+", "result": 1002}
{"question": "Solve (371 - 739)", "answer": "The result of (371 - 739) is -368\n\n####-368", "a": 371, "b": 739, "operator": "-", "result": -368}
{"question": "Solve (963 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (963 - 452) is 511\n\n####511", "a": 963, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": 511}
{"question": "Solve (432 / 288)", "answer": "The result of (432 / 288) is 1.5\n\n####1.5", "a": 432, "b": 288, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5}
{"question": "Solve (735 * 1)", "answer": "The result of (735 * 1) is 735\n\n####735", "a": 735, "b": 1, "operator": "*", "result": 735}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 2)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 2) is 1574\n\n####1574", "a": 787, "b": 2, "operator": "*", "result": 1574}
{"question": "Solve (940 * 831)", "answer": "The result of (940 * 831) is 781140\n\n####781140", "a": 940, "b": 831, "operator": "*", "result": 781140}
{"question": "Solve (553 - 871)", "answer": "The result of (553 - 871) is -318\n\n####-318", "a": 553, "b": 871, "operator": "-", "result": -318}
{"question": "Solve (601 + 459)", "answer": "The result of (601 + 459) is 1060\n\n####1060", "a": 601, "b": 459, "operator": "+", "result": 1060}
{"question": "Solve (489 + 878)", "answer": "The result of (489 + 878) is 1367\n\n####1367", "a": 489, "b": 878, "operator": "+", "result": 1367}
{"question": "Solve (99 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (99 - 802) is -703\n\n####-703", "a": 99, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -703}
{"question": "Solve (66 - 626)", "answer": "The result of (66 - 626) is -560\n\n####-560", "a": 66, "b": 626, "operator": "-", "result": -560}
{"question": "Solve (607 - 827)", "answer": "The result of (607 - 827) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 607, "b": 827, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (818 - 559)", "answer": "The result of (818 - 559) is 259\n\n####259", "a": 818, "b": 559, "operator": "-", "result": 259}
{"question": "Solve (883 * 297)", "answer": "The result of (883 * 297) is 262251\n\n####262251", "a": 883, "b": 297, "operator": "*", "result": 262251}
{"question": "Solve (629 / 616)", "answer": "The result of (629 / 616) is 1.0211\n\n####1.0211", "a": 629, "b": 616, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0211}
{"question": "Solve (205 - 788)", "answer": "The result of (205 - 788) is -583\n\n####-583", "a": 205, "b": 788, "operator": "-", "result": -583}
{"question": "Solve (902 / 861)", "answer": "The result of (902 / 861) is 1.0476\n\n####1.0476", "a": 902, "b": 861, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0476}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 376) is 1.8537\n\n####1.8537", "a": 697, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8537}
{"question": "Solve (824 - 944)", "answer": "The result of (824 - 944) is -120\n\n####-120", "a": 824, "b": 944, "operator": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve (82 + 733)", "answer": "The result of (82 + 733) is 815\n\n####815", "a": 82, "b": 733, "operator": "+", "result": 815}
{"question": "Solve (228 / 509)", "answer": "The result of (228 / 509) is 0.4479\n\n####0.4479", "a": 228, "b": 509, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4479}
{"question": "Solve (422 + 726)", "answer": "The result of (422 + 726) is 1148\n\n####1148", "a": 422, "b": 726, "operator": "+", "result": 1148}
{"question": "Solve (248 * 462)", "answer": "The result of (248 * 462) is 114576\n\n####114576", "a": 248, "b": 462, "operator": "*", "result": 114576}
{"question": "Solve (48 + 739)", "answer": "The result of (48 + 739) is 787\n\n####787", "a": 48, "b": 739, "operator": "+", "result": 787}
{"question": "Solve (514 * 55)", "answer": "The result of (514 * 55) is 28270\n\n####28270", "a": 514, "b": 55, "operator": "*", "result": 28270}
{"question": "Solve (951 - 746)", "answer": "The result of (951 - 746) is 205\n\n####205", "a": 951, "b": 746, "operator": "-", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 958)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 958) is -282\n\n####-282", "a": 676, "b": 958, "operator": "-", "result": -282}
{"question": "Solve (851 * 574)", "answer": "The result of (851 * 574) is 488474\n\n####488474", "a": 851, "b": 574, "operator": "*", "result": 488474}
{"question": "Solve (191 * 391)", "answer": "The result of (191 * 391) is 74681\n\n####74681", "a": 191, "b": 391, "operator": "*", "result": 74681}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 65)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 65) is 68\n\n####68", "a": 3, "b": 65, "operator": "+", "result": 68}
{"question": "Solve (953 - 486)", "answer": "The result of (953 - 486) is 467\n\n####467", "a": 953, "b": 486, "operator": "-", "result": 467}
{"question": "Solve (305 / 745)", "answer": "The result of (305 / 745) is 0.4094\n\n####0.4094", "a": 305, "b": 745, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4094}
{"question": "Solve (26 + 497)", "answer": "The result of (26 + 497) is 523\n\n####523", "a": 26, "b": 497, "operator": "+", "result": 523}
{"question": "Solve (174 - 457)", "answer": "The result of (174 - 457) is -283\n\n####-283", "a": 174, "b": 457, "operator": "-", "result": -283}
{"question": "Solve (639 - 903)", "answer": "The result of (639 - 903) is -264\n\n####-264", "a": 639, "b": 903, "operator": "-", "result": -264}
{"question": "Solve (698 + 181)", "answer": "The result of (698 + 181) is 879\n\n####879", "a": 698, "b": 181, "operator": "+", "result": 879}
{"question": "Solve (712 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (712 / 53) is 13.434\n\n####13.434", "a": 712, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 13.434}
{"question": "Solve (256 - 178)", "answer": "The result of (256 - 178) is 78\n\n####78", "a": 256, "b": 178, "operator": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve (254 * 186)", "answer": "The result of (254 * 186) is 47244\n\n####47244", "a": 254, "b": 186, "operator": "*", "result": 47244}
{"question": "Solve (669 + 225)", "answer": "The result of (669 + 225) is 894\n\n####894", "a": 669, "b": 225, "operator": "+", "result": 894}
{"question": "Solve (512 + 378)", "answer": "The result of (512 + 378) is 890\n\n####890", "a": 512, "b": 378, "operator": "+", "result": 890}
{"question": "Solve (178 - 461)", "answer": "The result of (178 - 461) is -283\n\n####-283", "a": 178, "b": 461, "operator": "-", "result": -283}
{"question": "Solve (551 / 231)", "answer": "The result of (551 / 231) is 2.3853\n\n####2.3853", "a": 551, "b": 231, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3853}
{"question": "Solve (88 + 613)", "answer": "The result of (88 + 613) is 701\n\n####701", "a": 88, "b": 613, "operator": "+", "result": 701}
{"question": "Solve (627 / 967)", "answer": "The result of (627 / 967) is 0.6484\n\n####0.6484", "a": 627, "b": 967, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6484}
{"question": "Solve (269 * 365)", "answer": "The result of (269 * 365) is 98185\n\n####98185", "a": 269, "b": 365, "operator": "*", "result": 98185}
{"question": "Solve (32 * 448)", "answer": "The result of (32 * 448) is 14336\n\n####14336", "a": 32, "b": 448, "operator": "*", "result": 14336}
{"question": "Solve (428 - 659)", "answer": "The result of (428 - 659) is -231\n\n####-231", "a": 428, "b": 659, "operator": "-", "result": -231}
{"question": "Solve (240 - 370)", "answer": "The result of (240 - 370) is -130\n\n####-130", "a": 240, "b": 370, "operator": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve (43 * 434)", "answer": "The result of (43 * 434) is 18662\n\n####18662", "a": 43, "b": 434, "operator": "*", "result": 18662}
{"question": "Solve (747 * 940)", "answer": "The result of (747 * 940) is 702180\n\n####702180", "a": 747, "b": 940, "operator": "*", "result": 702180}
{"question": "Solve (657 / 785)", "answer": "The result of (657 / 785) is 0.8369\n\n####0.8369", "a": 657, "b": 785, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8369}
{"question": "Solve (428 - 15)", "answer": "The result of (428 - 15) is 413\n\n####413", "a": 428, "b": 15, "operator": "-", "result": 413}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 870) is 544620\n\n####544620", "a": 626, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 544620}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 628)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 628) is 1.4618\n\n####1.4618", "a": 918, "b": 628, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4618}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 602)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 602) is -128\n\n####-128", "a": 474, "b": 602, "operator": "-", "result": -128}
{"question": "Solve (380 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (380 - 342) is 38\n\n####38", "a": 380, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": 38}
{"question": "Solve (221 / 967)", "answer": "The result of (221 / 967) is 0.2285\n\n####0.2285", "a": 221, "b": 967, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2285}
{"question": "Solve (632 / 72)", "answer": "The result of (632 / 72) is 8.7778\n\n####8.7778", "a": 632, "b": 72, "operator": "/", "result": 8.7778}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 526)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 526) is 949\n\n####949", "a": 423, "b": 526, "operator": "+", "result": 949}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 647) is 29\n\n####29", "a": 676, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": 29}
{"question": "Solve (746 + 302)", "answer": "The result of (746 + 302) is 1048\n\n####1048", "a": 746, "b": 302, "operator": "+", "result": 1048}
{"question": "Solve (525 / 353)", "answer": "The result of (525 / 353) is 1.4873\n\n####1.4873", "a": 525, "b": 353, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4873}
{"question": "Solve (738 * 241)", "answer": "The result of (738 * 241) is 177858\n\n####177858", "a": 738, "b": 241, "operator": "*", "result": 177858}
{"question": "Solve (871 / 28)", "answer": "The result of (871 / 28) is 31.1071\n\n####31.1071", "a": 871, "b": 28, "operator": "/", "result": 31.1071}
{"question": "Solve (396 / 318)", "answer": "The result of (396 / 318) is 1.2453\n\n####1.2453", "a": 396, "b": 318, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2453}
{"question": "Solve (214 / 358)", "answer": "The result of (214 / 358) is 0.5978\n\n####0.5978", "a": 214, "b": 358, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5978}
{"question": "Solve (323 * 486)", "answer": "The result of (323 * 486) is 156978\n\n####156978", "a": 323, "b": 486, "operator": "*", "result": 156978}
{"question": "Solve (343 - 759)", "answer": "The result of (343 - 759) is -416\n\n####-416", "a": 343, "b": 759, "operator": "-", "result": -416}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 8)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 8) is 20.625\n\n####20.625", "a": 165, "b": 8, "operator": "/", "result": 20.625}
{"question": "Solve (151 - 472)", "answer": "The result of (151 - 472) is -321\n\n####-321", "a": 151, "b": 472, "operator": "-", "result": -321}
{"question": "Solve (468 / 381)", "answer": "The result of (468 / 381) is 1.2283\n\n####1.2283", "a": 468, "b": 381, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2283}
{"question": "Solve (166 * 453)", "answer": "The result of (166 * 453) is 75198\n\n####75198", "a": 166, "b": 453, "operator": "*", "result": 75198}
{"question": "Solve (4 - 880)", "answer": "The result of (4 - 880) is -876\n\n####-876", "a": 4, "b": 880, "operator": "-", "result": -876}
{"question": "Solve (528 / 665)", "answer": "The result of (528 / 665) is 0.794\n\n####0.794", "a": 528, "b": 665, "operator": "/", "result": 0.794}
{"question": "Solve (211 * 271)", "answer": "The result of (211 * 271) is 57181\n\n####57181", "a": 211, "b": 271, "operator": "*", "result": 57181}
{"question": "Solve (256 + 251)", "answer": "The result of (256 + 251) is 507\n\n####507", "a": 256, "b": 251, "operator": "+", "result": 507}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 468)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 468) is 1.4701\n\n####1.4701", "a": 688, "b": 468, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4701}
{"question": "Solve (496 + 123)", "answer": "The result of (496 + 123) is 619\n\n####619", "a": 496, "b": 123, "operator": "+", "result": 619}
{"question": "Solve (447 + 532)", "answer": "The result of (447 + 532) is 979\n\n####979", "a": 447, "b": 532, "operator": "+", "result": 979}
{"question": "Solve (461 * 18)", "answer": "The result of (461 * 18) is 8298\n\n####8298", "a": 461, "b": 18, "operator": "*", "result": 8298}
{"question": "Solve (32 / 222)", "answer": "The result of (32 / 222) is 0.1441\n\n####0.1441", "a": 32, "b": 222, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1441}
{"question": "Solve (954 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (954 * 22) is 20988\n\n####20988", "a": 954, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 20988}
{"question": "Solve (443 - 715)", "answer": "The result of (443 - 715) is -272\n\n####-272", "a": 443, "b": 715, "operator": "-", "result": -272}
{"question": "Solve (875 - 401)", "answer": "The result of (875 - 401) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 875, "b": 401, "operator": "-", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (258 / 497)", "answer": "The result of (258 / 497) is 0.5191\n\n####0.5191", "a": 258, "b": 497, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5191}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 714)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 714) is 1581\n\n####1581", "a": 867, "b": 714, "operator": "+", "result": 1581}
{"question": "Solve (863 * 681)", "answer": "The result of (863 * 681) is 587703\n\n####587703", "a": 863, "b": 681, "operator": "*", "result": 587703}
{"question": "Solve (457 + 452)", "answer": "The result of (457 + 452) is 909\n\n####909", "a": 457, "b": 452, "operator": "+", "result": 909}
{"question": "Solve (571 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (571 - 992) is -421\n\n####-421", "a": 571, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -421}
{"question": "Solve (675 * 797)", "answer": "The result of (675 * 797) is 537975\n\n####537975", "a": 675, "b": 797, "operator": "*", "result": 537975}
{"question": "Solve (86 / 74)", "answer": "The result of (86 / 74) is 1.1622\n\n####1.1622", "a": 86, "b": 74, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1622}
{"question": "Solve (439 / 634)", "answer": "The result of (439 / 634) is 0.6924\n\n####0.6924", "a": 439, "b": 634, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6924}
{"question": "Solve (766 - 592)", "answer": "The result of (766 - 592) is 174\n\n####174", "a": 766, "b": 592, "operator": "-", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve (997 + 827)", "answer": "The result of (997 + 827) is 1824\n\n####1824", "a": 997, "b": 827, "operator": "+", "result": 1824}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 689)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 689) is -665\n\n####-665", "a": 24, "b": 689, "operator": "-", "result": -665}
{"question": "Solve (628 + 407)", "answer": "The result of (628 + 407) is 1035\n\n####1035", "a": 628, "b": 407, "operator": "+", "result": 1035}
{"question": "Solve (274 * 71)", "answer": "The result of (274 * 71) is 19454\n\n####19454", "a": 274, "b": 71, "operator": "*", "result": 19454}
{"question": "Solve (744 + 845)", "answer": "The result of (744 + 845) is 1589\n\n####1589", "a": 744, "b": 845, "operator": "+", "result": 1589}
{"question": "Solve (520 / 109)", "answer": "The result of (520 / 109) is 4.7706\n\n####4.7706", "a": 520, "b": 109, "operator": "/", "result": 4.7706}
{"question": "Solve (728 + 400)", "answer": "The result of (728 + 400) is 1128\n\n####1128", "a": 728, "b": 400, "operator": "+", "result": 1128}
{"question": "Solve (227 * 64)", "answer": "The result of (227 * 64) is 14528\n\n####14528", "a": 227, "b": 64, "operator": "*", "result": 14528}
{"question": "Solve (901 - 646)", "answer": "The result of (901 - 646) is 255\n\n####255", "a": 901, "b": 646, "operator": "-", "result": 255}
{"question": "Solve (385 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (385 * 596) is 229460\n\n####229460", "a": 385, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 229460}
{"question": "Solve (610 + 675)", "answer": "The result of (610 + 675) is 1285\n\n####1285", "a": 610, "b": 675, "operator": "+", "result": 1285}
{"question": "Solve (474 * 791)", "answer": "The result of (474 * 791) is 374934\n\n####374934", "a": 474, "b": 791, "operator": "*", "result": 374934}
{"question": "Solve (293 * 401)", "answer": "The result of (293 * 401) is 117493\n\n####117493", "a": 293, "b": 401, "operator": "*", "result": 117493}
{"question": "Solve (812 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (812 * 510) is 414120\n\n####414120", "a": 812, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 414120}
{"question": "Solve (539 - 422)", "answer": "The result of (539 - 422) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 539, "b": 422, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (189 - 479)", "answer": "The result of (189 - 479) is -290\n\n####-290", "a": 189, "b": 479, "operator": "-", "result": -290}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 357)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 357) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 763, "b": 357, "operator": "-", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (308 + 504)", "answer": "The result of (308 + 504) is 812\n\n####812", "a": 308, "b": 504, "operator": "+", "result": 812}
{"question": "Solve (921 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (921 - 283) is 638\n\n####638", "a": 921, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 638}
{"question": "Solve (18 + 732)", "answer": "The result of (18 + 732) is 750\n\n####750", "a": 18, "b": 732, "operator": "+", "result": 750}
{"question": "Solve (764 + 791)", "answer": "The result of (764 + 791) is 1555\n\n####1555", "a": 764, "b": 791, "operator": "+", "result": 1555}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 561)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 561) is -237\n\n####-237", "a": 324, "b": 561, "operator": "-", "result": -237}
{"question": "Solve (441 + 68)", "answer": "The result of (441 + 68) is 509\n\n####509", "a": 441, "b": 68, "operator": "+", "result": 509}
{"question": "Solve (681 - 157)", "answer": "The result of (681 - 157) is 524\n\n####524", "a": 681, "b": 157, "operator": "-", "result": 524}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 951)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 951) is -906\n\n####-906", "a": 45, "b": 951, "operator": "-", "result": -906}
{"question": "Solve (173 - 705)", "answer": "The result of (173 - 705) is -532\n\n####-532", "a": 173, "b": 705, "operator": "-", "result": -532}
{"question": "Solve (154 + 685)", "answer": "The result of (154 + 685) is 839\n\n####839", "a": 154, "b": 685, "operator": "+", "result": 839}
{"question": "Solve (655 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (655 - 195) is 460\n\n####460", "a": 655, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": 460}
{"question": "Solve (883 - 655)", "answer": "The result of (883 - 655) is 228\n\n####228", "a": 883, "b": 655, "operator": "-", "result": 228}
{"question": "Solve (821 * 699)", "answer": "The result of (821 * 699) is 573879\n\n####573879", "a": 821, "b": 699, "operator": "*", "result": 573879}
{"question": "Solve (514 / 173)", "answer": "The result of (514 / 173) is 2.9711\n\n####2.9711", "a": 514, "b": 173, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9711}
{"question": "Solve (499 + 446)", "answer": "The result of (499 + 446) is 945\n\n####945", "a": 499, "b": 446, "operator": "+", "result": 945}
{"question": "Solve (237 - 614)", "answer": "The result of (237 - 614) is -377\n\n####-377", "a": 237, "b": 614, "operator": "-", "result": -377}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 43)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 43) is 11524\n\n####11524", "a": 268, "b": 43, "operator": "*", "result": 11524}
{"question": "Solve (775 - 428)", "answer": "The result of (775 - 428) is 347\n\n####347", "a": 775, "b": 428, "operator": "-", "result": 347}
{"question": "Solve (818 - 511)", "answer": "The result of (818 - 511) is 307\n\n####307", "a": 818, "b": 511, "operator": "-", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve (661 - 38)", "answer": "The result of (661 - 38) is 623\n\n####623", "a": 661, "b": 38, "operator": "-", "result": 623}
{"question": "Solve (406 / 655)", "answer": "The result of (406 / 655) is 0.6198\n\n####0.6198", "a": 406, "b": 655, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6198}
{"question": "Solve (317 - 803)", "answer": "The result of (317 - 803) is -486\n\n####-486", "a": 317, "b": 803, "operator": "-", "result": -486}
{"question": "Solve (581 * 52)", "answer": "The result of (581 * 52) is 30212\n\n####30212", "a": 581, "b": 52, "operator": "*", "result": 30212}
{"question": "Solve (897 / 161)", "answer": "The result of (897 / 161) is 5.5714\n\n####5.5714", "a": 897, "b": 161, "operator": "/", "result": 5.5714}
{"question": "Solve (600 + 141)", "answer": "The result of (600 + 141) is 741\n\n####741", "a": 600, "b": 141, "operator": "+", "result": 741}
{"question": "Solve (670 - 662)", "answer": "The result of (670 - 662) is 8\n\n####8", "a": 670, "b": 662, "operator": "-", "result": 8}
{"question": "Solve (244 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (244 / 475) is 0.5137\n\n####0.5137", "a": 244, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5137}
{"question": "Solve (316 - 478)", "answer": "The result of (316 - 478) is -162\n\n####-162", "a": 316, "b": 478, "operator": "-", "result": -162}
{"question": "Solve (785 / 82)", "answer": "The result of (785 / 82) is 9.5732\n\n####9.5732", "a": 785, "b": 82, "operator": "/", "result": 9.5732}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 266)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 266) is 265\n\n####265", "a": 531, "b": 266, "operator": "-", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 567) is 363\n\n####363", "a": 930, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": 363}
{"question": "Solve (980 / 571)", "answer": "The result of (980 / 571) is 1.7163\n\n####1.7163", "a": 980, "b": 571, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7163}
{"question": "Solve (84 - 905)", "answer": "The result of (84 - 905) is -821\n\n####-821", "a": 84, "b": 905, "operator": "-", "result": -821}
{"question": "Solve (263 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (263 - 661) is -398\n\n####-398", "a": 263, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -398}
{"question": "Solve (979 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (979 - 6) is 973\n\n####973", "a": 979, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 973}
{"question": "Solve (458 / 825)", "answer": "The result of (458 / 825) is 0.5552\n\n####0.5552", "a": 458, "b": 825, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5552}
{"question": "Solve (854 - 361)", "answer": "The result of (854 - 361) is 493\n\n####493", "a": 854, "b": 361, "operator": "-", "result": 493}
{"question": "Solve (840 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (840 / 560) is 1.5\n\n####1.5", "a": 840, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5}
{"question": "Solve (317 / 215)", "answer": "The result of (317 / 215) is 1.4744\n\n####1.4744", "a": 317, "b": 215, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4744}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 348)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 348) is 13\n\n####13", "a": 361, "b": 348, "operator": "-", "result": 13}
{"question": "Solve (796 / 375)", "answer": "The result of (796 / 375) is 2.1227\n\n####2.1227", "a": 796, "b": 375, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1227}
{"question": "Solve (15 * 796)", "answer": "The result of (15 * 796) is 11940\n\n####11940", "a": 15, "b": 796, "operator": "*", "result": 11940}
{"question": "Solve (611 / 989)", "answer": "The result of (611 / 989) is 0.6178\n\n####0.6178", "a": 611, "b": 989, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6178}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 756)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 756) is 0.4048\n\n####0.4048", "a": 306, "b": 756, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4048}
{"question": "Solve (158 - 770)", "answer": "The result of (158 - 770) is -612\n\n####-612", "a": 158, "b": 770, "operator": "-", "result": -612}
{"question": "Solve (392 - 215)", "answer": "The result of (392 - 215) is 177\n\n####177", "a": 392, "b": 215, "operator": "-", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve (622 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (622 - 233) is 389\n\n####389", "a": 622, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": 389}
{"question": "Solve (992 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (992 / 87) is 11.4023\n\n####11.4023", "a": 992, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 11.4023}
{"question": "Solve (387 + 66)", "answer": "The result of (387 + 66) is 453\n\n####453", "a": 387, "b": 66, "operator": "+", "result": 453}
{"question": "Solve (956 * 625)", "answer": "The result of (956 * 625) is 597500\n\n####597500", "a": 956, "b": 625, "operator": "*", "result": 597500}
{"question": "Solve (825 - 43)", "answer": "The result of (825 - 43) is 782\n\n####782", "a": 825, "b": 43, "operator": "-", "result": 782}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 500) is 466\n\n####466", "a": 966, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": 466}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 295)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 295) is 476\n\n####476", "a": 181, "b": 295, "operator": "+", "result": 476}
{"question": "Solve (637 * 156)", "answer": "The result of (637 * 156) is 99372\n\n####99372", "a": 637, "b": 156, "operator": "*", "result": 99372}
{"question": "Solve (698 + 60)", "answer": "The result of (698 + 60) is 758\n\n####758", "a": 698, "b": 60, "operator": "+", "result": 758}
{"question": "Solve (323 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (323 * 357) is 115311\n\n####115311", "a": 323, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 115311}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 491)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 491) is 183634\n\n####183634", "a": 374, "b": 491, "operator": "*", "result": 183634}
{"question": "Solve (678 - 788)", "answer": "The result of (678 - 788) is -110\n\n####-110", "a": 678, "b": 788, "operator": "-", "result": -110}
{"question": "Solve (148 - 925)", "answer": "The result of (148 - 925) is -777\n\n####-777", "a": 148, "b": 925, "operator": "-", "result": -777}
{"question": "Solve (753 / 794)", "answer": "The result of (753 / 794) is 0.9484\n\n####0.9484", "a": 753, "b": 794, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9484}
{"question": "Solve (459 / 882)", "answer": "The result of (459 / 882) is 0.5204\n\n####0.5204", "a": 459, "b": 882, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5204}
{"question": "Solve (111 * 789)", "answer": "The result of (111 * 789) is 87579\n\n####87579", "a": 111, "b": 789, "operator": "*", "result": 87579}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 643)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 643) is 1566\n\n####1566", "a": 923, "b": 643, "operator": "+", "result": 1566}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 422)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 422) is 375\n\n####375", "a": 797, "b": 422, "operator": "-", "result": 375}
{"question": "Solve (402 / 460)", "answer": "The result of (402 / 460) is 0.8739\n\n####0.8739", "a": 402, "b": 460, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8739}
{"question": "Solve (953 + 35)", "answer": "The result of (953 + 35) is 988\n\n####988", "a": 953, "b": 35, "operator": "+", "result": 988}
{"question": "Solve (680 + 186)", "answer": "The result of (680 + 186) is 866\n\n####866", "a": 680, "b": 186, "operator": "+", "result": 866}
{"question": "Solve (825 + 174)", "answer": "The result of (825 + 174) is 999\n\n####999", "a": 825, "b": 174, "operator": "+", "result": 999}
{"question": "Solve (969 - 495)", "answer": "The result of (969 - 495) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 969, "b": 495, "operator": "-", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 409) is 532\n\n####532", "a": 941, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": 532}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 70)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 70) is 18480\n\n####18480", "a": 264, "b": 70, "operator": "*", "result": 18480}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 821) is 0.8794\n\n####0.8794", "a": 722, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8794}
{"question": "Solve (198 + 369)", "answer": "The result of (198 + 369) is 567\n\n####567", "a": 198, "b": 369, "operator": "+", "result": 567}
{"question": "Solve (129 * 224)", "answer": "The result of (129 * 224) is 28896\n\n####28896", "a": 129, "b": 224, "operator": "*", "result": 28896}
{"question": "Solve (541 / 801)", "answer": "The result of (541 / 801) is 0.6754\n\n####0.6754", "a": 541, "b": 801, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6754}
{"question": "Solve (912 * 224)", "answer": "The result of (912 * 224) is 204288\n\n####204288", "a": 912, "b": 224, "operator": "*", "result": 204288}
{"question": "Solve (717 * 304)", "answer": "The result of (717 * 304) is 217968\n\n####217968", "a": 717, "b": 304, "operator": "*", "result": 217968}
{"question": "Solve (149 - 433)", "answer": "The result of (149 - 433) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 149, "b": 433, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (29 * 313)", "answer": "The result of (29 * 313) is 9077\n\n####9077", "a": 29, "b": 313, "operator": "*", "result": 9077}
{"question": "Solve (700 / 571)", "answer": "The result of (700 / 571) is 1.2259\n\n####1.2259", "a": 700, "b": 571, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2259}
{"question": "Solve (504 / 454)", "answer": "The result of (504 / 454) is 1.1101\n\n####1.1101", "a": 504, "b": 454, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1101}
{"question": "Solve (835 / 861)", "answer": "The result of (835 / 861) is 0.9698\n\n####0.9698", "a": 835, "b": 861, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9698}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 582)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 582) is 0.1735\n\n####0.1735", "a": 101, "b": 582, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1735}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 763)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 763) is 79\n\n####79", "a": 842, "b": 763, "operator": "-", "result": 79}
{"question": "Solve (685 / 612)", "answer": "The result of (685 / 612) is 1.1193\n\n####1.1193", "a": 685, "b": 612, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1193}
{"question": "Solve (753 / 472)", "answer": "The result of (753 / 472) is 1.5953\n\n####1.5953", "a": 753, "b": 472, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5953}
{"question": "Solve (661 / 46)", "answer": "The result of (661 / 46) is 14.3696\n\n####14.3696", "a": 661, "b": 46, "operator": "/", "result": 14.3696}
{"question": "Solve (722 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (722 - 2) is 720\n\n####720", "a": 722, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 720}
{"question": "Solve (947 / 564)", "answer": "The result of (947 / 564) is 1.6791\n\n####1.6791", "a": 947, "b": 564, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6791}
{"question": "Solve (776 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (776 / 236) is 3.2881\n\n####3.2881", "a": 776, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2881}
{"question": "Solve (629 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (629 / 695) is 0.905\n\n####0.905", "a": 629, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 0.905}
{"question": "Solve (792 + 132)", "answer": "The result of (792 + 132) is 924\n\n####924", "a": 792, "b": 132, "operator": "+", "result": 924}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 250) is -157\n\n####-157", "a": 93, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": -157}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 144) is 0.1458\n\n####0.1458", "a": 21, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1458}
{"question": "Solve (801 + 644)", "answer": "The result of (801 + 644) is 1445\n\n####1445", "a": 801, "b": 644, "operator": "+", "result": 1445}
{"question": "Solve (233 - 389)", "answer": "The result of (233 - 389) is -156\n\n####-156", "a": 233, "b": 389, "operator": "-", "result": -156}
{"question": "Solve (115 / 384)", "answer": "The result of (115 / 384) is 0.2995\n\n####0.2995", "a": 115, "b": 384, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2995}
{"question": "Solve (662 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (662 * 698) is 462076\n\n####462076", "a": 662, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 462076}
{"question": "Solve (721 * 271)", "answer": "The result of (721 * 271) is 195391\n\n####195391", "a": 721, "b": 271, "operator": "*", "result": 195391}
{"question": "Solve (590 - 953)", "answer": "The result of (590 - 953) is -363\n\n####-363", "a": 590, "b": 953, "operator": "-", "result": -363}
{"question": "Solve (742 * 874)", "answer": "The result of (742 * 874) is 648508\n\n####648508", "a": 742, "b": 874, "operator": "*", "result": 648508}
{"question": "Solve (380 + 935)", "answer": "The result of (380 + 935) is 1315\n\n####1315", "a": 380, "b": 935, "operator": "+", "result": 1315}
{"question": "Solve (585 + 269)", "answer": "The result of (585 + 269) is 854\n\n####854", "a": 585, "b": 269, "operator": "+", "result": 854}
{"question": "Solve (759 * 784)", "answer": "The result of (759 * 784) is 595056\n\n####595056", "a": 759, "b": 784, "operator": "*", "result": 595056}
{"question": "Solve (563 * 299)", "answer": "The result of (563 * 299) is 168337\n\n####168337", "a": 563, "b": 299, "operator": "*", "result": 168337}
{"question": "Solve (252 - 400)", "answer": "The result of (252 - 400) is -148\n\n####-148", "a": 252, "b": 400, "operator": "-", "result": -148}
{"question": "Solve (944 - 461)", "answer": "The result of (944 - 461) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 944, "b": 461, "operator": "-", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (401 / 735)", "answer": "The result of (401 / 735) is 0.5456\n\n####0.5456", "a": 401, "b": 735, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5456}
{"question": "Solve (470 - 419)", "answer": "The result of (470 - 419) is 51\n\n####51", "a": 470, "b": 419, "operator": "-", "result": 51}
{"question": "Solve (826 / 912)", "answer": "The result of (826 / 912) is 0.9057\n\n####0.9057", "a": 826, "b": 912, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9057}
{"question": "Solve (573 / 610)", "answer": "The result of (573 / 610) is 0.9393\n\n####0.9393", "a": 573, "b": 610, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9393}
{"question": "Solve (388 / 194)", "answer": "The result of (388 / 194) is 2.0\n\n####2.0", "a": 388, "b": 194, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 133)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 133) is 556\n\n####556", "a": 423, "b": 133, "operator": "+", "result": 556}
{"question": "Solve (349 - 218)", "answer": "The result of (349 - 218) is 131\n\n####131", "a": 349, "b": 218, "operator": "-", "result": 131}
{"question": "Solve (641 - 775)", "answer": "The result of (641 - 775) is -134\n\n####-134", "a": 641, "b": 775, "operator": "-", "result": -134}
{"question": "Solve (60 - 771)", "answer": "The result of (60 - 771) is -711\n\n####-711", "a": 60, "b": 771, "operator": "-", "result": -711}
{"question": "Solve (518 - 23)", "answer": "The result of (518 - 23) is 495\n\n####495", "a": 518, "b": 23, "operator": "-", "result": 495}
{"question": "Solve (689 * 913)", "answer": "The result of (689 * 913) is 629057\n\n####629057", "a": 689, "b": 913, "operator": "*", "result": 629057}
{"question": "Solve (277 - 118)", "answer": "The result of (277 - 118) is 159\n\n####159", "a": 277, "b": 118, "operator": "-", "result": 159}
{"question": "Solve (84 * 551)", "answer": "The result of (84 * 551) is 46284\n\n####46284", "a": 84, "b": 551, "operator": "*", "result": 46284}
{"question": "Solve (811 * 658)", "answer": "The result of (811 * 658) is 533638\n\n####533638", "a": 811, "b": 658, "operator": "*", "result": 533638}
{"question": "Solve (348 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (348 - 175) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 348, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (877 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (877 - 408) is 469\n\n####469", "a": 877, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 469}
{"question": "Solve (185 - 139)", "answer": "The result of (185 - 139) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 185, "b": 139, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (969 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (969 / 289) is 3.3529\n\n####3.3529", "a": 969, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3529}
{"question": "Solve (164 * 859)", "answer": "The result of (164 * 859) is 140876\n\n####140876", "a": 164, "b": 859, "operator": "*", "result": 140876}
{"question": "Solve (891 - 193)", "answer": "The result of (891 - 193) is 698\n\n####698", "a": 891, "b": 193, "operator": "-", "result": 698}
{"question": "Solve (261 + 692)", "answer": "The result of (261 + 692) is 953\n\n####953", "a": 261, "b": 692, "operator": "+", "result": 953}
{"question": "Solve (168 / 992)", "answer": "The result of (168 / 992) is 0.1694\n\n####0.1694", "a": 168, "b": 992, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1694}
{"question": "Solve (518 / 134)", "answer": "The result of (518 / 134) is 3.8657\n\n####3.8657", "a": 518, "b": 134, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8657}
{"question": "Solve (138 / 429)", "answer": "The result of (138 / 429) is 0.3217\n\n####0.3217", "a": 138, "b": 429, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3217}
{"question": "Solve (661 - 749)", "answer": "The result of (661 - 749) is -88\n\n####-88", "a": 661, "b": 749, "operator": "-", "result": -88}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 130)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 130) is 0.0769\n\n####0.0769", "a": 10, "b": 130, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0769}
{"question": "Solve (565 / 990)", "answer": "The result of (565 / 990) is 0.5707\n\n####0.5707", "a": 565, "b": 990, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5707}
{"question": "Solve (137 - 729)", "answer": "The result of (137 - 729) is -592\n\n####-592", "a": 137, "b": 729, "operator": "-", "result": -592}
{"question": "Solve (385 / 963)", "answer": "The result of (385 / 963) is 0.3998\n\n####0.3998", "a": 385, "b": 963, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3998}
{"question": "Solve (377 / 485)", "answer": "The result of (377 / 485) is 0.7773\n\n####0.7773", "a": 377, "b": 485, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7773}
{"question": "Solve (337 * 433)", "answer": "The result of (337 * 433) is 145921\n\n####145921", "a": 337, "b": 433, "operator": "*", "result": 145921}
{"question": "Solve (194 / 247)", "answer": "The result of (194 / 247) is 0.7854\n\n####0.7854", "a": 194, "b": 247, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7854}
{"question": "Solve (489 + 652)", "answer": "The result of (489 + 652) is 1141\n\n####1141", "a": 489, "b": 652, "operator": "+", "result": 1141}
{"question": "Solve (315 - 586)", "answer": "The result of (315 - 586) is -271\n\n####-271", "a": 315, "b": 586, "operator": "-", "result": -271}
{"question": "Solve (857 - 976)", "answer": "The result of (857 - 976) is -119\n\n####-119", "a": 857, "b": 976, "operator": "-", "result": -119}
{"question": "Solve (4 - 685)", "answer": "The result of (4 - 685) is -681\n\n####-681", "a": 4, "b": 685, "operator": "-", "result": -681}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 692)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 692) is 245660\n\n####245660", "a": 355, "b": 692, "operator": "*", "result": 245660}
{"question": "Solve (124 + 379)", "answer": "The result of (124 + 379) is 503\n\n####503", "a": 124, "b": 379, "operator": "+", "result": 503}
{"question": "Solve (868 / 601)", "answer": "The result of (868 / 601) is 1.4443\n\n####1.4443", "a": 868, "b": 601, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4443}
{"question": "Solve (81 / 166)", "answer": "The result of (81 / 166) is 0.488\n\n####0.488", "a": 81, "b": 166, "operator": "/", "result": 0.488}
{"question": "Solve (608 / 931)", "answer": "The result of (608 / 931) is 0.6531\n\n####0.6531", "a": 608, "b": 931, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6531}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 190)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 190) is 330\n\n####330", "a": 520, "b": 190, "operator": "-", "result": 330}
{"question": "Solve (665 - 444)", "answer": "The result of (665 - 444) is 221\n\n####221", "a": 665, "b": 444, "operator": "-", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve (675 / 731)", "answer": "The result of (675 / 731) is 0.9234\n\n####0.9234", "a": 675, "b": 731, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9234}
{"question": "Solve (646 * 463)", "answer": "The result of (646 * 463) is 299098\n\n####299098", "a": 646, "b": 463, "operator": "*", "result": 299098}
{"question": "Solve (813 * 549)", "answer": "The result of (813 * 549) is 446337\n\n####446337", "a": 813, "b": 549, "operator": "*", "result": 446337}
{"question": "Solve (40 / 634)", "answer": "The result of (40 / 634) is 0.0631\n\n####0.0631", "a": 40, "b": 634, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0631}
{"question": "Solve (184 * 67)", "answer": "The result of (184 * 67) is 12328\n\n####12328", "a": 184, "b": 67, "operator": "*", "result": 12328}
{"question": "Solve (16 + 965)", "answer": "The result of (16 + 965) is 981\n\n####981", "a": 16, "b": 965, "operator": "+", "result": 981}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 431) is 290\n\n####290", "a": 721, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve (840 + 499)", "answer": "The result of (840 + 499) is 1339\n\n####1339", "a": 840, "b": 499, "operator": "+", "result": 1339}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 940)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 940) is -130\n\n####-130", "a": 810, "b": 940, "operator": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve (322 + 553)", "answer": "The result of (322 + 553) is 875\n\n####875", "a": 322, "b": 553, "operator": "+", "result": 875}
{"question": "Solve (655 / 760)", "answer": "The result of (655 / 760) is 0.8618\n\n####0.8618", "a": 655, "b": 760, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8618}
{"question": "Solve (280 - 739)", "answer": "The result of (280 - 739) is -459\n\n####-459", "a": 280, "b": 739, "operator": "-", "result": -459}
{"question": "Solve (53 - 7)", "answer": "The result of (53 - 7) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 53, "b": 7, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (258 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (258 / 773) is 0.3338\n\n####0.3338", "a": 258, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3338}
{"question": "Solve (519 + 321)", "answer": "The result of (519 + 321) is 840\n\n####840", "a": 519, "b": 321, "operator": "+", "result": 840}
{"question": "Solve (472 - 539)", "answer": "The result of (472 - 539) is -67\n\n####-67", "a": 472, "b": 539, "operator": "-", "result": -67}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 101)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 101) is 8.9505\n\n####8.9505", "a": 904, "b": 101, "operator": "/", "result": 8.9505}
{"question": "Solve (774 / 549)", "answer": "The result of (774 / 549) is 1.4098\n\n####1.4098", "a": 774, "b": 549, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4098}
{"question": "Solve (180 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (180 * 102) is 18360\n\n####18360", "a": 180, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 18360}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 654)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 654) is 0.7783\n\n####0.7783", "a": 509, "b": 654, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7783}
{"question": "Solve (778 + 139)", "answer": "The result of (778 + 139) is 917\n\n####917", "a": 778, "b": 139, "operator": "+", "result": 917}
{"question": "Solve (334 - 956)", "answer": "The result of (334 - 956) is -622\n\n####-622", "a": 334, "b": 956, "operator": "-", "result": -622}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 823) is 73247\n\n####73247", "a": 89, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 73247}
{"question": "Solve (820 + 547)", "answer": "The result of (820 + 547) is 1367\n\n####1367", "a": 820, "b": 547, "operator": "+", "result": 1367}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 666)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 666) is 0.1321\n\n####0.1321", "a": 88, "b": 666, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1321}
{"question": "Solve (408 + 930)", "answer": "The result of (408 + 930) is 1338\n\n####1338", "a": 408, "b": 930, "operator": "+", "result": 1338}
{"question": "Solve (623 * 925)", "answer": "The result of (623 * 925) is 576275\n\n####576275", "a": 623, "b": 925, "operator": "*", "result": 576275}
{"question": "Solve (510 + 152)", "answer": "The result of (510 + 152) is 662\n\n####662", "a": 510, "b": 152, "operator": "+", "result": 662}
{"question": "Solve (445 / 166)", "answer": "The result of (445 / 166) is 2.6807\n\n####2.6807", "a": 445, "b": 166, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6807}
{"question": "Solve (565 + 782)", "answer": "The result of (565 + 782) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 565, "b": 782, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (527 + 609)", "answer": "The result of (527 + 609) is 1136\n\n####1136", "a": 527, "b": 609, "operator": "+", "result": 1136}
{"question": "Solve (157 + 795)", "answer": "The result of (157 + 795) is 952\n\n####952", "a": 157, "b": 795, "operator": "+", "result": 952}
{"question": "Solve (970 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (970 / 445) is 2.1798\n\n####2.1798", "a": 970, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1798}
{"question": "Solve (163 * 534)", "answer": "The result of (163 * 534) is 87042\n\n####87042", "a": 163, "b": 534, "operator": "*", "result": 87042}
{"question": "Solve (980 - 877)", "answer": "The result of (980 - 877) is 103\n\n####103", "a": 980, "b": 877, "operator": "-", "result": 103}
{"question": "Solve (570 / 541)", "answer": "The result of (570 / 541) is 1.0536\n\n####1.0536", "a": 570, "b": 541, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0536}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 836)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 836) is -579\n\n####-579", "a": 257, "b": 836, "operator": "-", "result": -579}
{"question": "Solve (902 * 678)", "answer": "The result of (902 * 678) is 611556\n\n####611556", "a": 902, "b": 678, "operator": "*", "result": 611556}
{"question": "Solve (685 * 421)", "answer": "The result of (685 * 421) is 288385\n\n####288385", "a": 685, "b": 421, "operator": "*", "result": 288385}
{"question": "Solve (191 + 742)", "answer": "The result of (191 + 742) is 933\n\n####933", "a": 191, "b": 742, "operator": "+", "result": 933}
{"question": "Solve (86 - 836)", "answer": "The result of (86 - 836) is -750\n\n####-750", "a": 86, "b": 836, "operator": "-", "result": -750}
{"question": "Solve (940 + 114)", "answer": "The result of (940 + 114) is 1054\n\n####1054", "a": 940, "b": 114, "operator": "+", "result": 1054}
{"question": "Solve (184 - 769)", "answer": "The result of (184 - 769) is -585\n\n####-585", "a": 184, "b": 769, "operator": "-", "result": -585}
{"question": "Solve (77 / 593)", "answer": "The result of (77 / 593) is 0.1298\n\n####0.1298", "a": 77, "b": 593, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1298}
{"question": "Solve (683 * 902)", "answer": "The result of (683 * 902) is 616066\n\n####616066", "a": 683, "b": 902, "operator": "*", "result": 616066}
{"question": "Solve (192 / 806)", "answer": "The result of (192 / 806) is 0.2382\n\n####0.2382", "a": 192, "b": 806, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2382}
{"question": "Solve (489 * 409)", "answer": "The result of (489 * 409) is 200001\n\n####200001", "a": 489, "b": 409, "operator": "*", "result": 200001}
{"question": "Solve (811 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (811 * 423) is 343053\n\n####343053", "a": 811, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 343053}
{"question": "Solve (315 + 446)", "answer": "The result of (315 + 446) is 761\n\n####761", "a": 315, "b": 446, "operator": "+", "result": 761}
{"question": "Solve (351 / 704)", "answer": "The result of (351 / 704) is 0.4986\n\n####0.4986", "a": 351, "b": 704, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4986}
{"question": "Solve (332 + 529)", "answer": "The result of (332 + 529) is 861\n\n####861", "a": 332, "b": 529, "operator": "+", "result": 861}
{"question": "Solve (503 * 341)", "answer": "The result of (503 * 341) is 171523\n\n####171523", "a": 503, "b": 341, "operator": "*", "result": 171523}
{"question": "Solve (695 + 351)", "answer": "The result of (695 + 351) is 1046\n\n####1046", "a": 695, "b": 351, "operator": "+", "result": 1046}
{"question": "Solve (396 / 39)", "answer": "The result of (396 / 39) is 10.1538\n\n####10.1538", "a": 396, "b": 39, "operator": "/", "result": 10.1538}
{"question": "Solve (883 - 183)", "answer": "The result of (883 - 183) is 700\n\n####700", "a": 883, "b": 183, "operator": "-", "result": 700}
{"question": "Solve (612 * 900)", "answer": "The result of (612 * 900) is 550800\n\n####550800", "a": 612, "b": 900, "operator": "*", "result": 550800}
{"question": "Solve (26 + 292)", "answer": "The result of (26 + 292) is 318\n\n####318", "a": 26, "b": 292, "operator": "+", "result": 318}
{"question": "Solve (100 / 933)", "answer": "The result of (100 / 933) is 0.1072\n\n####0.1072", "a": 100, "b": 933, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1072}
{"question": "Solve (807 * 478)", "answer": "The result of (807 * 478) is 385746\n\n####385746", "a": 807, "b": 478, "operator": "*", "result": 385746}
{"question": "Solve (943 * 605)", "answer": "The result of (943 * 605) is 570515\n\n####570515", "a": 943, "b": 605, "operator": "*", "result": 570515}
{"question": "Solve (296 / 920)", "answer": "The result of (296 / 920) is 0.3217\n\n####0.3217", "a": 296, "b": 920, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3217}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 968)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 968) is 1891\n\n####1891", "a": 923, "b": 968, "operator": "+", "result": 1891}
{"question": "Solve (483 * 280)", "answer": "The result of (483 * 280) is 135240\n\n####135240", "a": 483, "b": 280, "operator": "*", "result": 135240}
{"question": "Solve (412 / 806)", "answer": "The result of (412 / 806) is 0.5112\n\n####0.5112", "a": 412, "b": 806, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5112}
{"question": "Solve (989 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (989 - 779) is 210\n\n####210", "a": 989, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve (241 + 322)", "answer": "The result of (241 + 322) is 563\n\n####563", "a": 241, "b": 322, "operator": "+", "result": 563}
{"question": "Solve (123 + 475)", "answer": "The result of (123 + 475) is 598\n\n####598", "a": 123, "b": 475, "operator": "+", "result": 598}
{"question": "Solve (473 / 844)", "answer": "The result of (473 / 844) is 0.5604\n\n####0.5604", "a": 473, "b": 844, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5604}
{"question": "Solve (79 / 520)", "answer": "The result of (79 / 520) is 0.1519\n\n####0.1519", "a": 79, "b": 520, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1519}
{"question": "Solve (659 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (659 / 891) is 0.7396\n\n####0.7396", "a": 659, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7396}
{"question": "Solve (112 - 964)", "answer": "The result of (112 - 964) is -852\n\n####-852", "a": 112, "b": 964, "operator": "-", "result": -852}
{"question": "Solve (603 / 296)", "answer": "The result of (603 / 296) is 2.0372\n\n####2.0372", "a": 603, "b": 296, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0372}
{"question": "Solve (707 - 947)", "answer": "The result of (707 - 947) is -240\n\n####-240", "a": 707, "b": 947, "operator": "-", "result": -240}
{"question": "Solve (104 + 51)", "answer": "The result of (104 + 51) is 155\n\n####155", "a": 104, "b": 51, "operator": "+", "result": 155}
{"question": "Solve (608 / 918)", "answer": "The result of (608 / 918) is 0.6623\n\n####0.6623", "a": 608, "b": 918, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6623}
{"question": "Solve (391 - 969)", "answer": "The result of (391 - 969) is -578\n\n####-578", "a": 391, "b": 969, "operator": "-", "result": -578}
{"question": "Solve (482 + 790)", "answer": "The result of (482 + 790) is 1272\n\n####1272", "a": 482, "b": 790, "operator": "+", "result": 1272}
{"question": "Solve (823 / 834)", "answer": "The result of (823 / 834) is 0.9868\n\n####0.9868", "a": 823, "b": 834, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9868}
{"question": "Solve (516 * 193)", "answer": "The result of (516 * 193) is 99588\n\n####99588", "a": 516, "b": 193, "operator": "*", "result": 99588}
{"question": "Solve (391 - 108)", "answer": "The result of (391 - 108) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 391, "b": 108, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (194 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (194 * 548) is 106312\n\n####106312", "a": 194, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 106312}
{"question": "Solve (733 / 436)", "answer": "The result of (733 / 436) is 1.6812\n\n####1.6812", "a": 733, "b": 436, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6812}
{"question": "Solve (213 * 119)", "answer": "The result of (213 * 119) is 25347\n\n####25347", "a": 213, "b": 119, "operator": "*", "result": 25347}
{"question": "Solve (700 + 266)", "answer": "The result of (700 + 266) is 966\n\n####966", "a": 700, "b": 266, "operator": "+", "result": 966}
{"question": "Solve (439 / 406)", "answer": "The result of (439 / 406) is 1.0813\n\n####1.0813", "a": 439, "b": 406, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0813}
{"question": "Solve (209 * 250)", "answer": "The result of (209 * 250) is 52250\n\n####52250", "a": 209, "b": 250, "operator": "*", "result": 52250}
{"question": "Solve (806 * 449)", "answer": "The result of (806 * 449) is 361894\n\n####361894", "a": 806, "b": 449, "operator": "*", "result": 361894}
{"question": "Solve (932 / 111)", "answer": "The result of (932 / 111) is 8.3964\n\n####8.3964", "a": 932, "b": 111, "operator": "/", "result": 8.3964}
{"question": "Solve (249 + 765)", "answer": "The result of (249 + 765) is 1014\n\n####1014", "a": 249, "b": 765, "operator": "+", "result": 1014}
{"question": "Solve (218 * 91)", "answer": "The result of (218 * 91) is 19838\n\n####19838", "a": 218, "b": 91, "operator": "*", "result": 19838}
{"question": "Solve (340 / 30)", "answer": "The result of (340 / 30) is 11.3333\n\n####11.3333", "a": 340, "b": 30, "operator": "/", "result": 11.3333}
{"question": "Solve (371 * 184)", "answer": "The result of (371 * 184) is 68264\n\n####68264", "a": 371, "b": 184, "operator": "*", "result": 68264}
{"question": "Solve (598 + 462)", "answer": "The result of (598 + 462) is 1060\n\n####1060", "a": 598, "b": 462, "operator": "+", "result": 1060}
{"question": "Solve (256 - 524)", "answer": "The result of (256 - 524) is -268\n\n####-268", "a": 256, "b": 524, "operator": "-", "result": -268}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 140)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 140) is 693\n\n####693", "a": 833, "b": 140, "operator": "-", "result": 693}
{"question": "Solve (345 - 993)", "answer": "The result of (345 - 993) is -648\n\n####-648", "a": 345, "b": 993, "operator": "-", "result": -648}
{"question": "Solve (997 * 379)", "answer": "The result of (997 * 379) is 377863\n\n####377863", "a": 997, "b": 379, "operator": "*", "result": 377863}
{"question": "Solve (141 + 466)", "answer": "The result of (141 + 466) is 607\n\n####607", "a": 141, "b": 466, "operator": "+", "result": 607}
{"question": "Solve (306 + 739)", "answer": "The result of (306 + 739) is 1045\n\n####1045", "a": 306, "b": 739, "operator": "+", "result": 1045}
{"question": "Solve (156 - 435)", "answer": "The result of (156 - 435) is -279\n\n####-279", "a": 156, "b": 435, "operator": "-", "result": -279}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 688)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 688) is -34\n\n####-34", "a": 654, "b": 688, "operator": "-", "result": -34}
{"question": "Solve (312 - 279)", "answer": "The result of (312 - 279) is 33\n\n####33", "a": 312, "b": 279, "operator": "-", "result": 33}
{"question": "Solve (807 - 312)", "answer": "The result of (807 - 312) is 495\n\n####495", "a": 807, "b": 312, "operator": "-", "result": 495}
{"question": "Solve (499 / 95)", "answer": "The result of (499 / 95) is 5.2526\n\n####5.2526", "a": 499, "b": 95, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2526}
{"question": "Solve (394 * 869)", "answer": "The result of (394 * 869) is 342386\n\n####342386", "a": 394, "b": 869, "operator": "*", "result": 342386}
{"question": "Solve (477 / 638)", "answer": "The result of (477 / 638) is 0.7476\n\n####0.7476", "a": 477, "b": 638, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7476}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 325)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 325) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 654, "b": 325, "operator": "-", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (123 / 234)", "answer": "The result of (123 / 234) is 0.5256\n\n####0.5256", "a": 123, "b": 234, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5256}
{"question": "Solve (249 * 74)", "answer": "The result of (249 * 74) is 18426\n\n####18426", "a": 249, "b": 74, "operator": "*", "result": 18426}
{"question": "Solve (533 - 15)", "answer": "The result of (533 - 15) is 518\n\n####518", "a": 533, "b": 15, "operator": "-", "result": 518}
{"question": "Solve (514 + 459)", "answer": "The result of (514 + 459) is 973\n\n####973", "a": 514, "b": 459, "operator": "+", "result": 973}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 118)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 118) is 7.7797\n\n####7.7797", "a": 918, "b": 118, "operator": "/", "result": 7.7797}
{"question": "Solve (478 / 616)", "answer": "The result of (478 / 616) is 0.776\n\n####0.776", "a": 478, "b": 616, "operator": "/", "result": 0.776}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 981)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 981) is -911\n\n####-911", "a": 70, "b": 981, "operator": "-", "result": -911}
{"question": "Solve (150 - 641)", "answer": "The result of (150 - 641) is -491\n\n####-491", "a": 150, "b": 641, "operator": "-", "result": -491}
{"question": "Solve (589 * 458)", "answer": "The result of (589 * 458) is 269762\n\n####269762", "a": 589, "b": 458, "operator": "*", "result": 269762}
{"question": "Solve (435 / 969)", "answer": "The result of (435 / 969) is 0.4489\n\n####0.4489", "a": 435, "b": 969, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4489}
{"question": "Solve (437 + 793)", "answer": "The result of (437 + 793) is 1230\n\n####1230", "a": 437, "b": 793, "operator": "+", "result": 1230}
{"question": "Solve (105 / 352)", "answer": "The result of (105 / 352) is 0.2983\n\n####0.2983", "a": 105, "b": 352, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2983}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 715)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 715) is -79\n\n####-79", "a": 636, "b": 715, "operator": "-", "result": -79}
{"question": "Solve (283 / 457)", "answer": "The result of (283 / 457) is 0.6193\n\n####0.6193", "a": 283, "b": 457, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6193}
{"question": "Solve (833 * 362)", "answer": "The result of (833 * 362) is 301546\n\n####301546", "a": 833, "b": 362, "operator": "*", "result": 301546}
{"question": "Solve (196 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (196 - 945) is -749\n\n####-749", "a": 196, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -749}
{"question": "Solve (760 - 585)", "answer": "The result of (760 - 585) is 175\n\n####175", "a": 760, "b": 585, "operator": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve (524 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (524 - 567) is -43\n\n####-43", "a": 524, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": -43}
{"question": "Solve (393 * 416)", "answer": "The result of (393 * 416) is 163488\n\n####163488", "a": 393, "b": 416, "operator": "*", "result": 163488}
{"question": "Solve (660 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (660 - 514) is 146\n\n####146", "a": 660, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": 146}
{"question": "Solve (243 * 122)", "answer": "The result of (243 * 122) is 29646\n\n####29646", "a": 243, "b": 122, "operator": "*", "result": 29646}
{"question": "Solve (990 * 539)", "answer": "The result of (990 * 539) is 533610\n\n####533610", "a": 990, "b": 539, "operator": "*", "result": 533610}
{"question": "Solve (99 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (99 / 300) is 0.33\n\n####0.33", "a": 99, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 0.33}
{"question": "Solve (496 / 733)", "answer": "The result of (496 / 733) is 0.6767\n\n####0.6767", "a": 496, "b": 733, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6767}
{"question": "Solve (598 + 29)", "answer": "The result of (598 + 29) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 598, "b": 29, "operator": "+", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (385 / 872)", "answer": "The result of (385 / 872) is 0.4415\n\n####0.4415", "a": 385, "b": 872, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4415}
{"question": "Solve (879 / 610)", "answer": "The result of (879 / 610) is 1.441\n\n####1.441", "a": 879, "b": 610, "operator": "/", "result": 1.441}
{"question": "Solve (442 - 264)", "answer": "The result of (442 - 264) is 178\n\n####178", "a": 442, "b": 264, "operator": "-", "result": 178}
{"question": "Solve (603 - 203)", "answer": "The result of (603 - 203) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 603, "b": 203, "operator": "-", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (275 - 950)", "answer": "The result of (275 - 950) is -675\n\n####-675", "a": 275, "b": 950, "operator": "-", "result": -675}
{"question": "Solve (821 * 436)", "answer": "The result of (821 * 436) is 357956\n\n####357956", "a": 821, "b": 436, "operator": "*", "result": 357956}
{"question": "Solve (409 - 296)", "answer": "The result of (409 - 296) is 113\n\n####113", "a": 409, "b": 296, "operator": "-", "result": 113}
{"question": "Solve (140 * 831)", "answer": "The result of (140 * 831) is 116340\n\n####116340", "a": 140, "b": 831, "operator": "*", "result": 116340}
{"question": "Solve (751 - 616)", "answer": "The result of (751 - 616) is 135\n\n####135", "a": 751, "b": 616, "operator": "-", "result": 135}
{"question": "Solve (6 + 793)", "answer": "The result of (6 + 793) is 799\n\n####799", "a": 6, "b": 793, "operator": "+", "result": 799}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 86)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 86) is -46\n\n####-46", "a": 40, "b": 86, "operator": "-", "result": -46}
{"question": "Solve (421 * 286)", "answer": "The result of (421 * 286) is 120406\n\n####120406", "a": 421, "b": 286, "operator": "*", "result": 120406}
{"question": "Solve (103 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (103 / 475) is 0.2168\n\n####0.2168", "a": 103, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2168}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 525)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 525) is -455\n\n####-455", "a": 70, "b": 525, "operator": "-", "result": -455}
{"question": "Solve (459 + 284)", "answer": "The result of (459 + 284) is 743\n\n####743", "a": 459, "b": 284, "operator": "+", "result": 743}
{"question": "Solve (944 / 325)", "answer": "The result of (944 / 325) is 2.9046\n\n####2.9046", "a": 944, "b": 325, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9046}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 484)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 484) is 6\n\n####6", "a": 490, "b": 484, "operator": "-", "result": 6}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 470)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 470) is -418\n\n####-418", "a": 52, "b": 470, "operator": "-", "result": -418}
{"question": "Solve (701 - 235)", "answer": "The result of (701 - 235) is 466\n\n####466", "a": 701, "b": 235, "operator": "-", "result": 466}
{"question": "Solve (515 - 40)", "answer": "The result of (515 - 40) is 475\n\n####475", "a": 515, "b": 40, "operator": "-", "result": 475}
{"question": "Solve (169 * 641)", "answer": "The result of (169 * 641) is 108329\n\n####108329", "a": 169, "b": 641, "operator": "*", "result": 108329}
{"question": "Solve (112 * 824)", "answer": "The result of (112 * 824) is 92288\n\n####92288", "a": 112, "b": 824, "operator": "*", "result": 92288}
{"question": "Solve (634 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (634 / 87) is 7.2874\n\n####7.2874", "a": 634, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 7.2874}
{"question": "Solve (252 + 917)", "answer": "The result of (252 + 917) is 1169\n\n####1169", "a": 252, "b": 917, "operator": "+", "result": 1169}
{"question": "Solve (516 - 694)", "answer": "The result of (516 - 694) is -178\n\n####-178", "a": 516, "b": 694, "operator": "-", "result": -178}
{"question": "Solve (804 - 171)", "answer": "The result of (804 - 171) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 804, "b": 171, "operator": "-", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (448 + 618)", "answer": "The result of (448 + 618) is 1066\n\n####1066", "a": 448, "b": 618, "operator": "+", "result": 1066}
{"question": "Solve (410 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (410 * 485) is 198850\n\n####198850", "a": 410, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 198850}
{"question": "Solve (45 + 492)", "answer": "The result of (45 + 492) is 537\n\n####537", "a": 45, "b": 492, "operator": "+", "result": 537}
{"question": "Solve (662 + 250)", "answer": "The result of (662 + 250) is 912\n\n####912", "a": 662, "b": 250, "operator": "+", "result": 912}
{"question": "Solve (865 / 143)", "answer": "The result of (865 / 143) is 6.049\n\n####6.049", "a": 865, "b": 143, "operator": "/", "result": 6.049}
{"question": "Solve (381 + 872)", "answer": "The result of (381 + 872) is 1253\n\n####1253", "a": 381, "b": 872, "operator": "+", "result": 1253}
{"question": "Solve (252 * 946)", "answer": "The result of (252 * 946) is 238392\n\n####238392", "a": 252, "b": 946, "operator": "*", "result": 238392}
{"question": "Solve (648 - 81)", "answer": "The result of (648 - 81) is 567\n\n####567", "a": 648, "b": 81, "operator": "-", "result": 567}
{"question": "Solve (837 + 850)", "answer": "The result of (837 + 850) is 1687\n\n####1687", "a": 837, "b": 850, "operator": "+", "result": 1687}
{"question": "Solve (645 - 345)", "answer": "The result of (645 - 345) is 300\n\n####300", "a": 645, "b": 345, "operator": "-", "result": 300}
{"question": "Solve (396 + 635)", "answer": "The result of (396 + 635) is 1031\n\n####1031", "a": 396, "b": 635, "operator": "+", "result": 1031}
{"question": "Solve (790 * 10)", "answer": "The result of (790 * 10) is 7900\n\n####7900", "a": 790, "b": 10, "operator": "*", "result": 7900}
{"question": "Solve (295 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (295 - 777) is -482\n\n####-482", "a": 295, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -482}
{"question": "Solve (783 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (783 - 256) is 527\n\n####527", "a": 783, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": 527}
{"question": "Solve (823 - 47)", "answer": "The result of (823 - 47) is 776\n\n####776", "a": 823, "b": 47, "operator": "-", "result": 776}
{"question": "Solve (358 / 170)", "answer": "The result of (358 / 170) is 2.1059\n\n####2.1059", "a": 358, "b": 170, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1059}
{"question": "Solve (932 / 988)", "answer": "The result of (932 / 988) is 0.9433\n\n####0.9433", "a": 932, "b": 988, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9433}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 528)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 528) is 0.6837\n\n####0.6837", "a": 361, "b": 528, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6837}
{"question": "Solve (935 - 625)", "answer": "The result of (935 - 625) is 310\n\n####310", "a": 935, "b": 625, "operator": "-", "result": 310}
{"question": "Solve (47 - 13)", "answer": "The result of (47 - 13) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 47, "b": 13, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (378 / 743)", "answer": "The result of (378 / 743) is 0.5087\n\n####0.5087", "a": 378, "b": 743, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5087}
{"question": "Solve (154 - 685)", "answer": "The result of (154 - 685) is -531\n\n####-531", "a": 154, "b": 685, "operator": "-", "result": -531}
{"question": "Solve (890 - 552)", "answer": "The result of (890 - 552) is 338\n\n####338", "a": 890, "b": 552, "operator": "-", "result": 338}
{"question": "Solve (782 - 716)", "answer": "The result of (782 - 716) is 66\n\n####66", "a": 782, "b": 716, "operator": "-", "result": 66}
{"question": "Solve (450 + 26)", "answer": "The result of (450 + 26) is 476\n\n####476", "a": 450, "b": 26, "operator": "+", "result": 476}
{"question": "Solve (614 * 579)", "answer": "The result of (614 * 579) is 355506\n\n####355506", "a": 614, "b": 579, "operator": "*", "result": 355506}
{"question": "Solve (588 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (588 * 596) is 350448\n\n####350448", "a": 588, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 350448}
{"question": "Solve (219 * 541)", "answer": "The result of (219 * 541) is 118479\n\n####118479", "a": 219, "b": 541, "operator": "*", "result": 118479}
{"question": "Solve (956 / 50)", "answer": "The result of (956 / 50) is 19.12\n\n####19.12", "a": 956, "b": 50, "operator": "/", "result": 19.12}
{"question": "Solve (718 / 848)", "answer": "The result of (718 / 848) is 0.8467\n\n####0.8467", "a": 718, "b": 848, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8467}
{"question": "Solve (216 - 984)", "answer": "The result of (216 - 984) is -768\n\n####-768", "a": 216, "b": 984, "operator": "-", "result": -768}
{"question": "Solve (74 - 370)", "answer": "The result of (74 - 370) is -296\n\n####-296", "a": 74, "b": 370, "operator": "-", "result": -296}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 282)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 282) is 656\n\n####656", "a": 938, "b": 282, "operator": "-", "result": 656}
{"question": "Solve (479 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (479 * 524) is 250996\n\n####250996", "a": 479, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 250996}
{"question": "Solve (158 + 972)", "answer": "The result of (158 + 972) is 1130\n\n####1130", "a": 158, "b": 972, "operator": "+", "result": 1130}
{"question": "Solve (871 - 993)", "answer": "The result of (871 - 993) is -122\n\n####-122", "a": 871, "b": 993, "operator": "-", "result": -122}
{"question": "Solve (327 * 544)", "answer": "The result of (327 * 544) is 177888\n\n####177888", "a": 327, "b": 544, "operator": "*", "result": 177888}
{"question": "Solve (926 - 60)", "answer": "The result of (926 - 60) is 866\n\n####866", "a": 926, "b": 60, "operator": "-", "result": 866}
{"question": "Solve (400 / 604)", "answer": "The result of (400 / 604) is 0.6623\n\n####0.6623", "a": 400, "b": 604, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6623}
{"question": "Solve (65 - 412)", "answer": "The result of (65 - 412) is -347\n\n####-347", "a": 65, "b": 412, "operator": "-", "result": -347}
{"question": "Solve (590 * 863)", "answer": "The result of (590 * 863) is 509170\n\n####509170", "a": 590, "b": 863, "operator": "*", "result": 509170}
{"question": "Solve (893 - 99)", "answer": "The result of (893 - 99) is 794\n\n####794", "a": 893, "b": 99, "operator": "-", "result": 794}
{"question": "Solve (764 - 977)", "answer": "The result of (764 - 977) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 764, "b": 977, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 242)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 242) is 119\n\n####119", "a": 361, "b": 242, "operator": "-", "result": 119}
{"question": "Solve (355 / 285)", "answer": "The result of (355 / 285) is 1.2456\n\n####1.2456", "a": 355, "b": 285, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2456}
{"question": "Solve (92 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (92 * 175) is 16100\n\n####16100", "a": 92, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 16100}
{"question": "Solve (641 * 806)", "answer": "The result of (641 * 806) is 516646\n\n####516646", "a": 641, "b": 806, "operator": "*", "result": 516646}
{"question": "Solve (658 - 83)", "answer": "The result of (658 - 83) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 658, "b": 83, "operator": "-", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (465 + 13)", "answer": "The result of (465 + 13) is 478\n\n####478", "a": 465, "b": 13, "operator": "+", "result": 478}
{"question": "Solve (292 * 27)", "answer": "The result of (292 * 27) is 7884\n\n####7884", "a": 292, "b": 27, "operator": "*", "result": 7884}
{"question": "Solve (303 / 699)", "answer": "The result of (303 / 699) is 0.4335\n\n####0.4335", "a": 303, "b": 699, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4335}
{"question": "Solve (357 - 66)", "answer": "The result of (357 - 66) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 357, "b": 66, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 231)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 231) is 0.5887\n\n####0.5887", "a": 136, "b": 231, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5887}
{"question": "Solve (523 + 788)", "answer": "The result of (523 + 788) is 1311\n\n####1311", "a": 523, "b": 788, "operator": "+", "result": 1311}
{"question": "Solve (957 + 731)", "answer": "The result of (957 + 731) is 1688\n\n####1688", "a": 957, "b": 731, "operator": "+", "result": 1688}
{"question": "Solve (386 * 600)", "answer": "The result of (386 * 600) is 231600\n\n####231600", "a": 386, "b": 600, "operator": "*", "result": 231600}
{"question": "Solve (612 + 815)", "answer": "The result of (612 + 815) is 1427\n\n####1427", "a": 612, "b": 815, "operator": "+", "result": 1427}
{"question": "Solve (640 + 798)", "answer": "The result of (640 + 798) is 1438\n\n####1438", "a": 640, "b": 798, "operator": "+", "result": 1438}
{"question": "Solve (690 + 828)", "answer": "The result of (690 + 828) is 1518\n\n####1518", "a": 690, "b": 828, "operator": "+", "result": 1518}
{"question": "Solve (581 * 653)", "answer": "The result of (581 * 653) is 379393\n\n####379393", "a": 581, "b": 653, "operator": "*", "result": 379393}
{"question": "Solve (434 / 42)", "answer": "The result of (434 / 42) is 10.3333\n\n####10.3333", "a": 434, "b": 42, "operator": "/", "result": 10.3333}
{"question": "Solve (98 * 352)", "answer": "The result of (98 * 352) is 34496\n\n####34496", "a": 98, "b": 352, "operator": "*", "result": 34496}
{"question": "Solve (442 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (442 - 342) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 442, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (467 - 309)", "answer": "The result of (467 - 309) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 467, "b": 309, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (579 / 637)", "answer": "The result of (579 / 637) is 0.9089\n\n####0.9089", "a": 579, "b": 637, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9089}
{"question": "Solve (391 * 624)", "answer": "The result of (391 * 624) is 243984\n\n####243984", "a": 391, "b": 624, "operator": "*", "result": 243984}
{"question": "Solve (845 / 970)", "answer": "The result of (845 / 970) is 0.8711\n\n####0.8711", "a": 845, "b": 970, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8711}
{"question": "Solve (324 + 496)", "answer": "The result of (324 + 496) is 820\n\n####820", "a": 324, "b": 496, "operator": "+", "result": 820}
{"question": "Solve (973 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (973 / 674) is 1.4436\n\n####1.4436", "a": 973, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4436}
{"question": "Solve (245 * 595)", "answer": "The result of (245 * 595) is 145775\n\n####145775", "a": 245, "b": 595, "operator": "*", "result": 145775}
{"question": "Solve (387 / 899)", "answer": "The result of (387 / 899) is 0.4305\n\n####0.4305", "a": 387, "b": 899, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4305}
{"question": "Solve (959 * 580)", "answer": "The result of (959 * 580) is 556220\n\n####556220", "a": 959, "b": 580, "operator": "*", "result": 556220}
{"question": "Solve (612 / 422)", "answer": "The result of (612 / 422) is 1.4502\n\n####1.4502", "a": 612, "b": 422, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4502}
{"question": "Solve (380 / 968)", "answer": "The result of (380 / 968) is 0.3926\n\n####0.3926", "a": 380, "b": 968, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3926}
{"question": "Solve (719 + 353)", "answer": "The result of (719 + 353) is 1072\n\n####1072", "a": 719, "b": 353, "operator": "+", "result": 1072}
{"question": "Solve (964 + 496)", "answer": "The result of (964 + 496) is 1460\n\n####1460", "a": 964, "b": 496, "operator": "+", "result": 1460}
{"question": "Solve (139 * 611)", "answer": "The result of (139 * 611) is 84929\n\n####84929", "a": 139, "b": 611, "operator": "*", "result": 84929}
{"question": "Solve (670 - 407)", "answer": "The result of (670 - 407) is 263\n\n####263", "a": 670, "b": 407, "operator": "-", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve (59 - 896)", "answer": "The result of (59 - 896) is -837\n\n####-837", "a": 59, "b": 896, "operator": "-", "result": -837}
{"question": "Solve (414 + 553)", "answer": "The result of (414 + 553) is 967\n\n####967", "a": 414, "b": 553, "operator": "+", "result": 967}
{"question": "Solve (15 + 337)", "answer": "The result of (15 + 337) is 352\n\n####352", "a": 15, "b": 337, "operator": "+", "result": 352}
{"question": "Solve (221 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (221 * 884) is 195364\n\n####195364", "a": 221, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 195364}
{"question": "Solve (644 / 952)", "answer": "The result of (644 / 952) is 0.6765\n\n####0.6765", "a": 644, "b": 952, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6765}
{"question": "Solve (618 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (618 - 496) is 122\n\n####122", "a": 618, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve (717 * 385)", "answer": "The result of (717 * 385) is 276045\n\n####276045", "a": 717, "b": 385, "operator": "*", "result": 276045}
{"question": "Solve (388 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (388 / 669) is 0.58\n\n####0.58", "a": 388, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 0.58}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 28)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 28) is 42\n\n####42", "a": 70, "b": 28, "operator": "-", "result": 42}
{"question": "Solve (228 + 204)", "answer": "The result of (228 + 204) is 432\n\n####432", "a": 228, "b": 204, "operator": "+", "result": 432}
{"question": "Solve (39 * 292)", "answer": "The result of (39 * 292) is 11388\n\n####11388", "a": 39, "b": 292, "operator": "*", "result": 11388}
{"question": "Solve (625 - 854)", "answer": "The result of (625 - 854) is -229\n\n####-229", "a": 625, "b": 854, "operator": "-", "result": -229}
{"question": "Solve (571 / 745)", "answer": "The result of (571 / 745) is 0.7664\n\n####0.7664", "a": 571, "b": 745, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7664}
{"question": "Solve (995 * 62)", "answer": "The result of (995 * 62) is 61690\n\n####61690", "a": 995, "b": 62, "operator": "*", "result": 61690}
{"question": "Solve (132 * 431)", "answer": "The result of (132 * 431) is 56892\n\n####56892", "a": 132, "b": 431, "operator": "*", "result": 56892}
{"question": "Solve (552 * 183)", "answer": "The result of (552 * 183) is 101016\n\n####101016", "a": 552, "b": 183, "operator": "*", "result": 101016}
{"question": "Solve (453 + 108)", "answer": "The result of (453 + 108) is 561\n\n####561", "a": 453, "b": 108, "operator": "+", "result": 561}
{"question": "Solve (84 * 921)", "answer": "The result of (84 * 921) is 77364\n\n####77364", "a": 84, "b": 921, "operator": "*", "result": 77364}
{"question": "Solve (784 + 27)", "answer": "The result of (784 + 27) is 811\n\n####811", "a": 784, "b": 27, "operator": "+", "result": 811}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 742)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 742) is 388808\n\n####388808", "a": 524, "b": 742, "operator": "*", "result": 388808}
{"question": "Solve (446 * 419)", "answer": "The result of (446 * 419) is 186874\n\n####186874", "a": 446, "b": 419, "operator": "*", "result": 186874}
{"question": "Solve (506 + 859)", "answer": "The result of (506 + 859) is 1365\n\n####1365", "a": 506, "b": 859, "operator": "+", "result": 1365}
{"question": "Solve (978 - 241)", "answer": "The result of (978 - 241) is 737\n\n####737", "a": 978, "b": 241, "operator": "-", "result": 737}
{"question": "Solve (852 * 329)", "answer": "The result of (852 * 329) is 280308\n\n####280308", "a": 852, "b": 329, "operator": "*", "result": 280308}
{"question": "Solve (437 + 391)", "answer": "The result of (437 + 391) is 828\n\n####828", "a": 437, "b": 391, "operator": "+", "result": 828}
{"question": "Solve (583 - 648)", "answer": "The result of (583 - 648) is -65\n\n####-65", "a": 583, "b": 648, "operator": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve (599 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (599 - 233) is 366\n\n####366", "a": 599, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": 366}
{"question": "Solve (51 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (51 * 823) is 41973\n\n####41973", "a": 51, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 41973}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 987)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 987) is 391839\n\n####391839", "a": 397, "b": 987, "operator": "*", "result": 391839}
{"question": "Solve (482 * 635)", "answer": "The result of (482 * 635) is 306070\n\n####306070", "a": 482, "b": 635, "operator": "*", "result": 306070}
{"question": "Solve (181 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (181 - 27) is 154\n\n####154", "a": 181, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 154}
{"question": "Solve (468 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (468 - 724) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 468, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (257 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (257 * 944) is 242608\n\n####242608", "a": 257, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 242608}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 68)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 68) is 742\n\n####742", "a": 810, "b": 68, "operator": "-", "result": 742}
{"question": "Solve (885 * 553)", "answer": "The result of (885 * 553) is 489405\n\n####489405", "a": 885, "b": 553, "operator": "*", "result": 489405}
{"question": "Solve (908 - 282)", "answer": "The result of (908 - 282) is 626\n\n####626", "a": 908, "b": 282, "operator": "-", "result": 626}
{"question": "Solve (772 * 486)", "answer": "The result of (772 * 486) is 375192\n\n####375192", "a": 772, "b": 486, "operator": "*", "result": 375192}
{"question": "Solve (671 + 599)", "answer": "The result of (671 + 599) is 1270\n\n####1270", "a": 671, "b": 599, "operator": "+", "result": 1270}
{"question": "Solve (696 - 15)", "answer": "The result of (696 - 15) is 681\n\n####681", "a": 696, "b": 15, "operator": "-", "result": 681}
{"question": "Solve (965 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (965 + 211) is 1176\n\n####1176", "a": 965, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 1176}
{"question": "Solve (378 - 589)", "answer": "The result of (378 - 589) is -211\n\n####-211", "a": 378, "b": 589, "operator": "-", "result": -211}
{"question": "Solve (865 * 235)", "answer": "The result of (865 * 235) is 203275\n\n####203275", "a": 865, "b": 235, "operator": "*", "result": 203275}
{"question": "Solve (483 - 597)", "answer": "The result of (483 - 597) is -114\n\n####-114", "a": 483, "b": 597, "operator": "-", "result": -114}
{"question": "Solve (385 / 772)", "answer": "The result of (385 / 772) is 0.4987\n\n####0.4987", "a": 385, "b": 772, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4987}
{"question": "Solve (876 / 493)", "answer": "The result of (876 / 493) is 1.7769\n\n####1.7769", "a": 876, "b": 493, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7769}
{"question": "Solve (555 / 175)", "answer": "The result of (555 / 175) is 3.1714\n\n####3.1714", "a": 555, "b": 175, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1714}
{"question": "Solve (179 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (179 / 385) is 0.4649\n\n####0.4649", "a": 179, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4649}
{"question": "Solve (221 / 851)", "answer": "The result of (221 / 851) is 0.2597\n\n####0.2597", "a": 221, "b": 851, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2597}
{"question": "Solve (140 + 151)", "answer": "The result of (140 + 151) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 140, "b": 151, "operator": "+", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 546)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 546) is 1518\n\n####1518", "a": 972, "b": 546, "operator": "+", "result": 1518}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 344) is -47\n\n####-47", "a": 297, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve (247 - 915)", "answer": "The result of (247 - 915) is -668\n\n####-668", "a": 247, "b": 915, "operator": "-", "result": -668}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 958) is 742450\n\n####742450", "a": 775, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 742450}
{"question": "Solve (712 - 264)", "answer": "The result of (712 - 264) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 712, "b": 264, "operator": "-", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (677 * 917)", "answer": "The result of (677 * 917) is 620809\n\n####620809", "a": 677, "b": 917, "operator": "*", "result": 620809}
{"question": "Solve (202 * 578)", "answer": "The result of (202 * 578) is 116756\n\n####116756", "a": 202, "b": 578, "operator": "*", "result": 116756}
{"question": "Solve (459 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (459 * 861) is 395199\n\n####395199", "a": 459, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 395199}
{"question": "Solve (363 * 227)", "answer": "The result of (363 * 227) is 82401\n\n####82401", "a": 363, "b": 227, "operator": "*", "result": 82401}
{"question": "Solve (275 - 915)", "answer": "The result of (275 - 915) is -640\n\n####-640", "a": 275, "b": 915, "operator": "-", "result": -640}
{"question": "Solve (93 * 405)", "answer": "The result of (93 * 405) is 37665\n\n####37665", "a": 93, "b": 405, "operator": "*", "result": 37665}
{"question": "Solve (110 + 335)", "answer": "The result of (110 + 335) is 445\n\n####445", "a": 110, "b": 335, "operator": "+", "result": 445}
{"question": "Solve (964 * 250)", "answer": "The result of (964 * 250) is 241000\n\n####241000", "a": 964, "b": 250, "operator": "*", "result": 241000}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 235)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 235) is -38\n\n####-38", "a": 197, "b": 235, "operator": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve (8 / 505)", "answer": "The result of (8 / 505) is 0.0158\n\n####0.0158", "a": 8, "b": 505, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0158}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 512) is 82\n\n####82", "a": 594, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve (899 / 74)", "answer": "The result of (899 / 74) is 12.1486\n\n####12.1486", "a": 899, "b": 74, "operator": "/", "result": 12.1486}
{"question": "Solve (81 + 537)", "answer": "The result of (81 + 537) is 618\n\n####618", "a": 81, "b": 537, "operator": "+", "result": 618}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 113)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 113) is 473\n\n####473", "a": 586, "b": 113, "operator": "-", "result": 473}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 281)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 281) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 361, "b": 281, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (858 + 353)", "answer": "The result of (858 + 353) is 1211\n\n####1211", "a": 858, "b": 353, "operator": "+", "result": 1211}
{"question": "Solve (598 * 286)", "answer": "The result of (598 * 286) is 171028\n\n####171028", "a": 598, "b": 286, "operator": "*", "result": 171028}
{"question": "Solve (93 * 775)", "answer": "The result of (93 * 775) is 72075\n\n####72075", "a": 93, "b": 775, "operator": "*", "result": 72075}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 938)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 938) is 94738\n\n####94738", "a": 101, "b": 938, "operator": "*", "result": 94738}
{"question": "Solve (378 + 415)", "answer": "The result of (378 + 415) is 793\n\n####793", "a": 378, "b": 415, "operator": "+", "result": 793}
{"question": "Solve (830 + 328)", "answer": "The result of (830 + 328) is 1158\n\n####1158", "a": 830, "b": 328, "operator": "+", "result": 1158}
{"question": "Solve (937 / 961)", "answer": "The result of (937 / 961) is 0.975\n\n####0.975", "a": 937, "b": 961, "operator": "/", "result": 0.975}
{"question": "Solve (264 + 349)", "answer": "The result of (264 + 349) is 613\n\n####613", "a": 264, "b": 349, "operator": "+", "result": 613}
{"question": "Solve (79 * 408)", "answer": "The result of (79 * 408) is 32232\n\n####32232", "a": 79, "b": 408, "operator": "*", "result": 32232}
{"question": "Solve (489 * 817)", "answer": "The result of (489 * 817) is 399513\n\n####399513", "a": 489, "b": 817, "operator": "*", "result": 399513}
{"question": "Solve (502 + 484)", "answer": "The result of (502 + 484) is 986\n\n####986", "a": 502, "b": 484, "operator": "+", "result": 986}
{"question": "Solve (900 + 67)", "answer": "The result of (900 + 67) is 967\n\n####967", "a": 900, "b": 67, "operator": "+", "result": 967}
{"question": "Solve (87 - 741)", "answer": "The result of (87 - 741) is -654\n\n####-654", "a": 87, "b": 741, "operator": "-", "result": -654}
{"question": "Solve (988 / 346)", "answer": "The result of (988 / 346) is 2.8555\n\n####2.8555", "a": 988, "b": 346, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8555}
{"question": "Solve (260 / 162)", "answer": "The result of (260 / 162) is 1.6049\n\n####1.6049", "a": 260, "b": 162, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6049}
{"question": "Solve (434 * 441)", "answer": "The result of (434 * 441) is 191394\n\n####191394", "a": 434, "b": 441, "operator": "*", "result": 191394}
{"question": "Solve (764 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (764 * 780) is 595920\n\n####595920", "a": 764, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 595920}
{"question": "Solve (642 * 157)", "answer": "The result of (642 * 157) is 100794\n\n####100794", "a": 642, "b": 157, "operator": "*", "result": 100794}
{"question": "Solve (289 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (289 - 949) is -660\n\n####-660", "a": 289, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -660}
{"question": "Solve (760 + 151)", "answer": "The result of (760 + 151) is 911\n\n####911", "a": 760, "b": 151, "operator": "+", "result": 911}
{"question": "Solve (498 - 44)", "answer": "The result of (498 - 44) is 454\n\n####454", "a": 498, "b": 44, "operator": "-", "result": 454}
{"question": "Solve (831 - 814)", "answer": "The result of (831 - 814) is 17\n\n####17", "a": 831, "b": 814, "operator": "-", "result": 17}
{"question": "Solve (242 - 400)", "answer": "The result of (242 - 400) is -158\n\n####-158", "a": 242, "b": 400, "operator": "-", "result": -158}
{"question": "Solve (487 - 407)", "answer": "The result of (487 - 407) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 487, "b": 407, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (585 / 115)", "answer": "The result of (585 / 115) is 5.087\n\n####5.087", "a": 585, "b": 115, "operator": "/", "result": 5.087}
{"question": "Solve (683 * 84)", "answer": "The result of (683 * 84) is 57372\n\n####57372", "a": 683, "b": 84, "operator": "*", "result": 57372}
{"question": "Solve (953 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (953 - 701) is 252\n\n####252", "a": 953, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": 252}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 805) is 1482\n\n####1482", "a": 677, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1482}
{"question": "Solve (213 + 948)", "answer": "The result of (213 + 948) is 1161\n\n####1161", "a": 213, "b": 948, "operator": "+", "result": 1161}
{"question": "Solve (439 / 17)", "answer": "The result of (439 / 17) is 25.8235\n\n####25.8235", "a": 439, "b": 17, "operator": "/", "result": 25.8235}
{"question": "Solve (191 + 115)", "answer": "The result of (191 + 115) is 306\n\n####306", "a": 191, "b": 115, "operator": "+", "result": 306}
{"question": "Solve (235 - 12)", "answer": "The result of (235 - 12) is 223\n\n####223", "a": 235, "b": 12, "operator": "-", "result": 223}
{"question": "Solve (185 / 708)", "answer": "The result of (185 / 708) is 0.2613\n\n####0.2613", "a": 185, "b": 708, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2613}
{"question": "Solve (550 + 199)", "answer": "The result of (550 + 199) is 749\n\n####749", "a": 550, "b": 199, "operator": "+", "result": 749}
{"question": "Solve (267 * 639)", "answer": "The result of (267 * 639) is 170613\n\n####170613", "a": 267, "b": 639, "operator": "*", "result": 170613}
{"question": "Solve (439 - 139)", "answer": "The result of (439 - 139) is 300\n\n####300", "a": 439, "b": 139, "operator": "-", "result": 300}
{"question": "Solve (118 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (118 * 142) is 16756\n\n####16756", "a": 118, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 16756}
{"question": "Solve (619 / 535)", "answer": "The result of (619 / 535) is 1.157\n\n####1.157", "a": 619, "b": 535, "operator": "/", "result": 1.157}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 344) is 49\n\n####49", "a": 393, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": 49}
{"question": "Solve (343 / 197)", "answer": "The result of (343 / 197) is 1.7411\n\n####1.7411", "a": 343, "b": 197, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7411}
{"question": "Solve (548 + 729)", "answer": "The result of (548 + 729) is 1277\n\n####1277", "a": 548, "b": 729, "operator": "+", "result": 1277}
{"question": "Solve (285 - 284)", "answer": "The result of (285 - 284) is 1\n\n####1", "a": 285, "b": 284, "operator": "-", "result": 1}
{"question": "Solve (727 - 539)", "answer": "The result of (727 - 539) is 188\n\n####188", "a": 727, "b": 539, "operator": "-", "result": 188}
{"question": "Solve (556 * 672)", "answer": "The result of (556 * 672) is 373632\n\n####373632", "a": 556, "b": 672, "operator": "*", "result": 373632}
{"question": "Solve (138 * 99)", "answer": "The result of (138 * 99) is 13662\n\n####13662", "a": 138, "b": 99, "operator": "*", "result": 13662}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 740)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 740) is 109\n\n####109", "a": 849, "b": 740, "operator": "-", "result": 109}
{"question": "Solve (417 + 89)", "answer": "The result of (417 + 89) is 506\n\n####506", "a": 417, "b": 89, "operator": "+", "result": 506}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 65)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 65) is 2.0769\n\n####2.0769", "a": 135, "b": 65, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0769}
{"question": "Solve (777 / 571)", "answer": "The result of (777 / 571) is 1.3608\n\n####1.3608", "a": 777, "b": 571, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3608}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 535)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 535) is -511\n\n####-511", "a": 24, "b": 535, "operator": "-", "result": -511}
{"question": "Solve (515 + 322)", "answer": "The result of (515 + 322) is 837\n\n####837", "a": 515, "b": 322, "operator": "+", "result": 837}
{"question": "Solve (33 + 67)", "answer": "The result of (33 + 67) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 33, "b": 67, "operator": "+", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (458 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (458 - 514) is -56\n\n####-56", "a": 458, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": -56}
{"question": "Solve (582 + 640)", "answer": "The result of (582 + 640) is 1222\n\n####1222", "a": 582, "b": 640, "operator": "+", "result": 1222}
{"question": "Solve (774 + 247)", "answer": "The result of (774 + 247) is 1021\n\n####1021", "a": 774, "b": 247, "operator": "+", "result": 1021}
{"question": "Solve (277 + 169)", "answer": "The result of (277 + 169) is 446\n\n####446", "a": 277, "b": 169, "operator": "+", "result": 446}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 395)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 395) is 208955\n\n####208955", "a": 529, "b": 395, "operator": "*", "result": 208955}
{"question": "Solve (760 + 369)", "answer": "The result of (760 + 369) is 1129\n\n####1129", "a": 760, "b": 369, "operator": "+", "result": 1129}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 830)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 830) is 643250\n\n####643250", "a": 775, "b": 830, "operator": "*", "result": 643250}
{"question": "Solve (483 - 291)", "answer": "The result of (483 - 291) is 192\n\n####192", "a": 483, "b": 291, "operator": "-", "result": 192}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 816)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 816) is -423\n\n####-423", "a": 393, "b": 816, "operator": "-", "result": -423}
{"question": "Solve (175 + 419)", "answer": "The result of (175 + 419) is 594\n\n####594", "a": 175, "b": 419, "operator": "+", "result": 594}
{"question": "Solve (54 / 729)", "answer": "The result of (54 / 729) is 0.0741\n\n####0.0741", "a": 54, "b": 729, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0741}
{"question": "Solve (985 - 535)", "answer": "The result of (985 - 535) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 985, "b": 535, "operator": "-", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 219)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 219) is -20\n\n####-20", "a": 199, "b": 219, "operator": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve (574 + 98)", "answer": "The result of (574 + 98) is 672\n\n####672", "a": 574, "b": 98, "operator": "+", "result": 672}
{"question": "Solve (606 * 228)", "answer": "The result of (606 * 228) is 138168\n\n####138168", "a": 606, "b": 228, "operator": "*", "result": 138168}
{"question": "Solve (631 / 496)", "answer": "The result of (631 / 496) is 1.2722\n\n####1.2722", "a": 631, "b": 496, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2722}
{"question": "Solve (134 / 964)", "answer": "The result of (134 / 964) is 0.139\n\n####0.139", "a": 134, "b": 964, "operator": "/", "result": 0.139}
{"question": "Solve (670 * 738)", "answer": "The result of (670 * 738) is 494460\n\n####494460", "a": 670, "b": 738, "operator": "*", "result": 494460}
{"question": "Solve (206 - 815)", "answer": "The result of (206 - 815) is -609\n\n####-609", "a": 206, "b": 815, "operator": "-", "result": -609}
{"question": "Solve (903 / 248)", "answer": "The result of (903 / 248) is 3.6411\n\n####3.6411", "a": 903, "b": 248, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6411}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 515)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 515) is 51\n\n####51", "a": 566, "b": 515, "operator": "-", "result": 51}
{"question": "Solve (75 / 54)", "answer": "The result of (75 / 54) is 1.3889\n\n####1.3889", "a": 75, "b": 54, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3889}
{"question": "Solve (283 / 350)", "answer": "The result of (283 / 350) is 0.8086\n\n####0.8086", "a": 283, "b": 350, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8086}
{"question": "Solve (824 - 904)", "answer": "The result of (824 - 904) is -80\n\n####-80", "a": 824, "b": 904, "operator": "-", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve (405 / 120)", "answer": "The result of (405 / 120) is 3.375\n\n####3.375", "a": 405, "b": 120, "operator": "/", "result": 3.375}
{"question": "Solve (864 * 842)", "answer": "The result of (864 * 842) is 727488\n\n####727488", "a": 864, "b": 842, "operator": "*", "result": 727488}
{"question": "Solve (889 - 798)", "answer": "The result of (889 - 798) is 91\n\n####91", "a": 889, "b": 798, "operator": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve (541 + 564)", "answer": "The result of (541 + 564) is 1105\n\n####1105", "a": 541, "b": 564, "operator": "+", "result": 1105}
{"question": "Solve (825 - 878)", "answer": "The result of (825 - 878) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 825, "b": 878, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 666)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 666) is 0.4039\n\n####0.4039", "a": 269, "b": 666, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4039}
{"question": "Solve (843 + 385)", "answer": "The result of (843 + 385) is 1228\n\n####1228", "a": 843, "b": 385, "operator": "+", "result": 1228}
{"question": "Solve (763 + 828)", "answer": "The result of (763 + 828) is 1591\n\n####1591", "a": 763, "b": 828, "operator": "+", "result": 1591}
{"question": "Solve (354 * 20)", "answer": "The result of (354 * 20) is 7080\n\n####7080", "a": 354, "b": 20, "operator": "*", "result": 7080}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 957)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 957) is 0.2894\n\n####0.2894", "a": 277, "b": 957, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2894}
{"question": "Solve (363 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (363 - 471) is -108\n\n####-108", "a": 363, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": -108}
{"question": "Solve (605 - 503)", "answer": "The result of (605 - 503) is 102\n\n####102", "a": 605, "b": 503, "operator": "-", "result": 102}
{"question": "Solve (822 / 364)", "answer": "The result of (822 / 364) is 2.2582\n\n####2.2582", "a": 822, "b": 364, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2582}
{"question": "Solve (962 + 508)", "answer": "The result of (962 + 508) is 1470\n\n####1470", "a": 962, "b": 508, "operator": "+", "result": 1470}
{"question": "Solve (664 * 121)", "answer": "The result of (664 * 121) is 80344\n\n####80344", "a": 664, "b": 121, "operator": "*", "result": 80344}
{"question": "Solve (631 + 289)", "answer": "The result of (631 + 289) is 920\n\n####920", "a": 631, "b": 289, "operator": "+", "result": 920}
{"question": "Solve (469 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (469 * 357) is 167433\n\n####167433", "a": 469, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 167433}
{"question": "Solve (784 - 527)", "answer": "The result of (784 - 527) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 784, "b": 527, "operator": "-", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (526 - 356)", "answer": "The result of (526 - 356) is 170\n\n####170", "a": 526, "b": 356, "operator": "-", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve (838 + 390)", "answer": "The result of (838 + 390) is 1228\n\n####1228", "a": 838, "b": 390, "operator": "+", "result": 1228}
{"question": "Solve (408 - 904)", "answer": "The result of (408 - 904) is -496\n\n####-496", "a": 408, "b": 904, "operator": "-", "result": -496}
{"question": "Solve (382 - 211)", "answer": "The result of (382 - 211) is 171\n\n####171", "a": 382, "b": 211, "operator": "-", "result": 171}
{"question": "Solve (124 / 929)", "answer": "The result of (124 / 929) is 0.1335\n\n####0.1335", "a": 124, "b": 929, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1335}
{"question": "Solve (416 - 202)", "answer": "The result of (416 - 202) is 214\n\n####214", "a": 416, "b": 202, "operator": "-", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 856)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 856) is 339832\n\n####339832", "a": 397, "b": 856, "operator": "*", "result": 339832}
{"question": "Solve (405 / 120)", "answer": "The result of (405 / 120) is 3.375\n\n####3.375", "a": 405, "b": 120, "operator": "/", "result": 3.375}
{"question": "Solve (733 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (733 - 262) is 471\n\n####471", "a": 733, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": 471}
{"question": "Solve (95 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (95 - 492) is -397\n\n####-397", "a": 95, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": -397}
{"question": "Solve (29 + 621)", "answer": "The result of (29 + 621) is 650\n\n####650", "a": 29, "b": 621, "operator": "+", "result": 650}
{"question": "Solve (251 / 812)", "answer": "The result of (251 / 812) is 0.3091\n\n####0.3091", "a": 251, "b": 812, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3091}
{"question": "Solve (805 + 188)", "answer": "The result of (805 + 188) is 993\n\n####993", "a": 805, "b": 188, "operator": "+", "result": 993}
{"question": "Solve (266 * 555)", "answer": "The result of (266 * 555) is 147630\n\n####147630", "a": 266, "b": 555, "operator": "*", "result": 147630}
{"question": "Solve (514 + 669)", "answer": "The result of (514 + 669) is 1183\n\n####1183", "a": 514, "b": 669, "operator": "+", "result": 1183}
{"question": "Solve (289 + 144)", "answer": "The result of (289 + 144) is 433\n\n####433", "a": 289, "b": 144, "operator": "+", "result": 433}
{"question": "Solve (953 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (953 - 471) is 482\n\n####482", "a": 953, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": 482}
{"question": "Solve (113 * 508)", "answer": "The result of (113 * 508) is 57404\n\n####57404", "a": 113, "b": 508, "operator": "*", "result": 57404}
{"question": "Solve (936 + 701)", "answer": "The result of (936 + 701) is 1637\n\n####1637", "a": 936, "b": 701, "operator": "+", "result": 1637}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 424)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 424) is 915\n\n####915", "a": 491, "b": 424, "operator": "+", "result": 915}
{"question": "Solve (320 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (320 - 604) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 320, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (145 / 478)", "answer": "The result of (145 / 478) is 0.3033\n\n####0.3033", "a": 145, "b": 478, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3033}
{"question": "Solve (939 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (939 / 289) is 3.2491\n\n####3.2491", "a": 939, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2491}
{"question": "Solve (329 - 778)", "answer": "The result of (329 - 778) is -449\n\n####-449", "a": 329, "b": 778, "operator": "-", "result": -449}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 296)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 296) is 567\n\n####567", "a": 863, "b": 296, "operator": "-", "result": 567}
{"question": "Solve (199 / 111)", "answer": "The result of (199 / 111) is 1.7928\n\n####1.7928", "a": 199, "b": 111, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7928}
{"question": "Solve (121 / 455)", "answer": "The result of (121 / 455) is 0.2659\n\n####0.2659", "a": 121, "b": 455, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2659}
{"question": "Solve (463 * 213)", "answer": "The result of (463 * 213) is 98619\n\n####98619", "a": 463, "b": 213, "operator": "*", "result": 98619}
{"question": "Solve (902 / 992)", "answer": "The result of (902 / 992) is 0.9093\n\n####0.9093", "a": 902, "b": 992, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9093}
{"question": "Solve (111 * 574)", "answer": "The result of (111 * 574) is 63714\n\n####63714", "a": 111, "b": 574, "operator": "*", "result": 63714}
{"question": "Solve (752 - 3)", "answer": "The result of (752 - 3) is 749\n\n####749", "a": 752, "b": 3, "operator": "-", "result": 749}
{"question": "Solve (853 + 441)", "answer": "The result of (853 + 441) is 1294\n\n####1294", "a": 853, "b": 441, "operator": "+", "result": 1294}
{"question": "Solve (64 - 897)", "answer": "The result of (64 - 897) is -833\n\n####-833", "a": 64, "b": 897, "operator": "-", "result": -833}
{"question": "Solve (979 - 8)", "answer": "The result of (979 - 8) is 971\n\n####971", "a": 979, "b": 8, "operator": "-", "result": 971}
{"question": "Solve (495 + 571)", "answer": "The result of (495 + 571) is 1066\n\n####1066", "a": 495, "b": 571, "operator": "+", "result": 1066}
{"question": "Solve (191 - 736)", "answer": "The result of (191 - 736) is -545\n\n####-545", "a": 191, "b": 736, "operator": "-", "result": -545}
{"question": "Solve (147 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (147 / 773) is 0.1902\n\n####0.1902", "a": 147, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1902}
{"question": "Solve (648 * 845)", "answer": "The result of (648 * 845) is 547560\n\n####547560", "a": 648, "b": 845, "operator": "*", "result": 547560}
{"question": "Solve (448 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (448 / 914) is 0.4902\n\n####0.4902", "a": 448, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4902}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 697)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 697) is 0.439\n\n####0.439", "a": 306, "b": 697, "operator": "/", "result": 0.439}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 595)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 595) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 393, "b": 595, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (989 / 654)", "answer": "The result of (989 / 654) is 1.5122\n\n####1.5122", "a": 989, "b": 654, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5122}
{"question": "Solve (476 + 471)", "answer": "The result of (476 + 471) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 476, "b": 471, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (356 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (356 - 276) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 356, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (578 - 778)", "answer": "The result of (578 - 778) is -200\n\n####-200", "a": 578, "b": 778, "operator": "-", "result": -200}
{"question": "Solve (573 / 174)", "answer": "The result of (573 / 174) is 3.2931\n\n####3.2931", "a": 573, "b": 174, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2931}
{"question": "Solve (223 / 51)", "answer": "The result of (223 / 51) is 4.3725\n\n####4.3725", "a": 223, "b": 51, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3725}
{"question": "Solve (675 * 984)", "answer": "The result of (675 * 984) is 664200\n\n####664200", "a": 675, "b": 984, "operator": "*", "result": 664200}
{"question": "Solve (583 - 249)", "answer": "The result of (583 - 249) is 334\n\n####334", "a": 583, "b": 249, "operator": "-", "result": 334}
{"question": "Solve (776 + 171)", "answer": "The result of (776 + 171) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 776, "b": 171, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (144 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (144 / 873) is 0.1649\n\n####0.1649", "a": 144, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1649}
{"question": "Solve (832 - 54)", "answer": "The result of (832 - 54) is 778\n\n####778", "a": 832, "b": 54, "operator": "-", "result": 778}
{"question": "Solve (945 - 632)", "answer": "The result of (945 - 632) is 313\n\n####313", "a": 945, "b": 632, "operator": "-", "result": 313}
{"question": "Solve (5 / 386)", "answer": "The result of (5 / 386) is 0.013\n\n####0.013", "a": 5, "b": 386, "operator": "/", "result": 0.013}
{"question": "Solve (112 - 550)", "answer": "The result of (112 - 550) is -438\n\n####-438", "a": 112, "b": 550, "operator": "-", "result": -438}
{"question": "Solve (61 * 612)", "answer": "The result of (61 * 612) is 37332\n\n####37332", "a": 61, "b": 612, "operator": "*", "result": 37332}
{"question": "Solve (773 + 533)", "answer": "The result of (773 + 533) is 1306\n\n####1306", "a": 773, "b": 533, "operator": "+", "result": 1306}
{"question": "Solve (792 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (792 - 634) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 792, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (911 / 763)", "answer": "The result of (911 / 763) is 1.194\n\n####1.194", "a": 911, "b": 763, "operator": "/", "result": 1.194}
{"question": "Solve (221 - 573)", "answer": "The result of (221 - 573) is -352\n\n####-352", "a": 221, "b": 573, "operator": "-", "result": -352}
{"question": "Solve (803 - 518)", "answer": "The result of (803 - 518) is 285\n\n####285", "a": 803, "b": 518, "operator": "-", "result": 285}
{"question": "Solve (555 - 225)", "answer": "The result of (555 - 225) is 330\n\n####330", "a": 555, "b": 225, "operator": "-", "result": 330}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 994)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 994) is 0.8531\n\n####0.8531", "a": 848, "b": 994, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8531}
{"question": "Solve (495 * 37)", "answer": "The result of (495 * 37) is 18315\n\n####18315", "a": 495, "b": 37, "operator": "*", "result": 18315}
{"question": "Solve (569 + 569)", "answer": "The result of (569 + 569) is 1138\n\n####1138", "a": 569, "b": 569, "operator": "+", "result": 1138}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 975)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 975) is 1.0062\n\n####1.0062", "a": 981, "b": 975, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0062}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 342)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 342) is 2.1111\n\n####2.1111", "a": 722, "b": 342, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1111}
{"question": "Solve (948 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (948 / 674) is 1.4065\n\n####1.4065", "a": 948, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4065}
{"question": "Solve (108 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (108 / 376) is 0.2872\n\n####0.2872", "a": 108, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2872}
{"question": "Solve (580 * 44)", "answer": "The result of (580 * 44) is 25520\n\n####25520", "a": 580, "b": 44, "operator": "*", "result": 25520}
{"question": "Solve (711 + 700)", "answer": "The result of (711 + 700) is 1411\n\n####1411", "a": 711, "b": 700, "operator": "+", "result": 1411}
{"question": "Solve (106 - 720)", "answer": "The result of (106 - 720) is -614\n\n####-614", "a": 106, "b": 720, "operator": "-", "result": -614}
{"question": "Solve (576 + 325)", "answer": "The result of (576 + 325) is 901\n\n####901", "a": 576, "b": 325, "operator": "+", "result": 901}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 924)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 924) is -114\n\n####-114", "a": 810, "b": 924, "operator": "-", "result": -114}
{"question": "Solve (403 + 61)", "answer": "The result of (403 + 61) is 464\n\n####464", "a": 403, "b": 61, "operator": "+", "result": 464}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 793)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 793) is 65\n\n####65", "a": 858, "b": 793, "operator": "-", "result": 65}
{"question": "Solve (137 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (137 + 124) is 261\n\n####261", "a": 137, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 261}
{"question": "Solve (164 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (164 - 520) is -356\n\n####-356", "a": 164, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": -356}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 151)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 151) is 5.6159\n\n####5.6159", "a": 848, "b": 151, "operator": "/", "result": 5.6159}
{"question": "Solve (657 * 26)", "answer": "The result of (657 * 26) is 17082\n\n####17082", "a": 657, "b": 26, "operator": "*", "result": 17082}
{"question": "Solve (76 / 33)", "answer": "The result of (76 / 33) is 2.303\n\n####2.303", "a": 76, "b": 33, "operator": "/", "result": 2.303}
{"question": "Solve (600 / 69)", "answer": "The result of (600 / 69) is 8.6957\n\n####8.6957", "a": 600, "b": 69, "operator": "/", "result": 8.6957}
{"question": "Solve (957 - 341)", "answer": "The result of (957 - 341) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 957, "b": 341, "operator": "-", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (284 * 16)", "answer": "The result of (284 * 16) is 4544\n\n####4544", "a": 284, "b": 16, "operator": "*", "result": 4544}
{"question": "Solve (412 * 561)", "answer": "The result of (412 * 561) is 231132\n\n####231132", "a": 412, "b": 561, "operator": "*", "result": 231132}
{"question": "Solve (532 * 825)", "answer": "The result of (532 * 825) is 438900\n\n####438900", "a": 532, "b": 825, "operator": "*", "result": 438900}
{"question": "Solve (444 / 789)", "answer": "The result of (444 / 789) is 0.5627\n\n####0.5627", "a": 444, "b": 789, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5627}
{"question": "Solve (258 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (258 * 524) is 135192\n\n####135192", "a": 258, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 135192}
{"question": "Solve (762 - 77)", "answer": "The result of (762 - 77) is 685\n\n####685", "a": 762, "b": 77, "operator": "-", "result": 685}
{"question": "Solve (209 - 540)", "answer": "The result of (209 - 540) is -331\n\n####-331", "a": 209, "b": 540, "operator": "-", "result": -331}
{"question": "Solve (683 / 318)", "answer": "The result of (683 / 318) is 2.1478\n\n####2.1478", "a": 683, "b": 318, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1478}
{"question": "Solve (157 * 952)", "answer": "The result of (157 * 952) is 149464\n\n####149464", "a": 157, "b": 952, "operator": "*", "result": 149464}
{"question": "Solve (779 / 363)", "answer": "The result of (779 / 363) is 2.146\n\n####2.146", "a": 779, "b": 363, "operator": "/", "result": 2.146}
{"question": "Solve (674 - 371)", "answer": "The result of (674 - 371) is 303\n\n####303", "a": 674, "b": 371, "operator": "-", "result": 303}
{"question": "Solve (603 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (603 - 514) is 89\n\n####89", "a": 603, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": 89}
{"question": "Solve (207 * 591)", "answer": "The result of (207 * 591) is 122337\n\n####122337", "a": 207, "b": 591, "operator": "*", "result": 122337}
{"question": "Solve (307 / 170)", "answer": "The result of (307 / 170) is 1.8059\n\n####1.8059", "a": 307, "b": 170, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8059}
{"question": "Solve (281 - 185)", "answer": "The result of (281 - 185) is 96\n\n####96", "a": 281, "b": 185, "operator": "-", "result": 96}
{"question": "Solve (393 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (393 * 332) is 130476\n\n####130476", "a": 393, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 130476}
{"question": "Solve (602 - 775)", "answer": "The result of (602 - 775) is -173\n\n####-173", "a": 602, "b": 775, "operator": "-", "result": -173}
{"question": "Solve (625 * 873)", "answer": "The result of (625 * 873) is 545625\n\n####545625", "a": 625, "b": 873, "operator": "*", "result": 545625}
{"question": "Solve (517 + 152)", "answer": "The result of (517 + 152) is 669\n\n####669", "a": 517, "b": 152, "operator": "+", "result": 669}
{"question": "Solve (982 - 444)", "answer": "The result of (982 - 444) is 538\n\n####538", "a": 982, "b": 444, "operator": "-", "result": 538}
{"question": "Solve (87 - 418)", "answer": "The result of (87 - 418) is -331\n\n####-331", "a": 87, "b": 418, "operator": "-", "result": -331}
{"question": "Solve (279 * 483)", "answer": "The result of (279 * 483) is 134757\n\n####134757", "a": 279, "b": 483, "operator": "*", "result": 134757}
{"question": "Solve (901 + 866)", "answer": "The result of (901 + 866) is 1767\n\n####1767", "a": 901, "b": 866, "operator": "+", "result": 1767}
{"question": "Solve (662 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (662 / 445) is 1.4876\n\n####1.4876", "a": 662, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4876}
{"question": "Solve (243 / 965)", "answer": "The result of (243 / 965) is 0.2518\n\n####0.2518", "a": 243, "b": 965, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2518}
{"question": "Solve (94 / 893)", "answer": "The result of (94 / 893) is 0.1053\n\n####0.1053", "a": 94, "b": 893, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1053}
{"question": "Solve (549 + 632)", "answer": "The result of (549 + 632) is 1181\n\n####1181", "a": 549, "b": 632, "operator": "+", "result": 1181}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 602)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 602) is -525\n\n####-525", "a": 77, "b": 602, "operator": "-", "result": -525}
{"question": "Solve (72 + 744)", "answer": "The result of (72 + 744) is 816\n\n####816", "a": 72, "b": 744, "operator": "+", "result": 816}
{"question": "Solve (410 - 223)", "answer": "The result of (410 - 223) is 187\n\n####187", "a": 410, "b": 223, "operator": "-", "result": 187}
{"question": "Solve (869 - 163)", "answer": "The result of (869 - 163) is 706\n\n####706", "a": 869, "b": 163, "operator": "-", "result": 706}
{"question": "Solve (915 + 765)", "answer": "The result of (915 + 765) is 1680\n\n####1680", "a": 915, "b": 765, "operator": "+", "result": 1680}
{"question": "Solve (429 / 335)", "answer": "The result of (429 / 335) is 1.2806\n\n####1.2806", "a": 429, "b": 335, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2806}
{"question": "Solve (958 / 507)", "answer": "The result of (958 / 507) is 1.8895\n\n####1.8895", "a": 958, "b": 507, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8895}
{"question": "Solve (90 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (90 * 911) is 81990\n\n####81990", "a": 90, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 81990}
{"question": "Solve (494 * 904)", "answer": "The result of (494 * 904) is 446576\n\n####446576", "a": 494, "b": 904, "operator": "*", "result": 446576}
{"question": "Solve (800 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (800 - 802) is -2\n\n####-2", "a": 800, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -2}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 158)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 158) is 428\n\n####428", "a": 586, "b": 158, "operator": "-", "result": 428}
{"question": "Solve (388 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (388 / 560) is 0.6929\n\n####0.6929", "a": 388, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6929}
{"question": "Solve (680 + 477)", "answer": "The result of (680 + 477) is 1157\n\n####1157", "a": 680, "b": 477, "operator": "+", "result": 1157}
{"question": "Solve (696 / 321)", "answer": "The result of (696 / 321) is 2.1682\n\n####2.1682", "a": 696, "b": 321, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1682}
{"question": "Solve (340 * 544)", "answer": "The result of (340 * 544) is 184960\n\n####184960", "a": 340, "b": 544, "operator": "*", "result": 184960}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 279)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 279) is 436\n\n####436", "a": 715, "b": 279, "operator": "-", "result": 436}
{"question": "Solve (630 + 969)", "answer": "The result of (630 + 969) is 1599\n\n####1599", "a": 630, "b": 969, "operator": "+", "result": 1599}
{"question": "Solve (202 + 130)", "answer": "The result of (202 + 130) is 332\n\n####332", "a": 202, "b": 130, "operator": "+", "result": 332}
{"question": "Solve (418 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (418 - 6) is 412\n\n####412", "a": 418, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 412}
{"question": "Solve (471 * 361)", "answer": "The result of (471 * 361) is 170031\n\n####170031", "a": 471, "b": 361, "operator": "*", "result": 170031}
{"question": "Solve (38 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (38 - 117) is -79\n\n####-79", "a": 38, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": -79}
{"question": "Solve (637 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (637 - 452) is 185\n\n####185", "a": 637, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": 185}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 944)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 944) is 1771\n\n####1771", "a": 827, "b": 944, "operator": "+", "result": 1771}
{"question": "Solve (877 * 721)", "answer": "The result of (877 * 721) is 632317\n\n####632317", "a": 877, "b": 721, "operator": "*", "result": 632317}
{"question": "Solve (532 / 635)", "answer": "The result of (532 / 635) is 0.8378\n\n####0.8378", "a": 532, "b": 635, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8378}
{"question": "Solve (729 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (729 * 407) is 296703\n\n####296703", "a": 729, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 296703}
{"question": "Solve (812 - 754)", "answer": "The result of (812 - 754) is 58\n\n####58", "a": 812, "b": 754, "operator": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve (340 - 622)", "answer": "The result of (340 - 622) is -282\n\n####-282", "a": 340, "b": 622, "operator": "-", "result": -282}
{"question": "Solve (301 * 625)", "answer": "The result of (301 * 625) is 188125\n\n####188125", "a": 301, "b": 625, "operator": "*", "result": 188125}
{"question": "Solve (278 / 992)", "answer": "The result of (278 / 992) is 0.2802\n\n####0.2802", "a": 278, "b": 992, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2802}
{"question": "Solve (791 - 376)", "answer": "The result of (791 - 376) is 415\n\n####415", "a": 791, "b": 376, "operator": "-", "result": 415}
{"question": "Solve (538 * 35)", "answer": "The result of (538 * 35) is 18830\n\n####18830", "a": 538, "b": 35, "operator": "*", "result": 18830}
{"question": "Solve (128 * 821)", "answer": "The result of (128 * 821) is 105088\n\n####105088", "a": 128, "b": 821, "operator": "*", "result": 105088}
{"question": "Solve (385 * 586)", "answer": "The result of (385 * 586) is 225610\n\n####225610", "a": 385, "b": 586, "operator": "*", "result": 225610}
{"question": "Solve (233 * 60)", "answer": "The result of (233 * 60) is 13980\n\n####13980", "a": 233, "b": 60, "operator": "*", "result": 13980}
{"question": "Solve (161 - 781)", "answer": "The result of (161 - 781) is -620\n\n####-620", "a": 161, "b": 781, "operator": "-", "result": -620}
{"question": "Solve (121 * 499)", "answer": "The result of (121 * 499) is 60379\n\n####60379", "a": 121, "b": 499, "operator": "*", "result": 60379}
{"question": "Solve (880 / 758)", "answer": "The result of (880 / 758) is 1.1609\n\n####1.1609", "a": 880, "b": 758, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1609}
{"question": "Solve (19 + 623)", "answer": "The result of (19 + 623) is 642\n\n####642", "a": 19, "b": 623, "operator": "+", "result": 642}
{"question": "Solve (633 + 454)", "answer": "The result of (633 + 454) is 1087\n\n####1087", "a": 633, "b": 454, "operator": "+", "result": 1087}
{"question": "Solve (455 * 301)", "answer": "The result of (455 * 301) is 136955\n\n####136955", "a": 455, "b": 301, "operator": "*", "result": 136955}
{"question": "Solve (46 / 226)", "answer": "The result of (46 / 226) is 0.2035\n\n####0.2035", "a": 46, "b": 226, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2035}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 456)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 456) is 341\n\n####341", "a": 797, "b": 456, "operator": "-", "result": 341}
{"question": "Solve (61 + 497)", "answer": "The result of (61 + 497) is 558\n\n####558", "a": 61, "b": 497, "operator": "+", "result": 558}
{"question": "Solve (782 * 211)", "answer": "The result of (782 * 211) is 165002\n\n####165002", "a": 782, "b": 211, "operator": "*", "result": 165002}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 159)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 159) is 5.7862\n\n####5.7862", "a": 920, "b": 159, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7862}
{"question": "Solve (384 / 482)", "answer": "The result of (384 / 482) is 0.7967\n\n####0.7967", "a": 384, "b": 482, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7967}
{"question": "Solve (409 / 880)", "answer": "The result of (409 / 880) is 0.4648\n\n####0.4648", "a": 409, "b": 880, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4648}
{"question": "Solve (87 + 963)", "answer": "The result of (87 + 963) is 1050\n\n####1050", "a": 87, "b": 963, "operator": "+", "result": 1050}
{"question": "Solve (873 / 689)", "answer": "The result of (873 / 689) is 1.2671\n\n####1.2671", "a": 873, "b": 689, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2671}
{"question": "Solve (386 - 13)", "answer": "The result of (386 - 13) is 373\n\n####373", "a": 386, "b": 13, "operator": "-", "result": 373}
{"question": "Solve (915 / 708)", "answer": "The result of (915 / 708) is 1.2924\n\n####1.2924", "a": 915, "b": 708, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2924}
{"question": "Solve (668 / 661)", "answer": "The result of (668 / 661) is 1.0106\n\n####1.0106", "a": 668, "b": 661, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0106}
{"question": "Solve (801 + 719)", "answer": "The result of (801 + 719) is 1520\n\n####1520", "a": 801, "b": 719, "operator": "+", "result": 1520}
{"question": "Solve (30 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (30 - 492) is -462\n\n####-462", "a": 30, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": -462}
{"question": "Solve (920 * 257)", "answer": "The result of (920 * 257) is 236440\n\n####236440", "a": 920, "b": 257, "operator": "*", "result": 236440}
{"question": "Solve (319 + 472)", "answer": "The result of (319 + 472) is 791\n\n####791", "a": 319, "b": 472, "operator": "+", "result": 791}
{"question": "Solve (343 - 74)", "answer": "The result of (343 - 74) is 269\n\n####269", "a": 343, "b": 74, "operator": "-", "result": 269}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 168) is 508\n\n####508", "a": 676, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": 508}
{"question": "Solve (475 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (475 / 289) is 1.6436\n\n####1.6436", "a": 475, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6436}
{"question": "Solve (119 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (119 - 354) is -235\n\n####-235", "a": 119, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": -235}
{"question": "Solve (110 - 728)", "answer": "The result of (110 - 728) is -618\n\n####-618", "a": 110, "b": 728, "operator": "-", "result": -618}
{"question": "Solve (506 - 559)", "answer": "The result of (506 - 559) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 506, "b": 559, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (411 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (411 - 295) is 116\n\n####116", "a": 411, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": 116}
{"question": "Solve (527 + 612)", "answer": "The result of (527 + 612) is 1139\n\n####1139", "a": 527, "b": 612, "operator": "+", "result": 1139}
{"question": "Solve (322 * 885)", "answer": "The result of (322 * 885) is 284970\n\n####284970", "a": 322, "b": 885, "operator": "*", "result": 284970}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 210) is 151\n\n####151", "a": 361, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": 151}
{"question": "Solve (578 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (578 / 276) is 2.0942\n\n####2.0942", "a": 578, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0942}
{"question": "Solve (765 * 286)", "answer": "The result of (765 * 286) is 218790\n\n####218790", "a": 765, "b": 286, "operator": "*", "result": 218790}
{"question": "Solve (506 * 582)", "answer": "The result of (506 * 582) is 294492\n\n####294492", "a": 506, "b": 582, "operator": "*", "result": 294492}
{"question": "Solve (783 * 68)", "answer": "The result of (783 * 68) is 53244\n\n####53244", "a": 783, "b": 68, "operator": "*", "result": 53244}
{"question": "Solve (731 - 967)", "answer": "The result of (731 - 967) is -236\n\n####-236", "a": 731, "b": 967, "operator": "-", "result": -236}
{"question": "Solve (251 - 503)", "answer": "The result of (251 - 503) is -252\n\n####-252", "a": 251, "b": 503, "operator": "-", "result": -252}
{"question": "Solve (291 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (291 / 773) is 0.3765\n\n####0.3765", "a": 291, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3765}
{"question": "Solve (870 * 281)", "answer": "The result of (870 * 281) is 244470\n\n####244470", "a": 870, "b": 281, "operator": "*", "result": 244470}
{"question": "Solve (137 / 938)", "answer": "The result of (137 / 938) is 0.1461\n\n####0.1461", "a": 137, "b": 938, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1461}
{"question": "Solve (130 * 313)", "answer": "The result of (130 * 313) is 40690\n\n####40690", "a": 130, "b": 313, "operator": "*", "result": 40690}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 741)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 741) is 583167\n\n####583167", "a": 787, "b": 741, "operator": "*", "result": 583167}
{"question": "Solve (678 + 557)", "answer": "The result of (678 + 557) is 1235\n\n####1235", "a": 678, "b": 557, "operator": "+", "result": 1235}
{"question": "Solve (559 - 280)", "answer": "The result of (559 - 280) is 279\n\n####279", "a": 559, "b": 280, "operator": "-", "result": 279}
{"question": "Solve (638 * 34)", "answer": "The result of (638 * 34) is 21692\n\n####21692", "a": 638, "b": 34, "operator": "*", "result": 21692}
{"question": "Solve (26 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (26 * 862) is 22412\n\n####22412", "a": 26, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 22412}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 795)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 795) is -725\n\n####-725", "a": 70, "b": 795, "operator": "-", "result": -725}
{"question": "Solve (785 - 750)", "answer": "The result of (785 - 750) is 35\n\n####35", "a": 785, "b": 750, "operator": "-", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve (39 + 740)", "answer": "The result of (39 + 740) is 779\n\n####779", "a": 39, "b": 740, "operator": "+", "result": 779}
{"question": "Solve (79 - 830)", "answer": "The result of (79 - 830) is -751\n\n####-751", "a": 79, "b": 830, "operator": "-", "result": -751}
{"question": "Solve (893 / 633)", "answer": "The result of (893 / 633) is 1.4107\n\n####1.4107", "a": 893, "b": 633, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4107}
{"question": "Solve (394 - 842)", "answer": "The result of (394 - 842) is -448\n\n####-448", "a": 394, "b": 842, "operator": "-", "result": -448}
{"question": "Solve (836 * 546)", "answer": "The result of (836 * 546) is 456456\n\n####456456", "a": 836, "b": 546, "operator": "*", "result": 456456}
{"question": "Solve (880 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (880 / 773) is 1.1384\n\n####1.1384", "a": 880, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1384}
{"question": "Solve (439 / 736)", "answer": "The result of (439 / 736) is 0.5965\n\n####0.5965", "a": 439, "b": 736, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5965}
{"question": "Solve (638 * 949)", "answer": "The result of (638 * 949) is 605462\n\n####605462", "a": 638, "b": 949, "operator": "*", "result": 605462}
{"question": "Solve (271 / 254)", "answer": "The result of (271 / 254) is 1.0669\n\n####1.0669", "a": 271, "b": 254, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0669}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 214)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 214) is 352\n\n####352", "a": 566, "b": 214, "operator": "-", "result": 352}
{"question": "Solve (588 + 643)", "answer": "The result of (588 + 643) is 1231\n\n####1231", "a": 588, "b": 643, "operator": "+", "result": 1231}
{"question": "Solve (827 - 28)", "answer": "The result of (827 - 28) is 799\n\n####799", "a": 827, "b": 28, "operator": "-", "result": 799}
{"question": "Solve (636 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (636 * 870) is 553320\n\n####553320", "a": 636, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 553320}
{"question": "Solve (798 * 239)", "answer": "The result of (798 * 239) is 190722\n\n####190722", "a": 798, "b": 239, "operator": "*", "result": 190722}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 183)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 183) is 3.8525\n\n####3.8525", "a": 705, "b": 183, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8525}
{"question": "Solve (918 + 587)", "answer": "The result of (918 + 587) is 1505\n\n####1505", "a": 918, "b": 587, "operator": "+", "result": 1505}
{"question": "Solve (795 / 831)", "answer": "The result of (795 / 831) is 0.9567\n\n####0.9567", "a": 795, "b": 831, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9567}
{"question": "Solve (436 * 300)", "answer": "The result of (436 * 300) is 130800\n\n####130800", "a": 436, "b": 300, "operator": "*", "result": 130800}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 642)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 642) is 207\n\n####207", "a": 849, "b": 642, "operator": "-", "result": 207}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 604) is -152\n\n####-152", "a": 452, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -152}
{"question": "Solve (473 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (473 - 245) is 228\n\n####228", "a": 473, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 228}
{"question": "Solve (945 * 209)", "answer": "The result of (945 * 209) is 197505\n\n####197505", "a": 945, "b": 209, "operator": "*", "result": 197505}
{"question": "Solve (38 + 987)", "answer": "The result of (38 + 987) is 1025\n\n####1025", "a": 38, "b": 987, "operator": "+", "result": 1025}
{"question": "Solve (417 / 224)", "answer": "The result of (417 / 224) is 1.8616\n\n####1.8616", "a": 417, "b": 224, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8616}
{"question": "Solve (502 / 597)", "answer": "The result of (502 / 597) is 0.8409\n\n####0.8409", "a": 502, "b": 597, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8409}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 25)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 25) is 449\n\n####449", "a": 474, "b": 25, "operator": "-", "result": 449}
{"question": "Solve (559 / 733)", "answer": "The result of (559 / 733) is 0.7626\n\n####0.7626", "a": 559, "b": 733, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7626}
{"question": "Solve (327 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (327 / 669) is 0.4888\n\n####0.4888", "a": 327, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4888}
{"question": "Solve (391 - 867)", "answer": "The result of (391 - 867) is -476\n\n####-476", "a": 391, "b": 867, "operator": "-", "result": -476}
{"question": "Solve (296 + 612)", "answer": "The result of (296 + 612) is 908\n\n####908", "a": 296, "b": 612, "operator": "+", "result": 908}
{"question": "Solve (549 - 658)", "answer": "The result of (549 - 658) is -109\n\n####-109", "a": 549, "b": 658, "operator": "-", "result": -109}
{"question": "Solve (953 * 509)", "answer": "The result of (953 * 509) is 485077\n\n####485077", "a": 953, "b": 509, "operator": "*", "result": 485077}
{"question": "Solve (861 - 623)", "answer": "The result of (861 - 623) is 238\n\n####238", "a": 861, "b": 623, "operator": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve (198 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (198 - 756) is -558\n\n####-558", "a": 198, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -558}
{"question": "Solve (239 / 798)", "answer": "The result of (239 / 798) is 0.2995\n\n####0.2995", "a": 239, "b": 798, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2995}
{"question": "Solve (806 + 126)", "answer": "The result of (806 + 126) is 932\n\n####932", "a": 806, "b": 126, "operator": "+", "result": 932}
{"question": "Solve (610 - 666)", "answer": "The result of (610 - 666) is -56\n\n####-56", "a": 610, "b": 666, "operator": "-", "result": -56}
{"question": "Solve (191 - 396)", "answer": "The result of (191 - 396) is -205\n\n####-205", "a": 191, "b": 396, "operator": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve (88 * 697)", "answer": "The result of (88 * 697) is 61336\n\n####61336", "a": 88, "b": 697, "operator": "*", "result": 61336}
{"question": "Solve (505 + 128)", "answer": "The result of (505 + 128) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 505, "b": 128, "operator": "+", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (894 + 108)", "answer": "The result of (894 + 108) is 1002\n\n####1002", "a": 894, "b": 108, "operator": "+", "result": 1002}
{"question": "Solve (32 + 739)", "answer": "The result of (32 + 739) is 771\n\n####771", "a": 32, "b": 739, "operator": "+", "result": 771}
{"question": "Solve (664 - 644)", "answer": "The result of (664 - 644) is 20\n\n####20", "a": 664, "b": 644, "operator": "-", "result": 20}
{"question": "Solve (261 - 220)", "answer": "The result of (261 - 220) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 261, "b": 220, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (96 / 958)", "answer": "The result of (96 / 958) is 0.1002\n\n####0.1002", "a": 96, "b": 958, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1002}
{"question": "Solve (972 * 208)", "answer": "The result of (972 * 208) is 202176\n\n####202176", "a": 972, "b": 208, "operator": "*", "result": 202176}
{"question": "Solve (88 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (88 - 918) is -830\n\n####-830", "a": 88, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -830}
{"question": "Solve (941 * 908)", "answer": "The result of (941 * 908) is 854428\n\n####854428", "a": 941, "b": 908, "operator": "*", "result": 854428}
{"question": "Solve (704 - 133)", "answer": "The result of (704 - 133) is 571\n\n####571", "a": 704, "b": 133, "operator": "-", "result": 571}
{"question": "Solve (504 * 81)", "answer": "The result of (504 * 81) is 40824\n\n####40824", "a": 504, "b": 81, "operator": "*", "result": 40824}
{"question": "Solve (153 - 96)", "answer": "The result of (153 - 96) is 57\n\n####57", "a": 153, "b": 96, "operator": "-", "result": 57}
{"question": "Solve (723 - 816)", "answer": "The result of (723 - 816) is -93\n\n####-93", "a": 723, "b": 816, "operator": "-", "result": -93}
{"question": "Solve (727 * 292)", "answer": "The result of (727 * 292) is 212284\n\n####212284", "a": 727, "b": 292, "operator": "*", "result": 212284}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 731)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 731) is -449\n\n####-449", "a": 282, "b": 731, "operator": "-", "result": -449}
{"question": "Solve (629 + 220)", "answer": "The result of (629 + 220) is 849\n\n####849", "a": 629, "b": 220, "operator": "+", "result": 849}
{"question": "Solve (312 - 350)", "answer": "The result of (312 - 350) is -38\n\n####-38", "a": 312, "b": 350, "operator": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 845)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 845) is 226460\n\n####226460", "a": 268, "b": 845, "operator": "*", "result": 226460}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 917)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 917) is 0.1559\n\n####0.1559", "a": 143, "b": 917, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1559}
{"question": "Solve (221 - 125)", "answer": "The result of (221 - 125) is 96\n\n####96", "a": 221, "b": 125, "operator": "-", "result": 96}
{"question": "Solve (412 + 364)", "answer": "The result of (412 + 364) is 776\n\n####776", "a": 412, "b": 364, "operator": "+", "result": 776}
{"question": "Solve (392 + 727)", "answer": "The result of (392 + 727) is 1119\n\n####1119", "a": 392, "b": 727, "operator": "+", "result": 1119}
{"question": "Solve (622 + 299)", "answer": "The result of (622 + 299) is 921\n\n####921", "a": 622, "b": 299, "operator": "+", "result": 921}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 285)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 285) is 776\n\n####776", "a": 491, "b": 285, "operator": "+", "result": 776}
{"question": "Solve (62 - 445)", "answer": "The result of (62 - 445) is -383\n\n####-383", "a": 62, "b": 445, "operator": "-", "result": -383}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 664)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 664) is 399728\n\n####399728", "a": 602, "b": 664, "operator": "*", "result": 399728}
{"question": "Solve (498 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (498 - 498) is 0\n\n####0", "a": 498, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": 0}
{"question": "Solve (574 + 288)", "answer": "The result of (574 + 288) is 862\n\n####862", "a": 574, "b": 288, "operator": "+", "result": 862}
{"question": "Solve (97 * 473)", "answer": "The result of (97 * 473) is 45881\n\n####45881", "a": 97, "b": 473, "operator": "*", "result": 45881}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 314)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 314) is 5338\n\n####5338", "a": 17, "b": 314, "operator": "*", "result": 5338}
{"question": "Solve (933 - 560)", "answer": "The result of (933 - 560) is 373\n\n####373", "a": 933, "b": 560, "operator": "-", "result": 373}
{"question": "Solve (71 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (71 * 251) is 17821\n\n####17821", "a": 71, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 17821}
{"question": "Solve (932 * 33)", "answer": "The result of (932 * 33) is 30756\n\n####30756", "a": 932, "b": 33, "operator": "*", "result": 30756}
{"question": "Solve (740 * 83)", "answer": "The result of (740 * 83) is 61420\n\n####61420", "a": 740, "b": 83, "operator": "*", "result": 61420}
{"question": "Solve (759 + 179)", "answer": "The result of (759 + 179) is 938\n\n####938", "a": 759, "b": 179, "operator": "+", "result": 938}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 271)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 271) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 3, "b": 271, "operator": "+", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 204)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 204) is 72420\n\n####72420", "a": 355, "b": 204, "operator": "*", "result": 72420}
{"question": "Solve (447 + 117)", "answer": "The result of (447 + 117) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 447, "b": 117, "operator": "+", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (370 * 535)", "answer": "The result of (370 * 535) is 197950\n\n####197950", "a": 370, "b": 535, "operator": "*", "result": 197950}
{"question": "Solve (149 + 879)", "answer": "The result of (149 + 879) is 1028\n\n####1028", "a": 149, "b": 879, "operator": "+", "result": 1028}
{"question": "Solve (344 / 309)", "answer": "The result of (344 / 309) is 1.1133\n\n####1.1133", "a": 344, "b": 309, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1133}
{"question": "Solve (522 * 473)", "answer": "The result of (522 * 473) is 246906\n\n####246906", "a": 522, "b": 473, "operator": "*", "result": 246906}
{"question": "Solve (224 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (224 - 846) is -622\n\n####-622", "a": 224, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -622}
{"question": "Solve (766 / 620)", "answer": "The result of (766 / 620) is 1.2355\n\n####1.2355", "a": 766, "b": 620, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2355}
{"question": "Solve (888 + 201)", "answer": "The result of (888 + 201) is 1089\n\n####1089", "a": 888, "b": 201, "operator": "+", "result": 1089}
{"question": "Solve (686 + 824)", "answer": "The result of (686 + 824) is 1510\n\n####1510", "a": 686, "b": 824, "operator": "+", "result": 1510}
{"question": "Solve (417 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (417 / 388) is 1.0747\n\n####1.0747", "a": 417, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0747}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 492) is 162\n\n####162", "a": 654, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": 162}
{"question": "Solve (922 * 542)", "answer": "The result of (922 * 542) is 499724\n\n####499724", "a": 922, "b": 542, "operator": "*", "result": 499724}
{"question": "Solve (61 / 378)", "answer": "The result of (61 / 378) is 0.1614\n\n####0.1614", "a": 61, "b": 378, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1614}
{"question": "Solve (780 * 339)", "answer": "The result of (780 * 339) is 264420\n\n####264420", "a": 780, "b": 339, "operator": "*", "result": 264420}
{"question": "Solve (122 - 897)", "answer": "The result of (122 - 897) is -775\n\n####-775", "a": 122, "b": 897, "operator": "-", "result": -775}
{"question": "Solve (74 / 99)", "answer": "The result of (74 / 99) is 0.7475\n\n####0.7475", "a": 74, "b": 99, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7475}
{"question": "Solve (362 - 322)", "answer": "The result of (362 - 322) is 40\n\n####40", "a": 362, "b": 322, "operator": "-", "result": 40}
{"question": "Solve (1 * 767)", "answer": "The result of (1 * 767) is 767\n\n####767", "a": 1, "b": 767, "operator": "*", "result": 767}
{"question": "Solve (189 + 79)", "answer": "The result of (189 + 79) is 268\n\n####268", "a": 189, "b": 79, "operator": "+", "result": 268}
{"question": "Solve (227 + 614)", "answer": "The result of (227 + 614) is 841\n\n####841", "a": 227, "b": 614, "operator": "+", "result": 841}
{"question": "Solve (715 * 657)", "answer": "The result of (715 * 657) is 469755\n\n####469755", "a": 715, "b": 657, "operator": "*", "result": 469755}
{"question": "Solve (485 / 832)", "answer": "The result of (485 / 832) is 0.5829\n\n####0.5829", "a": 485, "b": 832, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5829}
{"question": "Solve (330 + 506)", "answer": "The result of (330 + 506) is 836\n\n####836", "a": 330, "b": 506, "operator": "+", "result": 836}
{"question": "Solve (143 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (143 - 431) is -288\n\n####-288", "a": 143, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": -288}
{"question": "Solve (183 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (183 - 937) is -754\n\n####-754", "a": 183, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -754}
{"question": "Solve (686 / 530)", "answer": "The result of (686 / 530) is 1.2943\n\n####1.2943", "a": 686, "b": 530, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2943}
{"question": "Solve (551 + 917)", "answer": "The result of (551 + 917) is 1468\n\n####1468", "a": 551, "b": 917, "operator": "+", "result": 1468}
{"question": "Solve (853 + 439)", "answer": "The result of (853 + 439) is 1292\n\n####1292", "a": 853, "b": 439, "operator": "+", "result": 1292}
{"question": "Solve (651 - 129)", "answer": "The result of (651 - 129) is 522\n\n####522", "a": 651, "b": 129, "operator": "-", "result": 522}
{"question": "Solve (842 + 274)", "answer": "The result of (842 + 274) is 1116\n\n####1116", "a": 842, "b": 274, "operator": "+", "result": 1116}
{"question": "Solve (296 + 824)", "answer": "The result of (296 + 824) is 1120\n\n####1120", "a": 296, "b": 824, "operator": "+", "result": 1120}
{"question": "Solve (771 / 91)", "answer": "The result of (771 / 91) is 8.4725\n\n####8.4725", "a": 771, "b": 91, "operator": "/", "result": 8.4725}
{"question": "Solve (828 * 681)", "answer": "The result of (828 * 681) is 563868\n\n####563868", "a": 828, "b": 681, "operator": "*", "result": 563868}
{"question": "Solve (498 * 21)", "answer": "The result of (498 * 21) is 10458\n\n####10458", "a": 498, "b": 21, "operator": "*", "result": 10458}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 324)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 324) is 314604\n\n####314604", "a": 971, "b": 324, "operator": "*", "result": 314604}
{"question": "Solve (645 - 834)", "answer": "The result of (645 - 834) is -189\n\n####-189", "a": 645, "b": 834, "operator": "-", "result": -189}
{"question": "Solve (44 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (44 * 932) is 41008\n\n####41008", "a": 44, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 41008}
{"question": "Solve (682 + 200)", "answer": "The result of (682 + 200) is 882\n\n####882", "a": 682, "b": 200, "operator": "+", "result": 882}
{"question": "Solve (650 / 216)", "answer": "The result of (650 / 216) is 3.0093\n\n####3.0093", "a": 650, "b": 216, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0093}
{"question": "Solve (176 / 339)", "answer": "The result of (176 / 339) is 0.5192\n\n####0.5192", "a": 176, "b": 339, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5192}
{"question": "Solve (51 - 486)", "answer": "The result of (51 - 486) is -435\n\n####-435", "a": 51, "b": 486, "operator": "-", "result": -435}
{"question": "Solve (20 / 796)", "answer": "The result of (20 / 796) is 0.0251\n\n####0.0251", "a": 20, "b": 796, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0251}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 284)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 284) is -251\n\n####-251", "a": 33, "b": 284, "operator": "-", "result": -251}
{"question": "Solve (779 / 866)", "answer": "The result of (779 / 866) is 0.8995\n\n####0.8995", "a": 779, "b": 866, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8995}
{"question": "Solve (491 - 488)", "answer": "The result of (491 - 488) is 3\n\n####3", "a": 491, "b": 488, "operator": "-", "result": 3}
{"question": "Solve (536 + 171)", "answer": "The result of (536 + 171) is 707\n\n####707", "a": 536, "b": 171, "operator": "+", "result": 707}
{"question": "Solve (482 / 995)", "answer": "The result of (482 / 995) is 0.4844\n\n####0.4844", "a": 482, "b": 995, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4844}
{"question": "Solve (853 / 800)", "answer": "The result of (853 / 800) is 1.0662\n\n####1.0662", "a": 853, "b": 800, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0662}
{"question": "Solve (739 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (739 - 634) is 105\n\n####105", "a": 739, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": 105}
{"question": "Solve (627 * 779)", "answer": "The result of (627 * 779) is 488433\n\n####488433", "a": 627, "b": 779, "operator": "*", "result": 488433}
{"question": "Solve (597 - 528)", "answer": "The result of (597 - 528) is 69\n\n####69", "a": 597, "b": 528, "operator": "-", "result": 69}
{"question": "Solve (84 - 253)", "answer": "The result of (84 - 253) is -169\n\n####-169", "a": 84, "b": 253, "operator": "-", "result": -169}
{"question": "Solve (106 / 92)", "answer": "The result of (106 / 92) is 1.1522\n\n####1.1522", "a": 106, "b": 92, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1522}
{"question": "Solve (305 / 5)", "answer": "The result of (305 / 5) is 61.0\n\n####61.0", "a": 305, "b": 5, "operator": "/", "result": 61.0}
{"question": "Solve (731 - 281)", "answer": "The result of (731 - 281) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 731, "b": 281, "operator": "-", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (138 * 610)", "answer": "The result of (138 * 610) is 84180\n\n####84180", "a": 138, "b": 610, "operator": "*", "result": 84180}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 475) is 0.0758\n\n####0.0758", "a": 36, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0758}
{"question": "Solve (322 / 599)", "answer": "The result of (322 / 599) is 0.5376\n\n####0.5376", "a": 322, "b": 599, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5376}
{"question": "Solve (522 * 446)", "answer": "The result of (522 * 446) is 232812\n\n####232812", "a": 522, "b": 446, "operator": "*", "result": 232812}
{"question": "Solve (898 * 619)", "answer": "The result of (898 * 619) is 555862\n\n####555862", "a": 898, "b": 619, "operator": "*", "result": 555862}
{"question": "Solve (269 - 692)", "answer": "The result of (269 - 692) is -423\n\n####-423", "a": 269, "b": 692, "operator": "-", "result": -423}
{"question": "Solve (548 * 382)", "answer": "The result of (548 * 382) is 209336\n\n####209336", "a": 548, "b": 382, "operator": "*", "result": 209336}
{"question": "Solve (334 + 370)", "answer": "The result of (334 + 370) is 704\n\n####704", "a": 334, "b": 370, "operator": "+", "result": 704}
{"question": "Solve (366 + 708)", "answer": "The result of (366 + 708) is 1074\n\n####1074", "a": 366, "b": 708, "operator": "+", "result": 1074}
{"question": "Solve (74 * 144)", "answer": "The result of (74 * 144) is 10656\n\n####10656", "a": 74, "b": 144, "operator": "*", "result": 10656}
{"question": "Solve (546 - 34)", "answer": "The result of (546 - 34) is 512\n\n####512", "a": 546, "b": 34, "operator": "-", "result": 512}
{"question": "Solve (609 / 877)", "answer": "The result of (609 / 877) is 0.6944\n\n####0.6944", "a": 609, "b": 877, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6944}
{"question": "Solve (568 + 433)", "answer": "The result of (568 + 433) is 1001\n\n####1001", "a": 568, "b": 433, "operator": "+", "result": 1001}
{"question": "Solve (388 + 900)", "answer": "The result of (388 + 900) is 1288\n\n####1288", "a": 388, "b": 900, "operator": "+", "result": 1288}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 258)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 258) is 206400\n\n####206400", "a": 800, "b": 258, "operator": "*", "result": 206400}
{"question": "Solve (591 + 713)", "answer": "The result of (591 + 713) is 1304\n\n####1304", "a": 591, "b": 713, "operator": "+", "result": 1304}
{"question": "Solve (872 * 403)", "answer": "The result of (872 * 403) is 351416\n\n####351416", "a": 872, "b": 403, "operator": "*", "result": 351416}
{"question": "Solve (713 + 582)", "answer": "The result of (713 + 582) is 1295\n\n####1295", "a": 713, "b": 582, "operator": "+", "result": 1295}
{"question": "Solve (53 * 806)", "answer": "The result of (53 * 806) is 42718\n\n####42718", "a": 53, "b": 806, "operator": "*", "result": 42718}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 729)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 729) is 0.2826\n\n####0.2826", "a": 206, "b": 729, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2826}
{"question": "Solve (72 / 54)", "answer": "The result of (72 / 54) is 1.3333\n\n####1.3333", "a": 72, "b": 54, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3333}
{"question": "Solve (571 / 120)", "answer": "The result of (571 / 120) is 4.7583\n\n####4.7583", "a": 571, "b": 120, "operator": "/", "result": 4.7583}
{"question": "Solve (847 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (847 + 31) is 878\n\n####878", "a": 847, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 878}
{"question": "Solve (46 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (46 - 261) is -215\n\n####-215", "a": 46, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": -215}
{"question": "Solve (158 * 15)", "answer": "The result of (158 * 15) is 2370\n\n####2370", "a": 158, "b": 15, "operator": "*", "result": 2370}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 348)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 348) is 0.4109\n\n####0.4109", "a": 143, "b": 348, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4109}
{"question": "Solve (339 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (339 - 661) is -322\n\n####-322", "a": 339, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -322}
{"question": "Solve (571 / 535)", "answer": "The result of (571 / 535) is 1.0673\n\n####1.0673", "a": 571, "b": 535, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0673}
{"question": "Solve (759 + 889)", "answer": "The result of (759 + 889) is 1648\n\n####1648", "a": 759, "b": 889, "operator": "+", "result": 1648}
{"question": "Solve (215 + 382)", "answer": "The result of (215 + 382) is 597\n\n####597", "a": 215, "b": 382, "operator": "+", "result": 597}
{"question": "Solve (633 / 214)", "answer": "The result of (633 / 214) is 2.9579\n\n####2.9579", "a": 633, "b": 214, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9579}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 439) is 198428\n\n####198428", "a": 452, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 198428}
{"question": "Solve (433 / 376)", "answer": "The result of (433 / 376) is 1.1516\n\n####1.1516", "a": 433, "b": 376, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1516}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 228)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 228) is 119244\n\n####119244", "a": 523, "b": 228, "operator": "*", "result": 119244}
{"question": "Solve (92 * 979)", "answer": "The result of (92 * 979) is 90068\n\n####90068", "a": 92, "b": 979, "operator": "*", "result": 90068}
{"question": "Solve (583 - 558)", "answer": "The result of (583 - 558) is 25\n\n####25", "a": 583, "b": 558, "operator": "-", "result": 25}
{"question": "Solve (978 * 655)", "answer": "The result of (978 * 655) is 640590\n\n####640590", "a": 978, "b": 655, "operator": "*", "result": 640590}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 685)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 685) is 161660\n\n####161660", "a": 236, "b": 685, "operator": "*", "result": 161660}
{"question": "Solve (279 - 353)", "answer": "The result of (279 - 353) is -74\n\n####-74", "a": 279, "b": 353, "operator": "-", "result": -74}
{"question": "Solve (759 * 322)", "answer": "The result of (759 * 322) is 244398\n\n####244398", "a": 759, "b": 322, "operator": "*", "result": 244398}
{"question": "Solve (608 + 634)", "answer": "The result of (608 + 634) is 1242\n\n####1242", "a": 608, "b": 634, "operator": "+", "result": 1242}
{"question": "Solve (754 / 84)", "answer": "The result of (754 / 84) is 8.9762\n\n####8.9762", "a": 754, "b": 84, "operator": "/", "result": 8.9762}
{"question": "Solve (952 - 469)", "answer": "The result of (952 - 469) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 952, "b": 469, "operator": "-", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (486 + 482)", "answer": "The result of (486 + 482) is 968\n\n####968", "a": 486, "b": 482, "operator": "+", "result": 968}
{"question": "Solve (7 + 483)", "answer": "The result of (7 + 483) is 490\n\n####490", "a": 7, "b": 483, "operator": "+", "result": 490}
{"question": "Solve (896 * 119)", "answer": "The result of (896 * 119) is 106624\n\n####106624", "a": 896, "b": 119, "operator": "*", "result": 106624}
{"question": "Solve (150 / 747)", "answer": "The result of (150 / 747) is 0.2008\n\n####0.2008", "a": 150, "b": 747, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2008}
{"question": "Solve (872 / 819)", "answer": "The result of (872 / 819) is 1.0647\n\n####1.0647", "a": 872, "b": 819, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0647}
{"question": "Solve (314 - 812)", "answer": "The result of (314 - 812) is -498\n\n####-498", "a": 314, "b": 812, "operator": "-", "result": -498}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 975)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 975) is 0.3549\n\n####0.3549", "a": 346, "b": 975, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3549}
{"question": "Solve (56 - 672)", "answer": "The result of (56 - 672) is -616\n\n####-616", "a": 56, "b": 672, "operator": "-", "result": -616}
{"question": "Solve (616 + 627)", "answer": "The result of (616 + 627) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 616, "b": 627, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (491 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (491 - 262) is 229\n\n####229", "a": 491, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": 229}
{"question": "Solve (787 - 221)", "answer": "The result of (787 - 221) is 566\n\n####566", "a": 787, "b": 221, "operator": "-", "result": 566}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 184)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 184) is 111872\n\n####111872", "a": 608, "b": 184, "operator": "*", "result": 111872}
{"question": "Solve (197 * 569)", "answer": "The result of (197 * 569) is 112093\n\n####112093", "a": 197, "b": 569, "operator": "*", "result": 112093}
{"question": "Solve (871 / 432)", "answer": "The result of (871 / 432) is 2.0162\n\n####2.0162", "a": 871, "b": 432, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0162}
{"question": "Solve (617 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (617 / 388) is 1.5902\n\n####1.5902", "a": 617, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5902}
{"question": "Solve (173 / 131)", "answer": "The result of (173 / 131) is 1.3206\n\n####1.3206", "a": 173, "b": 131, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3206}
{"question": "Solve (11 - 455)", "answer": "The result of (11 - 455) is -444\n\n####-444", "a": 11, "b": 455, "operator": "-", "result": -444}
{"question": "Solve (314 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (314 - 512) is -198\n\n####-198", "a": 314, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": -198}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 940)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 940) is -643\n\n####-643", "a": 297, "b": 940, "operator": "-", "result": -643}
{"question": "Solve (948 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (948 - 751) is 197\n\n####197", "a": 948, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve (872 * 201)", "answer": "The result of (872 * 201) is 175272\n\n####175272", "a": 872, "b": 201, "operator": "*", "result": 175272}
{"question": "Solve (351 * 430)", "answer": "The result of (351 * 430) is 150930\n\n####150930", "a": 351, "b": 430, "operator": "*", "result": 150930}
{"question": "Solve (43 * 315)", "answer": "The result of (43 * 315) is 13545\n\n####13545", "a": 43, "b": 315, "operator": "*", "result": 13545}
{"question": "Solve (747 + 851)", "answer": "The result of (747 + 851) is 1598\n\n####1598", "a": 747, "b": 851, "operator": "+", "result": 1598}
{"question": "Solve (110 * 694)", "answer": "The result of (110 * 694) is 76340\n\n####76340", "a": 110, "b": 694, "operator": "*", "result": 76340}
{"question": "Solve (577 * 122)", "answer": "The result of (577 * 122) is 70394\n\n####70394", "a": 577, "b": 122, "operator": "*", "result": 70394}
{"question": "Solve (197 / 712)", "answer": "The result of (197 / 712) is 0.2767\n\n####0.2767", "a": 197, "b": 712, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2767}
{"question": "Solve (689 - 330)", "answer": "The result of (689 - 330) is 359\n\n####359", "a": 689, "b": 330, "operator": "-", "result": 359}
{"question": "Solve (327 + 378)", "answer": "The result of (327 + 378) is 705\n\n####705", "a": 327, "b": 378, "operator": "+", "result": 705}
{"question": "Solve (831 + 119)", "answer": "The result of (831 + 119) is 950\n\n####950", "a": 831, "b": 119, "operator": "+", "result": 950}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 567) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 650, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (904 + 308)", "answer": "The result of (904 + 308) is 1212\n\n####1212", "a": 904, "b": 308, "operator": "+", "result": 1212}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 917)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 917) is 81613\n\n####81613", "a": 89, "b": 917, "operator": "*", "result": 81613}
{"question": "Solve (343 * 223)", "answer": "The result of (343 * 223) is 76489\n\n####76489", "a": 343, "b": 223, "operator": "*", "result": 76489}
{"question": "Solve (826 + 207)", "answer": "The result of (826 + 207) is 1033\n\n####1033", "a": 826, "b": 207, "operator": "+", "result": 1033}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 15)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 15) is 289\n\n####289", "a": 304, "b": 15, "operator": "-", "result": 289}
{"question": "Solve (447 - 676)", "answer": "The result of (447 - 676) is -229\n\n####-229", "a": 447, "b": 676, "operator": "-", "result": -229}
{"question": "Solve (237 - 964)", "answer": "The result of (237 - 964) is -727\n\n####-727", "a": 237, "b": 964, "operator": "-", "result": -727}
{"question": "Solve (430 / 306)", "answer": "The result of (430 / 306) is 1.4052\n\n####1.4052", "a": 430, "b": 306, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4052}
{"question": "Solve (26 / 404)", "answer": "The result of (26 / 404) is 0.0644\n\n####0.0644", "a": 26, "b": 404, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0644}
{"question": "Solve (941 / 429)", "answer": "The result of (941 / 429) is 2.1935\n\n####2.1935", "a": 941, "b": 429, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1935}
{"question": "Solve (436 * 852)", "answer": "The result of (436 * 852) is 371472\n\n####371472", "a": 436, "b": 852, "operator": "*", "result": 371472}
{"question": "Solve (999 * 869)", "answer": "The result of (999 * 869) is 868131\n\n####868131", "a": 999, "b": 869, "operator": "*", "result": 868131}
{"question": "Solve (708 * 730)", "answer": "The result of (708 * 730) is 516840\n\n####516840", "a": 708, "b": 730, "operator": "*", "result": 516840}
{"question": "Solve (965 / 313)", "answer": "The result of (965 / 313) is 3.0831\n\n####3.0831", "a": 965, "b": 313, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0831}
{"question": "Solve (2 + 272)", "answer": "The result of (2 + 272) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 2, "b": 272, "operator": "+", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 307)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 307) is 634\n\n####634", "a": 941, "b": 307, "operator": "-", "result": 634}
{"question": "Solve (137 - 242)", "answer": "The result of (137 - 242) is -105\n\n####-105", "a": 137, "b": 242, "operator": "-", "result": -105}
{"question": "Solve (3 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (3 / 334) is 0.009\n\n####0.009", "a": 3, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 0.009}
{"question": "Solve (911 * 675)", "answer": "The result of (911 * 675) is 614925\n\n####614925", "a": 911, "b": 675, "operator": "*", "result": 614925}
{"question": "Solve (903 / 58)", "answer": "The result of (903 / 58) is 15.569\n\n####15.569", "a": 903, "b": 58, "operator": "/", "result": 15.569}
{"question": "Solve (948 + 793)", "answer": "The result of (948 + 793) is 1741\n\n####1741", "a": 948, "b": 793, "operator": "+", "result": 1741}
{"question": "Solve (605 * 861)", "answer": "The result of (605 * 861) is 520905\n\n####520905", "a": 605, "b": 861, "operator": "*", "result": 520905}
{"question": "Solve (36 * 246)", "answer": "The result of (36 * 246) is 8856\n\n####8856", "a": 36, "b": 246, "operator": "*", "result": 8856}
{"question": "Solve (742 + 874)", "answer": "The result of (742 + 874) is 1616\n\n####1616", "a": 742, "b": 874, "operator": "+", "result": 1616}
{"question": "Solve (90 + 143)", "answer": "The result of (90 + 143) is 233\n\n####233", "a": 90, "b": 143, "operator": "+", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve (777 + 448)", "answer": "The result of (777 + 448) is 1225\n\n####1225", "a": 777, "b": 448, "operator": "+", "result": 1225}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 451)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 451) is 1.8803\n\n####1.8803", "a": 848, "b": 451, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8803}
{"question": "Solve (542 * 84)", "answer": "The result of (542 * 84) is 45528\n\n####45528", "a": 542, "b": 84, "operator": "*", "result": 45528}
{"question": "Solve (767 * 476)", "answer": "The result of (767 * 476) is 365092\n\n####365092", "a": 767, "b": 476, "operator": "*", "result": 365092}
{"question": "Solve (223 - 479)", "answer": "The result of (223 - 479) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 223, "b": 479, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (59 + 234)", "answer": "The result of (59 + 234) is 293\n\n####293", "a": 59, "b": 234, "operator": "+", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve (112 * 543)", "answer": "The result of (112 * 543) is 60816\n\n####60816", "a": 112, "b": 543, "operator": "*", "result": 60816}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 95)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 95) is 86450\n\n####86450", "a": 910, "b": 95, "operator": "*", "result": 86450}
{"question": "Solve (492 + 588)", "answer": "The result of (492 + 588) is 1080\n\n####1080", "a": 492, "b": 588, "operator": "+", "result": 1080}
{"question": "Solve (614 * 631)", "answer": "The result of (614 * 631) is 387434\n\n####387434", "a": 614, "b": 631, "operator": "*", "result": 387434}
{"question": "Solve (146 * 815)", "answer": "The result of (146 * 815) is 118990\n\n####118990", "a": 146, "b": 815, "operator": "*", "result": 118990}
{"question": "Solve (349 / 492)", "answer": "The result of (349 / 492) is 0.7093\n\n####0.7093", "a": 349, "b": 492, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7093}
{"question": "Solve (154 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (154 - 918) is -764\n\n####-764", "a": 154, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -764}
{"question": "Solve (201 / 702)", "answer": "The result of (201 / 702) is 0.2863\n\n####0.2863", "a": 201, "b": 702, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2863}
{"question": "Solve (312 * 997)", "answer": "The result of (312 * 997) is 311064\n\n####311064", "a": 312, "b": 997, "operator": "*", "result": 311064}
{"question": "Solve (416 / 68)", "answer": "The result of (416 / 68) is 6.1176\n\n####6.1176", "a": 416, "b": 68, "operator": "/", "result": 6.1176}
{"question": "Solve (883 - 556)", "answer": "The result of (883 - 556) is 327\n\n####327", "a": 883, "b": 556, "operator": "-", "result": 327}
{"question": "Solve (928 * 473)", "answer": "The result of (928 * 473) is 438944\n\n####438944", "a": 928, "b": 473, "operator": "*", "result": 438944}
{"question": "Solve (746 - 928)", "answer": "The result of (746 - 928) is -182\n\n####-182", "a": 746, "b": 928, "operator": "-", "result": -182}
{"question": "Solve (777 / 128)", "answer": "The result of (777 / 128) is 6.0703\n\n####6.0703", "a": 777, "b": 128, "operator": "/", "result": 6.0703}
{"question": "Solve (264 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (264 / 290) is 0.9103\n\n####0.9103", "a": 264, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9103}
{"question": "Solve (94 + 758)", "answer": "The result of (94 + 758) is 852\n\n####852", "a": 94, "b": 758, "operator": "+", "result": 852}
{"question": "Solve (985 - 894)", "answer": "The result of (985 - 894) is 91\n\n####91", "a": 985, "b": 894, "operator": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve (959 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (959 - 998) is -39\n\n####-39", "a": 959, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -39}
{"question": "Solve (639 / 643)", "answer": "The result of (639 / 643) is 0.9938\n\n####0.9938", "a": 639, "b": 643, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9938}
{"question": "Solve (470 + 98)", "answer": "The result of (470 + 98) is 568\n\n####568", "a": 470, "b": 98, "operator": "+", "result": 568}
{"question": "Solve (763 / 437)", "answer": "The result of (763 / 437) is 1.746\n\n####1.746", "a": 763, "b": 437, "operator": "/", "result": 1.746}
{"question": "Solve (832 / 691)", "answer": "The result of (832 / 691) is 1.2041\n\n####1.2041", "a": 832, "b": 691, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2041}
{"question": "Solve (661 * 974)", "answer": "The result of (661 * 974) is 643814\n\n####643814", "a": 661, "b": 974, "operator": "*", "result": 643814}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 698)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 698) is 1666\n\n####1666", "a": 968, "b": 698, "operator": "+", "result": 1666}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 372)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 372) is -68\n\n####-68", "a": 304, "b": 372, "operator": "-", "result": -68}
{"question": "Solve (190 - 662)", "answer": "The result of (190 - 662) is -472\n\n####-472", "a": 190, "b": 662, "operator": "-", "result": -472}
{"question": "Solve (618 / 983)", "answer": "The result of (618 / 983) is 0.6287\n\n####0.6287", "a": 618, "b": 983, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6287}
{"question": "Solve (600 + 610)", "answer": "The result of (600 + 610) is 1210\n\n####1210", "a": 600, "b": 610, "operator": "+", "result": 1210}
{"question": "Solve (454 * 153)", "answer": "The result of (454 * 153) is 69462\n\n####69462", "a": 454, "b": 153, "operator": "*", "result": 69462}
{"question": "Solve (187 + 846)", "answer": "The result of (187 + 846) is 1033\n\n####1033", "a": 187, "b": 846, "operator": "+", "result": 1033}
{"question": "Solve (269 - 755)", "answer": "The result of (269 - 755) is -486\n\n####-486", "a": 269, "b": 755, "operator": "-", "result": -486}
{"question": "Solve (550 + 135)", "answer": "The result of (550 + 135) is 685\n\n####685", "a": 550, "b": 135, "operator": "+", "result": 685}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 943) is -507\n\n####-507", "a": 436, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -507}
{"question": "Solve (857 / 919)", "answer": "The result of (857 / 919) is 0.9325\n\n####0.9325", "a": 857, "b": 919, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9325}
{"question": "Solve (834 + 65)", "answer": "The result of (834 + 65) is 899\n\n####899", "a": 834, "b": 65, "operator": "+", "result": 899}
{"question": "Solve (345 + 456)", "answer": "The result of (345 + 456) is 801\n\n####801", "a": 345, "b": 456, "operator": "+", "result": 801}
{"question": "Solve (547 / 925)", "answer": "The result of (547 / 925) is 0.5914\n\n####0.5914", "a": 547, "b": 925, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5914}
{"question": "Solve (348 + 747)", "answer": "The result of (348 + 747) is 1095\n\n####1095", "a": 348, "b": 747, "operator": "+", "result": 1095}
{"question": "Solve (851 / 762)", "answer": "The result of (851 / 762) is 1.1168\n\n####1.1168", "a": 851, "b": 762, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1168}
{"question": "Solve (812 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (812 / 388) is 2.0928\n\n####2.0928", "a": 812, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0928}
{"question": "Solve (699 / 568)", "answer": "The result of (699 / 568) is 1.2306\n\n####1.2306", "a": 699, "b": 568, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2306}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 907)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 907) is 511548\n\n####511548", "a": 564, "b": 907, "operator": "*", "result": 511548}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 321) is -128\n\n####-128", "a": 193, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": -128}
{"question": "Solve (471 - 253)", "answer": "The result of (471 - 253) is 218\n\n####218", "a": 471, "b": 253, "operator": "-", "result": 218}
{"question": "Solve (744 + 191)", "answer": "The result of (744 + 191) is 935\n\n####935", "a": 744, "b": 191, "operator": "+", "result": 935}
{"question": "Solve (924 * 43)", "answer": "The result of (924 * 43) is 39732\n\n####39732", "a": 924, "b": 43, "operator": "*", "result": 39732}
{"question": "Solve (796 + 302)", "answer": "The result of (796 + 302) is 1098\n\n####1098", "a": 796, "b": 302, "operator": "+", "result": 1098}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 306)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 306) is 309\n\n####309", "a": 615, "b": 306, "operator": "-", "result": 309}
{"question": "Solve (496 - 437)", "answer": "The result of (496 - 437) is 59\n\n####59", "a": 496, "b": 437, "operator": "-", "result": 59}
{"question": "Solve (634 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (634 - 551) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 634, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (765 * 577)", "answer": "The result of (765 * 577) is 441405\n\n####441405", "a": 765, "b": 577, "operator": "*", "result": 441405}
{"question": "Solve (437 * 999)", "answer": "The result of (437 * 999) is 436563\n\n####436563", "a": 437, "b": 999, "operator": "*", "result": 436563}
{"question": "Solve (259 / 96)", "answer": "The result of (259 / 96) is 2.6979\n\n####2.6979", "a": 259, "b": 96, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6979}
{"question": "Solve (663 + 286)", "answer": "The result of (663 + 286) is 949\n\n####949", "a": 663, "b": 286, "operator": "+", "result": 949}
{"question": "Solve (921 - 677)", "answer": "The result of (921 - 677) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 921, "b": 677, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (810 + 455)", "answer": "The result of (810 + 455) is 1265\n\n####1265", "a": 810, "b": 455, "operator": "+", "result": 1265}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 183)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 183) is 348\n\n####348", "a": 531, "b": 183, "operator": "-", "result": 348}
{"question": "Solve (717 - 158)", "answer": "The result of (717 - 158) is 559\n\n####559", "a": 717, "b": 158, "operator": "-", "result": 559}
{"question": "Solve (358 - 255)", "answer": "The result of (358 - 255) is 103\n\n####103", "a": 358, "b": 255, "operator": "-", "result": 103}
{"question": "Solve (863 / 648)", "answer": "The result of (863 / 648) is 1.3318\n\n####1.3318", "a": 863, "b": 648, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3318}
{"question": "Solve (697 + 115)", "answer": "The result of (697 + 115) is 812\n\n####812", "a": 697, "b": 115, "operator": "+", "result": 812}
{"question": "Solve (72 * 87)", "answer": "The result of (72 * 87) is 6264\n\n####6264", "a": 72, "b": 87, "operator": "*", "result": 6264}
{"question": "Solve (189 / 537)", "answer": "The result of (189 / 537) is 0.352\n\n####0.352", "a": 189, "b": 537, "operator": "/", "result": 0.352}
{"question": "Solve (404 + 293)", "answer": "The result of (404 + 293) is 697\n\n####697", "a": 404, "b": 293, "operator": "+", "result": 697}
{"question": "Solve (79 - 969)", "answer": "The result of (79 - 969) is -890\n\n####-890", "a": 79, "b": 969, "operator": "-", "result": -890}
{"question": "Solve (57 - 450)", "answer": "The result of (57 - 450) is -393\n\n####-393", "a": 57, "b": 450, "operator": "-", "result": -393}
{"question": "Solve (204 * 289)", "answer": "The result of (204 * 289) is 58956\n\n####58956", "a": 204, "b": 289, "operator": "*", "result": 58956}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 729)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 729) is 381267\n\n####381267", "a": 523, "b": 729, "operator": "*", "result": 381267}
{"question": "Solve (699 / 923)", "answer": "The result of (699 / 923) is 0.7573\n\n####0.7573", "a": 699, "b": 923, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7573}
{"question": "Solve (355 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (355 / 53) is 6.6981\n\n####6.6981", "a": 355, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 6.6981}
{"question": "Solve (381 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (381 - 245) is 136\n\n####136", "a": 381, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 136}
{"question": "Solve (941 / 513)", "answer": "The result of (941 / 513) is 1.8343\n\n####1.8343", "a": 941, "b": 513, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8343}
{"question": "Solve (96 / 346)", "answer": "The result of (96 / 346) is 0.2775\n\n####0.2775", "a": 96, "b": 346, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2775}
{"question": "Solve (92 / 99)", "answer": "The result of (92 / 99) is 0.9293\n\n####0.9293", "a": 92, "b": 99, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9293}
{"question": "Solve (103 - 110)", "answer": "The result of (103 - 110) is -7\n\n####-7", "a": 103, "b": 110, "operator": "-", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve (768 - 31)", "answer": "The result of (768 - 31) is 737\n\n####737", "a": 768, "b": 31, "operator": "-", "result": 737}
{"question": "Solve (835 + 772)", "answer": "The result of (835 + 772) is 1607\n\n####1607", "a": 835, "b": 772, "operator": "+", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 366)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 366) is 0.4399\n\n####0.4399", "a": 161, "b": 366, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4399}
{"question": "Solve (225 / 666)", "answer": "The result of (225 / 666) is 0.3378\n\n####0.3378", "a": 225, "b": 666, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3378}
{"question": "Solve (190 * 626)", "answer": "The result of (190 * 626) is 118940\n\n####118940", "a": 190, "b": 626, "operator": "*", "result": 118940}
{"question": "Solve (106 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (106 / 236) is 0.4492\n\n####0.4492", "a": 106, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4492}
{"question": "Solve (549 - 63)", "answer": "The result of (549 - 63) is 486\n\n####486", "a": 549, "b": 63, "operator": "-", "result": 486}
{"question": "Solve (81 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (81 * 690) is 55890\n\n####55890", "a": 81, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 55890}
{"question": "Solve (288 * 828)", "answer": "The result of (288 * 828) is 238464\n\n####238464", "a": 288, "b": 828, "operator": "*", "result": 238464}
{"question": "Solve (340 - 772)", "answer": "The result of (340 - 772) is -432\n\n####-432", "a": 340, "b": 772, "operator": "-", "result": -432}
{"question": "Solve (969 / 430)", "answer": "The result of (969 / 430) is 2.2535\n\n####2.2535", "a": 969, "b": 430, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2535}
{"question": "Solve (968 - 556)", "answer": "The result of (968 - 556) is 412\n\n####412", "a": 968, "b": 556, "operator": "-", "result": 412}
{"question": "Solve (98 - 940)", "answer": "The result of (98 - 940) is -842\n\n####-842", "a": 98, "b": 940, "operator": "-", "result": -842}
{"question": "Solve (131 * 556)", "answer": "The result of (131 * 556) is 72836\n\n####72836", "a": 131, "b": 556, "operator": "*", "result": 72836}
{"question": "Solve (454 + 186)", "answer": "The result of (454 + 186) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 454, "b": 186, "operator": "+", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (398 + 298)", "answer": "The result of (398 + 298) is 696\n\n####696", "a": 398, "b": 298, "operator": "+", "result": 696}
{"question": "Solve (623 * 673)", "answer": "The result of (623 * 673) is 419279\n\n####419279", "a": 623, "b": 673, "operator": "*", "result": 419279}
{"question": "Solve (613 / 79)", "answer": "The result of (613 / 79) is 7.7595\n\n####7.7595", "a": 613, "b": 79, "operator": "/", "result": 7.7595}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 262)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 262) is 0.5802\n\n####0.5802", "a": 152, "b": 262, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5802}
{"question": "Solve (585 - 224)", "answer": "The result of (585 - 224) is 361\n\n####361", "a": 585, "b": 224, "operator": "-", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve (538 - 970)", "answer": "The result of (538 - 970) is -432\n\n####-432", "a": 538, "b": 970, "operator": "-", "result": -432}
{"question": "Solve (513 + 721)", "answer": "The result of (513 + 721) is 1234\n\n####1234", "a": 513, "b": 721, "operator": "+", "result": 1234}
{"question": "Solve (81 - 174)", "answer": "The result of (81 - 174) is -93\n\n####-93", "a": 81, "b": 174, "operator": "-", "result": -93}
{"question": "Solve (214 + 249)", "answer": "The result of (214 + 249) is 463\n\n####463", "a": 214, "b": 249, "operator": "+", "result": 463}
{"question": "Solve (369 / 321)", "answer": "The result of (369 / 321) is 1.1495\n\n####1.1495", "a": 369, "b": 321, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1495}
{"question": "Solve (288 * 248)", "answer": "The result of (288 * 248) is 71424\n\n####71424", "a": 288, "b": 248, "operator": "*", "result": 71424}
{"question": "Solve (246 * 868)", "answer": "The result of (246 * 868) is 213528\n\n####213528", "a": 246, "b": 868, "operator": "*", "result": 213528}
{"question": "Solve (685 - 69)", "answer": "The result of (685 - 69) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 685, "b": 69, "operator": "-", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (990 * 959)", "answer": "The result of (990 * 959) is 949410\n\n####949410", "a": 990, "b": 959, "operator": "*", "result": 949410}
{"question": "Solve (521 / 88)", "answer": "The result of (521 / 88) is 5.9205\n\n####5.9205", "a": 521, "b": 88, "operator": "/", "result": 5.9205}
{"question": "Solve (80 + 670)", "answer": "The result of (80 + 670) is 750\n\n####750", "a": 80, "b": 670, "operator": "+", "result": 750}
{"question": "Solve (224 / 755)", "answer": "The result of (224 / 755) is 0.2967\n\n####0.2967", "a": 224, "b": 755, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2967}
{"question": "Solve (622 / 493)", "answer": "The result of (622 / 493) is 1.2617\n\n####1.2617", "a": 622, "b": 493, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2617}
{"question": "Solve (888 + 28)", "answer": "The result of (888 + 28) is 916\n\n####916", "a": 888, "b": 28, "operator": "+", "result": 916}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 957)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 957) is -639\n\n####-639", "a": 318, "b": 957, "operator": "-", "result": -639}
{"question": "Solve (60 + 36)", "answer": "The result of (60 + 36) is 96\n\n####96", "a": 60, "b": 36, "operator": "+", "result": 96}
{"question": "Solve (285 / 529)", "answer": "The result of (285 / 529) is 0.5388\n\n####0.5388", "a": 285, "b": 529, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5388}
{"question": "Solve (587 * 890)", "answer": "The result of (587 * 890) is 522430\n\n####522430", "a": 587, "b": 890, "operator": "*", "result": 522430}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 509)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 509) is -158\n\n####-158", "a": 351, "b": 509, "operator": "-", "result": -158}
{"question": "Solve (886 - 216)", "answer": "The result of (886 - 216) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 886, "b": 216, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (274 * 382)", "answer": "The result of (274 * 382) is 104668\n\n####104668", "a": 274, "b": 382, "operator": "*", "result": 104668}
{"question": "Solve (359 / 19)", "answer": "The result of (359 / 19) is 18.8947\n\n####18.8947", "a": 359, "b": 19, "operator": "/", "result": 18.8947}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 548)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 548) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 930, "b": 548, "operator": "-", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (602 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (602 - 27) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 602, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (960 + 662)", "answer": "The result of (960 + 662) is 1622\n\n####1622", "a": 960, "b": 662, "operator": "+", "result": 1622}
{"question": "Solve (992 * 310)", "answer": "The result of (992 * 310) is 307520\n\n####307520", "a": 992, "b": 310, "operator": "*", "result": 307520}
{"question": "Solve (193 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (193 + 843) is 1036\n\n####1036", "a": 193, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 1036}
{"question": "Solve (182 * 232)", "answer": "The result of (182 * 232) is 42224\n\n####42224", "a": 182, "b": 232, "operator": "*", "result": 42224}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 290) is 75\n\n####75", "a": 365, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 75}
{"question": "Solve (648 / 778)", "answer": "The result of (648 / 778) is 0.8329\n\n####0.8329", "a": 648, "b": 778, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8329}
{"question": "Solve (79 / 205)", "answer": "The result of (79 / 205) is 0.3854\n\n####0.3854", "a": 79, "b": 205, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3854}
{"question": "Solve (955 / 657)", "answer": "The result of (955 / 657) is 1.4536\n\n####1.4536", "a": 955, "b": 657, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4536}
{"question": "Solve (743 / 871)", "answer": "The result of (743 / 871) is 0.853\n\n####0.853", "a": 743, "b": 871, "operator": "/", "result": 0.853}
{"question": "Solve (823 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (823 - 321) is 502\n\n####502", "a": 823, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 502}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 683)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 683) is 92205\n\n####92205", "a": 135, "b": 683, "operator": "*", "result": 92205}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 604) is -355\n\n####-355", "a": 249, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -355}
{"question": "Solve (691 + 695)", "answer": "The result of (691 + 695) is 1386\n\n####1386", "a": 691, "b": 695, "operator": "+", "result": 1386}
{"question": "Solve (986 / 773)", "answer": "The result of (986 / 773) is 1.2755\n\n####1.2755", "a": 986, "b": 773, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2755}
{"question": "Solve (481 / 495)", "answer": "The result of (481 / 495) is 0.9717\n\n####0.9717", "a": 481, "b": 495, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9717}
{"question": "Solve (248 - 320)", "answer": "The result of (248 - 320) is -72\n\n####-72", "a": 248, "b": 320, "operator": "-", "result": -72}
{"question": "Solve (229 * 363)", "answer": "The result of (229 * 363) is 83127\n\n####83127", "a": 229, "b": 363, "operator": "*", "result": 83127}
{"question": "Solve (746 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (746 / 489) is 1.5256\n\n####1.5256", "a": 746, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5256}
{"question": "Solve (264 - 381)", "answer": "The result of (264 - 381) is -117\n\n####-117", "a": 264, "b": 381, "operator": "-", "result": -117}
{"question": "Solve (940 / 209)", "answer": "The result of (940 / 209) is 4.4976\n\n####4.4976", "a": 940, "b": 209, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4976}
{"question": "Solve (392 * 438)", "answer": "The result of (392 * 438) is 171696\n\n####171696", "a": 392, "b": 438, "operator": "*", "result": 171696}
{"question": "Solve (745 + 329)", "answer": "The result of (745 + 329) is 1074\n\n####1074", "a": 745, "b": 329, "operator": "+", "result": 1074}
{"question": "Solve (998 * 772)", "answer": "The result of (998 * 772) is 770456\n\n####770456", "a": 998, "b": 772, "operator": "*", "result": 770456}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 745) is 113\n\n####113", "a": 858, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": 113}
{"question": "Solve (887 * 284)", "answer": "The result of (887 * 284) is 251908\n\n####251908", "a": 887, "b": 284, "operator": "*", "result": 251908}
{"question": "Solve (980 + 418)", "answer": "The result of (980 + 418) is 1398\n\n####1398", "a": 980, "b": 418, "operator": "+", "result": 1398}
{"question": "Solve (382 * 244)", "answer": "The result of (382 * 244) is 93208\n\n####93208", "a": 382, "b": 244, "operator": "*", "result": 93208}
{"question": "Solve (898 - 821)", "answer": "The result of (898 - 821) is 77\n\n####77", "a": 898, "b": 821, "operator": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve (703 * 299)", "answer": "The result of (703 * 299) is 210197\n\n####210197", "a": 703, "b": 299, "operator": "*", "result": 210197}
{"question": "Solve (673 - 352)", "answer": "The result of (673 - 352) is 321\n\n####321", "a": 673, "b": 352, "operator": "-", "result": 321}
{"question": "Solve (756 - 312)", "answer": "The result of (756 - 312) is 444\n\n####444", "a": 756, "b": 312, "operator": "-", "result": 444}
{"question": "Solve (593 + 893)", "answer": "The result of (593 + 893) is 1486\n\n####1486", "a": 593, "b": 893, "operator": "+", "result": 1486}
{"question": "Solve (742 + 592)", "answer": "The result of (742 + 592) is 1334\n\n####1334", "a": 742, "b": 592, "operator": "+", "result": 1334}
{"question": "Solve (928 * 629)", "answer": "The result of (928 * 629) is 583712\n\n####583712", "a": 928, "b": 629, "operator": "*", "result": 583712}
{"question": "Solve (205 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (205 * 510) is 104550\n\n####104550", "a": 205, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 104550}
{"question": "Solve (452 + 534)", "answer": "The result of (452 + 534) is 986\n\n####986", "a": 452, "b": 534, "operator": "+", "result": 986}
{"question": "Solve (944 + 736)", "answer": "The result of (944 + 736) is 1680\n\n####1680", "a": 944, "b": 736, "operator": "+", "result": 1680}
{"question": "Solve (627 + 313)", "answer": "The result of (627 + 313) is 940\n\n####940", "a": 627, "b": 313, "operator": "+", "result": 940}
{"question": "Solve (434 * 572)", "answer": "The result of (434 * 572) is 248248\n\n####248248", "a": 434, "b": 572, "operator": "*", "result": 248248}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 890)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 890) is -555\n\n####-555", "a": 335, "b": 890, "operator": "-", "result": -555}
{"question": "Solve (486 * 924)", "answer": "The result of (486 * 924) is 449064\n\n####449064", "a": 486, "b": 924, "operator": "*", "result": 449064}
{"question": "Solve (705 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (705 * 439) is 309495\n\n####309495", "a": 705, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 309495}
{"question": "Solve (399 * 807)", "answer": "The result of (399 * 807) is 321993\n\n####321993", "a": 399, "b": 807, "operator": "*", "result": 321993}
{"question": "Solve (725 / 618)", "answer": "The result of (725 / 618) is 1.1731\n\n####1.1731", "a": 725, "b": 618, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1731}
{"question": "Solve (171 / 477)", "answer": "The result of (171 / 477) is 0.3585\n\n####0.3585", "a": 171, "b": 477, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3585}
{"question": "Solve (337 * 535)", "answer": "The result of (337 * 535) is 180295\n\n####180295", "a": 337, "b": 535, "operator": "*", "result": 180295}
{"question": "Solve (235 / 992)", "answer": "The result of (235 / 992) is 0.2369\n\n####0.2369", "a": 235, "b": 992, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2369}
{"question": "Solve (530 * 590)", "answer": "The result of (530 * 590) is 312700\n\n####312700", "a": 530, "b": 590, "operator": "*", "result": 312700}
{"question": "Solve (218 - 109)", "answer": "The result of (218 - 109) is 109\n\n####109", "a": 218, "b": 109, "operator": "-", "result": 109}
{"question": "Solve (187 * 847)", "answer": "The result of (187 * 847) is 158389\n\n####158389", "a": 187, "b": 847, "operator": "*", "result": 158389}
{"question": "Solve (298 / 128)", "answer": "The result of (298 / 128) is 2.3281\n\n####2.3281", "a": 298, "b": 128, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3281}
{"question": "Solve (422 * 856)", "answer": "The result of (422 * 856) is 361232\n\n####361232", "a": 422, "b": 856, "operator": "*", "result": 361232}
{"question": "Solve (313 + 787)", "answer": "The result of (313 + 787) is 1100\n\n####1100", "a": 313, "b": 787, "operator": "+", "result": 1100}
{"question": "Solve (106 / 865)", "answer": "The result of (106 / 865) is 0.1225\n\n####0.1225", "a": 106, "b": 865, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1225}
{"question": "Solve (99 * 865)", "answer": "The result of (99 * 865) is 85635\n\n####85635", "a": 99, "b": 865, "operator": "*", "result": 85635}
{"question": "Solve (613 * 800)", "answer": "The result of (613 * 800) is 490400\n\n####490400", "a": 613, "b": 800, "operator": "*", "result": 490400}
{"question": "Solve (806 * 10)", "answer": "The result of (806 * 10) is 8060\n\n####8060", "a": 806, "b": 10, "operator": "*", "result": 8060}
{"question": "Solve (779 + 108)", "answer": "The result of (779 + 108) is 887\n\n####887", "a": 779, "b": 108, "operator": "+", "result": 887}
{"question": "Solve (205 - 668)", "answer": "The result of (205 - 668) is -463\n\n####-463", "a": 205, "b": 668, "operator": "-", "result": -463}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 802) is 136\n\n####136", "a": 938, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": 136}
{"question": "Solve (957 / 699)", "answer": "The result of (957 / 699) is 1.3691\n\n####1.3691", "a": 957, "b": 699, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3691}
{"question": "Solve (22 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (22 - 567) is -545\n\n####-545", "a": 22, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": -545}
{"question": "Solve (932 + 886)", "answer": "The result of (932 + 886) is 1818\n\n####1818", "a": 932, "b": 886, "operator": "+", "result": 1818}
{"question": "Solve (158 + 434)", "answer": "The result of (158 + 434) is 592\n\n####592", "a": 158, "b": 434, "operator": "+", "result": 592}
{"question": "Solve (462 * 745)", "answer": "The result of (462 * 745) is 344190\n\n####344190", "a": 462, "b": 745, "operator": "*", "result": 344190}
{"question": "Solve (287 * 904)", "answer": "The result of (287 * 904) is 259448\n\n####259448", "a": 287, "b": 904, "operator": "*", "result": 259448}
{"question": "Solve (193 / 198)", "answer": "The result of (193 / 198) is 0.9747\n\n####0.9747", "a": 193, "b": 198, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9747}
{"question": "Solve (556 * 51)", "answer": "The result of (556 * 51) is 28356\n\n####28356", "a": 556, "b": 51, "operator": "*", "result": 28356}
{"question": "Solve (398 / 10)", "answer": "The result of (398 / 10) is 39.8\n\n####39.8", "a": 398, "b": 10, "operator": "/", "result": 39.8}
{"question": "Solve (730 - 621)", "answer": "The result of (730 - 621) is 109\n\n####109", "a": 730, "b": 621, "operator": "-", "result": 109}
{"question": "Solve (511 / 810)", "answer": "The result of (511 / 810) is 0.6309\n\n####0.6309", "a": 511, "b": 810, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6309}
{"question": "Solve (155 * 671)", "answer": "The result of (155 * 671) is 104005\n\n####104005", "a": 155, "b": 671, "operator": "*", "result": 104005}
{"question": "Solve (221 * 816)", "answer": "The result of (221 * 816) is 180336\n\n####180336", "a": 221, "b": 816, "operator": "*", "result": 180336}
{"question": "Solve (243 / 722)", "answer": "The result of (243 / 722) is 0.3366\n\n####0.3366", "a": 243, "b": 722, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3366}
{"question": "Solve (108 + 59)", "answer": "The result of (108 + 59) is 167\n\n####167", "a": 108, "b": 59, "operator": "+", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve (885 - 277)", "answer": "The result of (885 - 277) is 608\n\n####608", "a": 885, "b": 277, "operator": "-", "result": 608}
{"question": "Solve (550 - 799)", "answer": "The result of (550 - 799) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 550, "b": 799, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (650 + 138)", "answer": "The result of (650 + 138) is 788\n\n####788", "a": 650, "b": 138, "operator": "+", "result": 788}
{"question": "Solve (542 + 798)", "answer": "The result of (542 + 798) is 1340\n\n####1340", "a": 542, "b": 798, "operator": "+", "result": 1340}
{"question": "Solve (984 * 17)", "answer": "The result of (984 * 17) is 16728\n\n####16728", "a": 984, "b": 17, "operator": "*", "result": 16728}
{"question": "Solve (983 * 677)", "answer": "The result of (983 * 677) is 665491\n\n####665491", "a": 983, "b": 677, "operator": "*", "result": 665491}
{"question": "Solve (960 - 443)", "answer": "The result of (960 - 443) is 517\n\n####517", "a": 960, "b": 443, "operator": "-", "result": 517}
{"question": "Solve (593 + 678)", "answer": "The result of (593 + 678) is 1271\n\n####1271", "a": 593, "b": 678, "operator": "+", "result": 1271}
{"question": "Solve (882 - 462)", "answer": "The result of (882 - 462) is 420\n\n####420", "a": 882, "b": 462, "operator": "-", "result": 420}
{"question": "Solve (636 + 690)", "answer": "The result of (636 + 690) is 1326\n\n####1326", "a": 636, "b": 690, "operator": "+", "result": 1326}
{"question": "Solve (513 - 676)", "answer": "The result of (513 - 676) is -163\n\n####-163", "a": 513, "b": 676, "operator": "-", "result": -163}
{"question": "Solve (398 + 139)", "answer": "The result of (398 + 139) is 537\n\n####537", "a": 398, "b": 139, "operator": "+", "result": 537}
{"question": "Solve (800 - 419)", "answer": "The result of (800 - 419) is 381\n\n####381", "a": 800, "b": 419, "operator": "-", "result": 381}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 634) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 842, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (975 / 410)", "answer": "The result of (975 / 410) is 2.378\n\n####2.378", "a": 975, "b": 410, "operator": "/", "result": 2.378}
{"question": "Solve (562 / 360)", "answer": "The result of (562 / 360) is 1.5611\n\n####1.5611", "a": 562, "b": 360, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5611}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 172)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 172) is 4.5988\n\n####4.5988", "a": 791, "b": 172, "operator": "/", "result": 4.5988}
{"question": "Solve (635 - 44)", "answer": "The result of (635 - 44) is 591\n\n####591", "a": 635, "b": 44, "operator": "-", "result": 591}
{"question": "Solve (105 - 12)", "answer": "The result of (105 - 12) is 93\n\n####93", "a": 105, "b": 12, "operator": "-", "result": 93}
{"question": "Solve (289 / 766)", "answer": "The result of (289 / 766) is 0.3773\n\n####0.3773", "a": 289, "b": 766, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3773}
{"question": "Solve (483 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (483 / 53) is 9.1132\n\n####9.1132", "a": 483, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 9.1132}
{"question": "Solve (11 - 297)", "answer": "The result of (11 - 297) is -286\n\n####-286", "a": 11, "b": 297, "operator": "-", "result": -286}
{"question": "Solve (337 - 443)", "answer": "The result of (337 - 443) is -106\n\n####-106", "a": 337, "b": 443, "operator": "-", "result": -106}
{"question": "Solve (727 * 660)", "answer": "The result of (727 * 660) is 479820\n\n####479820", "a": 727, "b": 660, "operator": "*", "result": 479820}
{"question": "Solve (219 * 434)", "answer": "The result of (219 * 434) is 95046\n\n####95046", "a": 219, "b": 434, "operator": "*", "result": 95046}
{"question": "Solve (312 + 996)", "answer": "The result of (312 + 996) is 1308\n\n####1308", "a": 312, "b": 996, "operator": "+", "result": 1308}
{"question": "Solve (805 - 425)", "answer": "The result of (805 - 425) is 380\n\n####380", "a": 805, "b": 425, "operator": "-", "result": 380}
{"question": "Solve (987 * 868)", "answer": "The result of (987 * 868) is 856716\n\n####856716", "a": 987, "b": 868, "operator": "*", "result": 856716}
{"question": "Solve (121 - 150)", "answer": "The result of (121 - 150) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 121, "b": 150, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 267)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 267) is 163\n\n####163", "a": 430, "b": 267, "operator": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve (544 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (544 * 944) is 513536\n\n####513536", "a": 544, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 513536}
{"question": "Solve (506 - 785)", "answer": "The result of (506 - 785) is -279\n\n####-279", "a": 506, "b": 785, "operator": "-", "result": -279}
{"question": "Solve (793 - 619)", "answer": "The result of (793 - 619) is 174\n\n####174", "a": 793, "b": 619, "operator": "-", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve (803 + 604)", "answer": "The result of (803 + 604) is 1407\n\n####1407", "a": 803, "b": 604, "operator": "+", "result": 1407}
{"question": "Solve (765 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (765 * 215) is 164475\n\n####164475", "a": 765, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 164475}
{"question": "Solve (633 + 957)", "answer": "The result of (633 + 957) is 1590\n\n####1590", "a": 633, "b": 957, "operator": "+", "result": 1590}
{"question": "Solve (824 + 154)", "answer": "The result of (824 + 154) is 978\n\n####978", "a": 824, "b": 154, "operator": "+", "result": 978}
{"question": "Solve (120 / 933)", "answer": "The result of (120 / 933) is 0.1286\n\n####0.1286", "a": 120, "b": 933, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1286}
{"question": "Solve (274 + 183)", "answer": "The result of (274 + 183) is 457\n\n####457", "a": 274, "b": 183, "operator": "+", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 189)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 189) is 139671\n\n####139671", "a": 739, "b": 189, "operator": "*", "result": 139671}
{"question": "Solve (183 + 567)", "answer": "The result of (183 + 567) is 750\n\n####750", "a": 183, "b": 567, "operator": "+", "result": 750}
{"question": "Solve (77 / 471)", "answer": "The result of (77 / 471) is 0.1635\n\n####0.1635", "a": 77, "b": 471, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1635}
{"question": "Solve (500 / 785)", "answer": "The result of (500 / 785) is 0.6369\n\n####0.6369", "a": 500, "b": 785, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6369}
{"question": "Solve (427 + 976)", "answer": "The result of (427 + 976) is 1403\n\n####1403", "a": 427, "b": 976, "operator": "+", "result": 1403}
{"question": "Solve (321 - 98)", "answer": "The result of (321 - 98) is 223\n\n####223", "a": 321, "b": 98, "operator": "-", "result": 223}
{"question": "Solve (149 * 248)", "answer": "The result of (149 * 248) is 36952\n\n####36952", "a": 149, "b": 248, "operator": "*", "result": 36952}
{"question": "Solve (377 / 369)", "answer": "The result of (377 / 369) is 1.0217\n\n####1.0217", "a": 377, "b": 369, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0217}
{"question": "Solve (959 + 237)", "answer": "The result of (959 + 237) is 1196\n\n####1196", "a": 959, "b": 237, "operator": "+", "result": 1196}
{"question": "Solve (602 - 440)", "answer": "The result of (602 - 440) is 162\n\n####162", "a": 602, "b": 440, "operator": "-", "result": 162}
{"question": "Solve (516 + 900)", "answer": "The result of (516 + 900) is 1416\n\n####1416", "a": 516, "b": 900, "operator": "+", "result": 1416}
{"question": "Solve (633 - 636)", "answer": "The result of (633 - 636) is -3\n\n####-3", "a": 633, "b": 636, "operator": "-", "result": -3}
{"question": "Solve (846 * 814)", "answer": "The result of (846 * 814) is 688644\n\n####688644", "a": 846, "b": 814, "operator": "*", "result": 688644}
{"question": "Solve (887 - 337)", "answer": "The result of (887 - 337) is 550\n\n####550", "a": 887, "b": 337, "operator": "-", "result": 550}
{"question": "Solve (314 + 272)", "answer": "The result of (314 + 272) is 586\n\n####586", "a": 314, "b": 272, "operator": "+", "result": 586}
{"question": "Solve (865 * 779)", "answer": "The result of (865 * 779) is 673835\n\n####673835", "a": 865, "b": 779, "operator": "*", "result": 673835}
{"question": "Solve (255 + 91)", "answer": "The result of (255 + 91) is 346\n\n####346", "a": 255, "b": 91, "operator": "+", "result": 346}
{"question": "Solve (401 - 240)", "answer": "The result of (401 - 240) is 161\n\n####161", "a": 401, "b": 240, "operator": "-", "result": 161}
{"question": "Solve (755 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (755 / 567) is 1.3316\n\n####1.3316", "a": 755, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3316}
{"question": "Solve (945 - 147)", "answer": "The result of (945 - 147) is 798\n\n####798", "a": 945, "b": 147, "operator": "-", "result": 798}
{"question": "Solve (86 - 243)", "answer": "The result of (86 - 243) is -157\n\n####-157", "a": 86, "b": 243, "operator": "-", "result": -157}
{"question": "Solve (411 - 808)", "answer": "The result of (411 - 808) is -397\n\n####-397", "a": 411, "b": 808, "operator": "-", "result": -397}
{"question": "Solve (966 / 832)", "answer": "The result of (966 / 832) is 1.1611\n\n####1.1611", "a": 966, "b": 832, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1611}
{"question": "Solve (902 / 607)", "answer": "The result of (902 / 607) is 1.486\n\n####1.486", "a": 902, "b": 607, "operator": "/", "result": 1.486}
{"question": "Solve (745 - 775)", "answer": "The result of (745 - 775) is -30\n\n####-30", "a": 745, "b": 775, "operator": "-", "result": -30}
{"question": "Solve (14 * 443)", "answer": "The result of (14 * 443) is 6202\n\n####6202", "a": 14, "b": 443, "operator": "*", "result": 6202}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 224)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 224) is 85\n\n####85", "a": 309, "b": 224, "operator": "-", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve (604 - 466)", "answer": "The result of (604 - 466) is 138\n\n####138", "a": 604, "b": 466, "operator": "-", "result": 138}
{"question": "Solve (677 / 580)", "answer": "The result of (677 / 580) is 1.1672\n\n####1.1672", "a": 677, "b": 580, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1672}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 869)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 869) is 0.0564\n\n####0.0564", "a": 49, "b": 869, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0564}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 1)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 1) is 653\n\n####653", "a": 654, "b": 1, "operator": "-", "result": 653}
{"question": "Solve (585 / 135)", "answer": "The result of (585 / 135) is 4.3333\n\n####4.3333", "a": 585, "b": 135, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3333}
{"question": "Solve (809 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (809 * 823) is 665807\n\n####665807", "a": 809, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 665807}
{"question": "Solve (157 - 226)", "answer": "The result of (157 - 226) is -69\n\n####-69", "a": 157, "b": 226, "operator": "-", "result": -69}
{"question": "Solve (963 - 249)", "answer": "The result of (963 - 249) is 714\n\n####714", "a": 963, "b": 249, "operator": "-", "result": 714}
{"question": "Solve (34 + 277)", "answer": "The result of (34 + 277) is 311\n\n####311", "a": 34, "b": 277, "operator": "+", "result": 311}
{"question": "Solve (512 + 163)", "answer": "The result of (512 + 163) is 675\n\n####675", "a": 512, "b": 163, "operator": "+", "result": 675}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 501)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 501) is 1.4411\n\n####1.4411", "a": 722, "b": 501, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4411}
{"question": "Solve (389 - 596)", "answer": "The result of (389 - 596) is -207\n\n####-207", "a": 389, "b": 596, "operator": "-", "result": -207}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 581)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 581) is 0.8382\n\n####0.8382", "a": 487, "b": 581, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8382}
{"question": "Solve (797 + 545)", "answer": "The result of (797 + 545) is 1342\n\n####1342", "a": 797, "b": 545, "operator": "+", "result": 1342}
{"question": "Solve (85 - 23)", "answer": "The result of (85 - 23) is 62\n\n####62", "a": 85, "b": 23, "operator": "-", "result": 62}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 710)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 710) is 0.1915\n\n####0.1915", "a": 136, "b": 710, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1915}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 741)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 741) is -300\n\n####-300", "a": 441, "b": 741, "operator": "-", "result": -300}
{"question": "Solve (668 + 971)", "answer": "The result of (668 + 971) is 1639\n\n####1639", "a": 668, "b": 971, "operator": "+", "result": 1639}
{"question": "Solve (324 + 293)", "answer": "The result of (324 + 293) is 617\n\n####617", "a": 324, "b": 293, "operator": "+", "result": 617}
{"question": "Solve (933 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (933 - 2) is 931\n\n####931", "a": 933, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 931}
{"question": "Solve (815 - 919)", "answer": "The result of (815 - 919) is -104\n\n####-104", "a": 815, "b": 919, "operator": "-", "result": -104}
{"question": "Solve (528 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (528 - 567) is -39\n\n####-39", "a": 528, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": -39}
{"question": "Solve (771 / 594)", "answer": "The result of (771 / 594) is 1.298\n\n####1.298", "a": 771, "b": 594, "operator": "/", "result": 1.298}
{"question": "Solve (802 - 605)", "answer": "The result of (802 - 605) is 197\n\n####197", "a": 802, "b": 605, "operator": "-", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve (369 / 656)", "answer": "The result of (369 / 656) is 0.5625\n\n####0.5625", "a": 369, "b": 656, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5625}
{"question": "Solve (929 / 127)", "answer": "The result of (929 / 127) is 7.315\n\n####7.315", "a": 929, "b": 127, "operator": "/", "result": 7.315}
{"question": "Solve (326 - 394)", "answer": "The result of (326 - 394) is -68\n\n####-68", "a": 326, "b": 394, "operator": "-", "result": -68}
{"question": "Solve (308 / 640)", "answer": "The result of (308 / 640) is 0.4813\n\n####0.4813", "a": 308, "b": 640, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4813}
{"question": "Solve (408 / 653)", "answer": "The result of (408 / 653) is 0.6248\n\n####0.6248", "a": 408, "b": 653, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6248}
{"question": "Solve (133 / 850)", "answer": "The result of (133 / 850) is 0.1565\n\n####0.1565", "a": 133, "b": 850, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1565}
{"question": "Solve (118 - 132)", "answer": "The result of (118 - 132) is -14\n\n####-14", "a": 118, "b": 132, "operator": "-", "result": -14}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 190)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 190) is 27360\n\n####27360", "a": 144, "b": 190, "operator": "*", "result": 27360}
{"question": "Solve (660 + 137)", "answer": "The result of (660 + 137) is 797\n\n####797", "a": 660, "b": 137, "operator": "+", "result": 797}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 129)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 129) is 847\n\n####847", "a": 976, "b": 129, "operator": "-", "result": 847}
{"question": "Solve (85 * 338)", "answer": "The result of (85 * 338) is 28730\n\n####28730", "a": 85, "b": 338, "operator": "*", "result": 28730}
{"question": "Solve (184 * 868)", "answer": "The result of (184 * 868) is 159712\n\n####159712", "a": 184, "b": 868, "operator": "*", "result": 159712}
{"question": "Solve (664 * 272)", "answer": "The result of (664 * 272) is 180608\n\n####180608", "a": 664, "b": 272, "operator": "*", "result": 180608}
{"question": "Solve (807 / 656)", "answer": "The result of (807 / 656) is 1.2302\n\n####1.2302", "a": 807, "b": 656, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2302}
{"question": "Solve (333 / 897)", "answer": "The result of (333 / 897) is 0.3712\n\n####0.3712", "a": 333, "b": 897, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3712}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 42)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 42) is 18.8333\n\n####18.8333", "a": 791, "b": 42, "operator": "/", "result": 18.8333}
{"question": "Solve (550 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (550 + 843) is 1393\n\n####1393", "a": 550, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 1393}
{"question": "Solve (141 / 916)", "answer": "The result of (141 / 916) is 0.1539\n\n####0.1539", "a": 141, "b": 916, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1539}
{"question": "Solve (575 - 950)", "answer": "The result of (575 - 950) is -375\n\n####-375", "a": 575, "b": 950, "operator": "-", "result": -375}
{"question": "Solve (591 * 342)", "answer": "The result of (591 * 342) is 202122\n\n####202122", "a": 591, "b": 342, "operator": "*", "result": 202122}
{"question": "Solve (866 / 494)", "answer": "The result of (866 / 494) is 1.753\n\n####1.753", "a": 866, "b": 494, "operator": "/", "result": 1.753}
{"question": "Solve (294 / 291)", "answer": "The result of (294 / 291) is 1.0103\n\n####1.0103", "a": 294, "b": 291, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0103}
{"question": "Solve (564 - 804)", "answer": "The result of (564 - 804) is -240\n\n####-240", "a": 564, "b": 804, "operator": "-", "result": -240}
{"question": "Solve (242 / 754)", "answer": "The result of (242 / 754) is 0.321\n\n####0.321", "a": 242, "b": 754, "operator": "/", "result": 0.321}
{"question": "Solve (313 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (313 * 910) is 284830\n\n####284830", "a": 313, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 284830}
{"question": "Solve (445 / 965)", "answer": "The result of (445 / 965) is 0.4611\n\n####0.4611", "a": 445, "b": 965, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4611}
{"question": "Solve (564 + 398)", "answer": "The result of (564 + 398) is 962\n\n####962", "a": 564, "b": 398, "operator": "+", "result": 962}
{"question": "Solve (223 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (223 - 777) is -554\n\n####-554", "a": 223, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -554}
{"question": "Solve (411 + 848)", "answer": "The result of (411 + 848) is 1259\n\n####1259", "a": 411, "b": 848, "operator": "+", "result": 1259}
{"question": "Solve (473 / 514)", "answer": "The result of (473 / 514) is 0.9202\n\n####0.9202", "a": 473, "b": 514, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9202}
{"question": "Solve (904 - 660)", "answer": "The result of (904 - 660) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 904, "b": 660, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (181 - 136)", "answer": "The result of (181 - 136) is 45\n\n####45", "a": 181, "b": 136, "operator": "-", "result": 45}
{"question": "Solve (371 - 69)", "answer": "The result of (371 - 69) is 302\n\n####302", "a": 371, "b": 69, "operator": "-", "result": 302}
{"question": "Solve (574 + 965)", "answer": "The result of (574 + 965) is 1539\n\n####1539", "a": 574, "b": 965, "operator": "+", "result": 1539}
{"question": "Solve (372 + 436)", "answer": "The result of (372 + 436) is 808\n\n####808", "a": 372, "b": 436, "operator": "+", "result": 808}
{"question": "Solve (162 - 928)", "answer": "The result of (162 - 928) is -766\n\n####-766", "a": 162, "b": 928, "operator": "-", "result": -766}
{"question": "Solve (31 / 343)", "answer": "The result of (31 / 343) is 0.0904\n\n####0.0904", "a": 31, "b": 343, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0904}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 390) is 2.2231\n\n####2.2231", "a": 867, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2231}
{"question": "Solve (301 * 123)", "answer": "The result of (301 * 123) is 37023\n\n####37023", "a": 301, "b": 123, "operator": "*", "result": 37023}
{"question": "Solve (550 / 264)", "answer": "The result of (550 / 264) is 2.0833\n\n####2.0833", "a": 550, "b": 264, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0833}
{"question": "Solve (517 - 794)", "answer": "The result of (517 - 794) is -277\n\n####-277", "a": 517, "b": 794, "operator": "-", "result": -277}
{"question": "Solve (530 - 732)", "answer": "The result of (530 - 732) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 530, "b": 732, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (82 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (82 + 843) is 925\n\n####925", "a": 82, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 925}
{"question": "Solve (887 * 492)", "answer": "The result of (887 * 492) is 436404\n\n####436404", "a": 887, "b": 492, "operator": "*", "result": 436404}
{"question": "Solve (970 + 724)", "answer": "The result of (970 + 724) is 1694\n\n####1694", "a": 970, "b": 724, "operator": "+", "result": 1694}
{"question": "Solve (584 + 341)", "answer": "The result of (584 + 341) is 925\n\n####925", "a": 584, "b": 341, "operator": "+", "result": 925}
{"question": "Solve (43 * 416)", "answer": "The result of (43 * 416) is 17888\n\n####17888", "a": 43, "b": 416, "operator": "*", "result": 17888}
{"question": "Solve (103 + 64)", "answer": "The result of (103 + 64) is 167\n\n####167", "a": 103, "b": 64, "operator": "+", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve (345 / 515)", "answer": "The result of (345 / 515) is 0.6699\n\n####0.6699", "a": 345, "b": 515, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6699}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 795)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 795) is -430\n\n####-430", "a": 365, "b": 795, "operator": "-", "result": -430}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 735)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 735) is 0.5769\n\n####0.5769", "a": 424, "b": 735, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5769}
{"question": "Solve (915 - 704)", "answer": "The result of (915 - 704) is 211\n\n####211", "a": 915, "b": 704, "operator": "-", "result": 211}
{"question": "Solve (914 / 951)", "answer": "The result of (914 / 951) is 0.9611\n\n####0.9611", "a": 914, "b": 951, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9611}
{"question": "Solve (864 + 458)", "answer": "The result of (864 + 458) is 1322\n\n####1322", "a": 864, "b": 458, "operator": "+", "result": 1322}
{"question": "Solve (404 / 183)", "answer": "The result of (404 / 183) is 2.2077\n\n####2.2077", "a": 404, "b": 183, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2077}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 875)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 875) is -593\n\n####-593", "a": 282, "b": 875, "operator": "-", "result": -593}
{"question": "Solve (238 + 162)", "answer": "The result of (238 + 162) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 238, "b": 162, "operator": "+", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (329 + 116)", "answer": "The result of (329 + 116) is 445\n\n####445", "a": 329, "b": 116, "operator": "+", "result": 445}
{"question": "Solve (261 / 100)", "answer": "The result of (261 / 100) is 2.61\n\n####2.61", "a": 261, "b": 100, "operator": "/", "result": 2.61}
{"question": "Solve (949 * 358)", "answer": "The result of (949 * 358) is 339742\n\n####339742", "a": 949, "b": 358, "operator": "*", "result": 339742}
{"question": "Solve (457 + 849)", "answer": "The result of (457 + 849) is 1306\n\n####1306", "a": 457, "b": 849, "operator": "+", "result": 1306}
{"question": "Solve (282 / 910)", "answer": "The result of (282 / 910) is 0.3099\n\n####0.3099", "a": 282, "b": 910, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3099}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 497)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 497) is -146\n\n####-146", "a": 351, "b": 497, "operator": "-", "result": -146}
{"question": "Solve (844 * 521)", "answer": "The result of (844 * 521) is 439724\n\n####439724", "a": 844, "b": 521, "operator": "*", "result": 439724}
{"question": "Solve (302 + 267)", "answer": "The result of (302 + 267) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 302, "b": 267, "operator": "+", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 205)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 205) is 4.4098\n\n####4.4098", "a": 904, "b": 205, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4098}
{"question": "Solve (83 + 636)", "answer": "The result of (83 + 636) is 719\n\n####719", "a": 83, "b": 636, "operator": "+", "result": 719}
{"question": "Solve (519 - 201)", "answer": "The result of (519 - 201) is 318\n\n####318", "a": 519, "b": 201, "operator": "-", "result": 318}
{"question": "Solve (455 + 914)", "answer": "The result of (455 + 914) is 1369\n\n####1369", "a": 455, "b": 914, "operator": "+", "result": 1369}
{"question": "Solve (822 / 273)", "answer": "The result of (822 / 273) is 3.011\n\n####3.011", "a": 822, "b": 273, "operator": "/", "result": 3.011}
{"question": "Solve (829 + 715)", "answer": "The result of (829 + 715) is 1544\n\n####1544", "a": 829, "b": 715, "operator": "+", "result": 1544}
{"question": "Solve (109 / 929)", "answer": "The result of (109 / 929) is 0.1173\n\n####0.1173", "a": 109, "b": 929, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1173}
{"question": "Solve (276 / 77)", "answer": "The result of (276 / 77) is 3.5844\n\n####3.5844", "a": 276, "b": 77, "operator": "/", "result": 3.5844}
{"question": "Solve (554 / 347)", "answer": "The result of (554 / 347) is 1.5965\n\n####1.5965", "a": 554, "b": 347, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5965}
{"question": "Solve (24 + 946)", "answer": "The result of (24 + 946) is 970\n\n####970", "a": 24, "b": 946, "operator": "+", "result": 970}
{"question": "Solve (20 * 181)", "answer": "The result of (20 * 181) is 3620\n\n####3620", "a": 20, "b": 181, "operator": "*", "result": 3620}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 871)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 871) is 393692\n\n####393692", "a": 452, "b": 871, "operator": "*", "result": 393692}
{"question": "Solve (530 * 95)", "answer": "The result of (530 * 95) is 50350\n\n####50350", "a": 530, "b": 95, "operator": "*", "result": 50350}
{"question": "Solve (375 - 788)", "answer": "The result of (375 - 788) is -413\n\n####-413", "a": 375, "b": 788, "operator": "-", "result": -413}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 562)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 562) is 338324\n\n####338324", "a": 602, "b": 562, "operator": "*", "result": 338324}
{"question": "Solve (150 - 669)", "answer": "The result of (150 - 669) is -519\n\n####-519", "a": 150, "b": 669, "operator": "-", "result": -519}
{"question": "Solve (815 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (815 * 390) is 317850\n\n####317850", "a": 815, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 317850}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 793)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 793) is 322751\n\n####322751", "a": 407, "b": 793, "operator": "*", "result": 322751}
{"question": "Solve (403 + 346)", "answer": "The result of (403 + 346) is 749\n\n####749", "a": 403, "b": 346, "operator": "+", "result": 749}
{"question": "Solve (201 + 496)", "answer": "The result of (201 + 496) is 697\n\n####697", "a": 201, "b": 496, "operator": "+", "result": 697}
{"question": "Solve (901 / 882)", "answer": "The result of (901 / 882) is 1.0215\n\n####1.0215", "a": 901, "b": 882, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0215}
{"question": "Solve (465 * 396)", "answer": "The result of (465 * 396) is 184140\n\n####184140", "a": 465, "b": 396, "operator": "*", "result": 184140}
{"question": "Solve (782 * 62)", "answer": "The result of (782 * 62) is 48484\n\n####48484", "a": 782, "b": 62, "operator": "*", "result": 48484}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 89)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 89) is 4.764\n\n####4.764", "a": 424, "b": 89, "operator": "/", "result": 4.764}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 169) is 769\n\n####769", "a": 938, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": 769}
{"question": "Solve (739 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (739 - 498) is 241\n\n####241", "a": 739, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve (815 / 279)", "answer": "The result of (815 / 279) is 2.9211\n\n####2.9211", "a": 815, "b": 279, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9211}
{"question": "Solve (95 / 737)", "answer": "The result of (95 / 737) is 0.1289\n\n####0.1289", "a": 95, "b": 737, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1289}
{"question": "Solve (962 - 265)", "answer": "The result of (962 - 265) is 697\n\n####697", "a": 962, "b": 265, "operator": "-", "result": 697}
{"question": "Solve (575 + 617)", "answer": "The result of (575 + 617) is 1192\n\n####1192", "a": 575, "b": 617, "operator": "+", "result": 1192}
{"question": "Solve (164 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (164 / 445) is 0.3685\n\n####0.3685", "a": 164, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3685}
{"question": "Solve (273 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (273 - 354) is -81\n\n####-81", "a": 273, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": -81}
{"question": "Solve (916 * 514)", "answer": "The result of (916 * 514) is 470824\n\n####470824", "a": 916, "b": 514, "operator": "*", "result": 470824}
{"question": "Solve (978 * 977)", "answer": "The result of (978 * 977) is 955506\n\n####955506", "a": 978, "b": 977, "operator": "*", "result": 955506}
{"question": "Solve (859 / 2)", "answer": "The result of (859 / 2) is 429.5\n\n####429.5", "a": 859, "b": 2, "operator": "/", "result": 429.5}
{"question": "Solve (251 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (251 + 211) is 462\n\n####462", "a": 251, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 462}
{"question": "Solve (801 - 119)", "answer": "The result of (801 - 119) is 682\n\n####682", "a": 801, "b": 119, "operator": "-", "result": 682}
{"question": "Solve (445 - 462)", "answer": "The result of (445 - 462) is -17\n\n####-17", "a": 445, "b": 462, "operator": "-", "result": -17}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 255)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 255) is 1.9961\n\n####1.9961", "a": 509, "b": 255, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9961}
{"question": "Solve (688 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (688 * 690) is 474720\n\n####474720", "a": 688, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 474720}
{"question": "Solve (432 / 258)", "answer": "The result of (432 / 258) is 1.6744\n\n####1.6744", "a": 432, "b": 258, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6744}
{"question": "Solve (47 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (47 - 452) is -405\n\n####-405", "a": 47, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": -405}
{"question": "Solve (599 + 864)", "answer": "The result of (599 + 864) is 1463\n\n####1463", "a": 599, "b": 864, "operator": "+", "result": 1463}
{"question": "Solve (177 - 301)", "answer": "The result of (177 - 301) is -124\n\n####-124", "a": 177, "b": 301, "operator": "-", "result": -124}
{"question": "Solve (769 - 723)", "answer": "The result of (769 - 723) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 769, "b": 723, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (406 + 937)", "answer": "The result of (406 + 937) is 1343\n\n####1343", "a": 406, "b": 937, "operator": "+", "result": 1343}
{"question": "Solve (430 * 403)", "answer": "The result of (430 * 403) is 173290\n\n####173290", "a": 430, "b": 403, "operator": "*", "result": 173290}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 290) is 71\n\n####71", "a": 361, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve (936 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (936 - 579) is 357\n\n####357", "a": 936, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": 357}
{"question": "Solve (705 + 984)", "answer": "The result of (705 + 984) is 1689\n\n####1689", "a": 705, "b": 984, "operator": "+", "result": 1689}
{"question": "Solve (987 - 848)", "answer": "The result of (987 - 848) is 139\n\n####139", "a": 987, "b": 848, "operator": "-", "result": 139}
{"question": "Solve (684 + 382)", "answer": "The result of (684 + 382) is 1066\n\n####1066", "a": 684, "b": 382, "operator": "+", "result": 1066}
{"question": "Solve (672 - 65)", "answer": "The result of (672 - 65) is 607\n\n####607", "a": 672, "b": 65, "operator": "-", "result": 607}
{"question": "Solve (995 - 447)", "answer": "The result of (995 - 447) is 548\n\n####548", "a": 995, "b": 447, "operator": "-", "result": 548}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 237)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 237) is 138882\n\n####138882", "a": 586, "b": 237, "operator": "*", "result": 138882}
{"question": "Solve (481 * 801)", "answer": "The result of (481 * 801) is 385281\n\n####385281", "a": 481, "b": 801, "operator": "*", "result": 385281}
{"question": "Solve (951 * 445)", "answer": "The result of (951 * 445) is 423195\n\n####423195", "a": 951, "b": 445, "operator": "*", "result": 423195}
{"question": "Solve (657 / 389)", "answer": "The result of (657 / 389) is 1.6889\n\n####1.6889", "a": 657, "b": 389, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6889}
{"question": "Solve (936 / 86)", "answer": "The result of (936 / 86) is 10.8837\n\n####10.8837", "a": 936, "b": 86, "operator": "/", "result": 10.8837}
{"question": "Solve (575 + 928)", "answer": "The result of (575 + 928) is 1503\n\n####1503", "a": 575, "b": 928, "operator": "+", "result": 1503}
{"question": "Solve (312 - 205)", "answer": "The result of (312 - 205) is 107\n\n####107", "a": 312, "b": 205, "operator": "-", "result": 107}
{"question": "Solve (455 / 898)", "answer": "The result of (455 / 898) is 0.5067\n\n####0.5067", "a": 455, "b": 898, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5067}
{"question": "Solve (736 - 811)", "answer": "The result of (736 - 811) is -75\n\n####-75", "a": 736, "b": 811, "operator": "-", "result": -75}
{"question": "Solve (440 + 252)", "answer": "The result of (440 + 252) is 692\n\n####692", "a": 440, "b": 252, "operator": "+", "result": 692}
{"question": "Solve (537 * 927)", "answer": "The result of (537 * 927) is 497799\n\n####497799", "a": 537, "b": 927, "operator": "*", "result": 497799}
{"question": "Solve (179 / 91)", "answer": "The result of (179 / 91) is 1.967\n\n####1.967", "a": 179, "b": 91, "operator": "/", "result": 1.967}
{"question": "Solve (301 + 349)", "answer": "The result of (301 + 349) is 650\n\n####650", "a": 301, "b": 349, "operator": "+", "result": 650}
{"question": "Solve (636 * 421)", "answer": "The result of (636 * 421) is 267756\n\n####267756", "a": 636, "b": 421, "operator": "*", "result": 267756}
{"question": "Solve (826 / 477)", "answer": "The result of (826 / 477) is 1.7317\n\n####1.7317", "a": 826, "b": 477, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7317}
{"question": "Solve (384 / 508)", "answer": "The result of (384 / 508) is 0.7559\n\n####0.7559", "a": 384, "b": 508, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7559}
{"question": "Solve (539 / 484)", "answer": "The result of (539 / 484) is 1.1136\n\n####1.1136", "a": 539, "b": 484, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1136}
{"question": "Solve (217 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (217 * 387) is 83979\n\n####83979", "a": 217, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 83979}
{"question": "Solve (248 * 877)", "answer": "The result of (248 * 877) is 217496\n\n####217496", "a": 248, "b": 877, "operator": "*", "result": 217496}
{"question": "Solve (211 - 302)", "answer": "The result of (211 - 302) is -91\n\n####-91", "a": 211, "b": 302, "operator": "-", "result": -91}
{"question": "Solve (786 * 164)", "answer": "The result of (786 * 164) is 128904\n\n####128904", "a": 786, "b": 164, "operator": "*", "result": 128904}
{"question": "Solve (552 - 423)", "answer": "The result of (552 - 423) is 129\n\n####129", "a": 552, "b": 423, "operator": "-", "result": 129}
{"question": "Solve (127 + 15)", "answer": "The result of (127 + 15) is 142\n\n####142", "a": 127, "b": 15, "operator": "+", "result": 142}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 650)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 650) is -138\n\n####-138", "a": 512, "b": 650, "operator": "-", "result": -138}
{"question": "Solve (580 + 593)", "answer": "The result of (580 + 593) is 1173\n\n####1173", "a": 580, "b": 593, "operator": "+", "result": 1173}
{"question": "Solve (148 - 815)", "answer": "The result of (148 - 815) is -667\n\n####-667", "a": 148, "b": 815, "operator": "-", "result": -667}
{"question": "Solve (743 / 451)", "answer": "The result of (743 / 451) is 1.6475\n\n####1.6475", "a": 743, "b": 451, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6475}
{"question": "Solve (711 * 974)", "answer": "The result of (711 * 974) is 692514\n\n####692514", "a": 711, "b": 974, "operator": "*", "result": 692514}
{"question": "Solve (293 / 440)", "answer": "The result of (293 / 440) is 0.6659\n\n####0.6659", "a": 293, "b": 440, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6659}
{"question": "Solve (980 * 945)", "answer": "The result of (980 * 945) is 926100\n\n####926100", "a": 980, "b": 945, "operator": "*", "result": 926100}
{"question": "Solve (437 * 434)", "answer": "The result of (437 * 434) is 189658\n\n####189658", "a": 437, "b": 434, "operator": "*", "result": 189658}
{"question": "Solve (582 * 628)", "answer": "The result of (582 * 628) is 365496\n\n####365496", "a": 582, "b": 628, "operator": "*", "result": 365496}
{"question": "Solve (903 * 128)", "answer": "The result of (903 * 128) is 115584\n\n####115584", "a": 903, "b": 128, "operator": "*", "result": 115584}
{"question": "Solve (612 / 799)", "answer": "The result of (612 / 799) is 0.766\n\n####0.766", "a": 612, "b": 799, "operator": "/", "result": 0.766}
{"question": "Solve (575 - 3)", "answer": "The result of (575 - 3) is 572\n\n####572", "a": 575, "b": 3, "operator": "-", "result": 572}
{"question": "Solve (776 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (776 + 868) is 1644\n\n####1644", "a": 776, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 1644}
{"question": "Solve (257 * 258)", "answer": "The result of (257 * 258) is 66306\n\n####66306", "a": 257, "b": 258, "operator": "*", "result": 66306}
{"question": "Solve (673 * 266)", "answer": "The result of (673 * 266) is 179018\n\n####179018", "a": 673, "b": 266, "operator": "*", "result": 179018}
{"question": "Solve (71 + 916)", "answer": "The result of (71 + 916) is 987\n\n####987", "a": 71, "b": 916, "operator": "+", "result": 987}
{"question": "Solve (491 - 728)", "answer": "The result of (491 - 728) is -237\n\n####-237", "a": 491, "b": 728, "operator": "-", "result": -237}
{"question": "Solve (714 - 40)", "answer": "The result of (714 - 40) is 674\n\n####674", "a": 714, "b": 40, "operator": "-", "result": 674}
{"question": "Solve (806 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (806 / 545) is 1.4789\n\n####1.4789", "a": 806, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4789}
{"question": "Solve (318 / 85)", "answer": "The result of (318 / 85) is 3.7412\n\n####3.7412", "a": 318, "b": 85, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7412}
{"question": "Solve (199 / 286)", "answer": "The result of (199 / 286) is 0.6958\n\n####0.6958", "a": 199, "b": 286, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6958}
{"question": "Solve (777 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (777 - 933) is -156\n\n####-156", "a": 777, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -156}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 717)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 717) is 1.3305\n\n####1.3305", "a": 954, "b": 717, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3305}
{"question": "Solve (919 + 3)", "answer": "The result of (919 + 3) is 922\n\n####922", "a": 919, "b": 3, "operator": "+", "result": 922}
{"question": "Solve (541 / 749)", "answer": "The result of (541 / 749) is 0.7223\n\n####0.7223", "a": 541, "b": 749, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7223}
{"question": "Solve (813 / 486)", "answer": "The result of (813 / 486) is 1.6728\n\n####1.6728", "a": 813, "b": 486, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6728}
{"question": "Solve (626 + 981)", "answer": "The result of (626 + 981) is 1607\n\n####1607", "a": 626, "b": 981, "operator": "+", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve (497 - 731)", "answer": "The result of (497 - 731) is -234\n\n####-234", "a": 497, "b": 731, "operator": "-", "result": -234}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 342) is -265\n\n####-265", "a": 77, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": -265}
{"question": "Solve (883 * 507)", "answer": "The result of (883 * 507) is 447681\n\n####447681", "a": 883, "b": 507, "operator": "*", "result": 447681}
{"question": "Solve (96 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (96 - 6) is 90\n\n####90", "a": 96, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 90}
{"question": "Solve (257 * 222)", "answer": "The result of (257 * 222) is 57054\n\n####57054", "a": 257, "b": 222, "operator": "*", "result": 57054}
{"question": "Solve (573 / 660)", "answer": "The result of (573 / 660) is 0.8682\n\n####0.8682", "a": 573, "b": 660, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8682}
{"question": "Solve (375 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (375 - 724) is -349\n\n####-349", "a": 375, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -349}
{"question": "Solve (684 * 931)", "answer": "The result of (684 * 931) is 636804\n\n####636804", "a": 684, "b": 931, "operator": "*", "result": 636804}
{"question": "Solve (113 / 593)", "answer": "The result of (113 / 593) is 0.1906\n\n####0.1906", "a": 113, "b": 593, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1906}
{"question": "Solve (122 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (122 / 427) is 0.2857\n\n####0.2857", "a": 122, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2857}
{"question": "Solve (885 * 704)", "answer": "The result of (885 * 704) is 623040\n\n####623040", "a": 885, "b": 704, "operator": "*", "result": 623040}
{"question": "Solve (60 * 954)", "answer": "The result of (60 * 954) is 57240\n\n####57240", "a": 60, "b": 954, "operator": "*", "result": 57240}
{"question": "Solve (832 * 808)", "answer": "The result of (832 * 808) is 672256\n\n####672256", "a": 832, "b": 808, "operator": "*", "result": 672256}
{"question": "Solve (11 - 217)", "answer": "The result of (11 - 217) is -206\n\n####-206", "a": 11, "b": 217, "operator": "-", "result": -206}
{"question": "Solve (416 * 109)", "answer": "The result of (416 * 109) is 45344\n\n####45344", "a": 416, "b": 109, "operator": "*", "result": 45344}
{"question": "Solve (674 * 546)", "answer": "The result of (674 * 546) is 368004\n\n####368004", "a": 674, "b": 546, "operator": "*", "result": 368004}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 390) is 1.2487\n\n####1.2487", "a": 487, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2487}
{"question": "Solve (158 * 708)", "answer": "The result of (158 * 708) is 111864\n\n####111864", "a": 158, "b": 708, "operator": "*", "result": 111864}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 193)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 193) is 131\n\n####131", "a": 324, "b": 193, "operator": "-", "result": 131}
{"question": "Solve (234 - 999)", "answer": "The result of (234 - 999) is -765\n\n####-765", "a": 234, "b": 999, "operator": "-", "result": -765}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 226)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 226) is 696\n\n####696", "a": 922, "b": 226, "operator": "-", "result": 696}
{"question": "Solve (494 / 270)", "answer": "The result of (494 / 270) is 1.8296\n\n####1.8296", "a": 494, "b": 270, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8296}
{"question": "Solve (153 * 388)", "answer": "The result of (153 * 388) is 59364\n\n####59364", "a": 153, "b": 388, "operator": "*", "result": 59364}
{"question": "Solve (190 + 247)", "answer": "The result of (190 + 247) is 437\n\n####437", "a": 190, "b": 247, "operator": "+", "result": 437}
{"question": "Solve (754 + 476)", "answer": "The result of (754 + 476) is 1230\n\n####1230", "a": 754, "b": 476, "operator": "+", "result": 1230}
{"question": "Solve (773 + 14)", "answer": "The result of (773 + 14) is 787\n\n####787", "a": 773, "b": 14, "operator": "+", "result": 787}
{"question": "Solve (97 - 302)", "answer": "The result of (97 - 302) is -205\n\n####-205", "a": 97, "b": 302, "operator": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve (612 - 142)", "answer": "The result of (612 - 142) is 470\n\n####470", "a": 612, "b": 142, "operator": "-", "result": 470}
{"question": "Solve (578 / 458)", "answer": "The result of (578 / 458) is 1.262\n\n####1.262", "a": 578, "b": 458, "operator": "/", "result": 1.262}
{"question": "Solve (955 / 528)", "answer": "The result of (955 / 528) is 1.8087\n\n####1.8087", "a": 955, "b": 528, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8087}
{"question": "Solve (549 * 688)", "answer": "The result of (549 * 688) is 377712\n\n####377712", "a": 549, "b": 688, "operator": "*", "result": 377712}
{"question": "Solve (289 + 791)", "answer": "The result of (289 + 791) is 1080\n\n####1080", "a": 289, "b": 791, "operator": "+", "result": 1080}
{"question": "Solve (913 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (913 * 357) is 325941\n\n####325941", "a": 913, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 325941}
{"question": "Solve (712 - 617)", "answer": "The result of (712 - 617) is 95\n\n####95", "a": 712, "b": 617, "operator": "-", "result": 95}
{"question": "Solve (154 / 890)", "answer": "The result of (154 / 890) is 0.173\n\n####0.173", "a": 154, "b": 890, "operator": "/", "result": 0.173}
{"question": "Solve (784 + 253)", "answer": "The result of (784 + 253) is 1037\n\n####1037", "a": 784, "b": 253, "operator": "+", "result": 1037}
{"question": "Solve (428 / 324)", "answer": "The result of (428 / 324) is 1.321\n\n####1.321", "a": 428, "b": 324, "operator": "/", "result": 1.321}
{"question": "Solve (71 * 413)", "answer": "The result of (71 * 413) is 29323\n\n####29323", "a": 71, "b": 413, "operator": "*", "result": 29323}
{"question": "Solve (706 - 251)", "answer": "The result of (706 - 251) is 455\n\n####455", "a": 706, "b": 251, "operator": "-", "result": 455}
{"question": "Solve (734 + 799)", "answer": "The result of (734 + 799) is 1533\n\n####1533", "a": 734, "b": 799, "operator": "+", "result": 1533}
{"question": "Solve (86 + 741)", "answer": "The result of (86 + 741) is 827\n\n####827", "a": 86, "b": 741, "operator": "+", "result": 827}
{"question": "Solve (654 * 442)", "answer": "The result of (654 * 442) is 289068\n\n####289068", "a": 654, "b": 442, "operator": "*", "result": 289068}
{"question": "Solve (160 - 735)", "answer": "The result of (160 - 735) is -575\n\n####-575", "a": 160, "b": 735, "operator": "-", "result": -575}
{"question": "Solve (544 - 774)", "answer": "The result of (544 - 774) is -230\n\n####-230", "a": 544, "b": 774, "operator": "-", "result": -230}
{"question": "Solve (115 * 365)", "answer": "The result of (115 * 365) is 41975\n\n####41975", "a": 115, "b": 365, "operator": "*", "result": 41975}
{"question": "Solve (319 / 919)", "answer": "The result of (319 / 919) is 0.3471\n\n####0.3471", "a": 319, "b": 919, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3471}
{"question": "Solve (129 + 976)", "answer": "The result of (129 + 976) is 1105\n\n####1105", "a": 129, "b": 976, "operator": "+", "result": 1105}
{"question": "Solve (695 / 589)", "answer": "The result of (695 / 589) is 1.18\n\n####1.18", "a": 695, "b": 589, "operator": "/", "result": 1.18}
{"question": "Solve (556 - 31)", "answer": "The result of (556 - 31) is 525\n\n####525", "a": 556, "b": 31, "operator": "-", "result": 525}
{"question": "Solve (866 * 704)", "answer": "The result of (866 * 704) is 609664\n\n####609664", "a": 866, "b": 704, "operator": "*", "result": 609664}
{"question": "Solve (462 / 394)", "answer": "The result of (462 / 394) is 1.1726\n\n####1.1726", "a": 462, "b": 394, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1726}
{"question": "Solve (124 / 274)", "answer": "The result of (124 / 274) is 0.4526\n\n####0.4526", "a": 124, "b": 274, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4526}
{"question": "Solve (483 * 554)", "answer": "The result of (483 * 554) is 267582\n\n####267582", "a": 483, "b": 554, "operator": "*", "result": 267582}
{"question": "Solve (614 * 171)", "answer": "The result of (614 * 171) is 104994\n\n####104994", "a": 614, "b": 171, "operator": "*", "result": 104994}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 63)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 63) is 800\n\n####800", "a": 863, "b": 63, "operator": "-", "result": 800}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 381)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 381) is 595\n\n####595", "a": 976, "b": 381, "operator": "-", "result": 595}
{"question": "Solve (928 + 17)", "answer": "The result of (928 + 17) is 945\n\n####945", "a": 928, "b": 17, "operator": "+", "result": 945}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 130)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 130) is 46930\n\n####46930", "a": 361, "b": 130, "operator": "*", "result": 46930}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 864)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 864) is 487296\n\n####487296", "a": 564, "b": 864, "operator": "*", "result": 487296}
{"question": "Solve (575 - 97)", "answer": "The result of (575 - 97) is 478\n\n####478", "a": 575, "b": 97, "operator": "-", "result": 478}
{"question": "Solve (356 + 598)", "answer": "The result of (356 + 598) is 954\n\n####954", "a": 356, "b": 598, "operator": "+", "result": 954}
{"question": "Solve (98 - 875)", "answer": "The result of (98 - 875) is -777\n\n####-777", "a": 98, "b": 875, "operator": "-", "result": -777}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 642)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 642) is 151512\n\n####151512", "a": 236, "b": 642, "operator": "*", "result": 151512}
{"question": "Solve (959 / 147)", "answer": "The result of (959 / 147) is 6.5238\n\n####6.5238", "a": 959, "b": 147, "operator": "/", "result": 6.5238}
{"question": "Solve (135 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (135 - 452) is -317\n\n####-317", "a": 135, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": -317}
{"question": "Solve (770 + 393)", "answer": "The result of (770 + 393) is 1163\n\n####1163", "a": 770, "b": 393, "operator": "+", "result": 1163}
{"question": "Solve (21 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (21 - 496) is -475\n\n####-475", "a": 21, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": -475}
{"question": "Solve (443 - 255)", "answer": "The result of (443 - 255) is 188\n\n####188", "a": 443, "b": 255, "operator": "-", "result": 188}
{"question": "Solve (862 / 362)", "answer": "The result of (862 / 362) is 2.3812\n\n####2.3812", "a": 862, "b": 362, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3812}
{"question": "Solve (564 / 906)", "answer": "The result of (564 / 906) is 0.6225\n\n####0.6225", "a": 564, "b": 906, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6225}
{"question": "Solve (211 * 272)", "answer": "The result of (211 * 272) is 57392\n\n####57392", "a": 211, "b": 272, "operator": "*", "result": 57392}
{"question": "Solve (636 + 260)", "answer": "The result of (636 + 260) is 896\n\n####896", "a": 636, "b": 260, "operator": "+", "result": 896}
{"question": "Solve (546 / 586)", "answer": "The result of (546 / 586) is 0.9317\n\n####0.9317", "a": 546, "b": 586, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9317}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 110)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 110) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 512, "b": 110, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (419 - 677)", "answer": "The result of (419 - 677) is -258\n\n####-258", "a": 419, "b": 677, "operator": "-", "result": -258}
{"question": "Solve (143 * 915)", "answer": "The result of (143 * 915) is 130845\n\n####130845", "a": 143, "b": 915, "operator": "*", "result": 130845}
{"question": "Solve (880 - 315)", "answer": "The result of (880 - 315) is 565\n\n####565", "a": 880, "b": 315, "operator": "-", "result": 565}
{"question": "Solve (292 * 450)", "answer": "The result of (292 * 450) is 131400\n\n####131400", "a": 292, "b": 450, "operator": "*", "result": 131400}
{"question": "Solve (535 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (535 - 2) is 533\n\n####533", "a": 535, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 533}
{"question": "Solve (825 + 636)", "answer": "The result of (825 + 636) is 1461\n\n####1461", "a": 825, "b": 636, "operator": "+", "result": 1461}
{"question": "Solve (278 - 237)", "answer": "The result of (278 - 237) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 278, "b": 237, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (454 + 773)", "answer": "The result of (454 + 773) is 1227\n\n####1227", "a": 454, "b": 773, "operator": "+", "result": 1227}
{"question": "Solve (399 * 269)", "answer": "The result of (399 * 269) is 107331\n\n####107331", "a": 399, "b": 269, "operator": "*", "result": 107331}
{"question": "Solve (832 + 561)", "answer": "The result of (832 + 561) is 1393\n\n####1393", "a": 832, "b": 561, "operator": "+", "result": 1393}
{"question": "Solve (814 + 861)", "answer": "The result of (814 + 861) is 1675\n\n####1675", "a": 814, "b": 861, "operator": "+", "result": 1675}
{"question": "Solve (848 + 749)", "answer": "The result of (848 + 749) is 1597\n\n####1597", "a": 848, "b": 749, "operator": "+", "result": 1597}
{"question": "Solve (446 * 674)", "answer": "The result of (446 * 674) is 300604\n\n####300604", "a": 446, "b": 674, "operator": "*", "result": 300604}
{"question": "Solve (232 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (232 * 387) is 89784\n\n####89784", "a": 232, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 89784}
{"question": "Solve (869 + 8)", "answer": "The result of (869 + 8) is 877\n\n####877", "a": 869, "b": 8, "operator": "+", "result": 877}
{"question": "Solve (823 - 255)", "answer": "The result of (823 - 255) is 568\n\n####568", "a": 823, "b": 255, "operator": "-", "result": 568}
{"question": "Solve (580 + 47)", "answer": "The result of (580 + 47) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 580, "b": 47, "operator": "+", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (791 * 738)", "answer": "The result of (791 * 738) is 583758\n\n####583758", "a": 791, "b": 738, "operator": "*", "result": 583758}
{"question": "Solve (677 - 467)", "answer": "The result of (677 - 467) is 210\n\n####210", "a": 677, "b": 467, "operator": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve (288 - 304)", "answer": "The result of (288 - 304) is -16\n\n####-16", "a": 288, "b": 304, "operator": "-", "result": -16}
{"question": "Solve (269 - 421)", "answer": "The result of (269 - 421) is -152\n\n####-152", "a": 269, "b": 421, "operator": "-", "result": -152}
{"question": "Solve (416 * 101)", "answer": "The result of (416 * 101) is 42016\n\n####42016", "a": 416, "b": 101, "operator": "*", "result": 42016}
{"question": "Solve (418 - 530)", "answer": "The result of (418 - 530) is -112\n\n####-112", "a": 418, "b": 530, "operator": "-", "result": -112}
{"question": "Solve (918 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (918 - 233) is 685\n\n####685", "a": 918, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": 685}
{"question": "Solve (332 * 989)", "answer": "The result of (332 * 989) is 328348\n\n####328348", "a": 332, "b": 989, "operator": "*", "result": 328348}
{"question": "Solve (914 - 479)", "answer": "The result of (914 - 479) is 435\n\n####435", "a": 914, "b": 479, "operator": "-", "result": 435}
{"question": "Solve (501 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (501 + 380) is 881\n\n####881", "a": 501, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 881}
{"question": "Solve (692 / 597)", "answer": "The result of (692 / 597) is 1.1591\n\n####1.1591", "a": 692, "b": 597, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1591}
{"question": "Solve (861 + 82)", "answer": "The result of (861 + 82) is 943\n\n####943", "a": 861, "b": 82, "operator": "+", "result": 943}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 108)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 108) is 741\n\n####741", "a": 849, "b": 108, "operator": "-", "result": 741}
{"question": "Solve (327 / 379)", "answer": "The result of (327 / 379) is 0.8628\n\n####0.8628", "a": 327, "b": 379, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8628}
{"question": "Solve (669 + 948)", "answer": "The result of (669 + 948) is 1617\n\n####1617", "a": 669, "b": 948, "operator": "+", "result": 1617}
{"question": "Solve (855 - 423)", "answer": "The result of (855 - 423) is 432\n\n####432", "a": 855, "b": 423, "operator": "-", "result": 432}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 701)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 701) is 979\n\n####979", "a": 278, "b": 701, "operator": "+", "result": 979}
{"question": "Solve (711 - 748)", "answer": "The result of (711 - 748) is -37\n\n####-37", "a": 711, "b": 748, "operator": "-", "result": -37}
{"question": "Solve (939 + 29)", "answer": "The result of (939 + 29) is 968\n\n####968", "a": 939, "b": 29, "operator": "+", "result": 968}
{"question": "Solve (541 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (541 - 647) is -106\n\n####-106", "a": 541, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": -106}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 110)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 110) is 9790\n\n####9790", "a": 89, "b": 110, "operator": "*", "result": 9790}
{"question": "Solve (212 - 875)", "answer": "The result of (212 - 875) is -663\n\n####-663", "a": 212, "b": 875, "operator": "-", "result": -663}
{"question": "Solve (464 / 242)", "answer": "The result of (464 / 242) is 1.9174\n\n####1.9174", "a": 464, "b": 242, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9174}
{"question": "Solve (13 * 617)", "answer": "The result of (13 * 617) is 8021\n\n####8021", "a": 13, "b": 617, "operator": "*", "result": 8021}
{"question": "Solve (487 - 640)", "answer": "The result of (487 - 640) is -153\n\n####-153", "a": 487, "b": 640, "operator": "-", "result": -153}
{"question": "Solve (12 + 5)", "answer": "The result of (12 + 5) is 17\n\n####17", "a": 12, "b": 5, "operator": "+", "result": 17}
{"question": "Solve (259 * 654)", "answer": "The result of (259 * 654) is 169386\n\n####169386", "a": 259, "b": 654, "operator": "*", "result": 169386}
{"question": "Solve (467 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (467 - 547) is -80\n\n####-80", "a": 467, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve (472 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (472 - 408) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 472, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (582 * 160)", "answer": "The result of (582 * 160) is 93120\n\n####93120", "a": 582, "b": 160, "operator": "*", "result": 93120}
{"question": "Solve (787 - 723)", "answer": "The result of (787 - 723) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 787, "b": 723, "operator": "-", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (429 * 268)", "answer": "The result of (429 * 268) is 114972\n\n####114972", "a": 429, "b": 268, "operator": "*", "result": 114972}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 792)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 792) is -431\n\n####-431", "a": 361, "b": 792, "operator": "-", "result": -431}
{"question": "Solve (272 - 389)", "answer": "The result of (272 - 389) is -117\n\n####-117", "a": 272, "b": 389, "operator": "-", "result": -117}
{"question": "Solve (610 * 389)", "answer": "The result of (610 * 389) is 237290\n\n####237290", "a": 610, "b": 389, "operator": "*", "result": 237290}
{"question": "Solve (858 / 698)", "answer": "The result of (858 / 698) is 1.2292\n\n####1.2292", "a": 858, "b": 698, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2292}
{"question": "Solve (57 / 758)", "answer": "The result of (57 / 758) is 0.0752\n\n####0.0752", "a": 57, "b": 758, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0752}
{"question": "Solve (603 * 593)", "answer": "The result of (603 * 593) is 357579\n\n####357579", "a": 603, "b": 593, "operator": "*", "result": 357579}
{"question": "Solve (884 + 526)", "answer": "The result of (884 + 526) is 1410\n\n####1410", "a": 884, "b": 526, "operator": "+", "result": 1410}
{"question": "Solve (157 * 541)", "answer": "The result of (157 * 541) is 84937\n\n####84937", "a": 157, "b": 541, "operator": "*", "result": 84937}
{"question": "Solve (949 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (949 / 768) is 1.2357\n\n####1.2357", "a": 949, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2357}
{"question": "Solve (214 - 633)", "answer": "The result of (214 - 633) is -419\n\n####-419", "a": 214, "b": 633, "operator": "-", "result": -419}
{"question": "Solve (363 / 392)", "answer": "The result of (363 / 392) is 0.926\n\n####0.926", "a": 363, "b": 392, "operator": "/", "result": 0.926}
{"question": "Solve (824 - 136)", "answer": "The result of (824 - 136) is 688\n\n####688", "a": 824, "b": 136, "operator": "-", "result": 688}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 244)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 244) is 151280\n\n####151280", "a": 620, "b": 244, "operator": "*", "result": 151280}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 642)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 642) is 85386\n\n####85386", "a": 133, "b": 642, "operator": "*", "result": 85386}
{"question": "Solve (196 * 288)", "answer": "The result of (196 * 288) is 56448\n\n####56448", "a": 196, "b": 288, "operator": "*", "result": 56448}
{"question": "Solve (974 * 454)", "answer": "The result of (974 * 454) is 442196\n\n####442196", "a": 974, "b": 454, "operator": "*", "result": 442196}
{"question": "Solve (310 + 109)", "answer": "The result of (310 + 109) is 419\n\n####419", "a": 310, "b": 109, "operator": "+", "result": 419}
{"question": "Solve (59 - 963)", "answer": "The result of (59 - 963) is -904\n\n####-904", "a": 59, "b": 963, "operator": "-", "result": -904}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 140)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 140) is 6.65\n\n####6.65", "a": 931, "b": 140, "operator": "/", "result": 6.65}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 30)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 30) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 130, "b": 30, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (560 - 786)", "answer": "The result of (560 - 786) is -226\n\n####-226", "a": 560, "b": 786, "operator": "-", "result": -226}
{"question": "Solve (150 - 639)", "answer": "The result of (150 - 639) is -489\n\n####-489", "a": 150, "b": 639, "operator": "-", "result": -489}
{"question": "Solve (474 + 994)", "answer": "The result of (474 + 994) is 1468\n\n####1468", "a": 474, "b": 994, "operator": "+", "result": 1468}
{"question": "Solve (561 * 569)", "answer": "The result of (561 * 569) is 319209\n\n####319209", "a": 561, "b": 569, "operator": "*", "result": 319209}
{"question": "Solve (544 / 408)", "answer": "The result of (544 / 408) is 1.3333\n\n####1.3333", "a": 544, "b": 408, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3333}
{"question": "Solve (268 - 155)", "answer": "The result of (268 - 155) is 113\n\n####113", "a": 268, "b": 155, "operator": "-", "result": 113}
{"question": "Solve (654 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (654 / 240) is 2.725\n\n####2.725", "a": 654, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 2.725}
{"question": "Solve (159 + 49)", "answer": "The result of (159 + 49) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 159, "b": 49, "operator": "+", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (259 / 381)", "answer": "The result of (259 / 381) is 0.6798\n\n####0.6798", "a": 259, "b": 381, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6798}
{"question": "Solve (976 * 833)", "answer": "The result of (976 * 833) is 813008\n\n####813008", "a": 976, "b": 833, "operator": "*", "result": 813008}
{"question": "Solve (653 + 103)", "answer": "The result of (653 + 103) is 756\n\n####756", "a": 653, "b": 103, "operator": "+", "result": 756}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 741)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 741) is 74841\n\n####74841", "a": 101, "b": 741, "operator": "*", "result": 74841}
{"question": "Solve (24 * 358)", "answer": "The result of (24 * 358) is 8592\n\n####8592", "a": 24, "b": 358, "operator": "*", "result": 8592}
{"question": "Solve (817 - 188)", "answer": "The result of (817 - 188) is 629\n\n####629", "a": 817, "b": 188, "operator": "-", "result": 629}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 432)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 432) is 334800\n\n####334800", "a": 775, "b": 432, "operator": "*", "result": 334800}
{"question": "Solve (589 * 600)", "answer": "The result of (589 * 600) is 353400\n\n####353400", "a": 589, "b": 600, "operator": "*", "result": 353400}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 835)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 835) is 1281\n\n####1281", "a": 446, "b": 835, "operator": "+", "result": 1281}
{"question": "Solve (972 - 272)", "answer": "The result of (972 - 272) is 700\n\n####700", "a": 972, "b": 272, "operator": "-", "result": 700}
{"question": "Solve (732 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (732 / 300) is 2.44\n\n####2.44", "a": 732, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 2.44}
{"question": "Solve (492 * 491)", "answer": "The result of (492 * 491) is 241572\n\n####241572", "a": 492, "b": 491, "operator": "*", "result": 241572}
{"question": "Solve (868 / 512)", "answer": "The result of (868 / 512) is 1.6953\n\n####1.6953", "a": 868, "b": 512, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6953}
{"question": "Solve (32 + 501)", "answer": "The result of (32 + 501) is 533\n\n####533", "a": 32, "b": 501, "operator": "+", "result": 533}
{"question": "Solve (275 + 626)", "answer": "The result of (275 + 626) is 901\n\n####901", "a": 275, "b": 626, "operator": "+", "result": 901}
{"question": "Solve (233 * 994)", "answer": "The result of (233 * 994) is 231602\n\n####231602", "a": 233, "b": 994, "operator": "*", "result": 231602}
{"question": "Solve (302 - 150)", "answer": "The result of (302 - 150) is 152\n\n####152", "a": 302, "b": 150, "operator": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 525)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 525) is -473\n\n####-473", "a": 52, "b": 525, "operator": "-", "result": -473}
{"question": "Solve (96 + 310)", "answer": "The result of (96 + 310) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 96, "b": 310, "operator": "+", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (395 / 713)", "answer": "The result of (395 / 713) is 0.554\n\n####0.554", "a": 395, "b": 713, "operator": "/", "result": 0.554}
{"question": "Solve (166 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (166 - 261) is -95\n\n####-95", "a": 166, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": -95}
{"question": "Solve (317 + 188)", "answer": "The result of (317 + 188) is 505\n\n####505", "a": 317, "b": 188, "operator": "+", "result": 505}
{"question": "Solve (288 * 616)", "answer": "The result of (288 * 616) is 177408\n\n####177408", "a": 288, "b": 616, "operator": "*", "result": 177408}
{"question": "Solve (231 - 414)", "answer": "The result of (231 - 414) is -183\n\n####-183", "a": 231, "b": 414, "operator": "-", "result": -183}
{"question": "Solve (244 / 601)", "answer": "The result of (244 / 601) is 0.406\n\n####0.406", "a": 244, "b": 601, "operator": "/", "result": 0.406}
{"question": "Solve (459 + 998)", "answer": "The result of (459 + 998) is 1457\n\n####1457", "a": 459, "b": 998, "operator": "+", "result": 1457}
{"question": "Solve (198 / 373)", "answer": "The result of (198 / 373) is 0.5308\n\n####0.5308", "a": 198, "b": 373, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5308}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 400) is 144400\n\n####144400", "a": 361, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 144400}
{"question": "Solve (295 - 785)", "answer": "The result of (295 - 785) is -490\n\n####-490", "a": 295, "b": 785, "operator": "-", "result": -490}
{"question": "Solve (850 + 744)", "answer": "The result of (850 + 744) is 1594\n\n####1594", "a": 850, "b": 744, "operator": "+", "result": 1594}
{"question": "Solve (712 - 97)", "answer": "The result of (712 - 97) is 615\n\n####615", "a": 712, "b": 97, "operator": "-", "result": 615}
{"question": "Solve (207 - 965)", "answer": "The result of (207 - 965) is -758\n\n####-758", "a": 207, "b": 965, "operator": "-", "result": -758}
{"question": "Solve (612 * 657)", "answer": "The result of (612 * 657) is 402084\n\n####402084", "a": 612, "b": 657, "operator": "*", "result": 402084}
{"question": "Solve (790 * 221)", "answer": "The result of (790 * 221) is 174590\n\n####174590", "a": 790, "b": 221, "operator": "*", "result": 174590}
{"question": "Solve (282 * 871)", "answer": "The result of (282 * 871) is 245622\n\n####245622", "a": 282, "b": 871, "operator": "*", "result": 245622}
{"question": "Solve (817 / 801)", "answer": "The result of (817 / 801) is 1.02\n\n####1.02", "a": 817, "b": 801, "operator": "/", "result": 1.02}
{"question": "Solve (122 * 767)", "answer": "The result of (122 * 767) is 93574\n\n####93574", "a": 122, "b": 767, "operator": "*", "result": 93574}
{"question": "Solve (234 - 789)", "answer": "The result of (234 - 789) is -555\n\n####-555", "a": 234, "b": 789, "operator": "-", "result": -555}
{"question": "Solve (328 - 789)", "answer": "The result of (328 - 789) is -461\n\n####-461", "a": 328, "b": 789, "operator": "-", "result": -461}
{"question": "Solve (719 / 358)", "answer": "The result of (719 / 358) is 2.0084\n\n####2.0084", "a": 719, "b": 358, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0084}
{"question": "Solve (711 + 194)", "answer": "The result of (711 + 194) is 905\n\n####905", "a": 711, "b": 194, "operator": "+", "result": 905}
{"question": "Solve (578 * 547)", "answer": "The result of (578 * 547) is 316166\n\n####316166", "a": 578, "b": 547, "operator": "*", "result": 316166}
{"question": "Solve (983 / 112)", "answer": "The result of (983 / 112) is 8.7768\n\n####8.7768", "a": 983, "b": 112, "operator": "/", "result": 8.7768}
{"question": "Solve (963 + 807)", "answer": "The result of (963 + 807) is 1770\n\n####1770", "a": 963, "b": 807, "operator": "+", "result": 1770}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 593)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 593) is 1.6088\n\n####1.6088", "a": 954, "b": 593, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6088}
{"question": "Solve (536 - 516)", "answer": "The result of (536 - 516) is 20\n\n####20", "a": 536, "b": 516, "operator": "-", "result": 20}
{"question": "Solve (433 / 116)", "answer": "The result of (433 / 116) is 3.7328\n\n####3.7328", "a": 433, "b": 116, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7328}
{"question": "Solve (622 / 100)", "answer": "The result of (622 / 100) is 6.22\n\n####6.22", "a": 622, "b": 100, "operator": "/", "result": 6.22}
{"question": "Solve (254 + 219)", "answer": "The result of (254 + 219) is 473\n\n####473", "a": 254, "b": 219, "operator": "+", "result": 473}
{"question": "Solve (404 + 148)", "answer": "The result of (404 + 148) is 552\n\n####552", "a": 404, "b": 148, "operator": "+", "result": 552}
{"question": "Solve (230 - 934)", "answer": "The result of (230 - 934) is -704\n\n####-704", "a": 230, "b": 934, "operator": "-", "result": -704}
{"question": "Solve (997 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (997 * 897) is 894309\n\n####894309", "a": 997, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 894309}
{"question": "Solve (717 * 454)", "answer": "The result of (717 * 454) is 325518\n\n####325518", "a": 717, "b": 454, "operator": "*", "result": 325518}
{"question": "Solve (881 * 152)", "answer": "The result of (881 * 152) is 133912\n\n####133912", "a": 881, "b": 152, "operator": "*", "result": 133912}
{"question": "Solve (499 - 721)", "answer": "The result of (499 - 721) is -222\n\n####-222", "a": 499, "b": 721, "operator": "-", "result": -222}
{"question": "Solve (538 / 749)", "answer": "The result of (538 / 749) is 0.7183\n\n####0.7183", "a": 538, "b": 749, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7183}
{"question": "Solve (376 * 889)", "answer": "The result of (376 * 889) is 334264\n\n####334264", "a": 376, "b": 889, "operator": "*", "result": 334264}
{"question": "Solve (607 - 957)", "answer": "The result of (607 - 957) is -350\n\n####-350", "a": 607, "b": 957, "operator": "-", "result": -350}
{"question": "Solve (976 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (976 * 762) is 743712\n\n####743712", "a": 976, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 743712}
{"question": "Solve (432 * 353)", "answer": "The result of (432 * 353) is 152496\n\n####152496", "a": 432, "b": 353, "operator": "*", "result": 152496}
{"question": "Solve (886 / 420)", "answer": "The result of (886 / 420) is 2.1095\n\n####2.1095", "a": 886, "b": 420, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1095}
{"question": "Solve (961 + 37)", "answer": "The result of (961 + 37) is 998\n\n####998", "a": 961, "b": 37, "operator": "+", "result": 998}
{"question": "Solve (752 / 762)", "answer": "The result of (752 / 762) is 0.9869\n\n####0.9869", "a": 752, "b": 762, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9869}
{"question": "Solve (74 * 323)", "answer": "The result of (74 * 323) is 23902\n\n####23902", "a": 74, "b": 323, "operator": "*", "result": 23902}
{"question": "Solve (223 + 354)", "answer": "The result of (223 + 354) is 577\n\n####577", "a": 223, "b": 354, "operator": "+", "result": 577}
{"question": "Solve (318 * 384)", "answer": "The result of (318 * 384) is 122112\n\n####122112", "a": 318, "b": 384, "operator": "*", "result": 122112}
{"question": "Solve (34 * 993)", "answer": "The result of (34 * 993) is 33762\n\n####33762", "a": 34, "b": 993, "operator": "*", "result": 33762}
{"question": "Solve (801 - 517)", "answer": "The result of (801 - 517) is 284\n\n####284", "a": 801, "b": 517, "operator": "-", "result": 284}
{"question": "Solve (253 - 642)", "answer": "The result of (253 - 642) is -389\n\n####-389", "a": 253, "b": 642, "operator": "-", "result": -389}
{"question": "Solve (966 + 187)", "answer": "The result of (966 + 187) is 1153\n\n####1153", "a": 966, "b": 187, "operator": "+", "result": 1153}
{"question": "Solve (460 - 360)", "answer": "The result of (460 - 360) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 460, "b": 360, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (238 - 761)", "answer": "The result of (238 - 761) is -523\n\n####-523", "a": 238, "b": 761, "operator": "-", "result": -523}
{"question": "Solve (101 - 669)", "answer": "The result of (101 - 669) is -568\n\n####-568", "a": 101, "b": 669, "operator": "-", "result": -568}
{"question": "Solve (278 * 459)", "answer": "The result of (278 * 459) is 127602\n\n####127602", "a": 278, "b": 459, "operator": "*", "result": 127602}
{"question": "Solve (110 / 208)", "answer": "The result of (110 / 208) is 0.5288\n\n####0.5288", "a": 110, "b": 208, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5288}
{"question": "Solve (532 - 128)", "answer": "The result of (532 - 128) is 404\n\n####404", "a": 532, "b": 128, "operator": "-", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve (793 * 310)", "answer": "The result of (793 * 310) is 245830\n\n####245830", "a": 793, "b": 310, "operator": "*", "result": 245830}
{"question": "Solve (599 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (599 - 184) is 415\n\n####415", "a": 599, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 415}
{"question": "Solve (191 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (191 - 779) is -588\n\n####-588", "a": 191, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": -588}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 557)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 557) is 118084\n\n####118084", "a": 212, "b": 557, "operator": "*", "result": 118084}
{"question": "Solve (809 - 57)", "answer": "The result of (809 - 57) is 752\n\n####752", "a": 809, "b": 57, "operator": "-", "result": 752}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 969)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 969) is 583338\n\n####583338", "a": 602, "b": 969, "operator": "*", "result": 583338}
{"question": "Solve (933 / 714)", "answer": "The result of (933 / 714) is 1.3067\n\n####1.3067", "a": 933, "b": 714, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3067}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 402)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 402) is -272\n\n####-272", "a": 130, "b": 402, "operator": "-", "result": -272}
{"question": "Solve (435 - 783)", "answer": "The result of (435 - 783) is -348\n\n####-348", "a": 435, "b": 783, "operator": "-", "result": -348}
{"question": "Solve (324 * 219)", "answer": "The result of (324 * 219) is 70956\n\n####70956", "a": 324, "b": 219, "operator": "*", "result": 70956}
{"question": "Solve (72 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (72 - 724) is -652\n\n####-652", "a": 72, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -652}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 71)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 71) is 381\n\n####381", "a": 452, "b": 71, "operator": "-", "result": 381}
{"question": "Solve (398 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (398 - 321) is 77\n\n####77", "a": 398, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve (809 * 245)", "answer": "The result of (809 * 245) is 198205\n\n####198205", "a": 809, "b": 245, "operator": "*", "result": 198205}
{"question": "Solve (915 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (915 - 238) is 677\n\n####677", "a": 915, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 677}
{"question": "Solve (385 + 966)", "answer": "The result of (385 + 966) is 1351\n\n####1351", "a": 385, "b": 966, "operator": "+", "result": 1351}
{"question": "Solve (705 + 365)", "answer": "The result of (705 + 365) is 1070\n\n####1070", "a": 705, "b": 365, "operator": "+", "result": 1070}
{"question": "Solve (215 + 789)", "answer": "The result of (215 + 789) is 1004\n\n####1004", "a": 215, "b": 789, "operator": "+", "result": 1004}
{"question": "Solve (749 * 420)", "answer": "The result of (749 * 420) is 314580\n\n####314580", "a": 749, "b": 420, "operator": "*", "result": 314580}
{"question": "Solve (53 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (53 - 317) is -264\n\n####-264", "a": 53, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": -264}
{"question": "Solve (61 * 144)", "answer": "The result of (61 * 144) is 8784\n\n####8784", "a": 61, "b": 144, "operator": "*", "result": 8784}
{"question": "Solve (894 * 240)", "answer": "The result of (894 * 240) is 214560\n\n####214560", "a": 894, "b": 240, "operator": "*", "result": 214560}
{"question": "Solve (753 / 8)", "answer": "The result of (753 / 8) is 94.125\n\n####94.125", "a": 753, "b": 8, "operator": "/", "result": 94.125}
{"question": "Solve (794 / 890)", "answer": "The result of (794 / 890) is 0.8921\n\n####0.8921", "a": 794, "b": 890, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8921}
{"question": "Solve (478 + 49)", "answer": "The result of (478 + 49) is 527\n\n####527", "a": 478, "b": 49, "operator": "+", "result": 527}
{"question": "Solve (405 * 219)", "answer": "The result of (405 * 219) is 88695\n\n####88695", "a": 405, "b": 219, "operator": "*", "result": 88695}
{"question": "Solve (788 + 970)", "answer": "The result of (788 + 970) is 1758\n\n####1758", "a": 788, "b": 970, "operator": "+", "result": 1758}
{"question": "Solve (892 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (892 - 238) is 654\n\n####654", "a": 892, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 654}
{"question": "Solve (798 / 964)", "answer": "The result of (798 / 964) is 0.8278\n\n####0.8278", "a": 798, "b": 964, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8278}
{"question": "Solve (906 + 435)", "answer": "The result of (906 + 435) is 1341\n\n####1341", "a": 906, "b": 435, "operator": "+", "result": 1341}
{"question": "Solve (470 - 539)", "answer": "The result of (470 - 539) is -69\n\n####-69", "a": 470, "b": 539, "operator": "-", "result": -69}
{"question": "Solve (639 - 450)", "answer": "The result of (639 - 450) is 189\n\n####189", "a": 639, "b": 450, "operator": "-", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve (365 - 975)", "answer": "The result of (365 - 975) is -610\n\n####-610", "a": 365, "b": 975, "operator": "-", "result": -610}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 329)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 329) is 0.462\n\n####0.462", "a": 152, "b": 329, "operator": "/", "result": 0.462}
{"question": "Solve (895 - 149)", "answer": "The result of (895 - 149) is 746\n\n####746", "a": 895, "b": 149, "operator": "-", "result": 746}
{"question": "Solve (943 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (943 / 385) is 2.4494\n\n####2.4494", "a": 943, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4494}
{"question": "Solve (160 - 397)", "answer": "The result of (160 - 397) is -237\n\n####-237", "a": 160, "b": 397, "operator": "-", "result": -237}
{"question": "Solve (111 / 25)", "answer": "The result of (111 / 25) is 4.44\n\n####4.44", "a": 111, "b": 25, "operator": "/", "result": 4.44}
{"question": "Solve (473 / 956)", "answer": "The result of (473 / 956) is 0.4948\n\n####0.4948", "a": 473, "b": 956, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4948}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 727)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 727) is 101\n\n####101", "a": 828, "b": 727, "operator": "-", "result": 101}
{"question": "Solve (511 + 320)", "answer": "The result of (511 + 320) is 831\n\n####831", "a": 511, "b": 320, "operator": "+", "result": 831}
{"question": "Solve (484 - 681)", "answer": "The result of (484 - 681) is -197\n\n####-197", "a": 484, "b": 681, "operator": "-", "result": -197}
{"question": "Solve (721 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (721 * 911) is 656831\n\n####656831", "a": 721, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 656831}
{"question": "Solve (221 + 207)", "answer": "The result of (221 + 207) is 428\n\n####428", "a": 221, "b": 207, "operator": "+", "result": 428}
{"question": "Solve (788 * 832)", "answer": "The result of (788 * 832) is 655616\n\n####655616", "a": 788, "b": 832, "operator": "*", "result": 655616}
{"question": "Solve (615 / 822)", "answer": "The result of (615 / 822) is 0.7482\n\n####0.7482", "a": 615, "b": 822, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7482}
{"question": "Solve (438 + 602)", "answer": "The result of (438 + 602) is 1040\n\n####1040", "a": 438, "b": 602, "operator": "+", "result": 1040}
{"question": "Solve (60 - 157)", "answer": "The result of (60 - 157) is -97\n\n####-97", "a": 60, "b": 157, "operator": "-", "result": -97}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 933) is -540\n\n####-540", "a": 393, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -540}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 225)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 225) is 135450\n\n####135450", "a": 602, "b": 225, "operator": "*", "result": 135450}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 408) is 522\n\n####522", "a": 930, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": 522}
{"question": "Solve (79 + 585)", "answer": "The result of (79 + 585) is 664\n\n####664", "a": 79, "b": 585, "operator": "+", "result": 664}
{"question": "Solve (403 * 99)", "answer": "The result of (403 * 99) is 39897\n\n####39897", "a": 403, "b": 99, "operator": "*", "result": 39897}
{"question": "Solve (529 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (529 - 943) is -414\n\n####-414", "a": 529, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -414}
{"question": "Solve (297 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (297 * 175) is 51975\n\n####51975", "a": 297, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 51975}
{"question": "Solve (746 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (746 * 780) is 581880\n\n####581880", "a": 746, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 581880}
{"question": "Solve (462 - 200)", "answer": "The result of (462 - 200) is 262\n\n####262", "a": 462, "b": 200, "operator": "-", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve (90 / 501)", "answer": "The result of (90 / 501) is 0.1796\n\n####0.1796", "a": 90, "b": 501, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1796}
{"question": "Solve (378 * 923)", "answer": "The result of (378 * 923) is 348894\n\n####348894", "a": 378, "b": 923, "operator": "*", "result": 348894}
{"question": "Solve (926 / 131)", "answer": "The result of (926 / 131) is 7.0687\n\n####7.0687", "a": 926, "b": 131, "operator": "/", "result": 7.0687}
{"question": "Solve (466 / 200)", "answer": "The result of (466 / 200) is 2.33\n\n####2.33", "a": 466, "b": 200, "operator": "/", "result": 2.33}
{"question": "Solve (369 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (369 - 512) is -143\n\n####-143", "a": 369, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": -143}
{"question": "Solve (513 * 106)", "answer": "The result of (513 * 106) is 54378\n\n####54378", "a": 513, "b": 106, "operator": "*", "result": 54378}
{"question": "Solve (618 / 93)", "answer": "The result of (618 / 93) is 6.6452\n\n####6.6452", "a": 618, "b": 93, "operator": "/", "result": 6.6452}
{"question": "Solve (430 * 413)", "answer": "The result of (430 * 413) is 177590\n\n####177590", "a": 430, "b": 413, "operator": "*", "result": 177590}
{"question": "Solve (861 * 769)", "answer": "The result of (861 * 769) is 662109\n\n####662109", "a": 861, "b": 769, "operator": "*", "result": 662109}
{"question": "Solve (167 - 725)", "answer": "The result of (167 - 725) is -558\n\n####-558", "a": 167, "b": 725, "operator": "-", "result": -558}
{"question": "Solve (246 / 632)", "answer": "The result of (246 / 632) is 0.3892\n\n####0.3892", "a": 246, "b": 632, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3892}
{"question": "Solve (886 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (886 * 939) is 831954\n\n####831954", "a": 886, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 831954}
{"question": "Solve (145 - 809)", "answer": "The result of (145 - 809) is -664\n\n####-664", "a": 145, "b": 809, "operator": "-", "result": -664}
{"question": "Solve (746 * 814)", "answer": "The result of (746 * 814) is 607244\n\n####607244", "a": 746, "b": 814, "operator": "*", "result": 607244}
{"question": "Solve (662 / 741)", "answer": "The result of (662 / 741) is 0.8934\n\n####0.8934", "a": 662, "b": 741, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8934}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 288)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 288) is -236\n\n####-236", "a": 52, "b": 288, "operator": "-", "result": -236}
{"question": "Solve (498 * 686)", "answer": "The result of (498 * 686) is 341628\n\n####341628", "a": 498, "b": 686, "operator": "*", "result": 341628}
{"question": "Solve (998 + 880)", "answer": "The result of (998 + 880) is 1878\n\n####1878", "a": 998, "b": 880, "operator": "+", "result": 1878}
{"question": "Solve (300 * 543)", "answer": "The result of (300 * 543) is 162900\n\n####162900", "a": 300, "b": 543, "operator": "*", "result": 162900}
{"question": "Solve (660 * 657)", "answer": "The result of (660 * 657) is 433620\n\n####433620", "a": 660, "b": 657, "operator": "*", "result": 433620}
{"question": "Solve (278 * 151)", "answer": "The result of (278 * 151) is 41978\n\n####41978", "a": 278, "b": 151, "operator": "*", "result": 41978}
{"question": "Solve (296 * 295)", "answer": "The result of (296 * 295) is 87320\n\n####87320", "a": 296, "b": 295, "operator": "*", "result": 87320}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 534)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 534) is 812\n\n####812", "a": 278, "b": 534, "operator": "+", "result": 812}
{"question": "Solve (752 * 542)", "answer": "The result of (752 * 542) is 407584\n\n####407584", "a": 752, "b": 542, "operator": "*", "result": 407584}
{"question": "Solve (975 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (975 * 251) is 244725\n\n####244725", "a": 975, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 244725}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 558)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 558) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 849, "b": 558, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 773)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 773) is -299\n\n####-299", "a": 474, "b": 773, "operator": "-", "result": -299}
{"question": "Solve (96 / 843)", "answer": "The result of (96 / 843) is 0.1139\n\n####0.1139", "a": 96, "b": 843, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1139}
{"question": "Solve (437 + 713)", "answer": "The result of (437 + 713) is 1150\n\n####1150", "a": 437, "b": 713, "operator": "+", "result": 1150}
{"question": "Solve (837 * 691)", "answer": "The result of (837 * 691) is 578367\n\n####578367", "a": 837, "b": 691, "operator": "*", "result": 578367}
{"question": "Solve (216 * 193)", "answer": "The result of (216 * 193) is 41688\n\n####41688", "a": 216, "b": 193, "operator": "*", "result": 41688}
{"question": "Solve (473 * 461)", "answer": "The result of (473 * 461) is 218053\n\n####218053", "a": 473, "b": 461, "operator": "*", "result": 218053}
{"question": "Solve (418 + 638)", "answer": "The result of (418 + 638) is 1056\n\n####1056", "a": 418, "b": 638, "operator": "+", "result": 1056}
{"question": "Solve (666 * 685)", "answer": "The result of (666 * 685) is 456210\n\n####456210", "a": 666, "b": 685, "operator": "*", "result": 456210}
{"question": "Solve (521 / 225)", "answer": "The result of (521 / 225) is 2.3156\n\n####2.3156", "a": 521, "b": 225, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3156}
{"question": "Solve (3 / 113)", "answer": "The result of (3 / 113) is 0.0265\n\n####0.0265", "a": 3, "b": 113, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0265}
{"question": "Solve (869 * 906)", "answer": "The result of (869 * 906) is 787314\n\n####787314", "a": 869, "b": 906, "operator": "*", "result": 787314}
{"question": "Solve (613 / 428)", "answer": "The result of (613 / 428) is 1.4322\n\n####1.4322", "a": 613, "b": 428, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4322}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 910)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 910) is 0.0538\n\n####0.0538", "a": 49, "b": 910, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0538}
{"question": "Solve (817 / 64)", "answer": "The result of (817 / 64) is 12.7656\n\n####12.7656", "a": 817, "b": 64, "operator": "/", "result": 12.7656}
{"question": "Solve (83 - 102)", "answer": "The result of (83 - 102) is -19\n\n####-19", "a": 83, "b": 102, "operator": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve (39 * 396)", "answer": "The result of (39 * 396) is 15444\n\n####15444", "a": 39, "b": 396, "operator": "*", "result": 15444}
{"question": "Solve (83 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (83 * 423) is 35109\n\n####35109", "a": 83, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 35109}
{"question": "Solve (973 - 890)", "answer": "The result of (973 - 890) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 973, "b": 890, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (735 * 273)", "answer": "The result of (735 * 273) is 200655\n\n####200655", "a": 735, "b": 273, "operator": "*", "result": 200655}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 430)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 430) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 217, "b": 430, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (105 / 511)", "answer": "The result of (105 / 511) is 0.2055\n\n####0.2055", "a": 105, "b": 511, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2055}
{"question": "Solve (469 / 326)", "answer": "The result of (469 / 326) is 1.4387\n\n####1.4387", "a": 469, "b": 326, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4387}
{"question": "Solve (732 - 734)", "answer": "The result of (732 - 734) is -2\n\n####-2", "a": 732, "b": 734, "operator": "-", "result": -2}
{"question": "Solve (813 - 727)", "answer": "The result of (813 - 727) is 86\n\n####86", "a": 813, "b": 727, "operator": "-", "result": 86}
{"question": "Solve (846 + 202)", "answer": "The result of (846 + 202) is 1048\n\n####1048", "a": 846, "b": 202, "operator": "+", "result": 1048}
{"question": "Solve (239 * 717)", "answer": "The result of (239 * 717) is 171363\n\n####171363", "a": 239, "b": 717, "operator": "*", "result": 171363}
{"question": "Solve (798 + 689)", "answer": "The result of (798 + 689) is 1487\n\n####1487", "a": 798, "b": 689, "operator": "+", "result": 1487}
{"question": "Solve (882 / 929)", "answer": "The result of (882 / 929) is 0.9494\n\n####0.9494", "a": 882, "b": 929, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9494}
{"question": "Solve (952 - 984)", "answer": "The result of (952 - 984) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 952, "b": 984, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (983 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (983 - 45) is 938\n\n####938", "a": 983, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 938}
{"question": "Solve (232 + 875)", "answer": "The result of (232 + 875) is 1107\n\n####1107", "a": 232, "b": 875, "operator": "+", "result": 1107}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 882)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 882) is 694134\n\n####694134", "a": 787, "b": 882, "operator": "*", "result": 694134}
{"question": "Solve (563 * 887)", "answer": "The result of (563 * 887) is 499381\n\n####499381", "a": 563, "b": 887, "operator": "*", "result": 499381}
{"question": "Solve (481 + 903)", "answer": "The result of (481 + 903) is 1384\n\n####1384", "a": 481, "b": 903, "operator": "+", "result": 1384}
{"question": "Solve (449 * 195)", "answer": "The result of (449 * 195) is 87555\n\n####87555", "a": 449, "b": 195, "operator": "*", "result": 87555}
{"question": "Solve (620 - 103)", "answer": "The result of (620 - 103) is 517\n\n####517", "a": 620, "b": 103, "operator": "-", "result": 517}
{"question": "Solve (21 + 612)", "answer": "The result of (21 + 612) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 21, "b": 612, "operator": "+", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (522 * 550)", "answer": "The result of (522 * 550) is 287100\n\n####287100", "a": 522, "b": 550, "operator": "*", "result": 287100}
{"question": "Solve (913 - 710)", "answer": "The result of (913 - 710) is 203\n\n####203", "a": 913, "b": 710, "operator": "-", "result": 203}
{"question": "Solve (157 / 837)", "answer": "The result of (157 / 837) is 0.1876\n\n####0.1876", "a": 157, "b": 837, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1876}
{"question": "Solve (385 * 168)", "answer": "The result of (385 * 168) is 64680\n\n####64680", "a": 385, "b": 168, "operator": "*", "result": 64680}
{"question": "Solve (92 - 1)", "answer": "The result of (92 - 1) is 91\n\n####91", "a": 92, "b": 1, "operator": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve (757 * 138)", "answer": "The result of (757 * 138) is 104466\n\n####104466", "a": 757, "b": 138, "operator": "*", "result": 104466}
{"question": "Solve (603 + 615)", "answer": "The result of (603 + 615) is 1218\n\n####1218", "a": 603, "b": 615, "operator": "+", "result": 1218}
{"question": "Solve (752 + 403)", "answer": "The result of (752 + 403) is 1155\n\n####1155", "a": 752, "b": 403, "operator": "+", "result": 1155}
{"question": "Solve (642 - 961)", "answer": "The result of (642 - 961) is -319\n\n####-319", "a": 642, "b": 961, "operator": "-", "result": -319}
{"question": "Solve (5 - 766)", "answer": "The result of (5 - 766) is -761\n\n####-761", "a": 5, "b": 766, "operator": "-", "result": -761}
{"question": "Solve (944 - 898)", "answer": "The result of (944 - 898) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 944, "b": 898, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (505 - 805)", "answer": "The result of (505 - 805) is -300\n\n####-300", "a": 505, "b": 805, "operator": "-", "result": -300}
{"question": "Solve (518 * 570)", "answer": "The result of (518 * 570) is 295260\n\n####295260", "a": 518, "b": 570, "operator": "*", "result": 295260}
{"question": "Solve (35 / 160)", "answer": "The result of (35 / 160) is 0.2188\n\n####0.2188", "a": 35, "b": 160, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2188}
{"question": "Solve (651 / 808)", "answer": "The result of (651 / 808) is 0.8057\n\n####0.8057", "a": 651, "b": 808, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8057}
{"question": "Solve (929 - 40)", "answer": "The result of (929 - 40) is 889\n\n####889", "a": 929, "b": 40, "operator": "-", "result": 889}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 13)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 13) is 114\n\n####114", "a": 127, "b": 13, "operator": "-", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 387)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 387) is -342\n\n####-342", "a": 45, "b": 387, "operator": "-", "result": -342}
{"question": "Solve (882 / 714)", "answer": "The result of (882 / 714) is 1.2353\n\n####1.2353", "a": 882, "b": 714, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2353}
{"question": "Solve (29 - 52)", "answer": "The result of (29 - 52) is -23\n\n####-23", "a": 29, "b": 52, "operator": "-", "result": -23}
{"question": "Solve (567 * 98)", "answer": "The result of (567 * 98) is 55566\n\n####55566", "a": 567, "b": 98, "operator": "*", "result": 55566}
{"question": "Solve (892 / 283)", "answer": "The result of (892 / 283) is 3.1519\n\n####3.1519", "a": 892, "b": 283, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1519}
{"question": "Solve (354 / 802)", "answer": "The result of (354 / 802) is 0.4414\n\n####0.4414", "a": 354, "b": 802, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4414}
{"question": "Solve (186 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (186 * 548) is 101928\n\n####101928", "a": 186, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 101928}
{"question": "Solve (383 / 8)", "answer": "The result of (383 / 8) is 47.875\n\n####47.875", "a": 383, "b": 8, "operator": "/", "result": 47.875}
{"question": "Solve (959 * 737)", "answer": "The result of (959 * 737) is 706783\n\n####706783", "a": 959, "b": 737, "operator": "*", "result": 706783}
{"question": "Solve (826 / 907)", "answer": "The result of (826 / 907) is 0.9107\n\n####0.9107", "a": 826, "b": 907, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9107}
{"question": "Solve (796 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (796 - 169) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 796, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (694 - 287)", "answer": "The result of (694 - 287) is 407\n\n####407", "a": 694, "b": 287, "operator": "-", "result": 407}
{"question": "Solve (803 + 889)", "answer": "The result of (803 + 889) is 1692\n\n####1692", "a": 803, "b": 889, "operator": "+", "result": 1692}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 158)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 158) is 124\n\n####124", "a": 282, "b": 158, "operator": "-", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve (2 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (2 + 31) is 33\n\n####33", "a": 2, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 33}
{"question": "Solve (903 / 337)", "answer": "The result of (903 / 337) is 2.6795\n\n####2.6795", "a": 903, "b": 337, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6795}
{"question": "Solve (832 * 864)", "answer": "The result of (832 * 864) is 718848\n\n####718848", "a": 832, "b": 864, "operator": "*", "result": 718848}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 751) is 98\n\n####98", "a": 849, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve (381 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (381 / 276) is 1.3804\n\n####1.3804", "a": 381, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3804}
{"question": "Solve (868 / 621)", "answer": "The result of (868 / 621) is 1.3977\n\n####1.3977", "a": 868, "b": 621, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3977}
{"question": "Solve (395 / 210)", "answer": "The result of (395 / 210) is 1.881\n\n####1.881", "a": 395, "b": 210, "operator": "/", "result": 1.881}
{"question": "Solve (212 / 456)", "answer": "The result of (212 / 456) is 0.4649\n\n####0.4649", "a": 212, "b": 456, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4649}
{"question": "Solve (333 - 158)", "answer": "The result of (333 - 158) is 175\n\n####175", "a": 333, "b": 158, "operator": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve (827 / 538)", "answer": "The result of (827 / 538) is 1.5372\n\n####1.5372", "a": 827, "b": 538, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5372}
{"question": "Solve (836 / 443)", "answer": "The result of (836 / 443) is 1.8871\n\n####1.8871", "a": 836, "b": 443, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8871}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 827)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 827) is 0.2491\n\n####0.2491", "a": 206, "b": 827, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2491}
{"question": "Solve (572 / 707)", "answer": "The result of (572 / 707) is 0.8091\n\n####0.8091", "a": 572, "b": 707, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8091}
{"question": "Solve (721 / 563)", "answer": "The result of (721 / 563) is 1.2806\n\n####1.2806", "a": 721, "b": 563, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2806}
{"question": "Solve (145 + 554)", "answer": "The result of (145 + 554) is 699\n\n####699", "a": 145, "b": 554, "operator": "+", "result": 699}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 760)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 760) is 0.475\n\n####0.475", "a": 361, "b": 760, "operator": "/", "result": 0.475}
{"question": "Solve (771 * 826)", "answer": "The result of (771 * 826) is 636846\n\n####636846", "a": 771, "b": 826, "operator": "*", "result": 636846}
{"question": "Solve (782 / 657)", "answer": "The result of (782 / 657) is 1.1903\n\n####1.1903", "a": 782, "b": 657, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1903}
{"question": "Solve (812 / 849)", "answer": "The result of (812 / 849) is 0.9564\n\n####0.9564", "a": 812, "b": 849, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9564}
{"question": "Solve (99 * 817)", "answer": "The result of (99 * 817) is 80883\n\n####80883", "a": 99, "b": 817, "operator": "*", "result": 80883}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 909)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 909) is -189\n\n####-189", "a": 720, "b": 909, "operator": "-", "result": -189}
{"question": "Solve (988 / 747)", "answer": "The result of (988 / 747) is 1.3226\n\n####1.3226", "a": 988, "b": 747, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3226}
{"question": "Solve (496 * 10)", "answer": "The result of (496 * 10) is 4960\n\n####4960", "a": 496, "b": 10, "operator": "*", "result": 4960}
{"question": "Solve (192 + 199)", "answer": "The result of (192 + 199) is 391\n\n####391", "a": 192, "b": 199, "operator": "+", "result": 391}
{"question": "Solve (209 / 711)", "answer": "The result of (209 / 711) is 0.294\n\n####0.294", "a": 209, "b": 711, "operator": "/", "result": 0.294}
{"question": "Solve (15 / 793)", "answer": "The result of (15 / 793) is 0.0189\n\n####0.0189", "a": 15, "b": 793, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0189}
{"question": "Solve (679 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (679 - 547) is 132\n\n####132", "a": 679, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": 132}
{"question": "Solve (137 + 942)", "answer": "The result of (137 + 942) is 1079\n\n####1079", "a": 137, "b": 942, "operator": "+", "result": 1079}
{"question": "Solve (944 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (944 + 805) is 1749\n\n####1749", "a": 944, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1749}
{"question": "Solve (844 * 207)", "answer": "The result of (844 * 207) is 174708\n\n####174708", "a": 844, "b": 207, "operator": "*", "result": 174708}
{"question": "Solve (576 - 232)", "answer": "The result of (576 - 232) is 344\n\n####344", "a": 576, "b": 232, "operator": "-", "result": 344}
{"question": "Solve (173 * 57)", "answer": "The result of (173 * 57) is 9861\n\n####9861", "a": 173, "b": 57, "operator": "*", "result": 9861}
{"question": "Solve (438 + 568)", "answer": "The result of (438 + 568) is 1006\n\n####1006", "a": 438, "b": 568, "operator": "+", "result": 1006}
{"question": "Solve (410 / 811)", "answer": "The result of (410 / 811) is 0.5055\n\n####0.5055", "a": 410, "b": 811, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5055}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 617)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 617) is 823\n\n####823", "a": 206, "b": 617, "operator": "+", "result": 823}
{"question": "Solve (412 - 542)", "answer": "The result of (412 - 542) is -130\n\n####-130", "a": 412, "b": 542, "operator": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve (337 * 814)", "answer": "The result of (337 * 814) is 274318\n\n####274318", "a": 337, "b": 814, "operator": "*", "result": 274318}
{"question": "Solve (912 * 276)", "answer": "The result of (912 * 276) is 251712\n\n####251712", "a": 912, "b": 276, "operator": "*", "result": 251712}
{"question": "Solve (213 * 193)", "answer": "The result of (213 * 193) is 41109\n\n####41109", "a": 213, "b": 193, "operator": "*", "result": 41109}
{"question": "Solve (442 + 351)", "answer": "The result of (442 + 351) is 793\n\n####793", "a": 442, "b": 351, "operator": "+", "result": 793}
{"question": "Solve (737 + 655)", "answer": "The result of (737 + 655) is 1392\n\n####1392", "a": 737, "b": 655, "operator": "+", "result": 1392}
{"question": "Solve (196 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (196 - 206) is -10\n\n####-10", "a": 196, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve (169 - 418)", "answer": "The result of (169 - 418) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 169, "b": 418, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (918 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (918 + 184) is 1102\n\n####1102", "a": 918, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 1102}
{"question": "Solve (378 / 56)", "answer": "The result of (378 / 56) is 6.75\n\n####6.75", "a": 378, "b": 56, "operator": "/", "result": 6.75}
{"question": "Solve (134 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (134 + 124) is 258\n\n####258", "a": 134, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 258}
{"question": "Solve (240 + 334)", "answer": "The result of (240 + 334) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 240, "b": 334, "operator": "+", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (262 + 212)", "answer": "The result of (262 + 212) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 262, "b": 212, "operator": "+", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (716 / 108)", "answer": "The result of (716 / 108) is 6.6296\n\n####6.6296", "a": 716, "b": 108, "operator": "/", "result": 6.6296}
{"question": "Solve (153 - 420)", "answer": "The result of (153 - 420) is -267\n\n####-267", "a": 153, "b": 420, "operator": "-", "result": -267}
{"question": "Solve (990 + 166)", "answer": "The result of (990 + 166) is 1156\n\n####1156", "a": 990, "b": 166, "operator": "+", "result": 1156}
{"question": "Solve (249 + 693)", "answer": "The result of (249 + 693) is 942\n\n####942", "a": 249, "b": 693, "operator": "+", "result": 942}
{"question": "Solve (67 * 505)", "answer": "The result of (67 * 505) is 33835\n\n####33835", "a": 67, "b": 505, "operator": "*", "result": 33835}
{"question": "Solve (308 + 966)", "answer": "The result of (308 + 966) is 1274\n\n####1274", "a": 308, "b": 966, "operator": "+", "result": 1274}
{"question": "Solve (51 + 996)", "answer": "The result of (51 + 996) is 1047\n\n####1047", "a": 51, "b": 996, "operator": "+", "result": 1047}
{"question": "Solve (877 / 928)", "answer": "The result of (877 / 928) is 0.945\n\n####0.945", "a": 877, "b": 928, "operator": "/", "result": 0.945}
{"question": "Solve (192 - 639)", "answer": "The result of (192 - 639) is -447\n\n####-447", "a": 192, "b": 639, "operator": "-", "result": -447}
{"question": "Solve (429 + 772)", "answer": "The result of (429 + 772) is 1201\n\n####1201", "a": 429, "b": 772, "operator": "+", "result": 1201}
{"question": "Solve (32 / 567)", "answer": "The result of (32 / 567) is 0.0564\n\n####0.0564", "a": 32, "b": 567, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0564}
{"question": "Solve (98 / 823)", "answer": "The result of (98 / 823) is 0.1191\n\n####0.1191", "a": 98, "b": 823, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1191}
{"question": "Solve (1 + 735)", "answer": "The result of (1 + 735) is 736\n\n####736", "a": 1, "b": 735, "operator": "+", "result": 736}
{"question": "Solve (200 / 893)", "answer": "The result of (200 / 893) is 0.224\n\n####0.224", "a": 200, "b": 893, "operator": "/", "result": 0.224}
{"question": "Solve (730 - 155)", "answer": "The result of (730 - 155) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 730, "b": 155, "operator": "-", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (7 / 56)", "answer": "The result of (7 / 56) is 0.125\n\n####0.125", "a": 7, "b": 56, "operator": "/", "result": 0.125}
{"question": "Solve (430 * 26)", "answer": "The result of (430 * 26) is 11180\n\n####11180", "a": 430, "b": 26, "operator": "*", "result": 11180}
{"question": "Solve (769 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (769 - 822) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 769, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (432 - 300)", "answer": "The result of (432 - 300) is 132\n\n####132", "a": 432, "b": 300, "operator": "-", "result": 132}
{"question": "Solve (534 + 73)", "answer": "The result of (534 + 73) is 607\n\n####607", "a": 534, "b": 73, "operator": "+", "result": 607}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 949) is -720\n\n####-720", "a": 229, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -720}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 939) is 655422\n\n####655422", "a": 698, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 655422}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 821)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 821) is 1789\n\n####1789", "a": 968, "b": 821, "operator": "+", "result": 1789}
{"question": "Solve (234 - 132)", "answer": "The result of (234 - 132) is 102\n\n####102", "a": 234, "b": 132, "operator": "-", "result": 102}
{"question": "Solve (435 * 176)", "answer": "The result of (435 * 176) is 76560\n\n####76560", "a": 435, "b": 176, "operator": "*", "result": 76560}
{"question": "Solve (53 + 541)", "answer": "The result of (53 + 541) is 594\n\n####594", "a": 53, "b": 541, "operator": "+", "result": 594}
{"question": "Solve (369 + 193)", "answer": "The result of (369 + 193) is 562\n\n####562", "a": 369, "b": 193, "operator": "+", "result": 562}
{"question": "Solve (446 / 119)", "answer": "The result of (446 / 119) is 3.7479\n\n####3.7479", "a": 446, "b": 119, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7479}
{"question": "Solve (172 * 89)", "answer": "The result of (172 * 89) is 15308\n\n####15308", "a": 172, "b": 89, "operator": "*", "result": 15308}
{"question": "Solve (495 - 137)", "answer": "The result of (495 - 137) is 358\n\n####358", "a": 495, "b": 137, "operator": "-", "result": 358}
{"question": "Solve (222 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (222 - 700) is -478\n\n####-478", "a": 222, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -478}
{"question": "Solve (607 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (607 - 551) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 607, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (735 + 478)", "answer": "The result of (735 + 478) is 1213\n\n####1213", "a": 735, "b": 478, "operator": "+", "result": 1213}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 447)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 447) is 330333\n\n####330333", "a": 739, "b": 447, "operator": "*", "result": 330333}
{"question": "Solve (106 / 223)", "answer": "The result of (106 / 223) is 0.4753\n\n####0.4753", "a": 106, "b": 223, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4753}
{"question": "Solve (510 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (510 - 551) is -41\n\n####-41", "a": 510, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": -41}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 125)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 125) is 268\n\n####268", "a": 393, "b": 125, "operator": "-", "result": 268}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 152)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 152) is 813\n\n####813", "a": 661, "b": 152, "operator": "+", "result": 813}
{"question": "Solve (168 / 283)", "answer": "The result of (168 / 283) is 0.5936\n\n####0.5936", "a": 168, "b": 283, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5936}
{"question": "Solve (762 - 92)", "answer": "The result of (762 - 92) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 762, "b": 92, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (248 + 134)", "answer": "The result of (248 + 134) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 248, "b": 134, "operator": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (790 - 768)", "answer": "The result of (790 - 768) is 22\n\n####22", "a": 790, "b": 768, "operator": "-", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve (59 + 187)", "answer": "The result of (59 + 187) is 246\n\n####246", "a": 59, "b": 187, "operator": "+", "result": 246}
{"question": "Solve (822 - 605)", "answer": "The result of (822 - 605) is 217\n\n####217", "a": 822, "b": 605, "operator": "-", "result": 217}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 915)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 915) is 0.3399\n\n####0.3399", "a": 311, "b": 915, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3399}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 614)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 614) is 162096\n\n####162096", "a": 264, "b": 614, "operator": "*", "result": 162096}
{"question": "Solve (319 - 957)", "answer": "The result of (319 - 957) is -638\n\n####-638", "a": 319, "b": 957, "operator": "-", "result": -638}
{"question": "Solve (384 + 45)", "answer": "The result of (384 + 45) is 429\n\n####429", "a": 384, "b": 45, "operator": "+", "result": 429}
{"question": "Solve (826 - 476)", "answer": "The result of (826 - 476) is 350\n\n####350", "a": 826, "b": 476, "operator": "-", "result": 350}
{"question": "Solve (287 / 861)", "answer": "The result of (287 / 861) is 0.3333\n\n####0.3333", "a": 287, "b": 861, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3333}
{"question": "Solve (561 * 277)", "answer": "The result of (561 * 277) is 155397\n\n####155397", "a": 561, "b": 277, "operator": "*", "result": 155397}
{"question": "Solve (459 / 995)", "answer": "The result of (459 / 995) is 0.4613\n\n####0.4613", "a": 459, "b": 995, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4613}
{"question": "Solve (171 + 314)", "answer": "The result of (171 + 314) is 485\n\n####485", "a": 171, "b": 314, "operator": "+", "result": 485}
{"question": "Solve (795 + 398)", "answer": "The result of (795 + 398) is 1193\n\n####1193", "a": 795, "b": 398, "operator": "+", "result": 1193}
{"question": "Solve (815 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (815 / 411) is 1.983\n\n####1.983", "a": 815, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 1.983}
{"question": "Solve (826 - 378)", "answer": "The result of (826 - 378) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 826, "b": 378, "operator": "-", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (29 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (29 + 487) is 516\n\n####516", "a": 29, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 516}
{"question": "Solve (536 / 738)", "answer": "The result of (536 / 738) is 0.7263\n\n####0.7263", "a": 536, "b": 738, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7263}
{"question": "Solve (536 - 935)", "answer": "The result of (536 - 935) is -399\n\n####-399", "a": 536, "b": 935, "operator": "-", "result": -399}
{"question": "Solve (238 / 565)", "answer": "The result of (238 / 565) is 0.4212\n\n####0.4212", "a": 238, "b": 565, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4212}
{"question": "Solve (555 + 159)", "answer": "The result of (555 + 159) is 714\n\n####714", "a": 555, "b": 159, "operator": "+", "result": 714}
{"question": "Solve (493 * 445)", "answer": "The result of (493 * 445) is 219385\n\n####219385", "a": 493, "b": 445, "operator": "*", "result": 219385}
{"question": "Solve (580 + 102)", "answer": "The result of (580 + 102) is 682\n\n####682", "a": 580, "b": 102, "operator": "+", "result": 682}
{"question": "Solve (634 - 418)", "answer": "The result of (634 - 418) is 216\n\n####216", "a": 634, "b": 418, "operator": "-", "result": 216}
{"question": "Solve (516 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (516 + 124) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 516, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (554 / 987)", "answer": "The result of (554 / 987) is 0.5613\n\n####0.5613", "a": 554, "b": 987, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5613}
{"question": "Solve (75 / 867)", "answer": "The result of (75 / 867) is 0.0865\n\n####0.0865", "a": 75, "b": 867, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0865}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 456)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 456) is 364800\n\n####364800", "a": 800, "b": 456, "operator": "*", "result": 364800}
{"question": "Solve (791 + 325)", "answer": "The result of (791 + 325) is 1116\n\n####1116", "a": 791, "b": 325, "operator": "+", "result": 1116}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 964)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 964) is 688296\n\n####688296", "a": 714, "b": 964, "operator": "*", "result": 688296}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 738)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 738) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 676, "b": 738, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (223 * 115)", "answer": "The result of (223 * 115) is 25645\n\n####25645", "a": 223, "b": 115, "operator": "*", "result": 25645}
{"question": "Solve (575 * 243)", "answer": "The result of (575 * 243) is 139725\n\n####139725", "a": 575, "b": 243, "operator": "*", "result": 139725}
{"question": "Solve (184 + 86)", "answer": "The result of (184 + 86) is 270\n\n####270", "a": 184, "b": 86, "operator": "+", "result": 270}
{"question": "Solve (803 * 483)", "answer": "The result of (803 * 483) is 387849\n\n####387849", "a": 803, "b": 483, "operator": "*", "result": 387849}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 704)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 704) is 138\n\n####138", "a": 842, "b": 704, "operator": "-", "result": 138}
{"question": "Solve (69 - 573)", "answer": "The result of (69 - 573) is -504\n\n####-504", "a": 69, "b": 573, "operator": "-", "result": -504}
{"question": "Solve (702 * 948)", "answer": "The result of (702 * 948) is 665496\n\n####665496", "a": 702, "b": 948, "operator": "*", "result": 665496}
{"question": "Solve (57 + 124)", "answer": "The result of (57 + 124) is 181\n\n####181", "a": 57, "b": 124, "operator": "+", "result": 181}
{"question": "Solve (489 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (489 - 745) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 489, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 358) is 804\n\n####804", "a": 446, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 804}
{"question": "Solve (585 * 91)", "answer": "The result of (585 * 91) is 53235\n\n####53235", "a": 585, "b": 91, "operator": "*", "result": 53235}
{"question": "Solve (230 / 284)", "answer": "The result of (230 / 284) is 0.8099\n\n####0.8099", "a": 230, "b": 284, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8099}
{"question": "Solve (251 + 460)", "answer": "The result of (251 + 460) is 711\n\n####711", "a": 251, "b": 460, "operator": "+", "result": 711}
{"question": "Solve (576 - 70)", "answer": "The result of (576 - 70) is 506\n\n####506", "a": 576, "b": 70, "operator": "-", "result": 506}
{"question": "Solve (153 + 61)", "answer": "The result of (153 + 61) is 214\n\n####214", "a": 153, "b": 61, "operator": "+", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve (204 * 301)", "answer": "The result of (204 * 301) is 61404\n\n####61404", "a": 204, "b": 301, "operator": "*", "result": 61404}
{"question": "Solve (525 + 164)", "answer": "The result of (525 + 164) is 689\n\n####689", "a": 525, "b": 164, "operator": "+", "result": 689}
{"question": "Solve (917 - 164)", "answer": "The result of (917 - 164) is 753\n\n####753", "a": 917, "b": 164, "operator": "-", "result": 753}
{"question": "Solve (487 * 261)", "answer": "The result of (487 * 261) is 127107\n\n####127107", "a": 487, "b": 261, "operator": "*", "result": 127107}
{"question": "Solve (10 * 249)", "answer": "The result of (10 * 249) is 2490\n\n####2490", "a": 10, "b": 249, "operator": "*", "result": 2490}
{"question": "Solve (631 / 923)", "answer": "The result of (631 / 923) is 0.6836\n\n####0.6836", "a": 631, "b": 923, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6836}
{"question": "Solve (356 / 295)", "answer": "The result of (356 / 295) is 1.2068\n\n####1.2068", "a": 356, "b": 295, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2068}
{"question": "Solve (484 - 410)", "answer": "The result of (484 - 410) is 74\n\n####74", "a": 484, "b": 410, "operator": "-", "result": 74}
{"question": "Solve (574 / 948)", "answer": "The result of (574 / 948) is 0.6055\n\n####0.6055", "a": 574, "b": 948, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6055}
{"question": "Solve (70 + 107)", "answer": "The result of (70 + 107) is 177\n\n####177", "a": 70, "b": 107, "operator": "+", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve (906 / 158)", "answer": "The result of (906 / 158) is 5.7342\n\n####5.7342", "a": 906, "b": 158, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7342}
{"question": "Solve (577 + 418)", "answer": "The result of (577 + 418) is 995\n\n####995", "a": 577, "b": 418, "operator": "+", "result": 995}
{"question": "Solve (643 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (643 - 927) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 643, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (25 - 400)", "answer": "The result of (25 - 400) is -375\n\n####-375", "a": 25, "b": 400, "operator": "-", "result": -375}
{"question": "Solve (651 - 244)", "answer": "The result of (651 - 244) is 407\n\n####407", "a": 651, "b": 244, "operator": "-", "result": 407}
{"question": "Solve (31 + 318)", "answer": "The result of (31 + 318) is 349\n\n####349", "a": 31, "b": 318, "operator": "+", "result": 349}
{"question": "Solve (278 / 553)", "answer": "The result of (278 / 553) is 0.5027\n\n####0.5027", "a": 278, "b": 553, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5027}
{"question": "Solve (754 - 607)", "answer": "The result of (754 - 607) is 147\n\n####147", "a": 754, "b": 607, "operator": "-", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 947)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 947) is -471\n\n####-471", "a": 476, "b": 947, "operator": "-", "result": -471}
{"question": "Solve (505 * 815)", "answer": "The result of (505 * 815) is 411575\n\n####411575", "a": 505, "b": 815, "operator": "*", "result": 411575}
{"question": "Solve (321 + 401)", "answer": "The result of (321 + 401) is 722\n\n####722", "a": 321, "b": 401, "operator": "+", "result": 722}
{"question": "Solve (503 * 638)", "answer": "The result of (503 * 638) is 320914\n\n####320914", "a": 503, "b": 638, "operator": "*", "result": 320914}
{"question": "Solve (15 * 348)", "answer": "The result of (15 * 348) is 5220\n\n####5220", "a": 15, "b": 348, "operator": "*", "result": 5220}
{"question": "Solve (669 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (669 - 777) is -108\n\n####-108", "a": 669, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -108}
{"question": "Solve (808 * 578)", "answer": "The result of (808 * 578) is 467024\n\n####467024", "a": 808, "b": 578, "operator": "*", "result": 467024}
{"question": "Solve (115 / 251)", "answer": "The result of (115 / 251) is 0.4582\n\n####0.4582", "a": 115, "b": 251, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4582}
{"question": "Solve (192 - 225)", "answer": "The result of (192 - 225) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 192, "b": 225, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (643 + 924)", "answer": "The result of (643 + 924) is 1567\n\n####1567", "a": 643, "b": 924, "operator": "+", "result": 1567}
{"question": "Solve (654 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (654 * 524) is 342696\n\n####342696", "a": 654, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 342696}
{"question": "Solve (764 * 782)", "answer": "The result of (764 * 782) is 597448\n\n####597448", "a": 764, "b": 782, "operator": "*", "result": 597448}
{"question": "Solve (847 + 546)", "answer": "The result of (847 + 546) is 1393\n\n####1393", "a": 847, "b": 546, "operator": "+", "result": 1393}
{"question": "Solve (364 + 654)", "answer": "The result of (364 + 654) is 1018\n\n####1018", "a": 364, "b": 654, "operator": "+", "result": 1018}
{"question": "Solve (448 * 640)", "answer": "The result of (448 * 640) is 286720\n\n####286720", "a": 448, "b": 640, "operator": "*", "result": 286720}
{"question": "Solve (753 + 707)", "answer": "The result of (753 + 707) is 1460\n\n####1460", "a": 753, "b": 707, "operator": "+", "result": 1460}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 344) is -300\n\n####-300", "a": 44, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": -300}
{"question": "Solve (838 - 612)", "answer": "The result of (838 - 612) is 226\n\n####226", "a": 838, "b": 612, "operator": "-", "result": 226}
{"question": "Solve (353 + 264)", "answer": "The result of (353 + 264) is 617\n\n####617", "a": 353, "b": 264, "operator": "+", "result": 617}
{"question": "Solve (963 + 791)", "answer": "The result of (963 + 791) is 1754\n\n####1754", "a": 963, "b": 791, "operator": "+", "result": 1754}
{"question": "Solve (420 + 92)", "answer": "The result of (420 + 92) is 512\n\n####512", "a": 420, "b": 92, "operator": "+", "result": 512}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 329)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 329) is 534\n\n####534", "a": 863, "b": 329, "operator": "-", "result": 534}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 451)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 451) is -321\n\n####-321", "a": 130, "b": 451, "operator": "-", "result": -321}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 385)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 385) is 284515\n\n####284515", "a": 739, "b": 385, "operator": "*", "result": 284515}
{"question": "Solve (835 + 796)", "answer": "The result of (835 + 796) is 1631\n\n####1631", "a": 835, "b": 796, "operator": "+", "result": 1631}
{"question": "Solve (151 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (151 - 496) is -345\n\n####-345", "a": 151, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": -345}
{"question": "Solve (675 / 361)", "answer": "The result of (675 / 361) is 1.8698\n\n####1.8698", "a": 675, "b": 361, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8698}
{"question": "Solve (754 - 666)", "answer": "The result of (754 - 666) is 88\n\n####88", "a": 754, "b": 666, "operator": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve (764 * 245)", "answer": "The result of (764 * 245) is 187180\n\n####187180", "a": 764, "b": 245, "operator": "*", "result": 187180}
{"question": "Solve (576 / 151)", "answer": "The result of (576 / 151) is 3.8146\n\n####3.8146", "a": 576, "b": 151, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8146}
{"question": "Solve (80 * 670)", "answer": "The result of (80 * 670) is 53600\n\n####53600", "a": 80, "b": 670, "operator": "*", "result": 53600}
{"question": "Solve (513 + 640)", "answer": "The result of (513 + 640) is 1153\n\n####1153", "a": 513, "b": 640, "operator": "+", "result": 1153}
{"question": "Solve (946 / 438)", "answer": "The result of (946 / 438) is 2.1598\n\n####2.1598", "a": 946, "b": 438, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1598}
{"question": "Solve (128 / 340)", "answer": "The result of (128 / 340) is 0.3765\n\n####0.3765", "a": 128, "b": 340, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3765}
{"question": "Solve (649 * 412)", "answer": "The result of (649 * 412) is 267388\n\n####267388", "a": 649, "b": 412, "operator": "*", "result": 267388}
{"question": "Solve (754 / 720)", "answer": "The result of (754 / 720) is 1.0472\n\n####1.0472", "a": 754, "b": 720, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0472}
{"question": "Solve (390 * 292)", "answer": "The result of (390 * 292) is 113880\n\n####113880", "a": 390, "b": 292, "operator": "*", "result": 113880}
{"question": "Solve (635 + 312)", "answer": "The result of (635 + 312) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 635, "b": 312, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (633 / 523)", "answer": "The result of (633 / 523) is 1.2103\n\n####1.2103", "a": 633, "b": 523, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2103}
{"question": "Solve (672 * 137)", "answer": "The result of (672 * 137) is 92064\n\n####92064", "a": 672, "b": 137, "operator": "*", "result": 92064}
{"question": "Solve (611 - 443)", "answer": "The result of (611 - 443) is 168\n\n####168", "a": 611, "b": 443, "operator": "-", "result": 168}
{"question": "Solve (427 / 663)", "answer": "The result of (427 / 663) is 0.644\n\n####0.644", "a": 427, "b": 663, "operator": "/", "result": 0.644}
{"question": "Solve (373 / 826)", "answer": "The result of (373 / 826) is 0.4516\n\n####0.4516", "a": 373, "b": 826, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4516}
{"question": "Solve (533 - 143)", "answer": "The result of (533 - 143) is 390\n\n####390", "a": 533, "b": 143, "operator": "-", "result": 390}
{"question": "Solve (534 - 430)", "answer": "The result of (534 - 430) is 104\n\n####104", "a": 534, "b": 430, "operator": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve (988 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (988 * 22) is 21736\n\n####21736", "a": 988, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 21736}
{"question": "Solve (292 - 294)", "answer": "The result of (292 - 294) is -2\n\n####-2", "a": 292, "b": 294, "operator": "-", "result": -2}
{"question": "Solve (535 - 695)", "answer": "The result of (535 - 695) is -160\n\n####-160", "a": 535, "b": 695, "operator": "-", "result": -160}
{"question": "Solve (187 + 479)", "answer": "The result of (187 + 479) is 666\n\n####666", "a": 187, "b": 479, "operator": "+", "result": 666}
{"question": "Solve (291 / 582)", "answer": "The result of (291 / 582) is 0.5\n\n####0.5", "a": 291, "b": 582, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5}
{"question": "Solve (749 - 545)", "answer": "The result of (749 - 545) is 204\n\n####204", "a": 749, "b": 545, "operator": "-", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve (118 * 537)", "answer": "The result of (118 * 537) is 63366\n\n####63366", "a": 118, "b": 537, "operator": "*", "result": 63366}
{"question": "Solve (436 / 168)", "answer": "The result of (436 / 168) is 2.5952\n\n####2.5952", "a": 436, "b": 168, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5952}
{"question": "Solve (655 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (655 - 162) is 493\n\n####493", "a": 655, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 493}
{"question": "Solve (239 - 76)", "answer": "The result of (239 - 76) is 163\n\n####163", "a": 239, "b": 76, "operator": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve (191 * 597)", "answer": "The result of (191 * 597) is 114027\n\n####114027", "a": 191, "b": 597, "operator": "*", "result": 114027}
{"question": "Solve (35 / 12)", "answer": "The result of (35 / 12) is 2.9167\n\n####2.9167", "a": 35, "b": 12, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9167}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 955)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 955) is 545305\n\n####545305", "a": 571, "b": 955, "operator": "*", "result": 545305}
{"question": "Solve (555 + 420)", "answer": "The result of (555 + 420) is 975\n\n####975", "a": 555, "b": 420, "operator": "+", "result": 975}
{"question": "Solve (74 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (74 + 868) is 942\n\n####942", "a": 74, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 942}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 577)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 577) is 9\n\n####9", "a": 586, "b": 577, "operator": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve (722 + 355)", "answer": "The result of (722 + 355) is 1077\n\n####1077", "a": 722, "b": 355, "operator": "+", "result": 1077}
{"question": "Solve (965 - 28)", "answer": "The result of (965 - 28) is 937\n\n####937", "a": 965, "b": 28, "operator": "-", "result": 937}
{"question": "Solve (22 * 764)", "answer": "The result of (22 * 764) is 16808\n\n####16808", "a": 22, "b": 764, "operator": "*", "result": 16808}
{"question": "Solve (500 + 849)", "answer": "The result of (500 + 849) is 1349\n\n####1349", "a": 500, "b": 849, "operator": "+", "result": 1349}
{"question": "Solve (979 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (979 - 162) is 817\n\n####817", "a": 979, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 817}
{"question": "Solve (526 / 739)", "answer": "The result of (526 / 739) is 0.7118\n\n####0.7118", "a": 526, "b": 739, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7118}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 162)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 162) is 84726\n\n####84726", "a": 523, "b": 162, "operator": "*", "result": 84726}
{"question": "Solve (451 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (451 * 510) is 230010\n\n####230010", "a": 451, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 230010}
{"question": "Solve (73 - 805)", "answer": "The result of (73 - 805) is -732\n\n####-732", "a": 73, "b": 805, "operator": "-", "result": -732}
{"question": "Solve (555 / 469)", "answer": "The result of (555 / 469) is 1.1834\n\n####1.1834", "a": 555, "b": 469, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1834}
{"question": "Solve (692 + 141)", "answer": "The result of (692 + 141) is 833\n\n####833", "a": 692, "b": 141, "operator": "+", "result": 833}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 230)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 230) is 0.6609\n\n####0.6609", "a": 152, "b": 230, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6609}
{"question": "Solve (824 / 830)", "answer": "The result of (824 / 830) is 0.9928\n\n####0.9928", "a": 824, "b": 830, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9928}
{"question": "Solve (421 + 928)", "answer": "The result of (421 + 928) is 1349\n\n####1349", "a": 421, "b": 928, "operator": "+", "result": 1349}
{"question": "Solve (328 / 444)", "answer": "The result of (328 / 444) is 0.7387\n\n####0.7387", "a": 328, "b": 444, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7387}
{"question": "Solve (803 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (803 / 669) is 1.2003\n\n####1.2003", "a": 803, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2003}
{"question": "Solve (712 + 319)", "answer": "The result of (712 + 319) is 1031\n\n####1031", "a": 712, "b": 319, "operator": "+", "result": 1031}
{"question": "Solve (48 / 434)", "answer": "The result of (48 / 434) is 0.1106\n\n####0.1106", "a": 48, "b": 434, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1106}
{"question": "Solve (262 + 612)", "answer": "The result of (262 + 612) is 874\n\n####874", "a": 262, "b": 612, "operator": "+", "result": 874}
{"question": "Solve (650 * 170)", "answer": "The result of (650 * 170) is 110500\n\n####110500", "a": 650, "b": 170, "operator": "*", "result": 110500}
{"question": "Solve (112 - 735)", "answer": "The result of (112 - 735) is -623\n\n####-623", "a": 112, "b": 735, "operator": "-", "result": -623}
{"question": "Solve (17 / 905)", "answer": "The result of (17 / 905) is 0.0188\n\n####0.0188", "a": 17, "b": 905, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0188}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 929)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 929) is 0.8719\n\n####0.8719", "a": 810, "b": 929, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8719}
{"question": "Solve (164 * 282)", "answer": "The result of (164 * 282) is 46248\n\n####46248", "a": 164, "b": 282, "operator": "*", "result": 46248}
{"question": "Solve (696 + 904)", "answer": "The result of (696 + 904) is 1600\n\n####1600", "a": 696, "b": 904, "operator": "+", "result": 1600}
{"question": "Solve (706 * 459)", "answer": "The result of (706 * 459) is 324054\n\n####324054", "a": 706, "b": 459, "operator": "*", "result": 324054}
{"question": "Solve (970 - 853)", "answer": "The result of (970 - 853) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 970, "b": 853, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (464 - 584)", "answer": "The result of (464 - 584) is -120\n\n####-120", "a": 464, "b": 584, "operator": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve (131 + 864)", "answer": "The result of (131 + 864) is 995\n\n####995", "a": 131, "b": 864, "operator": "+", "result": 995}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 612)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 612) is 323748\n\n####323748", "a": 529, "b": 612, "operator": "*", "result": 323748}
{"question": "Solve (365 + 759)", "answer": "The result of (365 + 759) is 1124\n\n####1124", "a": 365, "b": 759, "operator": "+", "result": 1124}
{"question": "Solve (517 * 108)", "answer": "The result of (517 * 108) is 55836\n\n####55836", "a": 517, "b": 108, "operator": "*", "result": 55836}
{"question": "Solve (935 - 64)", "answer": "The result of (935 - 64) is 871\n\n####871", "a": 935, "b": 64, "operator": "-", "result": 871}
{"question": "Solve (656 - 374)", "answer": "The result of (656 - 374) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 656, "b": 374, "operator": "-", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (459 - 832)", "answer": "The result of (459 - 832) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 459, "b": 832, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (235 - 864)", "answer": "The result of (235 - 864) is -629\n\n####-629", "a": 235, "b": 864, "operator": "-", "result": -629}
{"question": "Solve (955 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (955 * 175) is 167125\n\n####167125", "a": 955, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 167125}
{"question": "Solve (69 / 429)", "answer": "The result of (69 / 429) is 0.1608\n\n####0.1608", "a": 69, "b": 429, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1608}
{"question": "Solve (875 * 609)", "answer": "The result of (875 * 609) is 532875\n\n####532875", "a": 875, "b": 609, "operator": "*", "result": 532875}
{"question": "Solve (228 * 412)", "answer": "The result of (228 * 412) is 93936\n\n####93936", "a": 228, "b": 412, "operator": "*", "result": 93936}
{"question": "Solve (474 / 151)", "answer": "The result of (474 / 151) is 3.1391\n\n####3.1391", "a": 474, "b": 151, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1391}
{"question": "Solve (891 - 327)", "answer": "The result of (891 - 327) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 891, "b": 327, "operator": "-", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 211) is 872\n\n####872", "a": 661, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 872}
{"question": "Solve (691 - 653)", "answer": "The result of (691 - 653) is 38\n\n####38", "a": 691, "b": 653, "operator": "-", "result": 38}
{"question": "Solve (17 + 68)", "answer": "The result of (17 + 68) is 85\n\n####85", "a": 17, "b": 68, "operator": "+", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve (50 / 847)", "answer": "The result of (50 / 847) is 0.059\n\n####0.059", "a": 50, "b": 847, "operator": "/", "result": 0.059}
{"question": "Solve (181 + 377)", "answer": "The result of (181 + 377) is 558\n\n####558", "a": 181, "b": 377, "operator": "+", "result": 558}
{"question": "Solve (761 - 534)", "answer": "The result of (761 - 534) is 227\n\n####227", "a": 761, "b": 534, "operator": "-", "result": 227}
{"question": "Solve (881 - 934)", "answer": "The result of (881 - 934) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 881, "b": 934, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (746 - 507)", "answer": "The result of (746 - 507) is 239\n\n####239", "a": 746, "b": 507, "operator": "-", "result": 239}
{"question": "Solve (978 * 679)", "answer": "The result of (978 * 679) is 664062\n\n####664062", "a": 978, "b": 679, "operator": "*", "result": 664062}
{"question": "Solve (939 + 815)", "answer": "The result of (939 + 815) is 1754\n\n####1754", "a": 939, "b": 815, "operator": "+", "result": 1754}
{"question": "Solve (830 - 638)", "answer": "The result of (830 - 638) is 192\n\n####192", "a": 830, "b": 638, "operator": "-", "result": 192}
{"question": "Solve (413 + 102)", "answer": "The result of (413 + 102) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 413, "b": 102, "operator": "+", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (243 - 980)", "answer": "The result of (243 - 980) is -737\n\n####-737", "a": 243, "b": 980, "operator": "-", "result": -737}
{"question": "Solve (405 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (405 + 380) is 785\n\n####785", "a": 405, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 785}
{"question": "Solve (179 + 237)", "answer": "The result of (179 + 237) is 416\n\n####416", "a": 179, "b": 237, "operator": "+", "result": 416}
{"question": "Solve (94 * 645)", "answer": "The result of (94 * 645) is 60630\n\n####60630", "a": 94, "b": 645, "operator": "*", "result": 60630}
{"question": "Solve (138 - 794)", "answer": "The result of (138 - 794) is -656\n\n####-656", "a": 138, "b": 794, "operator": "-", "result": -656}
{"question": "Solve (165 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (165 - 777) is -612\n\n####-612", "a": 165, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -612}
{"question": "Solve (614 * 611)", "answer": "The result of (614 * 611) is 375154\n\n####375154", "a": 614, "b": 611, "operator": "*", "result": 375154}
{"question": "Solve (231 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (231 - 933) is -702\n\n####-702", "a": 231, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -702}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 894)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 894) is 56322\n\n####56322", "a": 63, "b": 894, "operator": "*", "result": 56322}
{"question": "Solve (661 + 803)", "answer": "The result of (661 + 803) is 1464\n\n####1464", "a": 661, "b": 803, "operator": "+", "result": 1464}
{"question": "Solve (350 / 313)", "answer": "The result of (350 / 313) is 1.1182\n\n####1.1182", "a": 350, "b": 313, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1182}
{"question": "Solve (624 + 320)", "answer": "The result of (624 + 320) is 944\n\n####944", "a": 624, "b": 320, "operator": "+", "result": 944}
{"question": "Solve (239 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (239 - 932) is -693\n\n####-693", "a": 239, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": -693}
{"question": "Solve (634 - 668)", "answer": "The result of (634 - 668) is -34\n\n####-34", "a": 634, "b": 668, "operator": "-", "result": -34}
{"question": "Solve (977 - 996)", "answer": "The result of (977 - 996) is -19\n\n####-19", "a": 977, "b": 996, "operator": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve (416 - 776)", "answer": "The result of (416 - 776) is -360\n\n####-360", "a": 416, "b": 776, "operator": "-", "result": -360}
{"question": "Solve (152 * 882)", "answer": "The result of (152 * 882) is 134064\n\n####134064", "a": 152, "b": 882, "operator": "*", "result": 134064}
{"question": "Solve (259 / 321)", "answer": "The result of (259 / 321) is 0.8069\n\n####0.8069", "a": 259, "b": 321, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8069}
{"question": "Solve (278 / 55)", "answer": "The result of (278 / 55) is 5.0545\n\n####5.0545", "a": 278, "b": 55, "operator": "/", "result": 5.0545}
{"question": "Solve (504 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (504 * 86) is 43344\n\n####43344", "a": 504, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 43344}
{"question": "Solve (868 - 896)", "answer": "The result of (868 - 896) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 868, "b": 896, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (326 + 636)", "answer": "The result of (326 + 636) is 962\n\n####962", "a": 326, "b": 636, "operator": "+", "result": 962}
{"question": "Solve (679 * 875)", "answer": "The result of (679 * 875) is 594125\n\n####594125", "a": 679, "b": 875, "operator": "*", "result": 594125}
{"question": "Solve (422 / 157)", "answer": "The result of (422 / 157) is 2.6879\n\n####2.6879", "a": 422, "b": 157, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6879}
{"question": "Solve (323 / 56)", "answer": "The result of (323 / 56) is 5.7679\n\n####5.7679", "a": 323, "b": 56, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7679}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 785)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 785) is -581\n\n####-581", "a": 204, "b": 785, "operator": "-", "result": -581}
{"question": "Solve (106 * 867)", "answer": "The result of (106 * 867) is 91902\n\n####91902", "a": 106, "b": 867, "operator": "*", "result": 91902}
{"question": "Solve (844 * 759)", "answer": "The result of (844 * 759) is 640596\n\n####640596", "a": 844, "b": 759, "operator": "*", "result": 640596}
{"question": "Solve (536 * 74)", "answer": "The result of (536 * 74) is 39664\n\n####39664", "a": 536, "b": 74, "operator": "*", "result": 39664}
{"question": "Solve (525 * 825)", "answer": "The result of (525 * 825) is 433125\n\n####433125", "a": 525, "b": 825, "operator": "*", "result": 433125}
{"question": "Solve (37 / 419)", "answer": "The result of (37 / 419) is 0.0883\n\n####0.0883", "a": 37, "b": 419, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0883}
{"question": "Solve (897 / 318)", "answer": "The result of (897 / 318) is 2.8208\n\n####2.8208", "a": 897, "b": 318, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8208}
{"question": "Solve (731 * 705)", "answer": "The result of (731 * 705) is 515355\n\n####515355", "a": 731, "b": 705, "operator": "*", "result": 515355}
{"question": "Solve (731 + 657)", "answer": "The result of (731 + 657) is 1388\n\n####1388", "a": 731, "b": 657, "operator": "+", "result": 1388}
{"question": "Solve (316 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (316 / 290) is 1.0897\n\n####1.0897", "a": 316, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0897}
{"question": "Solve (880 + 208)", "answer": "The result of (880 + 208) is 1088\n\n####1088", "a": 880, "b": 208, "operator": "+", "result": 1088}
{"question": "Solve (553 * 105)", "answer": "The result of (553 * 105) is 58065\n\n####58065", "a": 553, "b": 105, "operator": "*", "result": 58065}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 924)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 924) is -642\n\n####-642", "a": 282, "b": 924, "operator": "-", "result": -642}
{"question": "Solve (120 + 370)", "answer": "The result of (120 + 370) is 490\n\n####490", "a": 120, "b": 370, "operator": "+", "result": 490}
{"question": "Solve (843 + 989)", "answer": "The result of (843 + 989) is 1832\n\n####1832", "a": 843, "b": 989, "operator": "+", "result": 1832}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 75)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 75) is 2.1467\n\n####2.1467", "a": 161, "b": 75, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1467}
{"question": "Solve (274 + 179)", "answer": "The result of (274 + 179) is 453\n\n####453", "a": 274, "b": 179, "operator": "+", "result": 453}
{"question": "Solve (180 + 919)", "answer": "The result of (180 + 919) is 1099\n\n####1099", "a": 180, "b": 919, "operator": "+", "result": 1099}
{"question": "Solve (34 + 461)", "answer": "The result of (34 + 461) is 495\n\n####495", "a": 34, "b": 461, "operator": "+", "result": 495}
{"question": "Solve (140 - 596)", "answer": "The result of (140 - 596) is -456\n\n####-456", "a": 140, "b": 596, "operator": "-", "result": -456}
{"question": "Solve (691 * 990)", "answer": "The result of (691 * 990) is 684090\n\n####684090", "a": 691, "b": 990, "operator": "*", "result": 684090}
{"question": "Solve (692 / 408)", "answer": "The result of (692 / 408) is 1.6961\n\n####1.6961", "a": 692, "b": 408, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6961}
{"question": "Solve (712 / 936)", "answer": "The result of (712 / 936) is 0.7607\n\n####0.7607", "a": 712, "b": 936, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7607}
{"question": "Solve (954 / 673)", "answer": "The result of (954 / 673) is 1.4175\n\n####1.4175", "a": 954, "b": 673, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4175}
{"question": "Solve (393 + 510)", "answer": "The result of (393 + 510) is 903\n\n####903", "a": 393, "b": 510, "operator": "+", "result": 903}
{"question": "Solve (138 - 898)", "answer": "The result of (138 - 898) is -760\n\n####-760", "a": 138, "b": 898, "operator": "-", "result": -760}
{"question": "Solve (557 - 818)", "answer": "The result of (557 - 818) is -261\n\n####-261", "a": 557, "b": 818, "operator": "-", "result": -261}
{"question": "Solve (745 * 946)", "answer": "The result of (745 * 946) is 704770\n\n####704770", "a": 745, "b": 946, "operator": "*", "result": 704770}
{"question": "Solve (927 + 275)", "answer": "The result of (927 + 275) is 1202\n\n####1202", "a": 927, "b": 275, "operator": "+", "result": 1202}
{"question": "Solve (589 / 24)", "answer": "The result of (589 / 24) is 24.5417\n\n####24.5417", "a": 589, "b": 24, "operator": "/", "result": 24.5417}
{"question": "Solve (894 / 159)", "answer": "The result of (894 / 159) is 5.6226\n\n####5.6226", "a": 894, "b": 159, "operator": "/", "result": 5.6226}
{"question": "Solve (336 / 164)", "answer": "The result of (336 / 164) is 2.0488\n\n####2.0488", "a": 336, "b": 164, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0488}
{"question": "Solve (979 / 806)", "answer": "The result of (979 / 806) is 1.2146\n\n####1.2146", "a": 979, "b": 806, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2146}
{"question": "Solve (708 * 697)", "answer": "The result of (708 * 697) is 493476\n\n####493476", "a": 708, "b": 697, "operator": "*", "result": 493476}
{"question": "Solve (811 / 339)", "answer": "The result of (811 / 339) is 2.3923\n\n####2.3923", "a": 811, "b": 339, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3923}
{"question": "Solve (763 * 64)", "answer": "The result of (763 * 64) is 48832\n\n####48832", "a": 763, "b": 64, "operator": "*", "result": 48832}
{"question": "Solve (510 - 352)", "answer": "The result of (510 - 352) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 510, "b": 352, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (407 - 681)", "answer": "The result of (407 - 681) is -274\n\n####-274", "a": 407, "b": 681, "operator": "-", "result": -274}
{"question": "Solve (941 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (941 / 240) is 3.9208\n\n####3.9208", "a": 941, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9208}
{"question": "Solve (623 / 364)", "answer": "The result of (623 / 364) is 1.7115\n\n####1.7115", "a": 623, "b": 364, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7115}
{"question": "Solve (253 + 937)", "answer": "The result of (253 + 937) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 253, "b": 937, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (455 - 221)", "answer": "The result of (455 - 221) is 234\n\n####234", "a": 455, "b": 221, "operator": "-", "result": 234}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 324)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 324) is 0.6358\n\n####0.6358", "a": 206, "b": 324, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6358}
{"question": "Solve (50 - 223)", "answer": "The result of (50 - 223) is -173\n\n####-173", "a": 50, "b": 223, "operator": "-", "result": -173}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 577)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 577) is 525070\n\n####525070", "a": 910, "b": 577, "operator": "*", "result": 525070}
{"question": "Solve (873 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (873 * 510) is 445230\n\n####445230", "a": 873, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 445230}
{"question": "Solve (861 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (861 - 745) is 116\n\n####116", "a": 861, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": 116}
{"question": "Solve (187 + 54)", "answer": "The result of (187 + 54) is 241\n\n####241", "a": 187, "b": 54, "operator": "+", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve (88 - 18)", "answer": "The result of (88 - 18) is 70\n\n####70", "a": 88, "b": 18, "operator": "-", "result": 70}
{"question": "Solve (16 * 120)", "answer": "The result of (16 * 120) is 1920\n\n####1920", "a": 16, "b": 120, "operator": "*", "result": 1920}
{"question": "Solve (67 * 123)", "answer": "The result of (67 * 123) is 8241\n\n####8241", "a": 67, "b": 123, "operator": "*", "result": 8241}
{"question": "Solve (104 * 72)", "answer": "The result of (104 * 72) is 7488\n\n####7488", "a": 104, "b": 72, "operator": "*", "result": 7488}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 789)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 789) is 0.0456\n\n####0.0456", "a": 36, "b": 789, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0456}
{"question": "Solve (840 - 170)", "answer": "The result of (840 - 170) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 840, "b": 170, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (518 - 129)", "answer": "The result of (518 - 129) is 389\n\n####389", "a": 518, "b": 129, "operator": "-", "result": 389}
{"question": "Solve (878 - 421)", "answer": "The result of (878 - 421) is 457\n\n####457", "a": 878, "b": 421, "operator": "-", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 354) is 488\n\n####488", "a": 842, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": 488}
{"question": "Solve (974 + 269)", "answer": "The result of (974 + 269) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 974, "b": 269, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (899 * 229)", "answer": "The result of (899 * 229) is 205871\n\n####205871", "a": 899, "b": 229, "operator": "*", "result": 205871}
{"question": "Solve (359 - 869)", "answer": "The result of (359 - 869) is -510\n\n####-510", "a": 359, "b": 869, "operator": "-", "result": -510}
{"question": "Solve (847 - 938)", "answer": "The result of (847 - 938) is -91\n\n####-91", "a": 847, "b": 938, "operator": "-", "result": -91}
{"question": "Solve (127 * 35)", "answer": "The result of (127 * 35) is 4445\n\n####4445", "a": 127, "b": 35, "operator": "*", "result": 4445}
{"question": "Solve (43 * 118)", "answer": "The result of (43 * 118) is 5074\n\n####5074", "a": 43, "b": 118, "operator": "*", "result": 5074}
{"question": "Solve (769 / 22)", "answer": "The result of (769 / 22) is 34.9545\n\n####34.9545", "a": 769, "b": 22, "operator": "/", "result": 34.9545}
{"question": "Solve (191 / 971)", "answer": "The result of (191 / 971) is 0.1967\n\n####0.1967", "a": 191, "b": 971, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1967}
{"question": "Solve (191 / 496)", "answer": "The result of (191 / 496) is 0.3851\n\n####0.3851", "a": 191, "b": 496, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3851}
{"question": "Solve (253 + 910)", "answer": "The result of (253 + 910) is 1163\n\n####1163", "a": 253, "b": 910, "operator": "+", "result": 1163}
{"question": "Solve (602 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (602 / 545) is 1.1046\n\n####1.1046", "a": 602, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1046}
{"question": "Solve (973 * 310)", "answer": "The result of (973 * 310) is 301630\n\n####301630", "a": 973, "b": 310, "operator": "*", "result": 301630}
{"question": "Solve (473 + 506)", "answer": "The result of (473 + 506) is 979\n\n####979", "a": 473, "b": 506, "operator": "+", "result": 979}
{"question": "Solve (933 - 850)", "answer": "The result of (933 - 850) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 933, "b": 850, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (37 / 595)", "answer": "The result of (37 / 595) is 0.0622\n\n####0.0622", "a": 37, "b": 595, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0622}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 832)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 832) is -705\n\n####-705", "a": 127, "b": 832, "operator": "-", "result": -705}
{"question": "Solve (586 / 996)", "answer": "The result of (586 / 996) is 0.5884\n\n####0.5884", "a": 586, "b": 996, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5884}
{"question": "Solve (413 / 440)", "answer": "The result of (413 / 440) is 0.9386\n\n####0.9386", "a": 413, "b": 440, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9386}
{"question": "Solve (955 - 549)", "answer": "The result of (955 - 549) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 955, "b": 549, "operator": "-", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (189 + 423)", "answer": "The result of (189 + 423) is 612\n\n####612", "a": 189, "b": 423, "operator": "+", "result": 612}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 969)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 969) is 0.5593\n\n####0.5593", "a": 542, "b": 969, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5593}
{"question": "Solve (923 / 331)", "answer": "The result of (923 / 331) is 2.7885\n\n####2.7885", "a": 923, "b": 331, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7885}
{"question": "Solve (150 / 423)", "answer": "The result of (150 / 423) is 0.3546\n\n####0.3546", "a": 150, "b": 423, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3546}
{"question": "Solve (19 / 82)", "answer": "The result of (19 / 82) is 0.2317\n\n####0.2317", "a": 19, "b": 82, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2317}
{"question": "Solve (922 + 258)", "answer": "The result of (922 + 258) is 1180\n\n####1180", "a": 922, "b": 258, "operator": "+", "result": 1180}
{"question": "Solve (50 * 895)", "answer": "The result of (50 * 895) is 44750\n\n####44750", "a": 50, "b": 895, "operator": "*", "result": 44750}
{"question": "Solve (646 / 382)", "answer": "The result of (646 / 382) is 1.6911\n\n####1.6911", "a": 646, "b": 382, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6911}
{"question": "Solve (166 + 531)", "answer": "The result of (166 + 531) is 697\n\n####697", "a": 166, "b": 531, "operator": "+", "result": 697}
{"question": "Solve (471 * 878)", "answer": "The result of (471 * 878) is 413538\n\n####413538", "a": 471, "b": 878, "operator": "*", "result": 413538}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 240)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 240) is 34560\n\n####34560", "a": 144, "b": 240, "operator": "*", "result": 34560}
{"question": "Solve (221 - 316)", "answer": "The result of (221 - 316) is -95\n\n####-95", "a": 221, "b": 316, "operator": "-", "result": -95}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 367)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 367) is 288829\n\n####288829", "a": 787, "b": 367, "operator": "*", "result": 288829}
{"question": "Solve (43 - 275)", "answer": "The result of (43 - 275) is -232\n\n####-232", "a": 43, "b": 275, "operator": "-", "result": -232}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 858)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 858) is -292\n\n####-292", "a": 566, "b": 858, "operator": "-", "result": -292}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 89)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 89) is 4\n\n####4", "a": 93, "b": 89, "operator": "-", "result": 4}
{"question": "Solve (869 - 841)", "answer": "The result of (869 - 841) is 28\n\n####28", "a": 869, "b": 841, "operator": "-", "result": 28}
{"question": "Solve (440 * 547)", "answer": "The result of (440 * 547) is 240680\n\n####240680", "a": 440, "b": 547, "operator": "*", "result": 240680}
{"question": "Solve (123 - 199)", "answer": "The result of (123 - 199) is -76\n\n####-76", "a": 123, "b": 199, "operator": "-", "result": -76}
{"question": "Solve (924 * 981)", "answer": "The result of (924 * 981) is 906444\n\n####906444", "a": 924, "b": 981, "operator": "*", "result": 906444}
{"question": "Solve (555 + 609)", "answer": "The result of (555 + 609) is 1164\n\n####1164", "a": 555, "b": 609, "operator": "+", "result": 1164}
{"question": "Solve (494 / 600)", "answer": "The result of (494 / 600) is 0.8233\n\n####0.8233", "a": 494, "b": 600, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8233}
{"question": "Solve (821 / 292)", "answer": "The result of (821 / 292) is 2.8116\n\n####2.8116", "a": 821, "b": 292, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8116}
{"question": "Solve (426 / 521)", "answer": "The result of (426 / 521) is 0.8177\n\n####0.8177", "a": 426, "b": 521, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8177}
{"question": "Solve (915 + 165)", "answer": "The result of (915 + 165) is 1080\n\n####1080", "a": 915, "b": 165, "operator": "+", "result": 1080}
{"question": "Solve (111 - 65)", "answer": "The result of (111 - 65) is 46\n\n####46", "a": 111, "b": 65, "operator": "-", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 405)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 405) is 253530\n\n####253530", "a": 626, "b": 405, "operator": "*", "result": 253530}
{"question": "Solve (588 - 742)", "answer": "The result of (588 - 742) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 588, "b": 742, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (768 / 535)", "answer": "The result of (768 / 535) is 1.4355\n\n####1.4355", "a": 768, "b": 535, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4355}
{"question": "Solve (360 * 354)", "answer": "The result of (360 * 354) is 127440\n\n####127440", "a": 360, "b": 354, "operator": "*", "result": 127440}
{"question": "Solve (665 / 848)", "answer": "The result of (665 / 848) is 0.7842\n\n####0.7842", "a": 665, "b": 848, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7842}
{"question": "Solve (659 - 287)", "answer": "The result of (659 - 287) is 372\n\n####372", "a": 659, "b": 287, "operator": "-", "result": 372}
{"question": "Solve (387 - 888)", "answer": "The result of (387 - 888) is -501\n\n####-501", "a": 387, "b": 888, "operator": "-", "result": -501}
{"question": "Solve (504 - 296)", "answer": "The result of (504 - 296) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 504, "b": 296, "operator": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (406 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (406 - 998) is -592\n\n####-592", "a": 406, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -592}
{"question": "Solve (474 + 370)", "answer": "The result of (474 + 370) is 844\n\n####844", "a": 474, "b": 370, "operator": "+", "result": 844}
{"question": "Solve (902 / 664)", "answer": "The result of (902 / 664) is 1.3584\n\n####1.3584", "a": 902, "b": 664, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3584}
{"question": "Solve (469 + 502)", "answer": "The result of (469 + 502) is 971\n\n####971", "a": 469, "b": 502, "operator": "+", "result": 971}
{"question": "Solve (197 / 675)", "answer": "The result of (197 / 675) is 0.2919\n\n####0.2919", "a": 197, "b": 675, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2919}
{"question": "Solve (761 / 729)", "answer": "The result of (761 / 729) is 1.0439\n\n####1.0439", "a": 761, "b": 729, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0439}
{"question": "Solve (417 + 353)", "answer": "The result of (417 + 353) is 770\n\n####770", "a": 417, "b": 353, "operator": "+", "result": 770}
{"question": "Solve (800 - 130)", "answer": "The result of (800 - 130) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 800, "b": 130, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (200 * 127)", "answer": "The result of (200 * 127) is 25400\n\n####25400", "a": 200, "b": 127, "operator": "*", "result": 25400}
{"question": "Solve (234 / 204)", "answer": "The result of (234 / 204) is 1.1471\n\n####1.1471", "a": 234, "b": 204, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1471}
{"question": "Solve (540 / 344)", "answer": "The result of (540 / 344) is 1.5698\n\n####1.5698", "a": 540, "b": 344, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5698}
{"question": "Solve (683 / 928)", "answer": "The result of (683 / 928) is 0.736\n\n####0.736", "a": 683, "b": 928, "operator": "/", "result": 0.736}
{"question": "Solve (474 * 508)", "answer": "The result of (474 * 508) is 240792\n\n####240792", "a": 474, "b": 508, "operator": "*", "result": 240792}
{"question": "Solve (938 * 415)", "answer": "The result of (938 * 415) is 389270\n\n####389270", "a": 938, "b": 415, "operator": "*", "result": 389270}
{"question": "Solve (274 * 398)", "answer": "The result of (274 * 398) is 109052\n\n####109052", "a": 274, "b": 398, "operator": "*", "result": 109052}
{"question": "Solve (594 - 571)", "answer": "The result of (594 - 571) is 23\n\n####23", "a": 594, "b": 571, "operator": "-", "result": 23}
{"question": "Solve (908 / 141)", "answer": "The result of (908 / 141) is 6.4397\n\n####6.4397", "a": 908, "b": 141, "operator": "/", "result": 6.4397}
{"question": "Solve (453 + 274)", "answer": "The result of (453 + 274) is 727\n\n####727", "a": 453, "b": 274, "operator": "+", "result": 727}
{"question": "Solve (297 * 636)", "answer": "The result of (297 * 636) is 188892\n\n####188892", "a": 297, "b": 636, "operator": "*", "result": 188892}
{"question": "Solve (171 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (171 - 384) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 171, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (896 + 156)", "answer": "The result of (896 + 156) is 1052\n\n####1052", "a": 896, "b": 156, "operator": "+", "result": 1052}
{"question": "Solve (605 / 950)", "answer": "The result of (605 / 950) is 0.6368\n\n####0.6368", "a": 605, "b": 950, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6368}
{"question": "Solve (680 * 639)", "answer": "The result of (680 * 639) is 434520\n\n####434520", "a": 680, "b": 639, "operator": "*", "result": 434520}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 730)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 730) is 98550\n\n####98550", "a": 135, "b": 730, "operator": "*", "result": 98550}
{"question": "Solve (25 - 749)", "answer": "The result of (25 - 749) is -724\n\n####-724", "a": 25, "b": 749, "operator": "-", "result": -724}
{"question": "Solve (413 + 381)", "answer": "The result of (413 + 381) is 794\n\n####794", "a": 413, "b": 381, "operator": "+", "result": 794}
{"question": "Solve (811 + 216)", "answer": "The result of (811 + 216) is 1027\n\n####1027", "a": 811, "b": 216, "operator": "+", "result": 1027}
{"question": "Solve (215 * 58)", "answer": "The result of (215 * 58) is 12470\n\n####12470", "a": 215, "b": 58, "operator": "*", "result": 12470}
{"question": "Solve (153 * 736)", "answer": "The result of (153 * 736) is 112608\n\n####112608", "a": 153, "b": 736, "operator": "*", "result": 112608}
{"question": "Solve (684 - 630)", "answer": "The result of (684 - 630) is 54\n\n####54", "a": 684, "b": 630, "operator": "-", "result": 54}
{"question": "Solve (906 + 226)", "answer": "The result of (906 + 226) is 1132\n\n####1132", "a": 906, "b": 226, "operator": "+", "result": 1132}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 619)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 619) is 599192\n\n####599192", "a": 968, "b": 619, "operator": "*", "result": 599192}
{"question": "Solve (847 - 480)", "answer": "The result of (847 - 480) is 367\n\n####367", "a": 847, "b": 480, "operator": "-", "result": 367}
{"question": "Solve (735 + 51)", "answer": "The result of (735 + 51) is 786\n\n####786", "a": 735, "b": 51, "operator": "+", "result": 786}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 780)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 780) is 0.1128\n\n####0.1128", "a": 88, "b": 780, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1128}
{"question": "Solve (368 - 687)", "answer": "The result of (368 - 687) is -319\n\n####-319", "a": 368, "b": 687, "operator": "-", "result": -319}
{"question": "Solve (998 * 725)", "answer": "The result of (998 * 725) is 723550\n\n####723550", "a": 998, "b": 725, "operator": "*", "result": 723550}
{"question": "Solve (357 / 103)", "answer": "The result of (357 / 103) is 3.466\n\n####3.466", "a": 357, "b": 103, "operator": "/", "result": 3.466}
{"question": "Solve (707 / 329)", "answer": "The result of (707 / 329) is 2.1489\n\n####2.1489", "a": 707, "b": 329, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1489}
{"question": "Solve (854 / 128)", "answer": "The result of (854 / 128) is 6.6719\n\n####6.6719", "a": 854, "b": 128, "operator": "/", "result": 6.6719}
{"question": "Solve (471 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (471 / 294) is 1.602\n\n####1.602", "a": 471, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 1.602}
{"question": "Solve (362 - 79)", "answer": "The result of (362 - 79) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 362, "b": 79, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (141 / 203)", "answer": "The result of (141 / 203) is 0.6946\n\n####0.6946", "a": 141, "b": 203, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6946}
{"question": "Solve (344 * 880)", "answer": "The result of (344 * 880) is 302720\n\n####302720", "a": 344, "b": 880, "operator": "*", "result": 302720}
{"question": "Solve (820 * 535)", "answer": "The result of (820 * 535) is 438700\n\n####438700", "a": 820, "b": 535, "operator": "*", "result": 438700}
{"question": "Solve (232 / 648)", "answer": "The result of (232 / 648) is 0.358\n\n####0.358", "a": 232, "b": 648, "operator": "/", "result": 0.358}
{"question": "Solve (119 * 316)", "answer": "The result of (119 * 316) is 37604\n\n####37604", "a": 119, "b": 316, "operator": "*", "result": 37604}
{"question": "Solve (983 - 513)", "answer": "The result of (983 - 513) is 470\n\n####470", "a": 983, "b": 513, "operator": "-", "result": 470}
{"question": "Solve (855 * 857)", "answer": "The result of (855 * 857) is 732735\n\n####732735", "a": 855, "b": 857, "operator": "*", "result": 732735}
{"question": "Solve (376 + 386)", "answer": "The result of (376 + 386) is 762\n\n####762", "a": 376, "b": 386, "operator": "+", "result": 762}
{"question": "Solve (338 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (338 - 810) is -472\n\n####-472", "a": 338, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": -472}
{"question": "Solve (262 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (262 - 250) is 12\n\n####12", "a": 262, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": 12}
{"question": "Solve (478 - 752)", "answer": "The result of (478 - 752) is -274\n\n####-274", "a": 478, "b": 752, "operator": "-", "result": -274}
{"question": "Solve (399 - 8)", "answer": "The result of (399 - 8) is 391\n\n####391", "a": 399, "b": 8, "operator": "-", "result": 391}
{"question": "Solve (171 * 588)", "answer": "The result of (171 * 588) is 100548\n\n####100548", "a": 171, "b": 588, "operator": "*", "result": 100548}
{"question": "Solve (149 - 749)", "answer": "The result of (149 - 749) is -600\n\n####-600", "a": 149, "b": 749, "operator": "-", "result": -600}
{"question": "Solve (911 - 64)", "answer": "The result of (911 - 64) is 847\n\n####847", "a": 911, "b": 64, "operator": "-", "result": 847}
{"question": "Solve (649 / 224)", "answer": "The result of (649 / 224) is 2.8973\n\n####2.8973", "a": 649, "b": 224, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8973}
{"question": "Solve (697 - 768)", "answer": "The result of (697 - 768) is -71\n\n####-71", "a": 697, "b": 768, "operator": "-", "result": -71}
{"question": "Solve (2 + 401)", "answer": "The result of (2 + 401) is 403\n\n####403", "a": 2, "b": 401, "operator": "+", "result": 403}
{"question": "Solve (578 / 758)", "answer": "The result of (578 / 758) is 0.7625\n\n####0.7625", "a": 578, "b": 758, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7625}
{"question": "Solve (585 + 616)", "answer": "The result of (585 + 616) is 1201\n\n####1201", "a": 585, "b": 616, "operator": "+", "result": 1201}
{"question": "Solve (490 * 100)", "answer": "The result of (490 * 100) is 49000\n\n####49000", "a": 490, "b": 100, "operator": "*", "result": 49000}
{"question": "Solve (697 * 951)", "answer": "The result of (697 * 951) is 662847\n\n####662847", "a": 697, "b": 951, "operator": "*", "result": 662847}
{"question": "Solve (126 * 616)", "answer": "The result of (126 * 616) is 77616\n\n####77616", "a": 126, "b": 616, "operator": "*", "result": 77616}
{"question": "Solve (885 - 305)", "answer": "The result of (885 - 305) is 580\n\n####580", "a": 885, "b": 305, "operator": "-", "result": 580}
{"question": "Solve (226 + 990)", "answer": "The result of (226 + 990) is 1216\n\n####1216", "a": 226, "b": 990, "operator": "+", "result": 1216}
{"question": "Solve (414 * 984)", "answer": "The result of (414 * 984) is 407376\n\n####407376", "a": 414, "b": 984, "operator": "*", "result": 407376}
{"question": "Solve (360 - 606)", "answer": "The result of (360 - 606) is -246\n\n####-246", "a": 360, "b": 606, "operator": "-", "result": -246}
{"question": "Solve (535 / 598)", "answer": "The result of (535 / 598) is 0.8946\n\n####0.8946", "a": 535, "b": 598, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8946}
{"question": "Solve (285 - 85)", "answer": "The result of (285 - 85) is 200\n\n####200", "a": 285, "b": 85, "operator": "-", "result": 200}
{"question": "Solve (368 + 80)", "answer": "The result of (368 + 80) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 368, "b": 80, "operator": "+", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (860 + 115)", "answer": "The result of (860 + 115) is 975\n\n####975", "a": 860, "b": 115, "operator": "+", "result": 975}
{"question": "Solve (670 * 443)", "answer": "The result of (670 * 443) is 296810\n\n####296810", "a": 670, "b": 443, "operator": "*", "result": 296810}
{"question": "Solve (306 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (306 / 852) is 0.3592\n\n####0.3592", "a": 306, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3592}
{"question": "Solve (640 * 513)", "answer": "The result of (640 * 513) is 328320\n\n####328320", "a": 640, "b": 513, "operator": "*", "result": 328320}
{"question": "Solve (848 + 677)", "answer": "The result of (848 + 677) is 1525\n\n####1525", "a": 848, "b": 677, "operator": "+", "result": 1525}
{"question": "Solve (977 / 70)", "answer": "The result of (977 / 70) is 13.9571\n\n####13.9571", "a": 977, "b": 70, "operator": "/", "result": 13.9571}
{"question": "Solve (927 - 682)", "answer": "The result of (927 - 682) is 245\n\n####245", "a": 927, "b": 682, "operator": "-", "result": 245}
{"question": "Solve (776 * 264)", "answer": "The result of (776 * 264) is 204864\n\n####204864", "a": 776, "b": 264, "operator": "*", "result": 204864}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 515)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 515) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 615, "b": 515, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (100 + 954)", "answer": "The result of (100 + 954) is 1054\n\n####1054", "a": 100, "b": 954, "operator": "+", "result": 1054}
{"question": "Solve (96 - 309)", "answer": "The result of (96 - 309) is -213\n\n####-213", "a": 96, "b": 309, "operator": "-", "result": -213}
{"question": "Solve (859 * 842)", "answer": "The result of (859 * 842) is 723278\n\n####723278", "a": 859, "b": 842, "operator": "*", "result": 723278}
{"question": "Solve (681 / 396)", "answer": "The result of (681 / 396) is 1.7197\n\n####1.7197", "a": 681, "b": 396, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7197}
{"question": "Solve (407 / 594)", "answer": "The result of (407 / 594) is 0.6852\n\n####0.6852", "a": 407, "b": 594, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6852}
{"question": "Solve (393 / 743)", "answer": "The result of (393 / 743) is 0.5289\n\n####0.5289", "a": 393, "b": 743, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5289}
{"question": "Solve (681 - 901)", "answer": "The result of (681 - 901) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 681, "b": 901, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (408 * 731)", "answer": "The result of (408 * 731) is 298248\n\n####298248", "a": 408, "b": 731, "operator": "*", "result": 298248}
{"question": "Solve (627 * 975)", "answer": "The result of (627 * 975) is 611325\n\n####611325", "a": 627, "b": 975, "operator": "*", "result": 611325}
{"question": "Solve (175 * 750)", "answer": "The result of (175 * 750) is 131250\n\n####131250", "a": 175, "b": 750, "operator": "*", "result": 131250}
{"question": "Solve (928 * 444)", "answer": "The result of (928 * 444) is 412032\n\n####412032", "a": 928, "b": 444, "operator": "*", "result": 412032}
{"question": "Solve (670 * 866)", "answer": "The result of (670 * 866) is 580220\n\n####580220", "a": 670, "b": 866, "operator": "*", "result": 580220}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 768)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 768) is 450048\n\n####450048", "a": 586, "b": 768, "operator": "*", "result": 450048}
{"question": "Solve (787 / 335)", "answer": "The result of (787 / 335) is 2.3493\n\n####2.3493", "a": 787, "b": 335, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3493}
{"question": "Solve (17 / 641)", "answer": "The result of (17 / 641) is 0.0265\n\n####0.0265", "a": 17, "b": 641, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0265}
{"question": "Solve (767 - 764)", "answer": "The result of (767 - 764) is 3\n\n####3", "a": 767, "b": 764, "operator": "-", "result": 3}
{"question": "Solve (168 - 936)", "answer": "The result of (168 - 936) is -768\n\n####-768", "a": 168, "b": 936, "operator": "-", "result": -768}
{"question": "Solve (277 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (277 - 27) is 250\n\n####250", "a": 277, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 250}
{"question": "Solve (856 * 295)", "answer": "The result of (856 * 295) is 252520\n\n####252520", "a": 856, "b": 295, "operator": "*", "result": 252520}
{"question": "Solve (595 + 241)", "answer": "The result of (595 + 241) is 836\n\n####836", "a": 595, "b": 241, "operator": "+", "result": 836}
{"question": "Solve (996 * 300)", "answer": "The result of (996 * 300) is 298800\n\n####298800", "a": 996, "b": 300, "operator": "*", "result": 298800}
{"question": "Solve (603 + 654)", "answer": "The result of (603 + 654) is 1257\n\n####1257", "a": 603, "b": 654, "operator": "+", "result": 1257}
{"question": "Solve (870 * 619)", "answer": "The result of (870 * 619) is 538530\n\n####538530", "a": 870, "b": 619, "operator": "*", "result": 538530}
{"question": "Solve (267 / 362)", "answer": "The result of (267 / 362) is 0.7376\n\n####0.7376", "a": 267, "b": 362, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7376}
{"question": "Solve (988 + 512)", "answer": "The result of (988 + 512) is 1500\n\n####1500", "a": 988, "b": 512, "operator": "+", "result": 1500}
{"question": "Solve (732 - 623)", "answer": "The result of (732 - 623) is 109\n\n####109", "a": 732, "b": 623, "operator": "-", "result": 109}
{"question": "Solve (188 * 341)", "answer": "The result of (188 * 341) is 64108\n\n####64108", "a": 188, "b": 341, "operator": "*", "result": 64108}
{"question": "Solve (701 + 135)", "answer": "The result of (701 + 135) is 836\n\n####836", "a": 701, "b": 135, "operator": "+", "result": 836}
{"question": "Solve (967 / 256)", "answer": "The result of (967 / 256) is 3.7773\n\n####3.7773", "a": 967, "b": 256, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7773}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 623)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 623) is 98\n\n####98", "a": 721, "b": 623, "operator": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve (295 / 809)", "answer": "The result of (295 / 809) is 0.3646\n\n####0.3646", "a": 295, "b": 809, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3646}
{"question": "Solve (563 + 801)", "answer": "The result of (563 + 801) is 1364\n\n####1364", "a": 563, "b": 801, "operator": "+", "result": 1364}
{"question": "Solve (37 * 657)", "answer": "The result of (37 * 657) is 24309\n\n####24309", "a": 37, "b": 657, "operator": "*", "result": 24309}
{"question": "Solve (964 * 38)", "answer": "The result of (964 * 38) is 36632\n\n####36632", "a": 964, "b": 38, "operator": "*", "result": 36632}
{"question": "Solve (49 + 956)", "answer": "The result of (49 + 956) is 1005\n\n####1005", "a": 49, "b": 956, "operator": "+", "result": 1005}
{"question": "Solve (587 * 674)", "answer": "The result of (587 * 674) is 395638\n\n####395638", "a": 587, "b": 674, "operator": "*", "result": 395638}
{"question": "Solve (963 - 70)", "answer": "The result of (963 - 70) is 893\n\n####893", "a": 963, "b": 70, "operator": "-", "result": 893}
{"question": "Solve (956 + 481)", "answer": "The result of (956 + 481) is 1437\n\n####1437", "a": 956, "b": 481, "operator": "+", "result": 1437}
{"question": "Solve (863 + 736)", "answer": "The result of (863 + 736) is 1599\n\n####1599", "a": 863, "b": 736, "operator": "+", "result": 1599}
{"question": "Solve (765 * 706)", "answer": "The result of (765 * 706) is 540090\n\n####540090", "a": 765, "b": 706, "operator": "*", "result": 540090}
{"question": "Solve (838 + 361)", "answer": "The result of (838 + 361) is 1199\n\n####1199", "a": 838, "b": 361, "operator": "+", "result": 1199}
{"question": "Solve (403 / 258)", "answer": "The result of (403 / 258) is 1.562\n\n####1.562", "a": 403, "b": 258, "operator": "/", "result": 1.562}
{"question": "Solve (896 / 203)", "answer": "The result of (896 / 203) is 4.4138\n\n####4.4138", "a": 896, "b": 203, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4138}
{"question": "Solve (956 * 448)", "answer": "The result of (956 * 448) is 428288\n\n####428288", "a": 956, "b": 448, "operator": "*", "result": 428288}
{"question": "Solve (63 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (63 / 427) is 0.1475\n\n####0.1475", "a": 63, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1475}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 920)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 920) is 467360\n\n####467360", "a": 508, "b": 920, "operator": "*", "result": 467360}
{"question": "Solve (81 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (81 / 206) is 0.3932\n\n####0.3932", "a": 81, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3932}
{"question": "Solve (854 - 437)", "answer": "The result of (854 - 437) is 417\n\n####417", "a": 854, "b": 437, "operator": "-", "result": 417}
{"question": "Solve (294 + 988)", "answer": "The result of (294 + 988) is 1282\n\n####1282", "a": 294, "b": 988, "operator": "+", "result": 1282}
{"question": "Solve (237 / 820)", "answer": "The result of (237 / 820) is 0.289\n\n####0.289", "a": 237, "b": 820, "operator": "/", "result": 0.289}
{"question": "Solve (834 + 936)", "answer": "The result of (834 + 936) is 1770\n\n####1770", "a": 834, "b": 936, "operator": "+", "result": 1770}
{"question": "Solve (631 - 809)", "answer": "The result of (631 - 809) is -178\n\n####-178", "a": 631, "b": 809, "operator": "-", "result": -178}
{"question": "Solve (84 + 390)", "answer": "The result of (84 + 390) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 84, "b": 390, "operator": "+", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (267 * 812)", "answer": "The result of (267 * 812) is 216804\n\n####216804", "a": 267, "b": 812, "operator": "*", "result": 216804}
{"question": "Solve (833 / 994)", "answer": "The result of (833 / 994) is 0.838\n\n####0.838", "a": 833, "b": 994, "operator": "/", "result": 0.838}
{"question": "Solve (204 + 314)", "answer": "The result of (204 + 314) is 518\n\n####518", "a": 204, "b": 314, "operator": "+", "result": 518}
{"question": "Solve (961 * 706)", "answer": "The result of (961 * 706) is 678466\n\n####678466", "a": 961, "b": 706, "operator": "*", "result": 678466}
{"question": "Solve (883 + 958)", "answer": "The result of (883 + 958) is 1841\n\n####1841", "a": 883, "b": 958, "operator": "+", "result": 1841}
{"question": "Solve (186 - 33)", "answer": "The result of (186 - 33) is 153\n\n####153", "a": 186, "b": 33, "operator": "-", "result": 153}
{"question": "Solve (110 + 394)", "answer": "The result of (110 + 394) is 504\n\n####504", "a": 110, "b": 394, "operator": "+", "result": 504}
{"question": "Solve (834 - 191)", "answer": "The result of (834 - 191) is 643\n\n####643", "a": 834, "b": 191, "operator": "-", "result": 643}
{"question": "Solve (313 - 625)", "answer": "The result of (313 - 625) is -312\n\n####-312", "a": 313, "b": 625, "operator": "-", "result": -312}
{"question": "Solve (324 / 64)", "answer": "The result of (324 / 64) is 5.0625\n\n####5.0625", "a": 324, "b": 64, "operator": "/", "result": 5.0625}
{"question": "Solve (3 - 443)", "answer": "The result of (3 - 443) is -440\n\n####-440", "a": 3, "b": 443, "operator": "-", "result": -440}
{"question": "Solve (70 + 958)", "answer": "The result of (70 + 958) is 1028\n\n####1028", "a": 70, "b": 958, "operator": "+", "result": 1028}
{"question": "Solve (184 + 633)", "answer": "The result of (184 + 633) is 817\n\n####817", "a": 184, "b": 633, "operator": "+", "result": 817}
{"question": "Solve (270 * 839)", "answer": "The result of (270 * 839) is 226530\n\n####226530", "a": 270, "b": 839, "operator": "*", "result": 226530}
{"question": "Solve (553 + 378)", "answer": "The result of (553 + 378) is 931\n\n####931", "a": 553, "b": 378, "operator": "+", "result": 931}
{"question": "Solve (112 - 474)", "answer": "The result of (112 - 474) is -362\n\n####-362", "a": 112, "b": 474, "operator": "-", "result": -362}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 324)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 324) is 28836\n\n####28836", "a": 89, "b": 324, "operator": "*", "result": 28836}
{"question": "Solve (650 + 175)", "answer": "The result of (650 + 175) is 825\n\n####825", "a": 650, "b": 175, "operator": "+", "result": 825}
{"question": "Solve (253 + 579)", "answer": "The result of (253 + 579) is 832\n\n####832", "a": 253, "b": 579, "operator": "+", "result": 832}
{"question": "Solve (786 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (786 - 634) is 152\n\n####152", "a": 786, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 206) is 770\n\n####770", "a": 976, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": 770}
{"question": "Solve (504 - 494)", "answer": "The result of (504 - 494) is 10\n\n####10", "a": 504, "b": 494, "operator": "-", "result": 10}
{"question": "Solve (521 - 808)", "answer": "The result of (521 - 808) is -287\n\n####-287", "a": 521, "b": 808, "operator": "-", "result": -287}
{"question": "Solve (6 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (6 - 295) is -289\n\n####-289", "a": 6, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": -289}
{"question": "Solve (761 - 886)", "answer": "The result of (761 - 886) is -125\n\n####-125", "a": 761, "b": 886, "operator": "-", "result": -125}
{"question": "Solve (616 - 801)", "answer": "The result of (616 - 801) is -185\n\n####-185", "a": 616, "b": 801, "operator": "-", "result": -185}
{"question": "Solve (50 / 791)", "answer": "The result of (50 / 791) is 0.0632\n\n####0.0632", "a": 50, "b": 791, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0632}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 145) is 90770\n\n####90770", "a": 626, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 90770}
{"question": "Solve (523 / 952)", "answer": "The result of (523 / 952) is 0.5494\n\n####0.5494", "a": 523, "b": 952, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5494}
{"question": "Solve (993 - 434)", "answer": "The result of (993 - 434) is 559\n\n####559", "a": 993, "b": 434, "operator": "-", "result": 559}
{"question": "Solve (947 + 488)", "answer": "The result of (947 + 488) is 1435\n\n####1435", "a": 947, "b": 488, "operator": "+", "result": 1435}
{"question": "Solve (604 - 540)", "answer": "The result of (604 - 540) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 604, "b": 540, "operator": "-", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (255 + 710)", "answer": "The result of (255 + 710) is 965\n\n####965", "a": 255, "b": 710, "operator": "+", "result": 965}
{"question": "Solve (625 * 185)", "answer": "The result of (625 * 185) is 115625\n\n####115625", "a": 625, "b": 185, "operator": "*", "result": 115625}
{"question": "Solve (801 - 450)", "answer": "The result of (801 - 450) is 351\n\n####351", "a": 801, "b": 450, "operator": "-", "result": 351}
{"question": "Solve (845 / 656)", "answer": "The result of (845 / 656) is 1.2881\n\n####1.2881", "a": 845, "b": 656, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2881}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 645)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 645) is 293\n\n####293", "a": 938, "b": 645, "operator": "-", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve (435 + 254)", "answer": "The result of (435 + 254) is 689\n\n####689", "a": 435, "b": 254, "operator": "+", "result": 689}
{"question": "Solve (644 * 620)", "answer": "The result of (644 * 620) is 399280\n\n####399280", "a": 644, "b": 620, "operator": "*", "result": 399280}
{"question": "Solve (330 * 469)", "answer": "The result of (330 * 469) is 154770\n\n####154770", "a": 330, "b": 469, "operator": "*", "result": 154770}
{"question": "Solve (609 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (609 / 299) is 2.0368\n\n####2.0368", "a": 609, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0368}
{"question": "Solve (82 * 977)", "answer": "The result of (82 * 977) is 80114\n\n####80114", "a": 82, "b": 977, "operator": "*", "result": 80114}
{"question": "Solve (410 - 349)", "answer": "The result of (410 - 349) is 61\n\n####61", "a": 410, "b": 349, "operator": "-", "result": 61}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 66)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 66) is 570\n\n####570", "a": 636, "b": 66, "operator": "-", "result": 570}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 26)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 26) is 0.3846\n\n####0.3846", "a": 10, "b": 26, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3846}
{"question": "Solve (959 / 849)", "answer": "The result of (959 / 849) is 1.1296\n\n####1.1296", "a": 959, "b": 849, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1296}
{"question": "Solve (961 - 487)", "answer": "The result of (961 - 487) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 961, "b": 487, "operator": "-", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (570 * 559)", "answer": "The result of (570 * 559) is 318630\n\n####318630", "a": 570, "b": 559, "operator": "*", "result": 318630}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 802) is -350\n\n####-350", "a": 452, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -350}
{"question": "Solve (773 / 30)", "answer": "The result of (773 / 30) is 25.7667\n\n####25.7667", "a": 773, "b": 30, "operator": "/", "result": 25.7667}
{"question": "Solve (101 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (101 - 949) is -848\n\n####-848", "a": 101, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -848}
{"question": "Solve (975 - 959)", "answer": "The result of (975 - 959) is 16\n\n####16", "a": 975, "b": 959, "operator": "-", "result": 16}
{"question": "Solve (374 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (374 - 745) is -371\n\n####-371", "a": 374, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": -371}
{"question": "Solve (388 * 525)", "answer": "The result of (388 * 525) is 203700\n\n####203700", "a": 388, "b": 525, "operator": "*", "result": 203700}
{"question": "Solve (445 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (445 / 674) is 0.6602\n\n####0.6602", "a": 445, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6602}
{"question": "Solve (451 / 843)", "answer": "The result of (451 / 843) is 0.535\n\n####0.535", "a": 451, "b": 843, "operator": "/", "result": 0.535}
{"question": "Solve (551 * 434)", "answer": "The result of (551 * 434) is 239134\n\n####239134", "a": 551, "b": 434, "operator": "*", "result": 239134}
{"question": "Solve (948 + 157)", "answer": "The result of (948 + 157) is 1105\n\n####1105", "a": 948, "b": 157, "operator": "+", "result": 1105}
{"question": "Solve (329 * 938)", "answer": "The result of (329 * 938) is 308602\n\n####308602", "a": 329, "b": 938, "operator": "*", "result": 308602}
{"question": "Solve (806 * 881)", "answer": "The result of (806 * 881) is 710086\n\n####710086", "a": 806, "b": 881, "operator": "*", "result": 710086}
{"question": "Solve (914 - 814)", "answer": "The result of (914 - 814) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 914, "b": 814, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (45 / 350)", "answer": "The result of (45 / 350) is 0.1286\n\n####0.1286", "a": 45, "b": 350, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1286}
{"question": "Solve (120 - 570)", "answer": "The result of (120 - 570) is -450\n\n####-450", "a": 120, "b": 570, "operator": "-", "result": -450}
{"question": "Solve (103 * 927)", "answer": "The result of (103 * 927) is 95481\n\n####95481", "a": 103, "b": 927, "operator": "*", "result": 95481}
{"question": "Solve (416 - 838)", "answer": "The result of (416 - 838) is -422\n\n####-422", "a": 416, "b": 838, "operator": "-", "result": -422}
{"question": "Solve (317 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (317 * 102) is 32334\n\n####32334", "a": 317, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 32334}
{"question": "Solve (758 / 418)", "answer": "The result of (758 / 418) is 1.8134\n\n####1.8134", "a": 758, "b": 418, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8134}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 262)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 262) is 0.5153\n\n####0.5153", "a": 135, "b": 262, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5153}
{"question": "Solve (123 * 260)", "answer": "The result of (123 * 260) is 31980\n\n####31980", "a": 123, "b": 260, "operator": "*", "result": 31980}
{"question": "Solve (828 / 719)", "answer": "The result of (828 / 719) is 1.1516\n\n####1.1516", "a": 828, "b": 719, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1516}
{"question": "Solve (442 + 274)", "answer": "The result of (442 + 274) is 716\n\n####716", "a": 442, "b": 274, "operator": "+", "result": 716}
{"question": "Solve (632 - 591)", "answer": "The result of (632 - 591) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 632, "b": 591, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (543 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (543 / 489) is 1.1104\n\n####1.1104", "a": 543, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1104}
{"question": "Solve (897 + 206)", "answer": "The result of (897 + 206) is 1103\n\n####1103", "a": 897, "b": 206, "operator": "+", "result": 1103}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 246)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 246) is 149568\n\n####149568", "a": 608, "b": 246, "operator": "*", "result": 149568}
{"question": "Solve (875 - 671)", "answer": "The result of (875 - 671) is 204\n\n####204", "a": 875, "b": 671, "operator": "-", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve (881 - 329)", "answer": "The result of (881 - 329) is 552\n\n####552", "a": 881, "b": 329, "operator": "-", "result": 552}
{"question": "Solve (784 / 731)", "answer": "The result of (784 / 731) is 1.0725\n\n####1.0725", "a": 784, "b": 731, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0725}
{"question": "Solve (204 * 888)", "answer": "The result of (204 * 888) is 181152\n\n####181152", "a": 204, "b": 888, "operator": "*", "result": 181152}
{"question": "Solve (309 + 247)", "answer": "The result of (309 + 247) is 556\n\n####556", "a": 309, "b": 247, "operator": "+", "result": 556}
{"question": "Solve (868 - 281)", "answer": "The result of (868 - 281) is 587\n\n####587", "a": 868, "b": 281, "operator": "-", "result": 587}
{"question": "Solve (173 - 392)", "answer": "The result of (173 - 392) is -219\n\n####-219", "a": 173, "b": 392, "operator": "-", "result": -219}
{"question": "Solve (185 + 946)", "answer": "The result of (185 + 946) is 1131\n\n####1131", "a": 185, "b": 946, "operator": "+", "result": 1131}
{"question": "Solve (762 * 654)", "answer": "The result of (762 * 654) is 498348\n\n####498348", "a": 762, "b": 654, "operator": "*", "result": 498348}
{"question": "Solve (714 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (714 / 885) is 0.8068\n\n####0.8068", "a": 714, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8068}
{"question": "Solve (231 / 510)", "answer": "The result of (231 / 510) is 0.4529\n\n####0.4529", "a": 231, "b": 510, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4529}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 307)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 307) is 146\n\n####146", "a": 453, "b": 307, "operator": "-", "result": 146}
{"question": "Solve (13 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (13 - 169) is -156\n\n####-156", "a": 13, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": -156}
{"question": "Solve (406 * 142)", "answer": "The result of (406 * 142) is 57652\n\n####57652", "a": 406, "b": 142, "operator": "*", "result": 57652}
{"question": "Solve (25 - 596)", "answer": "The result of (25 - 596) is -571\n\n####-571", "a": 25, "b": 596, "operator": "-", "result": -571}
{"question": "Solve (249 * 156)", "answer": "The result of (249 * 156) is 38844\n\n####38844", "a": 249, "b": 156, "operator": "*", "result": 38844}
{"question": "Solve (951 + 96)", "answer": "The result of (951 + 96) is 1047\n\n####1047", "a": 951, "b": 96, "operator": "+", "result": 1047}
{"question": "Solve (493 - 429)", "answer": "The result of (493 - 429) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 493, "b": 429, "operator": "-", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (358 + 288)", "answer": "The result of (358 + 288) is 646\n\n####646", "a": 358, "b": 288, "operator": "+", "result": 646}
{"question": "Solve (789 - 892)", "answer": "The result of (789 - 892) is -103\n\n####-103", "a": 789, "b": 892, "operator": "-", "result": -103}
{"question": "Solve (403 + 979)", "answer": "The result of (403 + 979) is 1382\n\n####1382", "a": 403, "b": 979, "operator": "+", "result": 1382}
{"question": "Solve (601 / 95)", "answer": "The result of (601 / 95) is 6.3263\n\n####6.3263", "a": 601, "b": 95, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3263}
{"question": "Solve (811 / 31)", "answer": "The result of (811 / 31) is 26.1613\n\n####26.1613", "a": 811, "b": 31, "operator": "/", "result": 26.1613}
{"question": "Solve (217 + 592)", "answer": "The result of (217 + 592) is 809\n\n####809", "a": 217, "b": 592, "operator": "+", "result": 809}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 695)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 695) is -259\n\n####-259", "a": 436, "b": 695, "operator": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve (328 + 339)", "answer": "The result of (328 + 339) is 667\n\n####667", "a": 328, "b": 339, "operator": "+", "result": 667}
{"question": "Solve (984 - 811)", "answer": "The result of (984 - 811) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 984, "b": 811, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (975 / 533)", "answer": "The result of (975 / 533) is 1.8293\n\n####1.8293", "a": 975, "b": 533, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8293}
{"question": "Solve (9 + 996)", "answer": "The result of (9 + 996) is 1005\n\n####1005", "a": 9, "b": 996, "operator": "+", "result": 1005}
{"question": "Solve (932 - 660)", "answer": "The result of (932 - 660) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 932, "b": 660, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (629 / 538)", "answer": "The result of (629 / 538) is 1.1691\n\n####1.1691", "a": 629, "b": 538, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1691}
{"question": "Solve (240 - 444)", "answer": "The result of (240 - 444) is -204\n\n####-204", "a": 240, "b": 444, "operator": "-", "result": -204}
{"question": "Solve (458 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (458 - 745) is -287\n\n####-287", "a": 458, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": -287}
{"question": "Solve (655 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (655 - 166) is 489\n\n####489", "a": 655, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 489}
{"question": "Solve (417 / 186)", "answer": "The result of (417 / 186) is 2.2419\n\n####2.2419", "a": 417, "b": 186, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2419}
{"question": "Solve (142 * 127)", "answer": "The result of (142 * 127) is 18034\n\n####18034", "a": 142, "b": 127, "operator": "*", "result": 18034}
{"question": "Solve (912 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (912 - 168) is 744\n\n####744", "a": 912, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": 744}
{"question": "Solve (868 + 327)", "answer": "The result of (868 + 327) is 1195\n\n####1195", "a": 868, "b": 327, "operator": "+", "result": 1195}
{"question": "Solve (635 + 512)", "answer": "The result of (635 + 512) is 1147\n\n####1147", "a": 635, "b": 512, "operator": "+", "result": 1147}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 48)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 48) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 675, "b": 48, "operator": "-", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (927 / 870)", "answer": "The result of (927 / 870) is 1.0655\n\n####1.0655", "a": 927, "b": 870, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0655}
{"question": "Solve (106 + 510)", "answer": "The result of (106 + 510) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 106, "b": 510, "operator": "+", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (587 / 976)", "answer": "The result of (587 / 976) is 0.6014\n\n####0.6014", "a": 587, "b": 976, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6014}
{"question": "Solve (109 + 10)", "answer": "The result of (109 + 10) is 119\n\n####119", "a": 109, "b": 10, "operator": "+", "result": 119}
{"question": "Solve (843 - 889)", "answer": "The result of (843 - 889) is -46\n\n####-46", "a": 843, "b": 889, "operator": "-", "result": -46}
{"question": "Solve (278 - 437)", "answer": "The result of (278 - 437) is -159\n\n####-159", "a": 278, "b": 437, "operator": "-", "result": -159}
{"question": "Solve (425 - 1)", "answer": "The result of (425 - 1) is 424\n\n####424", "a": 425, "b": 1, "operator": "-", "result": 424}
{"question": "Solve (837 / 155)", "answer": "The result of (837 / 155) is 5.4\n\n####5.4", "a": 837, "b": 155, "operator": "/", "result": 5.4}
{"question": "Solve (559 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (559 + 380) is 939\n\n####939", "a": 559, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 939}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 242)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 242) is 2.8802\n\n####2.8802", "a": 697, "b": 242, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8802}
{"question": "Solve (211 / 715)", "answer": "The result of (211 / 715) is 0.2951\n\n####0.2951", "a": 211, "b": 715, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2951}
{"question": "Solve (524 / 691)", "answer": "The result of (524 / 691) is 0.7583\n\n####0.7583", "a": 524, "b": 691, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7583}
{"question": "Solve (269 * 403)", "answer": "The result of (269 * 403) is 108407\n\n####108407", "a": 269, "b": 403, "operator": "*", "result": 108407}
{"question": "Solve (126 / 48)", "answer": "The result of (126 / 48) is 2.625\n\n####2.625", "a": 126, "b": 48, "operator": "/", "result": 2.625}
{"question": "Solve (418 / 851)", "answer": "The result of (418 / 851) is 0.4912\n\n####0.4912", "a": 418, "b": 851, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4912}
{"question": "Solve (549 - 461)", "answer": "The result of (549 - 461) is 88\n\n####88", "a": 549, "b": 461, "operator": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve (30 / 913)", "answer": "The result of (30 / 913) is 0.0329\n\n####0.0329", "a": 30, "b": 913, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0329}
{"question": "Solve (567 - 395)", "answer": "The result of (567 - 395) is 172\n\n####172", "a": 567, "b": 395, "operator": "-", "result": 172}
{"question": "Solve (230 + 125)", "answer": "The result of (230 + 125) is 355\n\n####355", "a": 230, "b": 125, "operator": "+", "result": 355}
{"question": "Solve (701 * 586)", "answer": "The result of (701 * 586) is 410786\n\n####410786", "a": 701, "b": 586, "operator": "*", "result": 410786}
{"question": "Solve (322 / 699)", "answer": "The result of (322 / 699) is 0.4607\n\n####0.4607", "a": 322, "b": 699, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4607}
{"question": "Solve (426 / 789)", "answer": "The result of (426 / 789) is 0.5399\n\n####0.5399", "a": 426, "b": 789, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5399}
{"question": "Solve (609 * 442)", "answer": "The result of (609 * 442) is 269178\n\n####269178", "a": 609, "b": 442, "operator": "*", "result": 269178}
{"question": "Solve (541 + 62)", "answer": "The result of (541 + 62) is 603\n\n####603", "a": 541, "b": 62, "operator": "+", "result": 603}
{"question": "Solve (637 - 78)", "answer": "The result of (637 - 78) is 559\n\n####559", "a": 637, "b": 78, "operator": "-", "result": 559}
{"question": "Solve (237 * 379)", "answer": "The result of (237 * 379) is 89823\n\n####89823", "a": 237, "b": 379, "operator": "*", "result": 89823}
{"question": "Solve (886 * 492)", "answer": "The result of (886 * 492) is 435912\n\n####435912", "a": 886, "b": 492, "operator": "*", "result": 435912}
{"question": "Solve (201 * 131)", "answer": "The result of (201 * 131) is 26331\n\n####26331", "a": 201, "b": 131, "operator": "*", "result": 26331}
{"question": "Solve (13 / 568)", "answer": "The result of (13 / 568) is 0.0229\n\n####0.0229", "a": 13, "b": 568, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0229}
{"question": "Solve (386 * 213)", "answer": "The result of (386 * 213) is 82218\n\n####82218", "a": 386, "b": 213, "operator": "*", "result": 82218}
{"question": "Solve (113 * 148)", "answer": "The result of (113 * 148) is 16724\n\n####16724", "a": 113, "b": 148, "operator": "*", "result": 16724}
{"question": "Solve (908 - 981)", "answer": "The result of (908 - 981) is -73\n\n####-73", "a": 908, "b": 981, "operator": "-", "result": -73}
{"question": "Solve (423 / 10)", "answer": "The result of (423 / 10) is 42.3\n\n####42.3", "a": 423, "b": 10, "operator": "/", "result": 42.3}
{"question": "Solve (718 + 608)", "answer": "The result of (718 + 608) is 1326\n\n####1326", "a": 718, "b": 608, "operator": "+", "result": 1326}
{"question": "Solve (195 - 303)", "answer": "The result of (195 - 303) is -108\n\n####-108", "a": 195, "b": 303, "operator": "-", "result": -108}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 263)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 263) is 703\n\n####703", "a": 966, "b": 263, "operator": "-", "result": 703}
{"question": "Solve (666 - 481)", "answer": "The result of (666 - 481) is 185\n\n####185", "a": 666, "b": 481, "operator": "-", "result": 185}
{"question": "Solve (227 * 957)", "answer": "The result of (227 * 957) is 217239\n\n####217239", "a": 227, "b": 957, "operator": "*", "result": 217239}
{"question": "Solve (574 - 988)", "answer": "The result of (574 - 988) is -414\n\n####-414", "a": 574, "b": 988, "operator": "-", "result": -414}
{"question": "Solve (86 * 475)", "answer": "The result of (86 * 475) is 40850\n\n####40850", "a": 86, "b": 475, "operator": "*", "result": 40850}
{"question": "Solve (777 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (777 - 262) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 777, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (689 + 940)", "answer": "The result of (689 + 940) is 1629\n\n####1629", "a": 689, "b": 940, "operator": "+", "result": 1629}
{"question": "Solve (391 - 683)", "answer": "The result of (391 - 683) is -292\n\n####-292", "a": 391, "b": 683, "operator": "-", "result": -292}
{"question": "Solve (403 * 153)", "answer": "The result of (403 * 153) is 61659\n\n####61659", "a": 403, "b": 153, "operator": "*", "result": 61659}
{"question": "Solve (313 / 814)", "answer": "The result of (313 / 814) is 0.3845\n\n####0.3845", "a": 313, "b": 814, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3845}
{"question": "Solve (774 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (774 * 548) is 424152\n\n####424152", "a": 774, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 424152}
{"question": "Solve (56 * 765)", "answer": "The result of (56 * 765) is 42840\n\n####42840", "a": 56, "b": 765, "operator": "*", "result": 42840}
{"question": "Solve (250 - 898)", "answer": "The result of (250 - 898) is -648\n\n####-648", "a": 250, "b": 898, "operator": "-", "result": -648}
{"question": "Solve (792 + 415)", "answer": "The result of (792 + 415) is 1207\n\n####1207", "a": 792, "b": 415, "operator": "+", "result": 1207}
{"question": "Solve (122 + 479)", "answer": "The result of (122 + 479) is 601\n\n####601", "a": 122, "b": 479, "operator": "+", "result": 601}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 466)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 466) is 472\n\n####472", "a": 938, "b": 466, "operator": "-", "result": 472}
{"question": "Solve (217 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (217 / 885) is 0.2452\n\n####0.2452", "a": 217, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2452}
{"question": "Solve (942 * 876)", "answer": "The result of (942 * 876) is 825192\n\n####825192", "a": 942, "b": 876, "operator": "*", "result": 825192}
{"question": "Solve (616 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (616 / 885) is 0.696\n\n####0.696", "a": 616, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.696}
{"question": "Solve (221 - 373)", "answer": "The result of (221 - 373) is -152\n\n####-152", "a": 221, "b": 373, "operator": "-", "result": -152}
{"question": "Solve (104 / 846)", "answer": "The result of (104 / 846) is 0.1229\n\n####0.1229", "a": 104, "b": 846, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1229}
{"question": "Solve (372 + 717)", "answer": "The result of (372 + 717) is 1089\n\n####1089", "a": 372, "b": 717, "operator": "+", "result": 1089}
{"question": "Solve (875 + 71)", "answer": "The result of (875 + 71) is 946\n\n####946", "a": 875, "b": 71, "operator": "+", "result": 946}
{"question": "Solve (70 / 596)", "answer": "The result of (70 / 596) is 0.1174\n\n####0.1174", "a": 70, "b": 596, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1174}
{"question": "Solve (535 + 593)", "answer": "The result of (535 + 593) is 1128\n\n####1128", "a": 535, "b": 593, "operator": "+", "result": 1128}
{"question": "Solve (677 * 906)", "answer": "The result of (677 * 906) is 613362\n\n####613362", "a": 677, "b": 906, "operator": "*", "result": 613362}
{"question": "Solve (811 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (811 + 843) is 1654\n\n####1654", "a": 811, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 1654}
{"question": "Solve (107 * 48)", "answer": "The result of (107 * 48) is 5136\n\n####5136", "a": 107, "b": 48, "operator": "*", "result": 5136}
{"question": "Solve (753 - 651)", "answer": "The result of (753 - 651) is 102\n\n####102", "a": 753, "b": 651, "operator": "-", "result": 102}
{"question": "Solve (513 * 691)", "answer": "The result of (513 * 691) is 354483\n\n####354483", "a": 513, "b": 691, "operator": "*", "result": 354483}
{"question": "Solve (419 / 603)", "answer": "The result of (419 / 603) is 0.6949\n\n####0.6949", "a": 419, "b": 603, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6949}
{"question": "Solve (958 + 281)", "answer": "The result of (958 + 281) is 1239\n\n####1239", "a": 958, "b": 281, "operator": "+", "result": 1239}
{"question": "Solve (916 - 923)", "answer": "The result of (916 - 923) is -7\n\n####-7", "a": 916, "b": 923, "operator": "-", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve (454 - 198)", "answer": "The result of (454 - 198) is 256\n\n####256", "a": 454, "b": 198, "operator": "-", "result": 256}
{"question": "Solve (464 - 242)", "answer": "The result of (464 - 242) is 222\n\n####222", "a": 464, "b": 242, "operator": "-", "result": 222}
{"question": "Solve (835 - 252)", "answer": "The result of (835 - 252) is 583\n\n####583", "a": 835, "b": 252, "operator": "-", "result": 583}
{"question": "Solve (263 - 123)", "answer": "The result of (263 - 123) is 140\n\n####140", "a": 263, "b": 123, "operator": "-", "result": 140}
{"question": "Solve (774 - 319)", "answer": "The result of (774 - 319) is 455\n\n####455", "a": 774, "b": 319, "operator": "-", "result": 455}
{"question": "Solve (29 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (29 / 504) is 0.0575\n\n####0.0575", "a": 29, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0575}
{"question": "Solve (728 * 672)", "answer": "The result of (728 * 672) is 489216\n\n####489216", "a": 728, "b": 672, "operator": "*", "result": 489216}
{"question": "Solve (187 / 576)", "answer": "The result of (187 / 576) is 0.3247\n\n####0.3247", "a": 187, "b": 576, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3247}
{"question": "Solve (662 - 77)", "answer": "The result of (662 - 77) is 585\n\n####585", "a": 662, "b": 77, "operator": "-", "result": 585}
{"question": "Solve (931 + 94)", "answer": "The result of (931 + 94) is 1025\n\n####1025", "a": 931, "b": 94, "operator": "+", "result": 1025}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 965)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 965) is 0.1409\n\n####0.1409", "a": 136, "b": 965, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1409}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 668)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 668) is -215\n\n####-215", "a": 453, "b": 668, "operator": "-", "result": -215}
{"question": "Solve (194 + 935)", "answer": "The result of (194 + 935) is 1129\n\n####1129", "a": 194, "b": 935, "operator": "+", "result": 1129}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 792)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 792) is 167904\n\n####167904", "a": 212, "b": 792, "operator": "*", "result": 167904}
{"question": "Solve (830 * 78)", "answer": "The result of (830 * 78) is 64740\n\n####64740", "a": 830, "b": 78, "operator": "*", "result": 64740}
{"question": "Solve (559 - 977)", "answer": "The result of (559 - 977) is -418\n\n####-418", "a": 559, "b": 977, "operator": "-", "result": -418}
{"question": "Solve (282 + 151)", "answer": "The result of (282 + 151) is 433\n\n####433", "a": 282, "b": 151, "operator": "+", "result": 433}
{"question": "Solve (786 - 217)", "answer": "The result of (786 - 217) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 786, "b": 217, "operator": "-", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (79 * 305)", "answer": "The result of (79 * 305) is 24095\n\n####24095", "a": 79, "b": 305, "operator": "*", "result": 24095}
{"question": "Solve (855 * 81)", "answer": "The result of (855 * 81) is 69255\n\n####69255", "a": 855, "b": 81, "operator": "*", "result": 69255}
{"question": "Solve (29 / 645)", "answer": "The result of (29 / 645) is 0.045\n\n####0.045", "a": 29, "b": 645, "operator": "/", "result": 0.045}
{"question": "Solve (224 - 395)", "answer": "The result of (224 - 395) is -171\n\n####-171", "a": 224, "b": 395, "operator": "-", "result": -171}
{"question": "Solve (361 * 586)", "answer": "The result of (361 * 586) is 211546\n\n####211546", "a": 361, "b": 586, "operator": "*", "result": 211546}
{"question": "Solve (931 + 447)", "answer": "The result of (931 + 447) is 1378\n\n####1378", "a": 931, "b": 447, "operator": "+", "result": 1378}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 496)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 496) is 0.0988\n\n####0.0988", "a": 49, "b": 496, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0988}
{"question": "Solve (635 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (635 - 262) is 373\n\n####373", "a": 635, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": 373}
{"question": "Solve (362 - 417)", "answer": "The result of (362 - 417) is -55\n\n####-55", "a": 362, "b": 417, "operator": "-", "result": -55}
{"question": "Solve (175 + 291)", "answer": "The result of (175 + 291) is 466\n\n####466", "a": 175, "b": 291, "operator": "+", "result": 466}
{"question": "Solve (948 + 110)", "answer": "The result of (948 + 110) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 948, "b": 110, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (242 / 252)", "answer": "The result of (242 / 252) is 0.9603\n\n####0.9603", "a": 242, "b": 252, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9603}
{"question": "Solve (114 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (114 - 846) is -732\n\n####-732", "a": 114, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -732}
{"question": "Solve (324 + 282)", "answer": "The result of (324 + 282) is 606\n\n####606", "a": 324, "b": 282, "operator": "+", "result": 606}
{"question": "Solve (463 - 516)", "answer": "The result of (463 - 516) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 463, "b": 516, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (907 * 998)", "answer": "The result of (907 * 998) is 905186\n\n####905186", "a": 907, "b": 998, "operator": "*", "result": 905186}
{"question": "Solve (245 + 751)", "answer": "The result of (245 + 751) is 996\n\n####996", "a": 245, "b": 751, "operator": "+", "result": 996}
{"question": "Solve (863 + 639)", "answer": "The result of (863 + 639) is 1502\n\n####1502", "a": 863, "b": 639, "operator": "+", "result": 1502}
{"question": "Solve (811 * 659)", "answer": "The result of (811 * 659) is 534449\n\n####534449", "a": 811, "b": 659, "operator": "*", "result": 534449}
{"question": "Solve (315 + 226)", "answer": "The result of (315 + 226) is 541\n\n####541", "a": 315, "b": 226, "operator": "+", "result": 541}
{"question": "Solve (541 - 144)", "answer": "The result of (541 - 144) is 397\n\n####397", "a": 541, "b": 144, "operator": "-", "result": 397}
{"question": "Solve (33 * 666)", "answer": "The result of (33 * 666) is 21978\n\n####21978", "a": 33, "b": 666, "operator": "*", "result": 21978}
{"question": "Solve (892 - 588)", "answer": "The result of (892 - 588) is 304\n\n####304", "a": 892, "b": 588, "operator": "-", "result": 304}
{"question": "Solve (19 / 75)", "answer": "The result of (19 / 75) is 0.2533\n\n####0.2533", "a": 19, "b": 75, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2533}
{"question": "Solve (605 / 797)", "answer": "The result of (605 / 797) is 0.7591\n\n####0.7591", "a": 605, "b": 797, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7591}
{"question": "Solve (290 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (290 - 245) is 45\n\n####45", "a": 290, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 45}
{"question": "Solve (708 * 89)", "answer": "The result of (708 * 89) is 63012\n\n####63012", "a": 708, "b": 89, "operator": "*", "result": 63012}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 247)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 247) is 3.2024\n\n####3.2024", "a": 791, "b": 247, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2024}
{"question": "Solve (467 / 111)", "answer": "The result of (467 / 111) is 4.2072\n\n####4.2072", "a": 467, "b": 111, "operator": "/", "result": 4.2072}
{"question": "Solve (135 + 919)", "answer": "The result of (135 + 919) is 1054\n\n####1054", "a": 135, "b": 919, "operator": "+", "result": 1054}
{"question": "Solve (284 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (284 * 423) is 120132\n\n####120132", "a": 284, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 120132}
{"question": "Solve (540 - 328)", "answer": "The result of (540 - 328) is 212\n\n####212", "a": 540, "b": 328, "operator": "-", "result": 212}
{"question": "Solve (517 / 617)", "answer": "The result of (517 / 617) is 0.8379\n\n####0.8379", "a": 517, "b": 617, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8379}
{"question": "Solve (304 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (304 / 545) is 0.5578\n\n####0.5578", "a": 304, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5578}
{"question": "Solve (422 / 398)", "answer": "The result of (422 / 398) is 1.0603\n\n####1.0603", "a": 422, "b": 398, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0603}
{"question": "Solve (328 - 468)", "answer": "The result of (328 - 468) is -140\n\n####-140", "a": 328, "b": 468, "operator": "-", "result": -140}
{"question": "Solve (751 * 25)", "answer": "The result of (751 * 25) is 18775\n\n####18775", "a": 751, "b": 25, "operator": "*", "result": 18775}
{"question": "Solve (295 / 808)", "answer": "The result of (295 / 808) is 0.3651\n\n####0.3651", "a": 295, "b": 808, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3651}
{"question": "Solve (598 / 976)", "answer": "The result of (598 / 976) is 0.6127\n\n####0.6127", "a": 598, "b": 976, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6127}
{"question": "Solve (616 + 785)", "answer": "The result of (616 + 785) is 1401\n\n####1401", "a": 616, "b": 785, "operator": "+", "result": 1401}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 324)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 324) is 0.6235\n\n####0.6235", "a": 202, "b": 324, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6235}
{"question": "Solve (706 - 22)", "answer": "The result of (706 - 22) is 684\n\n####684", "a": 706, "b": 22, "operator": "-", "result": 684}
{"question": "Solve (193 * 280)", "answer": "The result of (193 * 280) is 54040\n\n####54040", "a": 193, "b": 280, "operator": "*", "result": 54040}
{"question": "Solve (737 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (737 * 637) is 469469\n\n####469469", "a": 737, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 469469}
{"question": "Solve (232 / 703)", "answer": "The result of (232 / 703) is 0.33\n\n####0.33", "a": 232, "b": 703, "operator": "/", "result": 0.33}
{"question": "Solve (733 / 705)", "answer": "The result of (733 / 705) is 1.0397\n\n####1.0397", "a": 733, "b": 705, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0397}
{"question": "Solve (544 * 945)", "answer": "The result of (544 * 945) is 514080\n\n####514080", "a": 544, "b": 945, "operator": "*", "result": 514080}
{"question": "Solve (483 * 329)", "answer": "The result of (483 * 329) is 158907\n\n####158907", "a": 483, "b": 329, "operator": "*", "result": 158907}
{"question": "Solve (967 - 18)", "answer": "The result of (967 - 18) is 949\n\n####949", "a": 967, "b": 18, "operator": "-", "result": 949}
{"question": "Solve (350 + 589)", "answer": "The result of (350 + 589) is 939\n\n####939", "a": 350, "b": 589, "operator": "+", "result": 939}
{"question": "Solve (536 * 547)", "answer": "The result of (536 * 547) is 293192\n\n####293192", "a": 536, "b": 547, "operator": "*", "result": 293192}
{"question": "Solve (669 * 978)", "answer": "The result of (669 * 978) is 654282\n\n####654282", "a": 669, "b": 978, "operator": "*", "result": 654282}
{"question": "Solve (57 / 104)", "answer": "The result of (57 / 104) is 0.5481\n\n####0.5481", "a": 57, "b": 104, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5481}
{"question": "Solve (957 - 546)", "answer": "The result of (957 - 546) is 411\n\n####411", "a": 957, "b": 546, "operator": "-", "result": 411}
{"question": "Solve (326 + 449)", "answer": "The result of (326 + 449) is 775\n\n####775", "a": 326, "b": 449, "operator": "+", "result": 775}
{"question": "Solve (633 / 570)", "answer": "The result of (633 / 570) is 1.1105\n\n####1.1105", "a": 633, "b": 570, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1105}
{"question": "Solve (823 / 750)", "answer": "The result of (823 / 750) is 1.0973\n\n####1.0973", "a": 823, "b": 750, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0973}
{"question": "Solve (86 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (86 - 342) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 86, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (117 / 759)", "answer": "The result of (117 / 759) is 0.1542\n\n####0.1542", "a": 117, "b": 759, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1542}
{"question": "Solve (479 + 871)", "answer": "The result of (479 + 871) is 1350\n\n####1350", "a": 479, "b": 871, "operator": "+", "result": 1350}
{"question": "Solve (300 + 101)", "answer": "The result of (300 + 101) is 401\n\n####401", "a": 300, "b": 101, "operator": "+", "result": 401}
{"question": "Solve (413 * 328)", "answer": "The result of (413 * 328) is 135464\n\n####135464", "a": 413, "b": 328, "operator": "*", "result": 135464}
{"question": "Solve (399 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (399 - 449) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 399, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (961 + 591)", "answer": "The result of (961 + 591) is 1552\n\n####1552", "a": 961, "b": 591, "operator": "+", "result": 1552}
{"question": "Solve (950 / 732)", "answer": "The result of (950 / 732) is 1.2978\n\n####1.2978", "a": 950, "b": 732, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2978}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 134)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 134) is 76514\n\n####76514", "a": 571, "b": 134, "operator": "*", "result": 76514}
{"question": "Solve (513 - 289)", "answer": "The result of (513 - 289) is 224\n\n####224", "a": 513, "b": 289, "operator": "-", "result": 224}
{"question": "Solve (737 - 787)", "answer": "The result of (737 - 787) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 737, "b": 787, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (869 * 299)", "answer": "The result of (869 * 299) is 259831\n\n####259831", "a": 869, "b": 299, "operator": "*", "result": 259831}
{"question": "Solve (596 - 698)", "answer": "The result of (596 - 698) is -102\n\n####-102", "a": 596, "b": 698, "operator": "-", "result": -102}
{"question": "Solve (819 * 926)", "answer": "The result of (819 * 926) is 758394\n\n####758394", "a": 819, "b": 926, "operator": "*", "result": 758394}
{"question": "Solve (377 * 336)", "answer": "The result of (377 * 336) is 126672\n\n####126672", "a": 377, "b": 336, "operator": "*", "result": 126672}
{"question": "Solve (188 / 315)", "answer": "The result of (188 / 315) is 0.5968\n\n####0.5968", "a": 188, "b": 315, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5968}
{"question": "Solve (905 + 776)", "answer": "The result of (905 + 776) is 1681\n\n####1681", "a": 905, "b": 776, "operator": "+", "result": 1681}
{"question": "Solve (564 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (564 - 261) is 303\n\n####303", "a": 564, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": 303}
{"question": "Solve (872 / 796)", "answer": "The result of (872 / 796) is 1.0955\n\n####1.0955", "a": 872, "b": 796, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0955}
{"question": "Solve (444 + 999)", "answer": "The result of (444 + 999) is 1443\n\n####1443", "a": 444, "b": 999, "operator": "+", "result": 1443}
{"question": "Solve (437 - 896)", "answer": "The result of (437 - 896) is -459\n\n####-459", "a": 437, "b": 896, "operator": "-", "result": -459}
{"question": "Solve (494 + 75)", "answer": "The result of (494 + 75) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 494, "b": 75, "operator": "+", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (221 + 444)", "answer": "The result of (221 + 444) is 665\n\n####665", "a": 221, "b": 444, "operator": "+", "result": 665}
{"question": "Solve (317 * 301)", "answer": "The result of (317 * 301) is 95417\n\n####95417", "a": 317, "b": 301, "operator": "*", "result": 95417}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 389)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 389) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 863, "b": 389, "operator": "-", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (303 + 706)", "answer": "The result of (303 + 706) is 1009\n\n####1009", "a": 303, "b": 706, "operator": "+", "result": 1009}
{"question": "Solve (778 + 884)", "answer": "The result of (778 + 884) is 1662\n\n####1662", "a": 778, "b": 884, "operator": "+", "result": 1662}
{"question": "Solve (984 * 266)", "answer": "The result of (984 * 266) is 261744\n\n####261744", "a": 984, "b": 266, "operator": "*", "result": 261744}
{"question": "Solve (653 + 384)", "answer": "The result of (653 + 384) is 1037\n\n####1037", "a": 653, "b": 384, "operator": "+", "result": 1037}
{"question": "Solve (204 + 325)", "answer": "The result of (204 + 325) is 529\n\n####529", "a": 204, "b": 325, "operator": "+", "result": 529}
{"question": "Solve (82 * 438)", "answer": "The result of (82 * 438) is 35916\n\n####35916", "a": 82, "b": 438, "operator": "*", "result": 35916}
{"question": "Solve (671 + 153)", "answer": "The result of (671 + 153) is 824\n\n####824", "a": 671, "b": 153, "operator": "+", "result": 824}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 548)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 548) is 393\n\n####393", "a": 941, "b": 548, "operator": "-", "result": 393}
{"question": "Solve (459 + 343)", "answer": "The result of (459 + 343) is 802\n\n####802", "a": 459, "b": 343, "operator": "+", "result": 802}
{"question": "Solve (591 + 593)", "answer": "The result of (591 + 593) is 1184\n\n####1184", "a": 591, "b": 593, "operator": "+", "result": 1184}
{"question": "Solve (762 - 187)", "answer": "The result of (762 - 187) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 762, "b": 187, "operator": "-", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (519 + 869)", "answer": "The result of (519 + 869) is 1388\n\n####1388", "a": 519, "b": 869, "operator": "+", "result": 1388}
{"question": "Solve (562 * 799)", "answer": "The result of (562 * 799) is 449038\n\n####449038", "a": 562, "b": 799, "operator": "*", "result": 449038}
{"question": "Solve (255 / 735)", "answer": "The result of (255 / 735) is 0.3469\n\n####0.3469", "a": 255, "b": 735, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3469}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 719)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 719) is 501862\n\n####501862", "a": 698, "b": 719, "operator": "*", "result": 501862}
{"question": "Solve (971 - 178)", "answer": "The result of (971 - 178) is 793\n\n####793", "a": 971, "b": 178, "operator": "-", "result": 793}
{"question": "Solve (149 * 20)", "answer": "The result of (149 * 20) is 2980\n\n####2980", "a": 149, "b": 20, "operator": "*", "result": 2980}
{"question": "Solve (903 * 469)", "answer": "The result of (903 * 469) is 423507\n\n####423507", "a": 903, "b": 469, "operator": "*", "result": 423507}
{"question": "Solve (916 - 149)", "answer": "The result of (916 - 149) is 767\n\n####767", "a": 916, "b": 149, "operator": "-", "result": 767}
{"question": "Solve (263 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (263 - 730) is -467\n\n####-467", "a": 263, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -467}
{"question": "Solve (990 / 814)", "answer": "The result of (990 / 814) is 1.2162\n\n####1.2162", "a": 990, "b": 814, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2162}
{"question": "Solve (498 + 789)", "answer": "The result of (498 + 789) is 1287\n\n####1287", "a": 498, "b": 789, "operator": "+", "result": 1287}
{"question": "Solve (809 - 185)", "answer": "The result of (809 - 185) is 624\n\n####624", "a": 809, "b": 185, "operator": "-", "result": 624}
{"question": "Solve (695 + 466)", "answer": "The result of (695 + 466) is 1161\n\n####1161", "a": 695, "b": 466, "operator": "+", "result": 1161}
{"question": "Solve (911 / 558)", "answer": "The result of (911 / 558) is 1.6326\n\n####1.6326", "a": 911, "b": 558, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6326}
{"question": "Solve (951 - 555)", "answer": "The result of (951 - 555) is 396\n\n####396", "a": 951, "b": 555, "operator": "-", "result": 396}
{"question": "Solve (487 * 373)", "answer": "The result of (487 * 373) is 181651\n\n####181651", "a": 487, "b": 373, "operator": "*", "result": 181651}
{"question": "Solve (454 - 303)", "answer": "The result of (454 - 303) is 151\n\n####151", "a": 454, "b": 303, "operator": "-", "result": 151}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 611)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 611) is 1478\n\n####1478", "a": 867, "b": 611, "operator": "+", "result": 1478}
{"question": "Solve (208 / 813)", "answer": "The result of (208 / 813) is 0.2558\n\n####0.2558", "a": 208, "b": 813, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2558}
{"question": "Solve (949 - 564)", "answer": "The result of (949 - 564) is 385\n\n####385", "a": 949, "b": 564, "operator": "-", "result": 385}
{"question": "Solve (764 / 47)", "answer": "The result of (764 / 47) is 16.2553\n\n####16.2553", "a": 764, "b": 47, "operator": "/", "result": 16.2553}
{"question": "Solve (389 / 828)", "answer": "The result of (389 / 828) is 0.4698\n\n####0.4698", "a": 389, "b": 828, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4698}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 941)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 941) is -500\n\n####-500", "a": 441, "b": 941, "operator": "-", "result": -500}
{"question": "Solve (606 + 737)", "answer": "The result of (606 + 737) is 1343\n\n####1343", "a": 606, "b": 737, "operator": "+", "result": 1343}
{"question": "Solve (673 / 136)", "answer": "The result of (673 / 136) is 4.9485\n\n####4.9485", "a": 673, "b": 136, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9485}
{"question": "Solve (803 - 225)", "answer": "The result of (803 - 225) is 578\n\n####578", "a": 803, "b": 225, "operator": "-", "result": 578}
{"question": "Solve (409 - 955)", "answer": "The result of (409 - 955) is -546\n\n####-546", "a": 409, "b": 955, "operator": "-", "result": -546}
{"question": "Solve (589 + 248)", "answer": "The result of (589 + 248) is 837\n\n####837", "a": 589, "b": 248, "operator": "+", "result": 837}
{"question": "Solve (150 - 898)", "answer": "The result of (150 - 898) is -748\n\n####-748", "a": 150, "b": 898, "operator": "-", "result": -748}
{"question": "Solve (132 + 512)", "answer": "The result of (132 + 512) is 644\n\n####644", "a": 132, "b": 512, "operator": "+", "result": 644}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 882)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 882) is -574\n\n####-574", "a": 308, "b": 882, "operator": "-", "result": -574}
{"question": "Solve (977 - 242)", "answer": "The result of (977 - 242) is 735\n\n####735", "a": 977, "b": 242, "operator": "-", "result": 735}
{"question": "Solve (36 + 695)", "answer": "The result of (36 + 695) is 731\n\n####731", "a": 36, "b": 695, "operator": "+", "result": 731}
{"question": "Solve (503 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (503 + 380) is 883\n\n####883", "a": 503, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 883}
{"question": "Solve (758 * 261)", "answer": "The result of (758 * 261) is 197838\n\n####197838", "a": 758, "b": 261, "operator": "*", "result": 197838}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 946)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 946) is 223256\n\n####223256", "a": 236, "b": 946, "operator": "*", "result": 223256}
{"question": "Solve (196 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (196 * 86) is 16856\n\n####16856", "a": 196, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 16856}
{"question": "Solve (267 - 799)", "answer": "The result of (267 - 799) is -532\n\n####-532", "a": 267, "b": 799, "operator": "-", "result": -532}
{"question": "Solve (180 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (180 / 290) is 0.6207\n\n####0.6207", "a": 180, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6207}
{"question": "Solve (486 * 555)", "answer": "The result of (486 * 555) is 269730\n\n####269730", "a": 486, "b": 555, "operator": "*", "result": 269730}
{"question": "Solve (286 + 206)", "answer": "The result of (286 + 206) is 492\n\n####492", "a": 286, "b": 206, "operator": "+", "result": 492}
{"question": "Solve (389 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (389 - 825) is -436\n\n####-436", "a": 389, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": -436}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 185)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 185) is 16465\n\n####16465", "a": 89, "b": 185, "operator": "*", "result": 16465}
{"question": "Solve (732 / 93)", "answer": "The result of (732 / 93) is 7.871\n\n####7.871", "a": 732, "b": 93, "operator": "/", "result": 7.871}
{"question": "Solve (769 - 593)", "answer": "The result of (769 - 593) is 176\n\n####176", "a": 769, "b": 593, "operator": "-", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve (298 - 425)", "answer": "The result of (298 - 425) is -127\n\n####-127", "a": 298, "b": 425, "operator": "-", "result": -127}
{"question": "Solve (341 * 230)", "answer": "The result of (341 * 230) is 78430\n\n####78430", "a": 341, "b": 230, "operator": "*", "result": 78430}
{"question": "Solve (690 - 229)", "answer": "The result of (690 - 229) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 690, "b": 229, "operator": "-", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (691 / 558)", "answer": "The result of (691 / 558) is 1.2384\n\n####1.2384", "a": 691, "b": 558, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2384}
{"question": "Solve (95 * 311)", "answer": "The result of (95 * 311) is 29545\n\n####29545", "a": 95, "b": 311, "operator": "*", "result": 29545}
{"question": "Solve (766 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (766 / 852) is 0.8991\n\n####0.8991", "a": 766, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8991}
{"question": "Solve (504 + 58)", "answer": "The result of (504 + 58) is 562\n\n####562", "a": 504, "b": 58, "operator": "+", "result": 562}
{"question": "Solve (778 / 239)", "answer": "The result of (778 / 239) is 3.2552\n\n####3.2552", "a": 778, "b": 239, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2552}
{"question": "Solve (538 - 925)", "answer": "The result of (538 - 925) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 538, "b": 925, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (600 + 197)", "answer": "The result of (600 + 197) is 797\n\n####797", "a": 600, "b": 197, "operator": "+", "result": 797}
{"question": "Solve (468 * 96)", "answer": "The result of (468 * 96) is 44928\n\n####44928", "a": 468, "b": 96, "operator": "*", "result": 44928}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 616)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 616) is 1.1185\n\n####1.1185", "a": 689, "b": 616, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1185}
{"question": "Solve (542 - 533)", "answer": "The result of (542 - 533) is 9\n\n####9", "a": 542, "b": 533, "operator": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 516)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 516) is 1.6802\n\n####1.6802", "a": 867, "b": 516, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6802}
{"question": "Solve (163 / 528)", "answer": "The result of (163 / 528) is 0.3087\n\n####0.3087", "a": 163, "b": 528, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3087}
{"question": "Solve (212 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (212 / 276) is 0.7681\n\n####0.7681", "a": 212, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7681}
{"question": "Solve (315 + 335)", "answer": "The result of (315 + 335) is 650\n\n####650", "a": 315, "b": 335, "operator": "+", "result": 650}
{"question": "Solve (715 * 459)", "answer": "The result of (715 * 459) is 328185\n\n####328185", "a": 715, "b": 459, "operator": "*", "result": 328185}
{"question": "Solve (10 * 205)", "answer": "The result of (10 * 205) is 2050\n\n####2050", "a": 10, "b": 205, "operator": "*", "result": 2050}
{"question": "Solve (743 / 476)", "answer": "The result of (743 / 476) is 1.5609\n\n####1.5609", "a": 743, "b": 476, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5609}
{"question": "Solve (762 * 372)", "answer": "The result of (762 * 372) is 283464\n\n####283464", "a": 762, "b": 372, "operator": "*", "result": 283464}
{"question": "Solve (583 / 393)", "answer": "The result of (583 / 393) is 1.4835\n\n####1.4835", "a": 583, "b": 393, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4835}
{"question": "Solve (537 * 941)", "answer": "The result of (537 * 941) is 505317\n\n####505317", "a": 537, "b": 941, "operator": "*", "result": 505317}
{"question": "Solve (950 - 586)", "answer": "The result of (950 - 586) is 364\n\n####364", "a": 950, "b": 586, "operator": "-", "result": 364}
{"question": "Solve (236 - 335)", "answer": "The result of (236 - 335) is -99\n\n####-99", "a": 236, "b": 335, "operator": "-", "result": -99}
{"question": "Solve (238 * 563)", "answer": "The result of (238 * 563) is 133994\n\n####133994", "a": 238, "b": 563, "operator": "*", "result": 133994}
{"question": "Solve (852 + 632)", "answer": "The result of (852 + 632) is 1484\n\n####1484", "a": 852, "b": 632, "operator": "+", "result": 1484}
{"question": "Solve (199 * 819)", "answer": "The result of (199 * 819) is 162981\n\n####162981", "a": 199, "b": 819, "operator": "*", "result": 162981}
{"question": "Solve (802 - 765)", "answer": "The result of (802 - 765) is 37\n\n####37", "a": 802, "b": 765, "operator": "-", "result": 37}
{"question": "Solve (153 + 579)", "answer": "The result of (153 + 579) is 732\n\n####732", "a": 153, "b": 579, "operator": "+", "result": 732}
{"question": "Solve (641 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (641 - 730) is -89\n\n####-89", "a": 641, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -89}
{"question": "Solve (633 - 203)", "answer": "The result of (633 - 203) is 430\n\n####430", "a": 633, "b": 203, "operator": "-", "result": 430}
{"question": "Solve (338 + 252)", "answer": "The result of (338 + 252) is 590\n\n####590", "a": 338, "b": 252, "operator": "+", "result": 590}
{"question": "Solve (490 + 917)", "answer": "The result of (490 + 917) is 1407\n\n####1407", "a": 490, "b": 917, "operator": "+", "result": 1407}
{"question": "Solve (238 - 483)", "answer": "The result of (238 - 483) is -245\n\n####-245", "a": 238, "b": 483, "operator": "-", "result": -245}
{"question": "Solve (652 - 906)", "answer": "The result of (652 - 906) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 652, "b": 906, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (573 * 256)", "answer": "The result of (573 * 256) is 146688\n\n####146688", "a": 573, "b": 256, "operator": "*", "result": 146688}
{"question": "Solve (6 - 214)", "answer": "The result of (6 - 214) is -208\n\n####-208", "a": 6, "b": 214, "operator": "-", "result": -208}
{"question": "Solve (292 - 593)", "answer": "The result of (292 - 593) is -301\n\n####-301", "a": 292, "b": 593, "operator": "-", "result": -301}
{"question": "Solve (444 - 29)", "answer": "The result of (444 - 29) is 415\n\n####415", "a": 444, "b": 29, "operator": "-", "result": 415}
{"question": "Solve (6 + 927)", "answer": "The result of (6 + 927) is 933\n\n####933", "a": 6, "b": 927, "operator": "+", "result": 933}
{"question": "Solve (361 - 980)", "answer": "The result of (361 - 980) is -619\n\n####-619", "a": 361, "b": 980, "operator": "-", "result": -619}
{"question": "Solve (651 - 327)", "answer": "The result of (651 - 327) is 324\n\n####324", "a": 651, "b": 327, "operator": "-", "result": 324}
{"question": "Solve (419 + 67)", "answer": "The result of (419 + 67) is 486\n\n####486", "a": 419, "b": 67, "operator": "+", "result": 486}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 735)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 735) is -148\n\n####-148", "a": 587, "b": 735, "operator": "-", "result": -148}
{"question": "Solve (207 + 602)", "answer": "The result of (207 + 602) is 809\n\n####809", "a": 207, "b": 602, "operator": "+", "result": 809}
{"question": "Solve (46 - 339)", "answer": "The result of (46 - 339) is -293\n\n####-293", "a": 46, "b": 339, "operator": "-", "result": -293}
{"question": "Solve (474 * 894)", "answer": "The result of (474 * 894) is 423756\n\n####423756", "a": 474, "b": 894, "operator": "*", "result": 423756}
{"question": "Solve (386 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (386 - 706) is -320\n\n####-320", "a": 386, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -320}
{"question": "Solve (239 * 245)", "answer": "The result of (239 * 245) is 58555\n\n####58555", "a": 239, "b": 245, "operator": "*", "result": 58555}
{"question": "Solve (376 + 238)", "answer": "The result of (376 + 238) is 614\n\n####614", "a": 376, "b": 238, "operator": "+", "result": 614}
{"question": "Solve (868 * 572)", "answer": "The result of (868 * 572) is 496496\n\n####496496", "a": 868, "b": 572, "operator": "*", "result": 496496}
{"question": "Solve (721 / 586)", "answer": "The result of (721 / 586) is 1.2304\n\n####1.2304", "a": 721, "b": 586, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2304}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 706) is 44\n\n####44", "a": 750, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": 44}
{"question": "Solve (276 - 665)", "answer": "The result of (276 - 665) is -389\n\n####-389", "a": 276, "b": 665, "operator": "-", "result": -389}
{"question": "Solve (817 * 872)", "answer": "The result of (817 * 872) is 712424\n\n####712424", "a": 817, "b": 872, "operator": "*", "result": 712424}
{"question": "Solve (963 - 568)", "answer": "The result of (963 - 568) is 395\n\n####395", "a": 963, "b": 568, "operator": "-", "result": 395}
{"question": "Solve (297 + 816)", "answer": "The result of (297 + 816) is 1113\n\n####1113", "a": 297, "b": 816, "operator": "+", "result": 1113}
{"question": "Solve (250 - 946)", "answer": "The result of (250 - 946) is -696\n\n####-696", "a": 250, "b": 946, "operator": "-", "result": -696}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 215) is 21715\n\n####21715", "a": 101, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 21715}
{"question": "Solve (816 - 543)", "answer": "The result of (816 - 543) is 273\n\n####273", "a": 816, "b": 543, "operator": "-", "result": 273}
{"question": "Solve (907 - 87)", "answer": "The result of (907 - 87) is 820\n\n####820", "a": 907, "b": 87, "operator": "-", "result": 820}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 747)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 747) is -670\n\n####-670", "a": 77, "b": 747, "operator": "-", "result": -670}
{"question": "Solve (569 - 753)", "answer": "The result of (569 - 753) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 569, "b": 753, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (160 * 399)", "answer": "The result of (160 * 399) is 63840\n\n####63840", "a": 160, "b": 399, "operator": "*", "result": 63840}
{"question": "Solve (713 / 251)", "answer": "The result of (713 / 251) is 2.8406\n\n####2.8406", "a": 713, "b": 251, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8406}
{"question": "Solve (294 + 627)", "answer": "The result of (294 + 627) is 921\n\n####921", "a": 294, "b": 627, "operator": "+", "result": 921}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 756) is -629\n\n####-629", "a": 127, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -629}
{"question": "Solve (929 / 84)", "answer": "The result of (929 / 84) is 11.0595\n\n####11.0595", "a": 929, "b": 84, "operator": "/", "result": 11.0595}
{"question": "Solve (331 - 142)", "answer": "The result of (331 - 142) is 189\n\n####189", "a": 331, "b": 142, "operator": "-", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve (469 - 133)", "answer": "The result of (469 - 133) is 336\n\n####336", "a": 469, "b": 133, "operator": "-", "result": 336}
{"question": "Solve (756 - 96)", "answer": "The result of (756 - 96) is 660\n\n####660", "a": 756, "b": 96, "operator": "-", "result": 660}
{"question": "Solve (790 * 624)", "answer": "The result of (790 * 624) is 492960\n\n####492960", "a": 790, "b": 624, "operator": "*", "result": 492960}
{"question": "Solve (506 * 366)", "answer": "The result of (506 * 366) is 185196\n\n####185196", "a": 506, "b": 366, "operator": "*", "result": 185196}
{"question": "Solve (912 - 760)", "answer": "The result of (912 - 760) is 152\n\n####152", "a": 912, "b": 760, "operator": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 786)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 786) is 477888\n\n####477888", "a": 608, "b": 786, "operator": "*", "result": 477888}
{"question": "Solve (398 * 299)", "answer": "The result of (398 * 299) is 119002\n\n####119002", "a": 398, "b": 299, "operator": "*", "result": 119002}
{"question": "Solve (912 - 913)", "answer": "The result of (912 - 913) is -1\n\n####-1", "a": 912, "b": 913, "operator": "-", "result": -1}
{"question": "Solve (835 / 139)", "answer": "The result of (835 / 139) is 6.0072\n\n####6.0072", "a": 835, "b": 139, "operator": "/", "result": 6.0072}
{"question": "Solve (331 * 988)", "answer": "The result of (331 * 988) is 327028\n\n####327028", "a": 331, "b": 988, "operator": "*", "result": 327028}
{"question": "Solve (31 - 361)", "answer": "The result of (31 - 361) is -330\n\n####-330", "a": 31, "b": 361, "operator": "-", "result": -330}
{"question": "Solve (884 - 589)", "answer": "The result of (884 - 589) is 295\n\n####295", "a": 884, "b": 589, "operator": "-", "result": 295}
{"question": "Solve (140 * 333)", "answer": "The result of (140 * 333) is 46620\n\n####46620", "a": 140, "b": 333, "operator": "*", "result": 46620}
{"question": "Solve (529 * 295)", "answer": "The result of (529 * 295) is 156055\n\n####156055", "a": 529, "b": 295, "operator": "*", "result": 156055}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 332) is 237048\n\n####237048", "a": 714, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 237048}
{"question": "Solve (624 * 692)", "answer": "The result of (624 * 692) is 431808\n\n####431808", "a": 624, "b": 692, "operator": "*", "result": 431808}
{"question": "Solve (805 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (805 - 512) is 293\n\n####293", "a": 805, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve (722 - 960)", "answer": "The result of (722 - 960) is -238\n\n####-238", "a": 722, "b": 960, "operator": "-", "result": -238}
{"question": "Solve (600 * 440)", "answer": "The result of (600 * 440) is 264000\n\n####264000", "a": 600, "b": 440, "operator": "*", "result": 264000}
{"question": "Solve (645 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (645 - 918) is -273\n\n####-273", "a": 645, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -273}
{"question": "Solve (653 - 827)", "answer": "The result of (653 - 827) is -174\n\n####-174", "a": 653, "b": 827, "operator": "-", "result": -174}
{"question": "Solve (172 / 463)", "answer": "The result of (172 / 463) is 0.3715\n\n####0.3715", "a": 172, "b": 463, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3715}
{"question": "Solve (558 * 745)", "answer": "The result of (558 * 745) is 415710\n\n####415710", "a": 558, "b": 745, "operator": "*", "result": 415710}
{"question": "Solve (439 - 708)", "answer": "The result of (439 - 708) is -269\n\n####-269", "a": 439, "b": 708, "operator": "-", "result": -269}
{"question": "Solve (792 + 392)", "answer": "The result of (792 + 392) is 1184\n\n####1184", "a": 792, "b": 392, "operator": "+", "result": 1184}
{"question": "Solve (800 + 355)", "answer": "The result of (800 + 355) is 1155\n\n####1155", "a": 800, "b": 355, "operator": "+", "result": 1155}
{"question": "Solve (836 + 829)", "answer": "The result of (836 + 829) is 1665\n\n####1665", "a": 836, "b": 829, "operator": "+", "result": 1665}
{"question": "Solve (170 + 497)", "answer": "The result of (170 + 497) is 667\n\n####667", "a": 170, "b": 497, "operator": "+", "result": 667}
{"question": "Solve (854 * 516)", "answer": "The result of (854 * 516) is 440664\n\n####440664", "a": 854, "b": 516, "operator": "*", "result": 440664}
{"question": "Solve (438 + 756)", "answer": "The result of (438 + 756) is 1194\n\n####1194", "a": 438, "b": 756, "operator": "+", "result": 1194}
{"question": "Solve (355 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (355 - 2) is 353\n\n####353", "a": 355, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 353}
{"question": "Solve (672 * 268)", "answer": "The result of (672 * 268) is 180096\n\n####180096", "a": 672, "b": 268, "operator": "*", "result": 180096}
{"question": "Solve (623 / 633)", "answer": "The result of (623 / 633) is 0.9842\n\n####0.9842", "a": 623, "b": 633, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9842}
{"question": "Solve (159 / 265)", "answer": "The result of (159 / 265) is 0.6\n\n####0.6", "a": 159, "b": 265, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6}
{"question": "Solve (575 / 315)", "answer": "The result of (575 / 315) is 1.8254\n\n####1.8254", "a": 575, "b": 315, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8254}
{"question": "Solve (434 / 325)", "answer": "The result of (434 / 325) is 1.3354\n\n####1.3354", "a": 434, "b": 325, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3354}
{"question": "Solve (885 / 745)", "answer": "The result of (885 / 745) is 1.1879\n\n####1.1879", "a": 885, "b": 745, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1879}
{"question": "Solve (812 - 21)", "answer": "The result of (812 - 21) is 791\n\n####791", "a": 812, "b": 21, "operator": "-", "result": 791}
{"question": "Solve (148 * 972)", "answer": "The result of (148 * 972) is 143856\n\n####143856", "a": 148, "b": 972, "operator": "*", "result": 143856}
{"question": "Solve (456 / 99)", "answer": "The result of (456 / 99) is 4.6061\n\n####4.6061", "a": 456, "b": 99, "operator": "/", "result": 4.6061}
{"question": "Solve (366 + 454)", "answer": "The result of (366 + 454) is 820\n\n####820", "a": 366, "b": 454, "operator": "+", "result": 820}
{"question": "Solve (33 / 547)", "answer": "The result of (33 / 547) is 0.0603\n\n####0.0603", "a": 33, "b": 547, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0603}
{"question": "Solve (242 - 775)", "answer": "The result of (242 - 775) is -533\n\n####-533", "a": 242, "b": 775, "operator": "-", "result": -533}
{"question": "Solve (575 / 853)", "answer": "The result of (575 / 853) is 0.6741\n\n####0.6741", "a": 575, "b": 853, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6741}
{"question": "Solve (908 / 419)", "answer": "The result of (908 / 419) is 2.1671\n\n####2.1671", "a": 908, "b": 419, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1671}
{"question": "Solve (40 * 238)", "answer": "The result of (40 * 238) is 9520\n\n####9520", "a": 40, "b": 238, "operator": "*", "result": 9520}
{"question": "Solve (965 - 932)", "answer": "The result of (965 - 932) is 33\n\n####33", "a": 965, "b": 932, "operator": "-", "result": 33}
{"question": "Solve (305 * 778)", "answer": "The result of (305 * 778) is 237290\n\n####237290", "a": 305, "b": 778, "operator": "*", "result": 237290}
{"question": "Solve (626 * 389)", "answer": "The result of (626 * 389) is 243514\n\n####243514", "a": 626, "b": 389, "operator": "*", "result": 243514}
{"question": "Solve (521 / 876)", "answer": "The result of (521 / 876) is 0.5947\n\n####0.5947", "a": 521, "b": 876, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5947}
{"question": "Solve (426 / 910)", "answer": "The result of (426 / 910) is 0.4681\n\n####0.4681", "a": 426, "b": 910, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4681}
{"question": "Solve (830 - 713)", "answer": "The result of (830 - 713) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 830, "b": 713, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (65 - 763)", "answer": "The result of (65 - 763) is -698\n\n####-698", "a": 65, "b": 763, "operator": "-", "result": -698}
{"question": "Solve (299 * 253)", "answer": "The result of (299 * 253) is 75647\n\n####75647", "a": 299, "b": 253, "operator": "*", "result": 75647}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 293)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 293) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 44, "b": 293, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (966 + 839)", "answer": "The result of (966 + 839) is 1805\n\n####1805", "a": 966, "b": 839, "operator": "+", "result": 1805}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 431)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 431) is 318509\n\n####318509", "a": 739, "b": 431, "operator": "*", "result": 318509}
{"question": "Solve (112 * 819)", "answer": "The result of (112 * 819) is 91728\n\n####91728", "a": 112, "b": 819, "operator": "*", "result": 91728}
{"question": "Solve (917 * 199)", "answer": "The result of (917 * 199) is 182483\n\n####182483", "a": 917, "b": 199, "operator": "*", "result": 182483}
{"question": "Solve (395 * 536)", "answer": "The result of (395 * 536) is 211720\n\n####211720", "a": 395, "b": 536, "operator": "*", "result": 211720}
{"question": "Solve (676 * 920)", "answer": "The result of (676 * 920) is 621920\n\n####621920", "a": 676, "b": 920, "operator": "*", "result": 621920}
{"question": "Solve (115 + 823)", "answer": "The result of (115 + 823) is 938\n\n####938", "a": 115, "b": 823, "operator": "+", "result": 938}
{"question": "Solve (817 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (817 + 358) is 1175\n\n####1175", "a": 817, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 1175}
{"question": "Solve (461 * 755)", "answer": "The result of (461 * 755) is 348055\n\n####348055", "a": 461, "b": 755, "operator": "*", "result": 348055}
{"question": "Solve (522 / 832)", "answer": "The result of (522 / 832) is 0.6274\n\n####0.6274", "a": 522, "b": 832, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6274}
{"question": "Solve (868 - 177)", "answer": "The result of (868 - 177) is 691\n\n####691", "a": 868, "b": 177, "operator": "-", "result": 691}
{"question": "Solve (40 * 645)", "answer": "The result of (40 * 645) is 25800\n\n####25800", "a": 40, "b": 645, "operator": "*", "result": 25800}
{"question": "Solve (729 - 149)", "answer": "The result of (729 - 149) is 580\n\n####580", "a": 729, "b": 149, "operator": "-", "result": 580}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 981)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 981) is -529\n\n####-529", "a": 452, "b": 981, "operator": "-", "result": -529}
{"question": "Solve (950 / 696)", "answer": "The result of (950 / 696) is 1.3649\n\n####1.3649", "a": 950, "b": 696, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3649}
{"question": "Solve (241 / 632)", "answer": "The result of (241 / 632) is 0.3813\n\n####0.3813", "a": 241, "b": 632, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3813}
{"question": "Solve (736 - 253)", "answer": "The result of (736 - 253) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 736, "b": 253, "operator": "-", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (874 - 781)", "answer": "The result of (874 - 781) is 93\n\n####93", "a": 874, "b": 781, "operator": "-", "result": 93}
{"question": "Solve (267 + 15)", "answer": "The result of (267 + 15) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 267, "b": 15, "operator": "+", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (469 - 615)", "answer": "The result of (469 - 615) is -146\n\n####-146", "a": 469, "b": 615, "operator": "-", "result": -146}
{"question": "Solve (619 / 413)", "answer": "The result of (619 / 413) is 1.4988\n\n####1.4988", "a": 619, "b": 413, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4988}
{"question": "Solve (228 * 519)", "answer": "The result of (228 * 519) is 118332\n\n####118332", "a": 228, "b": 519, "operator": "*", "result": 118332}
{"question": "Solve (984 * 815)", "answer": "The result of (984 * 815) is 801960\n\n####801960", "a": 984, "b": 815, "operator": "*", "result": 801960}
{"question": "Solve (448 * 34)", "answer": "The result of (448 * 34) is 15232\n\n####15232", "a": 448, "b": 34, "operator": "*", "result": 15232}
{"question": "Solve (966 + 790)", "answer": "The result of (966 + 790) is 1756\n\n####1756", "a": 966, "b": 790, "operator": "+", "result": 1756}
{"question": "Solve (861 + 337)", "answer": "The result of (861 + 337) is 1198\n\n####1198", "a": 861, "b": 337, "operator": "+", "result": 1198}
{"question": "Solve (633 * 512)", "answer": "The result of (633 * 512) is 324096\n\n####324096", "a": 633, "b": 512, "operator": "*", "result": 324096}
{"question": "Solve (92 / 58)", "answer": "The result of (92 / 58) is 1.5862\n\n####1.5862", "a": 92, "b": 58, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5862}
{"question": "Solve (473 + 923)", "answer": "The result of (473 + 923) is 1396\n\n####1396", "a": 473, "b": 923, "operator": "+", "result": 1396}
{"question": "Solve (493 / 191)", "answer": "The result of (493 / 191) is 2.5812\n\n####2.5812", "a": 493, "b": 191, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5812}
{"question": "Solve (311 * 43)", "answer": "The result of (311 * 43) is 13373\n\n####13373", "a": 311, "b": 43, "operator": "*", "result": 13373}
{"question": "Solve (953 * 838)", "answer": "The result of (953 * 838) is 798614\n\n####798614", "a": 953, "b": 838, "operator": "*", "result": 798614}
{"question": "Solve (765 + 712)", "answer": "The result of (765 + 712) is 1477\n\n####1477", "a": 765, "b": 712, "operator": "+", "result": 1477}
{"question": "Solve (112 * 521)", "answer": "The result of (112 * 521) is 58352\n\n####58352", "a": 112, "b": 521, "operator": "*", "result": 58352}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 108)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 108) is -1\n\n####-1", "a": 107, "b": 108, "operator": "-", "result": -1}
{"question": "Solve (321 * 11)", "answer": "The result of (321 * 11) is 3531\n\n####3531", "a": 321, "b": 11, "operator": "*", "result": 3531}
{"question": "Solve (13 / 611)", "answer": "The result of (13 / 611) is 0.0213\n\n####0.0213", "a": 13, "b": 611, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0213}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 180)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 180) is 0.75\n\n####0.75", "a": 135, "b": 180, "operator": "/", "result": 0.75}
{"question": "Solve (310 * 67)", "answer": "The result of (310 * 67) is 20770\n\n####20770", "a": 310, "b": 67, "operator": "*", "result": 20770}
{"question": "Solve (164 / 155)", "answer": "The result of (164 / 155) is 1.0581\n\n####1.0581", "a": 164, "b": 155, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0581}
{"question": "Solve (429 / 3)", "answer": "The result of (429 / 3) is 143.0\n\n####143.0", "a": 429, "b": 3, "operator": "/", "result": 143.0}
{"question": "Solve (349 / 134)", "answer": "The result of (349 / 134) is 2.6045\n\n####2.6045", "a": 349, "b": 134, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6045}
{"question": "Solve (509 / 722)", "answer": "The result of (509 / 722) is 0.705\n\n####0.705", "a": 509, "b": 722, "operator": "/", "result": 0.705}
{"question": "Solve (121 / 441)", "answer": "The result of (121 / 441) is 0.2744\n\n####0.2744", "a": 121, "b": 441, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2744}
{"question": "Solve (41 - 423)", "answer": "The result of (41 - 423) is -382\n\n####-382", "a": 41, "b": 423, "operator": "-", "result": -382}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 945) is -636\n\n####-636", "a": 309, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -636}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 604)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 604) is 225896\n\n####225896", "a": 374, "b": 604, "operator": "*", "result": 225896}
{"question": "Solve (422 * 103)", "answer": "The result of (422 * 103) is 43466\n\n####43466", "a": 422, "b": 103, "operator": "*", "result": 43466}
{"question": "Solve (385 - 395)", "answer": "The result of (385 - 395) is -10\n\n####-10", "a": 385, "b": 395, "operator": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve (408 * 781)", "answer": "The result of (408 * 781) is 318648\n\n####318648", "a": 408, "b": 781, "operator": "*", "result": 318648}
{"question": "Solve (706 - 818)", "answer": "The result of (706 - 818) is -112\n\n####-112", "a": 706, "b": 818, "operator": "-", "result": -112}
{"question": "Solve (45 - 870)", "answer": "The result of (45 - 870) is -825\n\n####-825", "a": 45, "b": 870, "operator": "-", "result": -825}
{"question": "Solve (986 * 971)", "answer": "The result of (986 * 971) is 957406\n\n####957406", "a": 986, "b": 971, "operator": "*", "result": 957406}
{"question": "Solve (521 * 91)", "answer": "The result of (521 * 91) is 47411\n\n####47411", "a": 521, "b": 91, "operator": "*", "result": 47411}
{"question": "Solve (461 + 488)", "answer": "The result of (461 + 488) is 949\n\n####949", "a": 461, "b": 488, "operator": "+", "result": 949}
{"question": "Solve (942 * 952)", "answer": "The result of (942 * 952) is 896784\n\n####896784", "a": 942, "b": 952, "operator": "*", "result": 896784}
{"question": "Solve (637 * 484)", "answer": "The result of (637 * 484) is 308308\n\n####308308", "a": 637, "b": 484, "operator": "*", "result": 308308}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 98)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 98) is 3.3163\n\n####3.3163", "a": 325, "b": 98, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3163}
{"question": "Solve (679 / 939)", "answer": "The result of (679 / 939) is 0.7231\n\n####0.7231", "a": 679, "b": 939, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7231}
{"question": "Solve (52 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (52 + 805) is 857\n\n####857", "a": 52, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 857}
{"question": "Solve (994 + 810)", "answer": "The result of (994 + 810) is 1804\n\n####1804", "a": 994, "b": 810, "operator": "+", "result": 1804}
{"question": "Solve (744 + 339)", "answer": "The result of (744 + 339) is 1083\n\n####1083", "a": 744, "b": 339, "operator": "+", "result": 1083}
{"question": "Solve (405 + 174)", "answer": "The result of (405 + 174) is 579\n\n####579", "a": 405, "b": 174, "operator": "+", "result": 579}
{"question": "Solve (338 + 513)", "answer": "The result of (338 + 513) is 851\n\n####851", "a": 338, "b": 513, "operator": "+", "result": 851}
{"question": "Solve (621 + 701)", "answer": "The result of (621 + 701) is 1322\n\n####1322", "a": 621, "b": 701, "operator": "+", "result": 1322}
{"question": "Solve (550 * 411)", "answer": "The result of (550 * 411) is 226050\n\n####226050", "a": 550, "b": 411, "operator": "*", "result": 226050}
{"question": "Solve (568 * 730)", "answer": "The result of (568 * 730) is 414640\n\n####414640", "a": 568, "b": 730, "operator": "*", "result": 414640}
{"question": "Solve (666 / 180)", "answer": "The result of (666 / 180) is 3.7\n\n####3.7", "a": 666, "b": 180, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 978)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 978) is 0.5695\n\n####0.5695", "a": 557, "b": 978, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5695}
{"question": "Solve (429 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (429 - 810) is -381\n\n####-381", "a": 429, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": -381}
{"question": "Solve (703 / 68)", "answer": "The result of (703 / 68) is 10.3382\n\n####10.3382", "a": 703, "b": 68, "operator": "/", "result": 10.3382}
{"question": "Solve (248 - 635)", "answer": "The result of (248 - 635) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 248, "b": 635, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (671 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (671 * 780) is 523380\n\n####523380", "a": 671, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 523380}
{"question": "Solve (683 / 526)", "answer": "The result of (683 / 526) is 1.2985\n\n####1.2985", "a": 683, "b": 526, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2985}
{"question": "Solve (654 / 150)", "answer": "The result of (654 / 150) is 4.36\n\n####4.36", "a": 654, "b": 150, "operator": "/", "result": 4.36}
{"question": "Solve (257 + 512)", "answer": "The result of (257 + 512) is 769\n\n####769", "a": 257, "b": 512, "operator": "+", "result": 769}
{"question": "Solve (981 * 929)", "answer": "The result of (981 * 929) is 911349\n\n####911349", "a": 981, "b": 929, "operator": "*", "result": 911349}
{"question": "Solve (200 / 640)", "answer": "The result of (200 / 640) is 0.3125\n\n####0.3125", "a": 200, "b": 640, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3125}
{"question": "Solve (834 / 430)", "answer": "The result of (834 / 430) is 1.9395\n\n####1.9395", "a": 834, "b": 430, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9395}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 620)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 620) is 247\n\n####247", "a": 867, "b": 620, "operator": "-", "result": 247}
{"question": "Solve (460 - 446)", "answer": "The result of (460 - 446) is 14\n\n####14", "a": 460, "b": 446, "operator": "-", "result": 14}
{"question": "Solve (657 + 440)", "answer": "The result of (657 + 440) is 1097\n\n####1097", "a": 657, "b": 440, "operator": "+", "result": 1097}
{"question": "Solve (819 + 314)", "answer": "The result of (819 + 314) is 1133\n\n####1133", "a": 819, "b": 314, "operator": "+", "result": 1133}
{"question": "Solve (975 + 911)", "answer": "The result of (975 + 911) is 1886\n\n####1886", "a": 975, "b": 911, "operator": "+", "result": 1886}
{"question": "Solve (203 + 576)", "answer": "The result of (203 + 576) is 779\n\n####779", "a": 203, "b": 576, "operator": "+", "result": 779}
{"question": "Solve (486 + 973)", "answer": "The result of (486 + 973) is 1459\n\n####1459", "a": 486, "b": 973, "operator": "+", "result": 1459}
{"question": "Solve (45 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (45 / 334) is 0.1347\n\n####0.1347", "a": 45, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1347}
{"question": "Solve (670 / 310)", "answer": "The result of (670 / 310) is 2.1613\n\n####2.1613", "a": 670, "b": 310, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1613}
{"question": "Solve (862 + 288)", "answer": "The result of (862 + 288) is 1150\n\n####1150", "a": 862, "b": 288, "operator": "+", "result": 1150}
{"question": "Solve (699 / 852)", "answer": "The result of (699 / 852) is 0.8204\n\n####0.8204", "a": 699, "b": 852, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8204}
{"question": "Solve (287 + 924)", "answer": "The result of (287 + 924) is 1211\n\n####1211", "a": 287, "b": 924, "operator": "+", "result": 1211}
{"question": "Solve (275 - 998)", "answer": "The result of (275 - 998) is -723\n\n####-723", "a": 275, "b": 998, "operator": "-", "result": -723}
{"question": "Solve (74 + 220)", "answer": "The result of (74 + 220) is 294\n\n####294", "a": 74, "b": 220, "operator": "+", "result": 294}
{"question": "Solve (592 - 841)", "answer": "The result of (592 - 841) is -249\n\n####-249", "a": 592, "b": 841, "operator": "-", "result": -249}
{"question": "Solve (155 + 417)", "answer": "The result of (155 + 417) is 572\n\n####572", "a": 155, "b": 417, "operator": "+", "result": 572}
{"question": "Solve (773 / 776)", "answer": "The result of (773 / 776) is 0.9961\n\n####0.9961", "a": 773, "b": 776, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9961}
{"question": "Solve (577 - 657)", "answer": "The result of (577 - 657) is -80\n\n####-80", "a": 577, "b": 657, "operator": "-", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 66)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 66) is 2.5\n\n####2.5", "a": 165, "b": 66, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5}
{"question": "Solve (426 - 508)", "answer": "The result of (426 - 508) is -82\n\n####-82", "a": 426, "b": 508, "operator": "-", "result": -82}
{"question": "Solve (266 + 253)", "answer": "The result of (266 + 253) is 519\n\n####519", "a": 266, "b": 253, "operator": "+", "result": 519}
{"question": "Solve (585 * 673)", "answer": "The result of (585 * 673) is 393705\n\n####393705", "a": 585, "b": 673, "operator": "*", "result": 393705}
{"question": "Solve (392 * 753)", "answer": "The result of (392 * 753) is 295176\n\n####295176", "a": 392, "b": 753, "operator": "*", "result": 295176}
{"question": "Solve (198 * 254)", "answer": "The result of (198 * 254) is 50292\n\n####50292", "a": 198, "b": 254, "operator": "*", "result": 50292}
{"question": "Solve (255 + 616)", "answer": "The result of (255 + 616) is 871\n\n####871", "a": 255, "b": 616, "operator": "+", "result": 871}
{"question": "Solve (465 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (465 - 661) is -196\n\n####-196", "a": 465, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -196}
{"question": "Solve (921 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (921 * 357) is 328797\n\n####328797", "a": 921, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 328797}
{"question": "Solve (778 / 931)", "answer": "The result of (778 / 931) is 0.8357\n\n####0.8357", "a": 778, "b": 931, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8357}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 667)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 667) is 249458\n\n####249458", "a": 374, "b": 667, "operator": "*", "result": 249458}
{"question": "Solve (712 + 895)", "answer": "The result of (712 + 895) is 1607\n\n####1607", "a": 712, "b": 895, "operator": "+", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve (558 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (558 - 537) is 21\n\n####21", "a": 558, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": 21}
{"question": "Solve (871 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (871 * 762) is 663702\n\n####663702", "a": 871, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 663702}
{"question": "Solve (59 / 488)", "answer": "The result of (59 / 488) is 0.1209\n\n####0.1209", "a": 59, "b": 488, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1209}
{"question": "Solve (86 / 356)", "answer": "The result of (86 / 356) is 0.2416\n\n####0.2416", "a": 86, "b": 356, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2416}
{"question": "Solve (800 + 948)", "answer": "The result of (800 + 948) is 1748\n\n####1748", "a": 800, "b": 948, "operator": "+", "result": 1748}
{"question": "Solve (290 + 588)", "answer": "The result of (290 + 588) is 878\n\n####878", "a": 290, "b": 588, "operator": "+", "result": 878}
{"question": "Solve (595 + 89)", "answer": "The result of (595 + 89) is 684\n\n####684", "a": 595, "b": 89, "operator": "+", "result": 684}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 17)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 17) is 212\n\n####212", "a": 229, "b": 17, "operator": "-", "result": 212}
{"question": "Solve (863 / 139)", "answer": "The result of (863 / 139) is 6.2086\n\n####6.2086", "a": 863, "b": 139, "operator": "/", "result": 6.2086}
{"question": "Solve (596 / 757)", "answer": "The result of (596 / 757) is 0.7873\n\n####0.7873", "a": 596, "b": 757, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7873}
{"question": "Solve (810 - 246)", "answer": "The result of (810 - 246) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 810, "b": 246, "operator": "-", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (364 * 981)", "answer": "The result of (364 * 981) is 357084\n\n####357084", "a": 364, "b": 981, "operator": "*", "result": 357084}
{"question": "Solve (852 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (852 - 730) is 122\n\n####122", "a": 852, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve (660 / 548)", "answer": "The result of (660 / 548) is 1.2044\n\n####1.2044", "a": 660, "b": 548, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2044}
{"question": "Solve (724 - 183)", "answer": "The result of (724 - 183) is 541\n\n####541", "a": 724, "b": 183, "operator": "-", "result": 541}
{"question": "Solve (876 / 629)", "answer": "The result of (876 / 629) is 1.3927\n\n####1.3927", "a": 876, "b": 629, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3927}
{"question": "Solve (995 - 673)", "answer": "The result of (995 - 673) is 322\n\n####322", "a": 995, "b": 673, "operator": "-", "result": 322}
{"question": "Solve (517 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (517 / 411) is 1.2579\n\n####1.2579", "a": 517, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2579}
{"question": "Solve (609 + 461)", "answer": "The result of (609 + 461) is 1070\n\n####1070", "a": 609, "b": 461, "operator": "+", "result": 1070}
{"question": "Solve (145 - 351)", "answer": "The result of (145 - 351) is -206\n\n####-206", "a": 145, "b": 351, "operator": "-", "result": -206}
{"question": "Solve (214 - 330)", "answer": "The result of (214 - 330) is -116\n\n####-116", "a": 214, "b": 330, "operator": "-", "result": -116}
{"question": "Solve (515 / 509)", "answer": "The result of (515 / 509) is 1.0118\n\n####1.0118", "a": 515, "b": 509, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0118}
{"question": "Solve (903 - 973)", "answer": "The result of (903 - 973) is -70\n\n####-70", "a": 903, "b": 973, "operator": "-", "result": -70}
{"question": "Solve (281 * 892)", "answer": "The result of (281 * 892) is 250652\n\n####250652", "a": 281, "b": 892, "operator": "*", "result": 250652}
{"question": "Solve (738 + 508)", "answer": "The result of (738 + 508) is 1246\n\n####1246", "a": 738, "b": 508, "operator": "+", "result": 1246}
{"question": "Solve (573 + 313)", "answer": "The result of (573 + 313) is 886\n\n####886", "a": 573, "b": 313, "operator": "+", "result": 886}
{"question": "Solve (433 - 599)", "answer": "The result of (433 - 599) is -166\n\n####-166", "a": 433, "b": 599, "operator": "-", "result": -166}
{"question": "Solve (640 * 972)", "answer": "The result of (640 * 972) is 622080\n\n####622080", "a": 640, "b": 972, "operator": "*", "result": 622080}
{"question": "Solve (971 / 810)", "answer": "The result of (971 / 810) is 1.1988\n\n####1.1988", "a": 971, "b": 810, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1988}
{"question": "Solve (290 / 606)", "answer": "The result of (290 / 606) is 0.4785\n\n####0.4785", "a": 290, "b": 606, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4785}
{"question": "Solve (158 * 544)", "answer": "The result of (158 * 544) is 85952\n\n####85952", "a": 158, "b": 544, "operator": "*", "result": 85952}
{"question": "Solve (24 / 973)", "answer": "The result of (24 / 973) is 0.0247\n\n####0.0247", "a": 24, "b": 973, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0247}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 156)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 156) is 5.9679\n\n####5.9679", "a": 931, "b": 156, "operator": "/", "result": 5.9679}
{"question": "Solve (123 + 819)", "answer": "The result of (123 + 819) is 942\n\n####942", "a": 123, "b": 819, "operator": "+", "result": 942}
{"question": "Solve (68 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (68 / 240) is 0.2833\n\n####0.2833", "a": 68, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2833}
{"question": "Solve (926 / 85)", "answer": "The result of (926 / 85) is 10.8941\n\n####10.8941", "a": 926, "b": 85, "operator": "/", "result": 10.8941}
{"question": "Solve (789 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (789 - 485) is 304\n\n####304", "a": 789, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": 304}
{"question": "Solve (170 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (170 * 637) is 108290\n\n####108290", "a": 170, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 108290}
{"question": "Solve (37 / 295)", "answer": "The result of (37 / 295) is 0.1254\n\n####0.1254", "a": 37, "b": 295, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1254}
{"question": "Solve (458 - 845)", "answer": "The result of (458 - 845) is -387\n\n####-387", "a": 458, "b": 845, "operator": "-", "result": -387}
{"question": "Solve (835 * 177)", "answer": "The result of (835 * 177) is 147795\n\n####147795", "a": 835, "b": 177, "operator": "*", "result": 147795}
{"question": "Solve (814 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (814 * 958) is 779812\n\n####779812", "a": 814, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 779812}
{"question": "Solve (788 / 378)", "answer": "The result of (788 / 378) is 2.0847\n\n####2.0847", "a": 788, "b": 378, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0847}
{"question": "Solve (639 / 729)", "answer": "The result of (639 / 729) is 0.8765\n\n####0.8765", "a": 639, "b": 729, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8765}
{"question": "Solve (819 * 377)", "answer": "The result of (819 * 377) is 308763\n\n####308763", "a": 819, "b": 377, "operator": "*", "result": 308763}
{"question": "Solve (233 + 539)", "answer": "The result of (233 + 539) is 772\n\n####772", "a": 233, "b": 539, "operator": "+", "result": 772}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 454)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 454) is 133\n\n####133", "a": 587, "b": 454, "operator": "-", "result": 133}
{"question": "Solve (805 * 520)", "answer": "The result of (805 * 520) is 418600\n\n####418600", "a": 805, "b": 520, "operator": "*", "result": 418600}
{"question": "Solve (979 * 951)", "answer": "The result of (979 * 951) is 931029\n\n####931029", "a": 979, "b": 951, "operator": "*", "result": 931029}
{"question": "Solve (250 - 383)", "answer": "The result of (250 - 383) is -133\n\n####-133", "a": 250, "b": 383, "operator": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve (156 / 586)", "answer": "The result of (156 / 586) is 0.2662\n\n####0.2662", "a": 156, "b": 586, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2662}
{"question": "Solve (355 + 61)", "answer": "The result of (355 + 61) is 416\n\n####416", "a": 355, "b": 61, "operator": "+", "result": 416}
{"question": "Solve (433 + 762)", "answer": "The result of (433 + 762) is 1195\n\n####1195", "a": 433, "b": 762, "operator": "+", "result": 1195}
{"question": "Solve (618 - 149)", "answer": "The result of (618 - 149) is 469\n\n####469", "a": 618, "b": 149, "operator": "-", "result": 469}
{"question": "Solve (108 + 369)", "answer": "The result of (108 + 369) is 477\n\n####477", "a": 108, "b": 369, "operator": "+", "result": 477}
{"question": "Solve (516 + 446)", "answer": "The result of (516 + 446) is 962\n\n####962", "a": 516, "b": 446, "operator": "+", "result": 962}
{"question": "Solve (210 + 321)", "answer": "The result of (210 + 321) is 531\n\n####531", "a": 210, "b": 321, "operator": "+", "result": 531}
{"question": "Solve (837 - 130)", "answer": "The result of (837 - 130) is 707\n\n####707", "a": 837, "b": 130, "operator": "-", "result": 707}
{"question": "Solve (581 - 22)", "answer": "The result of (581 - 22) is 559\n\n####559", "a": 581, "b": 22, "operator": "-", "result": 559}
{"question": "Solve (300 * 25)", "answer": "The result of (300 * 25) is 7500\n\n####7500", "a": 300, "b": 25, "operator": "*", "result": 7500}
{"question": "Solve (966 + 265)", "answer": "The result of (966 + 265) is 1231\n\n####1231", "a": 966, "b": 265, "operator": "+", "result": 1231}
{"question": "Solve (305 - 41)", "answer": "The result of (305 - 41) is 264\n\n####264", "a": 305, "b": 41, "operator": "-", "result": 264}
{"question": "Solve (430 / 938)", "answer": "The result of (430 / 938) is 0.4584\n\n####0.4584", "a": 430, "b": 938, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4584}
{"question": "Solve (998 + 769)", "answer": "The result of (998 + 769) is 1767\n\n####1767", "a": 998, "b": 769, "operator": "+", "result": 1767}
{"question": "Solve (302 * 21)", "answer": "The result of (302 * 21) is 6342\n\n####6342", "a": 302, "b": 21, "operator": "*", "result": 6342}
{"question": "Solve (237 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (237 - 485) is -248\n\n####-248", "a": 237, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": -248}
{"question": "Solve (357 - 72)", "answer": "The result of (357 - 72) is 285\n\n####285", "a": 357, "b": 72, "operator": "-", "result": 285}
{"question": "Solve (644 + 455)", "answer": "The result of (644 + 455) is 1099\n\n####1099", "a": 644, "b": 455, "operator": "+", "result": 1099}
{"question": "Solve (126 * 520)", "answer": "The result of (126 * 520) is 65520\n\n####65520", "a": 126, "b": 520, "operator": "*", "result": 65520}
{"question": "Solve (344 * 800)", "answer": "The result of (344 * 800) is 275200\n\n####275200", "a": 344, "b": 800, "operator": "*", "result": 275200}
{"question": "Solve (958 + 908)", "answer": "The result of (958 + 908) is 1866\n\n####1866", "a": 958, "b": 908, "operator": "+", "result": 1866}
{"question": "Solve (717 - 204)", "answer": "The result of (717 - 204) is 513\n\n####513", "a": 717, "b": 204, "operator": "-", "result": 513}
{"question": "Solve (612 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (612 - 918) is -306\n\n####-306", "a": 612, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -306}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 234)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 234) is 1.3291\n\n####1.3291", "a": 311, "b": 234, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3291}
{"question": "Solve (584 + 763)", "answer": "The result of (584 + 763) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 584, "b": 763, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (740 * 48)", "answer": "The result of (740 * 48) is 35520\n\n####35520", "a": 740, "b": 48, "operator": "*", "result": 35520}
{"question": "Solve (95 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (95 * 407) is 38665\n\n####38665", "a": 95, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 38665}
{"question": "Solve (332 + 665)", "answer": "The result of (332 + 665) is 997\n\n####997", "a": 332, "b": 665, "operator": "+", "result": 997}
{"question": "Solve (36 + 949)", "answer": "The result of (36 + 949) is 985\n\n####985", "a": 36, "b": 949, "operator": "+", "result": 985}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 513)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 513) is 1481\n\n####1481", "a": 968, "b": 513, "operator": "+", "result": 1481}
{"question": "Solve (776 + 599)", "answer": "The result of (776 + 599) is 1375\n\n####1375", "a": 776, "b": 599, "operator": "+", "result": 1375}
{"question": "Solve (329 / 533)", "answer": "The result of (329 / 533) is 0.6173\n\n####0.6173", "a": 329, "b": 533, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6173}
{"question": "Solve (341 - 889)", "answer": "The result of (341 - 889) is -548\n\n####-548", "a": 341, "b": 889, "operator": "-", "result": -548}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 86)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 86) is 777\n\n####777", "a": 863, "b": 86, "operator": "-", "result": 777}
{"question": "Solve (802 - 513)", "answer": "The result of (802 - 513) is 289\n\n####289", "a": 802, "b": 513, "operator": "-", "result": 289}
{"question": "Solve (537 - 704)", "answer": "The result of (537 - 704) is -167\n\n####-167", "a": 537, "b": 704, "operator": "-", "result": -167}
{"question": "Solve (277 + 520)", "answer": "The result of (277 + 520) is 797\n\n####797", "a": 277, "b": 520, "operator": "+", "result": 797}
{"question": "Solve (799 + 444)", "answer": "The result of (799 + 444) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 799, "b": 444, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (903 + 708)", "answer": "The result of (903 + 708) is 1611\n\n####1611", "a": 903, "b": 708, "operator": "+", "result": 1611}
{"question": "Solve (154 * 751)", "answer": "The result of (154 * 751) is 115654\n\n####115654", "a": 154, "b": 751, "operator": "*", "result": 115654}
{"question": "Solve (115 - 93)", "answer": "The result of (115 - 93) is 22\n\n####22", "a": 115, "b": 93, "operator": "-", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve (781 - 460)", "answer": "The result of (781 - 460) is 321\n\n####321", "a": 781, "b": 460, "operator": "-", "result": 321}
{"question": "Solve (513 + 288)", "answer": "The result of (513 + 288) is 801\n\n####801", "a": 513, "b": 288, "operator": "+", "result": 801}
{"question": "Solve (593 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (593 - 250) is 343\n\n####343", "a": 593, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": 343}
{"question": "Solve (255 / 580)", "answer": "The result of (255 / 580) is 0.4397\n\n####0.4397", "a": 255, "b": 580, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4397}
{"question": "Solve (701 / 774)", "answer": "The result of (701 / 774) is 0.9057\n\n####0.9057", "a": 701, "b": 774, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9057}
{"question": "Solve (102 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (102 * 61) is 6222\n\n####6222", "a": 102, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 6222}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 645)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 645) is 648\n\n####648", "a": 3, "b": 645, "operator": "+", "result": 648}
{"question": "Solve (429 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (429 - 206) is 223\n\n####223", "a": 429, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": 223}
{"question": "Solve (597 * 377)", "answer": "The result of (597 * 377) is 225069\n\n####225069", "a": 597, "b": 377, "operator": "*", "result": 225069}
{"question": "Solve (686 + 641)", "answer": "The result of (686 + 641) is 1327\n\n####1327", "a": 686, "b": 641, "operator": "+", "result": 1327}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 69)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 69) is 24495\n\n####24495", "a": 355, "b": 69, "operator": "*", "result": 24495}
{"question": "Solve (29 * 969)", "answer": "The result of (29 * 969) is 28101\n\n####28101", "a": 29, "b": 969, "operator": "*", "result": 28101}
{"question": "Solve (749 / 658)", "answer": "The result of (749 / 658) is 1.1383\n\n####1.1383", "a": 749, "b": 658, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1383}
{"question": "Solve (166 - 348)", "answer": "The result of (166 - 348) is -182\n\n####-182", "a": 166, "b": 348, "operator": "-", "result": -182}
{"question": "Solve (9 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (9 / 427) is 0.0211\n\n####0.0211", "a": 9, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0211}
{"question": "Solve (952 + 377)", "answer": "The result of (952 + 377) is 1329\n\n####1329", "a": 952, "b": 377, "operator": "+", "result": 1329}
{"question": "Solve (499 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (499 - 166) is 333\n\n####333", "a": 499, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 333}
{"question": "Solve (114 + 613)", "answer": "The result of (114 + 613) is 727\n\n####727", "a": 114, "b": 613, "operator": "+", "result": 727}
{"question": "Solve (685 - 4)", "answer": "The result of (685 - 4) is 681\n\n####681", "a": 685, "b": 4, "operator": "-", "result": 681}
{"question": "Solve (284 / 119)", "answer": "The result of (284 / 119) is 2.3866\n\n####2.3866", "a": 284, "b": 119, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3866}
{"question": "Solve (653 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (653 - 6) is 647\n\n####647", "a": 653, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 647}
{"question": "Solve (218 + 524)", "answer": "The result of (218 + 524) is 742\n\n####742", "a": 218, "b": 524, "operator": "+", "result": 742}
{"question": "Solve (583 - 834)", "answer": "The result of (583 - 834) is -251\n\n####-251", "a": 583, "b": 834, "operator": "-", "result": -251}
{"question": "Solve (454 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (454 / 821) is 0.553\n\n####0.553", "a": 454, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.553}
{"question": "Solve (704 - 59)", "answer": "The result of (704 - 59) is 645\n\n####645", "a": 704, "b": 59, "operator": "-", "result": 645}
{"question": "Solve (201 + 210)", "answer": "The result of (201 + 210) is 411\n\n####411", "a": 201, "b": 210, "operator": "+", "result": 411}
{"question": "Solve (390 * 282)", "answer": "The result of (390 * 282) is 109980\n\n####109980", "a": 390, "b": 282, "operator": "*", "result": 109980}
{"question": "Solve (821 + 296)", "answer": "The result of (821 + 296) is 1117\n\n####1117", "a": 821, "b": 296, "operator": "+", "result": 1117}
{"question": "Solve (765 - 749)", "answer": "The result of (765 - 749) is 16\n\n####16", "a": 765, "b": 749, "operator": "-", "result": 16}
{"question": "Solve (388 / 731)", "answer": "The result of (388 / 731) is 0.5308\n\n####0.5308", "a": 388, "b": 731, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5308}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 706)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 706) is 358648\n\n####358648", "a": 508, "b": 706, "operator": "*", "result": 358648}
{"question": "Solve (559 * 761)", "answer": "The result of (559 * 761) is 425399\n\n####425399", "a": 559, "b": 761, "operator": "*", "result": 425399}
{"question": "Solve (818 + 637)", "answer": "The result of (818 + 637) is 1455\n\n####1455", "a": 818, "b": 637, "operator": "+", "result": 1455}
{"question": "Solve (314 + 143)", "answer": "The result of (314 + 143) is 457\n\n####457", "a": 314, "b": 143, "operator": "+", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve (673 - 139)", "answer": "The result of (673 - 139) is 534\n\n####534", "a": 673, "b": 139, "operator": "-", "result": 534}
{"question": "Solve (293 - 318)", "answer": "The result of (293 - 318) is -25\n\n####-25", "a": 293, "b": 318, "operator": "-", "result": -25}
{"question": "Solve (430 * 449)", "answer": "The result of (430 * 449) is 193070\n\n####193070", "a": 430, "b": 449, "operator": "*", "result": 193070}
{"question": "Solve (182 + 702)", "answer": "The result of (182 + 702) is 884\n\n####884", "a": 182, "b": 702, "operator": "+", "result": 884}
{"question": "Solve (147 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (147 + 239) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 147, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (155 * 808)", "answer": "The result of (155 * 808) is 125240\n\n####125240", "a": 155, "b": 808, "operator": "*", "result": 125240}
{"question": "Solve (364 * 171)", "answer": "The result of (364 * 171) is 62244\n\n####62244", "a": 364, "b": 171, "operator": "*", "result": 62244}
{"question": "Solve (996 / 615)", "answer": "The result of (996 / 615) is 1.6195\n\n####1.6195", "a": 996, "b": 615, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6195}
{"question": "Solve (153 / 495)", "answer": "The result of (153 / 495) is 0.3091\n\n####0.3091", "a": 153, "b": 495, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3091}
{"question": "Solve (205 * 331)", "answer": "The result of (205 * 331) is 67855\n\n####67855", "a": 205, "b": 331, "operator": "*", "result": 67855}
{"question": "Solve (617 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (617 / 299) is 2.0635\n\n####2.0635", "a": 617, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0635}
{"question": "Solve (156 * 730)", "answer": "The result of (156 * 730) is 113880\n\n####113880", "a": 156, "b": 730, "operator": "*", "result": 113880}
{"question": "Solve (569 * 398)", "answer": "The result of (569 * 398) is 226462\n\n####226462", "a": 569, "b": 398, "operator": "*", "result": 226462}
{"question": "Solve (577 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (577 / 768) is 0.7513\n\n####0.7513", "a": 577, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7513}
{"question": "Solve (5 * 147)", "answer": "The result of (5 * 147) is 735\n\n####735", "a": 5, "b": 147, "operator": "*", "result": 735}
{"question": "Solve (477 / 574)", "answer": "The result of (477 / 574) is 0.831\n\n####0.831", "a": 477, "b": 574, "operator": "/", "result": 0.831}
{"question": "Solve (591 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (591 - 943) is -352\n\n####-352", "a": 591, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -352}
{"question": "Solve (226 * 948)", "answer": "The result of (226 * 948) is 214248\n\n####214248", "a": 226, "b": 948, "operator": "*", "result": 214248}
{"question": "Solve (816 + 655)", "answer": "The result of (816 + 655) is 1471\n\n####1471", "a": 816, "b": 655, "operator": "+", "result": 1471}
{"question": "Solve (121 - 41)", "answer": "The result of (121 - 41) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 121, "b": 41, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (140 / 858)", "answer": "The result of (140 / 858) is 0.1632\n\n####0.1632", "a": 140, "b": 858, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1632}
{"question": "Solve (191 - 339)", "answer": "The result of (191 - 339) is -148\n\n####-148", "a": 191, "b": 339, "operator": "-", "result": -148}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 792)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 792) is 766656\n\n####766656", "a": 968, "b": 792, "operator": "*", "result": 766656}
{"question": "Solve (302 + 857)", "answer": "The result of (302 + 857) is 1159\n\n####1159", "a": 302, "b": 857, "operator": "+", "result": 1159}
{"question": "Solve (483 * 716)", "answer": "The result of (483 * 716) is 345828\n\n####345828", "a": 483, "b": 716, "operator": "*", "result": 345828}
{"question": "Solve (423 - 404)", "answer": "The result of (423 - 404) is 19\n\n####19", "a": 423, "b": 404, "operator": "-", "result": 19}
{"question": "Solve (802 + 390)", "answer": "The result of (802 + 390) is 1192\n\n####1192", "a": 802, "b": 390, "operator": "+", "result": 1192}
{"question": "Solve (778 - 841)", "answer": "The result of (778 - 841) is -63\n\n####-63", "a": 778, "b": 841, "operator": "-", "result": -63}
{"question": "Solve (144 / 203)", "answer": "The result of (144 / 203) is 0.7094\n\n####0.7094", "a": 144, "b": 203, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7094}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 412)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 412) is 0.6723\n\n####0.6723", "a": 277, "b": 412, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6723}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 619)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 619) is 0.559\n\n####0.559", "a": 346, "b": 619, "operator": "/", "result": 0.559}
{"question": "Solve (190 - 737)", "answer": "The result of (190 - 737) is -547\n\n####-547", "a": 190, "b": 737, "operator": "-", "result": -547}
{"question": "Solve (216 / 950)", "answer": "The result of (216 / 950) is 0.2274\n\n####0.2274", "a": 216, "b": 950, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2274}
{"question": "Solve (37 - 99)", "answer": "The result of (37 - 99) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 37, "b": 99, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (930 * 790)", "answer": "The result of (930 * 790) is 734700\n\n####734700", "a": 930, "b": 790, "operator": "*", "result": 734700}
{"question": "Solve (192 * 545)", "answer": "The result of (192 * 545) is 104640\n\n####104640", "a": 192, "b": 545, "operator": "*", "result": 104640}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 336)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 336) is -292\n\n####-292", "a": 44, "b": 336, "operator": "-", "result": -292}
{"question": "Solve (81 - 328)", "answer": "The result of (81 - 328) is -247\n\n####-247", "a": 81, "b": 328, "operator": "-", "result": -247}
{"question": "Solve (667 * 74)", "answer": "The result of (667 * 74) is 49358\n\n####49358", "a": 667, "b": 74, "operator": "*", "result": 49358}
{"question": "Solve (460 + 280)", "answer": "The result of (460 + 280) is 740\n\n####740", "a": 460, "b": 280, "operator": "+", "result": 740}
{"question": "Solve (502 + 909)", "answer": "The result of (502 + 909) is 1411\n\n####1411", "a": 502, "b": 909, "operator": "+", "result": 1411}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 571)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 571) is 202705\n\n####202705", "a": 355, "b": 571, "operator": "*", "result": 202705}
{"question": "Solve (316 / 492)", "answer": "The result of (316 / 492) is 0.6423\n\n####0.6423", "a": 316, "b": 492, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6423}
{"question": "Solve (852 / 57)", "answer": "The result of (852 / 57) is 14.9474\n\n####14.9474", "a": 852, "b": 57, "operator": "/", "result": 14.9474}
{"question": "Solve (268 - 322)", "answer": "The result of (268 - 322) is -54\n\n####-54", "a": 268, "b": 322, "operator": "-", "result": -54}
{"question": "Solve (553 / 690)", "answer": "The result of (553 / 690) is 0.8014\n\n####0.8014", "a": 553, "b": 690, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8014}
{"question": "Solve (925 * 986)", "answer": "The result of (925 * 986) is 912050\n\n####912050", "a": 925, "b": 986, "operator": "*", "result": 912050}
{"question": "Solve (4 + 406)", "answer": "The result of (4 + 406) is 410\n\n####410", "a": 4, "b": 406, "operator": "+", "result": 410}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 671)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 671) is -374\n\n####-374", "a": 297, "b": 671, "operator": "-", "result": -374}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 537) is -144\n\n####-144", "a": 393, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": -144}
{"question": "Solve (356 + 991)", "answer": "The result of (356 + 991) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 356, "b": 991, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (773 / 361)", "answer": "The result of (773 / 361) is 2.1413\n\n####2.1413", "a": 773, "b": 361, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1413}
{"question": "Solve (552 - 132)", "answer": "The result of (552 - 132) is 420\n\n####420", "a": 552, "b": 132, "operator": "-", "result": 420}
{"question": "Solve (39 - 542)", "answer": "The result of (39 - 542) is -503\n\n####-503", "a": 39, "b": 542, "operator": "-", "result": -503}
{"question": "Solve (907 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (907 - 700) is 207\n\n####207", "a": 907, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": 207}
{"question": "Solve (116 / 606)", "answer": "The result of (116 / 606) is 0.1914\n\n####0.1914", "a": 116, "b": 606, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1914}
{"question": "Solve (221 * 841)", "answer": "The result of (221 * 841) is 185861\n\n####185861", "a": 221, "b": 841, "operator": "*", "result": 185861}
{"question": "Solve (188 - 157)", "answer": "The result of (188 - 157) is 31\n\n####31", "a": 188, "b": 157, "operator": "-", "result": 31}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 805)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 805) is 0.5714\n\n####0.5714", "a": 460, "b": 805, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5714}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 779) is -326\n\n####-326", "a": 453, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": -326}
{"question": "Solve (132 - 268)", "answer": "The result of (132 - 268) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 132, "b": 268, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (571 * 603)", "answer": "The result of (571 * 603) is 344313\n\n####344313", "a": 571, "b": 603, "operator": "*", "result": 344313}
{"question": "Solve (310 + 341)", "answer": "The result of (310 + 341) is 651\n\n####651", "a": 310, "b": 341, "operator": "+", "result": 651}
{"question": "Solve (945 + 2)", "answer": "The result of (945 + 2) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 945, "b": 2, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (573 * 154)", "answer": "The result of (573 * 154) is 88242\n\n####88242", "a": 573, "b": 154, "operator": "*", "result": 88242}
{"question": "Solve (536 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (536 - 166) is 370\n\n####370", "a": 536, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 370}
{"question": "Solve (139 / 309)", "answer": "The result of (139 / 309) is 0.4498\n\n####0.4498", "a": 139, "b": 309, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4498}
{"question": "Solve (581 / 360)", "answer": "The result of (581 / 360) is 1.6139\n\n####1.6139", "a": 581, "b": 360, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6139}
{"question": "Solve (962 + 680)", "answer": "The result of (962 + 680) is 1642\n\n####1642", "a": 962, "b": 680, "operator": "+", "result": 1642}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 612)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 612) is 40392\n\n####40392", "a": 66, "b": 612, "operator": "*", "result": 40392}
{"question": "Solve (785 + 468)", "answer": "The result of (785 + 468) is 1253\n\n####1253", "a": 785, "b": 468, "operator": "+", "result": 1253}
{"question": "Solve (533 / 120)", "answer": "The result of (533 / 120) is 4.4417\n\n####4.4417", "a": 533, "b": 120, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4417}
{"question": "Solve (246 + 861)", "answer": "The result of (246 + 861) is 1107\n\n####1107", "a": 246, "b": 861, "operator": "+", "result": 1107}
{"question": "Solve (809 - 630)", "answer": "The result of (809 - 630) is 179\n\n####179", "a": 809, "b": 630, "operator": "-", "result": 179}
{"question": "Solve (882 * 163)", "answer": "The result of (882 * 163) is 143766\n\n####143766", "a": 882, "b": 163, "operator": "*", "result": 143766}
{"question": "Solve (967 + 886)", "answer": "The result of (967 + 886) is 1853\n\n####1853", "a": 967, "b": 886, "operator": "+", "result": 1853}
{"question": "Solve (28 * 298)", "answer": "The result of (28 * 298) is 8344\n\n####8344", "a": 28, "b": 298, "operator": "*", "result": 8344}
{"question": "Solve (238 * 78)", "answer": "The result of (238 * 78) is 18564\n\n####18564", "a": 238, "b": 78, "operator": "*", "result": 18564}
{"question": "Solve (959 + 381)", "answer": "The result of (959 + 381) is 1340\n\n####1340", "a": 959, "b": 381, "operator": "+", "result": 1340}
{"question": "Solve (478 + 831)", "answer": "The result of (478 + 831) is 1309\n\n####1309", "a": 478, "b": 831, "operator": "+", "result": 1309}
{"question": "Solve (974 + 937)", "answer": "The result of (974 + 937) is 1911\n\n####1911", "a": 974, "b": 937, "operator": "+", "result": 1911}
{"question": "Solve (593 * 397)", "answer": "The result of (593 * 397) is 235421\n\n####235421", "a": 593, "b": 397, "operator": "*", "result": 235421}
{"question": "Solve (458 * 460)", "answer": "The result of (458 * 460) is 210680\n\n####210680", "a": 458, "b": 460, "operator": "*", "result": 210680}
{"question": "Solve (439 - 151)", "answer": "The result of (439 - 151) is 288\n\n####288", "a": 439, "b": 151, "operator": "-", "result": 288}
{"question": "Solve (553 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (553 * 958) is 529774\n\n####529774", "a": 553, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 529774}
{"question": "Solve (721 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (721 - 317) is 404\n\n####404", "a": 721, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve (399 + 587)", "answer": "The result of (399 + 587) is 986\n\n####986", "a": 399, "b": 587, "operator": "+", "result": 986}
{"question": "Solve (833 * 957)", "answer": "The result of (833 * 957) is 797181\n\n####797181", "a": 833, "b": 957, "operator": "*", "result": 797181}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 545) is 1.5908\n\n####1.5908", "a": 867, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5908}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 343)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 343) is 0.1429\n\n####0.1429", "a": 49, "b": 343, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1429}
{"question": "Solve (429 * 969)", "answer": "The result of (429 * 969) is 415701\n\n####415701", "a": 429, "b": 969, "operator": "*", "result": 415701}
{"question": "Solve (696 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (696 * 387) is 269352\n\n####269352", "a": 696, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 269352}
{"question": "Solve (396 + 759)", "answer": "The result of (396 + 759) is 1155\n\n####1155", "a": 396, "b": 759, "operator": "+", "result": 1155}
{"question": "Solve (76 / 447)", "answer": "The result of (76 / 447) is 0.17\n\n####0.17", "a": 76, "b": 447, "operator": "/", "result": 0.17}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 754)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 754) is 12818\n\n####12818", "a": 17, "b": 754, "operator": "*", "result": 12818}
{"question": "Solve (422 * 525)", "answer": "The result of (422 * 525) is 221550\n\n####221550", "a": 422, "b": 525, "operator": "*", "result": 221550}
{"question": "Solve (705 * 339)", "answer": "The result of (705 * 339) is 238995\n\n####238995", "a": 705, "b": 339, "operator": "*", "result": 238995}
{"question": "Solve (7 * 746)", "answer": "The result of (7 * 746) is 5222\n\n####5222", "a": 7, "b": 746, "operator": "*", "result": 5222}
{"question": "Solve (24 / 664)", "answer": "The result of (24 / 664) is 0.0361\n\n####0.0361", "a": 24, "b": 664, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0361}
{"question": "Solve (511 * 626)", "answer": "The result of (511 * 626) is 319886\n\n####319886", "a": 511, "b": 626, "operator": "*", "result": 319886}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 753)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 753) is 0.2138\n\n####0.2138", "a": 161, "b": 753, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2138}
{"question": "Solve (531 - 715)", "answer": "The result of (531 - 715) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 531, "b": 715, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (989 - 122)", "answer": "The result of (989 - 122) is 867\n\n####867", "a": 989, "b": 122, "operator": "-", "result": 867}
{"question": "Solve (984 * 515)", "answer": "The result of (984 * 515) is 506760\n\n####506760", "a": 984, "b": 515, "operator": "*", "result": 506760}
{"question": "Solve (49 * 222)", "answer": "The result of (49 * 222) is 10878\n\n####10878", "a": 49, "b": 222, "operator": "*", "result": 10878}
{"question": "Solve (308 + 855)", "answer": "The result of (308 + 855) is 1163\n\n####1163", "a": 308, "b": 855, "operator": "+", "result": 1163}
{"question": "Solve (357 - 775)", "answer": "The result of (357 - 775) is -418\n\n####-418", "a": 357, "b": 775, "operator": "-", "result": -418}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 184) is 679\n\n####679", "a": 863, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 679}
{"question": "Solve (698 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (698 - 498) is 200\n\n####200", "a": 698, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": 200}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 601)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 601) is 365\n\n####365", "a": 966, "b": 601, "operator": "-", "result": 365}
{"question": "Solve (653 * 190)", "answer": "The result of (653 * 190) is 124070\n\n####124070", "a": 653, "b": 190, "operator": "*", "result": 124070}
{"question": "Solve (355 * 95)", "answer": "The result of (355 * 95) is 33725\n\n####33725", "a": 355, "b": 95, "operator": "*", "result": 33725}
{"question": "Solve (53 + 529)", "answer": "The result of (53 + 529) is 582\n\n####582", "a": 53, "b": 529, "operator": "+", "result": 582}
{"question": "Solve (804 / 423)", "answer": "The result of (804 / 423) is 1.9007\n\n####1.9007", "a": 804, "b": 423, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9007}
{"question": "Solve (270 * 572)", "answer": "The result of (270 * 572) is 154440\n\n####154440", "a": 270, "b": 572, "operator": "*", "result": 154440}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 588)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 588) is 470400\n\n####470400", "a": 800, "b": 588, "operator": "*", "result": 470400}
{"question": "Solve (127 * 717)", "answer": "The result of (127 * 717) is 91059\n\n####91059", "a": 127, "b": 717, "operator": "*", "result": 91059}
{"question": "Solve (352 / 664)", "answer": "The result of (352 / 664) is 0.5301\n\n####0.5301", "a": 352, "b": 664, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5301}
{"question": "Solve (62 + 509)", "answer": "The result of (62 + 509) is 571\n\n####571", "a": 62, "b": 509, "operator": "+", "result": 571}
{"question": "Solve (953 / 713)", "answer": "The result of (953 / 713) is 1.3366\n\n####1.3366", "a": 953, "b": 713, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3366}
{"question": "Solve (534 + 924)", "answer": "The result of (534 + 924) is 1458\n\n####1458", "a": 534, "b": 924, "operator": "+", "result": 1458}
{"question": "Solve (512 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (512 * 911) is 466432\n\n####466432", "a": 512, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 466432}
{"question": "Solve (438 + 295)", "answer": "The result of (438 + 295) is 733\n\n####733", "a": 438, "b": 295, "operator": "+", "result": 733}
{"question": "Solve (183 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (183 * 910) is 166530\n\n####166530", "a": 183, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 166530}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 399)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 399) is 434\n\n####434", "a": 833, "b": 399, "operator": "-", "result": 434}
{"question": "Solve (527 * 429)", "answer": "The result of (527 * 429) is 226083\n\n####226083", "a": 527, "b": 429, "operator": "*", "result": 226083}
{"question": "Solve (670 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (670 - 634) is 36\n\n####36", "a": 670, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": 36}
{"question": "Solve (861 - 275)", "answer": "The result of (861 - 275) is 586\n\n####586", "a": 861, "b": 275, "operator": "-", "result": 586}
{"question": "Solve (409 * 460)", "answer": "The result of (409 * 460) is 188140\n\n####188140", "a": 409, "b": 460, "operator": "*", "result": 188140}
{"question": "Solve (415 / 269)", "answer": "The result of (415 / 269) is 1.5428\n\n####1.5428", "a": 415, "b": 269, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5428}
{"question": "Solve (501 * 235)", "answer": "The result of (501 * 235) is 117735\n\n####117735", "a": 501, "b": 235, "operator": "*", "result": 117735}
{"question": "Solve (717 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (717 * 897) is 643149\n\n####643149", "a": 717, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 643149}
{"question": "Solve (85 * 515)", "answer": "The result of (85 * 515) is 43775\n\n####43775", "a": 85, "b": 515, "operator": "*", "result": 43775}
{"question": "Solve (762 - 331)", "answer": "The result of (762 - 331) is 431\n\n####431", "a": 762, "b": 331, "operator": "-", "result": 431}
{"question": "Solve (326 + 133)", "answer": "The result of (326 + 133) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 326, "b": 133, "operator": "+", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (576 * 863)", "answer": "The result of (576 * 863) is 497088\n\n####497088", "a": 576, "b": 863, "operator": "*", "result": 497088}
{"question": "Solve (456 + 17)", "answer": "The result of (456 + 17) is 473\n\n####473", "a": 456, "b": 17, "operator": "+", "result": 473}
{"question": "Solve (698 - 76)", "answer": "The result of (698 - 76) is 622\n\n####622", "a": 698, "b": 76, "operator": "-", "result": 622}
{"question": "Solve (61 * 853)", "answer": "The result of (61 * 853) is 52033\n\n####52033", "a": 61, "b": 853, "operator": "*", "result": 52033}
{"question": "Solve (866 - 292)", "answer": "The result of (866 - 292) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 866, "b": 292, "operator": "-", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (938 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (938 - 551) is 387\n\n####387", "a": 938, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 387}
{"question": "Solve (896 + 657)", "answer": "The result of (896 + 657) is 1553\n\n####1553", "a": 896, "b": 657, "operator": "+", "result": 1553}
{"question": "Solve (381 * 260)", "answer": "The result of (381 * 260) is 99060\n\n####99060", "a": 381, "b": 260, "operator": "*", "result": 99060}
{"question": "Solve (626 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (626 - 846) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 626, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (680 + 380)", "answer": "The result of (680 + 380) is 1060\n\n####1060", "a": 680, "b": 380, "operator": "+", "result": 1060}
{"question": "Solve (561 + 758)", "answer": "The result of (561 + 758) is 1319\n\n####1319", "a": 561, "b": 758, "operator": "+", "result": 1319}
{"question": "Solve (74 - 765)", "answer": "The result of (74 - 765) is -691\n\n####-691", "a": 74, "b": 765, "operator": "-", "result": -691}
{"question": "Solve (978 - 959)", "answer": "The result of (978 - 959) is 19\n\n####19", "a": 978, "b": 959, "operator": "-", "result": 19}
{"question": "Solve (681 * 726)", "answer": "The result of (681 * 726) is 494406\n\n####494406", "a": 681, "b": 726, "operator": "*", "result": 494406}
{"question": "Solve (459 * 699)", "answer": "The result of (459 * 699) is 320841\n\n####320841", "a": 459, "b": 699, "operator": "*", "result": 320841}
{"question": "Solve (478 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (478 / 815) is 0.5865\n\n####0.5865", "a": 478, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5865}
{"question": "Solve (347 - 70)", "answer": "The result of (347 - 70) is 277\n\n####277", "a": 347, "b": 70, "operator": "-", "result": 277}
{"question": "Solve (614 + 415)", "answer": "The result of (614 + 415) is 1029\n\n####1029", "a": 614, "b": 415, "operator": "+", "result": 1029}
{"question": "Solve (149 + 526)", "answer": "The result of (149 + 526) is 675\n\n####675", "a": 149, "b": 526, "operator": "+", "result": 675}
{"question": "Solve (808 - 401)", "answer": "The result of (808 - 401) is 407\n\n####407", "a": 808, "b": 401, "operator": "-", "result": 407}
{"question": "Solve (501 - 783)", "answer": "The result of (501 - 783) is -282\n\n####-282", "a": 501, "b": 783, "operator": "-", "result": -282}
{"question": "Solve (535 - 173)", "answer": "The result of (535 - 173) is 362\n\n####362", "a": 535, "b": 173, "operator": "-", "result": 362}
{"question": "Solve (602 * 371)", "answer": "The result of (602 * 371) is 223342\n\n####223342", "a": 602, "b": 371, "operator": "*", "result": 223342}
{"question": "Solve (836 - 603)", "answer": "The result of (836 - 603) is 233\n\n####233", "a": 836, "b": 603, "operator": "-", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve (984 - 292)", "answer": "The result of (984 - 292) is 692\n\n####692", "a": 984, "b": 292, "operator": "-", "result": 692}
{"question": "Solve (877 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (877 - 471) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 877, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (23 * 286)", "answer": "The result of (23 * 286) is 6578\n\n####6578", "a": 23, "b": 286, "operator": "*", "result": 6578}
{"question": "Solve (959 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (959 / 695) is 1.3799\n\n####1.3799", "a": 959, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3799}
{"question": "Solve (865 - 42)", "answer": "The result of (865 - 42) is 823\n\n####823", "a": 865, "b": 42, "operator": "-", "result": 823}
{"question": "Solve (175 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (175 / 914) is 0.1915\n\n####0.1915", "a": 175, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1915}
{"question": "Solve (579 + 16)", "answer": "The result of (579 + 16) is 595\n\n####595", "a": 579, "b": 16, "operator": "+", "result": 595}
{"question": "Solve (895 * 607)", "answer": "The result of (895 * 607) is 543265\n\n####543265", "a": 895, "b": 607, "operator": "*", "result": 543265}
{"question": "Solve (178 + 189)", "answer": "The result of (178 + 189) is 367\n\n####367", "a": 178, "b": 189, "operator": "+", "result": 367}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 911) is 728800\n\n####728800", "a": 800, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 728800}
{"question": "Solve (373 / 171)", "answer": "The result of (373 / 171) is 2.1813\n\n####2.1813", "a": 373, "b": 171, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1813}
{"question": "Solve (46 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (46 * 387) is 17802\n\n####17802", "a": 46, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 17802}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 145) is 140795\n\n####140795", "a": 971, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 140795}
{"question": "Solve (130 - 332)", "answer": "The result of (130 - 332) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 130, "b": 332, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (493 - 684)", "answer": "The result of (493 - 684) is -191\n\n####-191", "a": 493, "b": 684, "operator": "-", "result": -191}
{"question": "Solve (302 - 576)", "answer": "The result of (302 - 576) is -274\n\n####-274", "a": 302, "b": 576, "operator": "-", "result": -274}
{"question": "Solve (796 + 868)", "answer": "The result of (796 + 868) is 1664\n\n####1664", "a": 796, "b": 868, "operator": "+", "result": 1664}
{"question": "Solve (85 - 235)", "answer": "The result of (85 - 235) is -150\n\n####-150", "a": 85, "b": 235, "operator": "-", "result": -150}
{"question": "Solve (965 * 195)", "answer": "The result of (965 * 195) is 188175\n\n####188175", "a": 965, "b": 195, "operator": "*", "result": 188175}
{"question": "Solve (134 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (134 - 358) is -224\n\n####-224", "a": 134, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": -224}
{"question": "Solve (751 + 504)", "answer": "The result of (751 + 504) is 1255\n\n####1255", "a": 751, "b": 504, "operator": "+", "result": 1255}
{"question": "Solve (447 - 105)", "answer": "The result of (447 - 105) is 342\n\n####342", "a": 447, "b": 105, "operator": "-", "result": 342}
{"question": "Solve (824 / 793)", "answer": "The result of (824 / 793) is 1.0391\n\n####1.0391", "a": 824, "b": 793, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0391}
{"question": "Solve (529 - 826)", "answer": "The result of (529 - 826) is -297\n\n####-297", "a": 529, "b": 826, "operator": "-", "result": -297}
{"question": "Solve (442 / 220)", "answer": "The result of (442 / 220) is 2.0091\n\n####2.0091", "a": 442, "b": 220, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0091}
{"question": "Solve (407 / 769)", "answer": "The result of (407 / 769) is 0.5293\n\n####0.5293", "a": 407, "b": 769, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5293}
{"question": "Solve (937 * 516)", "answer": "The result of (937 * 516) is 483492\n\n####483492", "a": 937, "b": 516, "operator": "*", "result": 483492}
{"question": "Solve (289 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (289 / 322) is 0.8975\n\n####0.8975", "a": 289, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8975}
{"question": "Solve (397 - 251)", "answer": "The result of (397 - 251) is 146\n\n####146", "a": 397, "b": 251, "operator": "-", "result": 146}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 591)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 591) is 1082\n\n####1082", "a": 491, "b": 591, "operator": "+", "result": 1082}
{"question": "Solve (830 / 566)", "answer": "The result of (830 / 566) is 1.4664\n\n####1.4664", "a": 830, "b": 566, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4664}
{"question": "Solve (748 / 108)", "answer": "The result of (748 / 108) is 6.9259\n\n####6.9259", "a": 748, "b": 108, "operator": "/", "result": 6.9259}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 961)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 961) is 1904\n\n####1904", "a": 943, "b": 961, "operator": "+", "result": 1904}
{"question": "Solve (148 / 138)", "answer": "The result of (148 / 138) is 1.0725\n\n####1.0725", "a": 148, "b": 138, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0725}
{"question": "Solve (372 / 244)", "answer": "The result of (372 / 244) is 1.5246\n\n####1.5246", "a": 372, "b": 244, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5246}
{"question": "Solve (654 * 206)", "answer": "The result of (654 * 206) is 134724\n\n####134724", "a": 654, "b": 206, "operator": "*", "result": 134724}
{"question": "Solve (823 - 339)", "answer": "The result of (823 - 339) is 484\n\n####484", "a": 823, "b": 339, "operator": "-", "result": 484}
{"question": "Solve (439 * 798)", "answer": "The result of (439 * 798) is 350322\n\n####350322", "a": 439, "b": 798, "operator": "*", "result": 350322}
{"question": "Solve (489 - 10)", "answer": "The result of (489 - 10) is 479\n\n####479", "a": 489, "b": 10, "operator": "-", "result": 479}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 577)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 577) is 0.5633\n\n####0.5633", "a": 325, "b": 577, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5633}
{"question": "Solve (956 / 41)", "answer": "The result of (956 / 41) is 23.3171\n\n####23.3171", "a": 956, "b": 41, "operator": "/", "result": 23.3171}
{"question": "Solve (966 * 172)", "answer": "The result of (966 * 172) is 166152\n\n####166152", "a": 966, "b": 172, "operator": "*", "result": 166152}
{"question": "Solve (57 + 743)", "answer": "The result of (57 + 743) is 800\n\n####800", "a": 57, "b": 743, "operator": "+", "result": 800}
{"question": "Solve (279 - 86)", "answer": "The result of (279 - 86) is 193\n\n####193", "a": 279, "b": 86, "operator": "-", "result": 193}
{"question": "Solve (500 + 847)", "answer": "The result of (500 + 847) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 500, "b": 847, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (484 / 936)", "answer": "The result of (484 / 936) is 0.5171\n\n####0.5171", "a": 484, "b": 936, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5171}
{"question": "Solve (439 * 732)", "answer": "The result of (439 * 732) is 321348\n\n####321348", "a": 439, "b": 732, "operator": "*", "result": 321348}
{"question": "Solve (175 * 482)", "answer": "The result of (175 * 482) is 84350\n\n####84350", "a": 175, "b": 482, "operator": "*", "result": 84350}
{"question": "Solve (118 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (118 - 937) is -819\n\n####-819", "a": 118, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -819}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 150)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 150) is 0.6733\n\n####0.6733", "a": 101, "b": 150, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6733}
{"question": "Solve (88 + 406)", "answer": "The result of (88 + 406) is 494\n\n####494", "a": 88, "b": 406, "operator": "+", "result": 494}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 686) is 0.0146\n\n####0.0146", "a": 10, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0146}
{"question": "Solve (583 * 549)", "answer": "The result of (583 * 549) is 320067\n\n####320067", "a": 583, "b": 549, "operator": "*", "result": 320067}
{"question": "Solve (410 + 599)", "answer": "The result of (410 + 599) is 1009\n\n####1009", "a": 410, "b": 599, "operator": "+", "result": 1009}
{"question": "Solve (73 - 865)", "answer": "The result of (73 - 865) is -792\n\n####-792", "a": 73, "b": 865, "operator": "-", "result": -792}
{"question": "Solve (343 / 109)", "answer": "The result of (343 / 109) is 3.1468\n\n####3.1468", "a": 343, "b": 109, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1468}
{"question": "Solve (539 - 809)", "answer": "The result of (539 - 809) is -270\n\n####-270", "a": 539, "b": 809, "operator": "-", "result": -270}
{"question": "Solve (772 - 672)", "answer": "The result of (772 - 672) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 772, "b": 672, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (272 - 458)", "answer": "The result of (272 - 458) is -186\n\n####-186", "a": 272, "b": 458, "operator": "-", "result": -186}
{"question": "Solve (304 / 170)", "answer": "The result of (304 / 170) is 1.7882\n\n####1.7882", "a": 304, "b": 170, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7882}
{"question": "Solve (212 / 659)", "answer": "The result of (212 / 659) is 0.3217\n\n####0.3217", "a": 212, "b": 659, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3217}
{"question": "Solve (981 + 795)", "answer": "The result of (981 + 795) is 1776\n\n####1776", "a": 981, "b": 795, "operator": "+", "result": 1776}
{"question": "Solve (490 / 198)", "answer": "The result of (490 / 198) is 2.4747\n\n####2.4747", "a": 490, "b": 198, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4747}
{"question": "Solve (798 * 304)", "answer": "The result of (798 * 304) is 242592\n\n####242592", "a": 798, "b": 304, "operator": "*", "result": 242592}
{"question": "Solve (787 + 981)", "answer": "The result of (787 + 981) is 1768\n\n####1768", "a": 787, "b": 981, "operator": "+", "result": 1768}
{"question": "Solve (90 * 515)", "answer": "The result of (90 * 515) is 46350\n\n####46350", "a": 90, "b": 515, "operator": "*", "result": 46350}
{"question": "Solve (525 + 67)", "answer": "The result of (525 + 67) is 592\n\n####592", "a": 525, "b": 67, "operator": "+", "result": 592}
{"question": "Solve (868 / 976)", "answer": "The result of (868 / 976) is 0.8893\n\n####0.8893", "a": 868, "b": 976, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8893}
{"question": "Solve (770 * 378)", "answer": "The result of (770 * 378) is 291060\n\n####291060", "a": 770, "b": 378, "operator": "*", "result": 291060}
{"question": "Solve (996 + 857)", "answer": "The result of (996 + 857) is 1853\n\n####1853", "a": 996, "b": 857, "operator": "+", "result": 1853}
{"question": "Solve (517 + 77)", "answer": "The result of (517 + 77) is 594\n\n####594", "a": 517, "b": 77, "operator": "+", "result": 594}
{"question": "Solve (213 / 570)", "answer": "The result of (213 / 570) is 0.3737\n\n####0.3737", "a": 213, "b": 570, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3737}
{"question": "Solve (285 + 285)", "answer": "The result of (285 + 285) is 570\n\n####570", "a": 285, "b": 285, "operator": "+", "result": 570}
{"question": "Solve (122 / 617)", "answer": "The result of (122 / 617) is 0.1977\n\n####0.1977", "a": 122, "b": 617, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1977}
{"question": "Solve (983 + 853)", "answer": "The result of (983 + 853) is 1836\n\n####1836", "a": 983, "b": 853, "operator": "+", "result": 1836}
{"question": "Solve (603 / 152)", "answer": "The result of (603 / 152) is 3.9671\n\n####3.9671", "a": 603, "b": 152, "operator": "/", "result": 3.9671}
{"question": "Solve (281 / 843)", "answer": "The result of (281 / 843) is 0.3333\n\n####0.3333", "a": 281, "b": 843, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3333}
{"question": "Solve (738 * 102)", "answer": "The result of (738 * 102) is 75276\n\n####75276", "a": 738, "b": 102, "operator": "*", "result": 75276}
{"question": "Solve (530 + 904)", "answer": "The result of (530 + 904) is 1434\n\n####1434", "a": 530, "b": 904, "operator": "+", "result": 1434}
{"question": "Solve (407 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (407 + 805) is 1212\n\n####1212", "a": 407, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1212}
{"question": "Solve (131 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (131 * 637) is 83447\n\n####83447", "a": 131, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 83447}
{"question": "Solve (897 + 986)", "answer": "The result of (897 + 986) is 1883\n\n####1883", "a": 897, "b": 986, "operator": "+", "result": 1883}
{"question": "Solve (829 / 469)", "answer": "The result of (829 / 469) is 1.7676\n\n####1.7676", "a": 829, "b": 469, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7676}
{"question": "Solve (457 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (457 - 233) is 224\n\n####224", "a": 457, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": 224}
{"question": "Solve (254 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (254 / 821) is 0.3094\n\n####0.3094", "a": 254, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3094}
{"question": "Solve (166 - 465)", "answer": "The result of (166 - 465) is -299\n\n####-299", "a": 166, "b": 465, "operator": "-", "result": -299}
{"question": "Solve (614 / 424)", "answer": "The result of (614 / 424) is 1.4481\n\n####1.4481", "a": 614, "b": 424, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4481}
{"question": "Solve (154 / 92)", "answer": "The result of (154 / 92) is 1.6739\n\n####1.6739", "a": 154, "b": 92, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6739}
{"question": "Solve (124 - 659)", "answer": "The result of (124 - 659) is -535\n\n####-535", "a": 124, "b": 659, "operator": "-", "result": -535}
{"question": "Solve (595 * 709)", "answer": "The result of (595 * 709) is 421855\n\n####421855", "a": 595, "b": 709, "operator": "*", "result": 421855}
{"question": "Solve (304 * 259)", "answer": "The result of (304 * 259) is 78736\n\n####78736", "a": 304, "b": 259, "operator": "*", "result": 78736}
{"question": "Solve (60 - 796)", "answer": "The result of (60 - 796) is -736\n\n####-736", "a": 60, "b": 796, "operator": "-", "result": -736}
{"question": "Solve (531 + 335)", "answer": "The result of (531 + 335) is 866\n\n####866", "a": 531, "b": 335, "operator": "+", "result": 866}
{"question": "Solve (574 + 107)", "answer": "The result of (574 + 107) is 681\n\n####681", "a": 574, "b": 107, "operator": "+", "result": 681}
{"question": "Solve (103 + 115)", "answer": "The result of (103 + 115) is 218\n\n####218", "a": 103, "b": 115, "operator": "+", "result": 218}
{"question": "Solve (745 / 491)", "answer": "The result of (745 / 491) is 1.5173\n\n####1.5173", "a": 745, "b": 491, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5173}
{"question": "Solve (684 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (684 - 452) is 232\n\n####232", "a": 684, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve (765 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (765 - 933) is -168\n\n####-168", "a": 765, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -168}
{"question": "Solve (628 / 107)", "answer": "The result of (628 / 107) is 5.8692\n\n####5.8692", "a": 628, "b": 107, "operator": "/", "result": 5.8692}
{"question": "Solve (572 / 383)", "answer": "The result of (572 / 383) is 1.4935\n\n####1.4935", "a": 572, "b": 383, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4935}
{"question": "Solve (406 + 167)", "answer": "The result of (406 + 167) is 573\n\n####573", "a": 406, "b": 167, "operator": "+", "result": 573}
{"question": "Solve (570 + 362)", "answer": "The result of (570 + 362) is 932\n\n####932", "a": 570, "b": 362, "operator": "+", "result": 932}
{"question": "Solve (926 / 138)", "answer": "The result of (926 / 138) is 6.7101\n\n####6.7101", "a": 926, "b": 138, "operator": "/", "result": 6.7101}
{"question": "Solve (401 - 718)", "answer": "The result of (401 - 718) is -317\n\n####-317", "a": 401, "b": 718, "operator": "-", "result": -317}
{"question": "Solve (301 - 516)", "answer": "The result of (301 - 516) is -215\n\n####-215", "a": 301, "b": 516, "operator": "-", "result": -215}
{"question": "Solve (969 * 719)", "answer": "The result of (969 * 719) is 696711\n\n####696711", "a": 969, "b": 719, "operator": "*", "result": 696711}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 409)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 409) is 1086\n\n####1086", "a": 677, "b": 409, "operator": "+", "result": 1086}
{"question": "Solve (850 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (850 - 354) is 496\n\n####496", "a": 850, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": 496}
{"question": "Solve (143 * 88)", "answer": "The result of (143 * 88) is 12584\n\n####12584", "a": 143, "b": 88, "operator": "*", "result": 12584}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 49)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 49) is 6615\n\n####6615", "a": 135, "b": 49, "operator": "*", "result": 6615}
{"question": "Solve (62 - 314)", "answer": "The result of (62 - 314) is -252\n\n####-252", "a": 62, "b": 314, "operator": "-", "result": -252}
{"question": "Solve (552 * 558)", "answer": "The result of (552 * 558) is 308016\n\n####308016", "a": 552, "b": 558, "operator": "*", "result": 308016}
{"question": "Solve (25 - 639)", "answer": "The result of (25 - 639) is -614\n\n####-614", "a": 25, "b": 639, "operator": "-", "result": -614}
{"question": "Solve (470 / 175)", "answer": "The result of (470 / 175) is 2.6857\n\n####2.6857", "a": 470, "b": 175, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6857}
{"question": "Solve (62 - 128)", "answer": "The result of (62 - 128) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 62, "b": 128, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (927 + 995)", "answer": "The result of (927 + 995) is 1922\n\n####1922", "a": 927, "b": 995, "operator": "+", "result": 1922}
{"question": "Solve (325 - 705)", "answer": "The result of (325 - 705) is -380\n\n####-380", "a": 325, "b": 705, "operator": "-", "result": -380}
{"question": "Solve (363 + 96)", "answer": "The result of (363 + 96) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 363, "b": 96, "operator": "+", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (24 + 478)", "answer": "The result of (24 + 478) is 502\n\n####502", "a": 24, "b": 478, "operator": "+", "result": 502}
{"question": "Solve (939 - 229)", "answer": "The result of (939 - 229) is 710\n\n####710", "a": 939, "b": 229, "operator": "-", "result": 710}
{"question": "Solve (289 - 814)", "answer": "The result of (289 - 814) is -525\n\n####-525", "a": 289, "b": 814, "operator": "-", "result": -525}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 557)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 557) is 1.6481\n\n####1.6481", "a": 918, "b": 557, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6481}
{"question": "Solve (792 - 229)", "answer": "The result of (792 - 229) is 563\n\n####563", "a": 792, "b": 229, "operator": "-", "result": 563}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 856)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 856) is 0.2407\n\n####0.2407", "a": 206, "b": 856, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2407}
{"question": "Solve (876 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (876 - 117) is 759\n\n####759", "a": 876, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": 759}
{"question": "Solve (565 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (565 / 240) is 2.3542\n\n####2.3542", "a": 565, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3542}
{"question": "Solve (989 + 85)", "answer": "The result of (989 + 85) is 1074\n\n####1074", "a": 989, "b": 85, "operator": "+", "result": 1074}
{"question": "Solve (246 + 940)", "answer": "The result of (246 + 940) is 1186\n\n####1186", "a": 246, "b": 940, "operator": "+", "result": 1186}
{"question": "Solve (947 * 647)", "answer": "The result of (947 * 647) is 612709\n\n####612709", "a": 947, "b": 647, "operator": "*", "result": 612709}
{"question": "Solve (806 - 83)", "answer": "The result of (806 - 83) is 723\n\n####723", "a": 806, "b": 83, "operator": "-", "result": 723}
{"question": "Solve (968 / 986)", "answer": "The result of (968 / 986) is 0.9817\n\n####0.9817", "a": 968, "b": 986, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9817}
{"question": "Solve (642 * 242)", "answer": "The result of (642 * 242) is 155364\n\n####155364", "a": 642, "b": 242, "operator": "*", "result": 155364}
{"question": "Solve (150 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (150 / 300) is 0.5\n\n####0.5", "a": 150, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5}
{"question": "Solve (800 - 977)", "answer": "The result of (800 - 977) is -177\n\n####-177", "a": 800, "b": 977, "operator": "-", "result": -177}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 424)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 424) is 61056\n\n####61056", "a": 144, "b": 424, "operator": "*", "result": 61056}
{"question": "Solve (306 * 116)", "answer": "The result of (306 * 116) is 35496\n\n####35496", "a": 306, "b": 116, "operator": "*", "result": 35496}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 215)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 215) is 706\n\n####706", "a": 491, "b": 215, "operator": "+", "result": 706}
{"question": "Solve (16 / 907)", "answer": "The result of (16 / 907) is 0.0176\n\n####0.0176", "a": 16, "b": 907, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0176}
{"question": "Solve (311 - 680)", "answer": "The result of (311 - 680) is -369\n\n####-369", "a": 311, "b": 680, "operator": "-", "result": -369}
{"question": "Solve (329 / 588)", "answer": "The result of (329 / 588) is 0.5595\n\n####0.5595", "a": 329, "b": 588, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5595}
{"question": "Solve (410 * 19)", "answer": "The result of (410 * 19) is 7790\n\n####7790", "a": 410, "b": 19, "operator": "*", "result": 7790}
{"question": "Solve (304 * 348)", "answer": "The result of (304 * 348) is 105792\n\n####105792", "a": 304, "b": 348, "operator": "*", "result": 105792}
{"question": "Solve (883 + 876)", "answer": "The result of (883 + 876) is 1759\n\n####1759", "a": 883, "b": 876, "operator": "+", "result": 1759}
{"question": "Solve (822 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (822 - 45) is 777\n\n####777", "a": 822, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 777}
{"question": "Solve (665 + 852)", "answer": "The result of (665 + 852) is 1517\n\n####1517", "a": 665, "b": 852, "operator": "+", "result": 1517}
{"question": "Solve (362 / 543)", "answer": "The result of (362 / 543) is 0.6667\n\n####0.6667", "a": 362, "b": 543, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6667}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 14)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 14) is 0.7143\n\n####0.7143", "a": 10, "b": 14, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7143}
{"question": "Solve (784 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (784 - 849) is -65\n\n####-65", "a": 784, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve (576 * 723)", "answer": "The result of (576 * 723) is 416448\n\n####416448", "a": 576, "b": 723, "operator": "*", "result": 416448}
{"question": "Solve (734 - 664)", "answer": "The result of (734 - 664) is 70\n\n####70", "a": 734, "b": 664, "operator": "-", "result": 70}
{"question": "Solve (792 / 454)", "answer": "The result of (792 / 454) is 1.7445\n\n####1.7445", "a": 792, "b": 454, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7445}
{"question": "Solve (104 * 428)", "answer": "The result of (104 * 428) is 44512\n\n####44512", "a": 104, "b": 428, "operator": "*", "result": 44512}
{"question": "Solve (982 - 624)", "answer": "The result of (982 - 624) is 358\n\n####358", "a": 982, "b": 624, "operator": "-", "result": 358}
{"question": "Solve (235 - 893)", "answer": "The result of (235 - 893) is -658\n\n####-658", "a": 235, "b": 893, "operator": "-", "result": -658}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 601)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 601) is 232\n\n####232", "a": 833, "b": 601, "operator": "-", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve (471 * 139)", "answer": "The result of (471 * 139) is 65469\n\n####65469", "a": 471, "b": 139, "operator": "*", "result": 65469}
{"question": "Solve (64 * 204)", "answer": "The result of (64 * 204) is 13056\n\n####13056", "a": 64, "b": 204, "operator": "*", "result": 13056}
{"question": "Solve (117 - 672)", "answer": "The result of (117 - 672) is -555\n\n####-555", "a": 117, "b": 672, "operator": "-", "result": -555}
{"question": "Solve (176 * 310)", "answer": "The result of (176 * 310) is 54560\n\n####54560", "a": 176, "b": 310, "operator": "*", "result": 54560}
{"question": "Solve (164 * 797)", "answer": "The result of (164 * 797) is 130708\n\n####130708", "a": 164, "b": 797, "operator": "*", "result": 130708}
{"question": "Solve (83 / 61)", "answer": "The result of (83 / 61) is 1.3607\n\n####1.3607", "a": 83, "b": 61, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3607}
{"question": "Solve (248 + 828)", "answer": "The result of (248 + 828) is 1076\n\n####1076", "a": 248, "b": 828, "operator": "+", "result": 1076}
{"question": "Solve (65 / 578)", "answer": "The result of (65 / 578) is 0.1125\n\n####0.1125", "a": 65, "b": 578, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1125}
{"question": "Solve (921 * 264)", "answer": "The result of (921 * 264) is 243144\n\n####243144", "a": 921, "b": 264, "operator": "*", "result": 243144}
{"question": "Solve (915 - 983)", "answer": "The result of (915 - 983) is -68\n\n####-68", "a": 915, "b": 983, "operator": "-", "result": -68}
{"question": "Solve (764 * 793)", "answer": "The result of (764 * 793) is 605852\n\n####605852", "a": 764, "b": 793, "operator": "*", "result": 605852}
{"question": "Solve (408 * 758)", "answer": "The result of (408 * 758) is 309264\n\n####309264", "a": 408, "b": 758, "operator": "*", "result": 309264}
{"question": "Solve (224 - 752)", "answer": "The result of (224 - 752) is -528\n\n####-528", "a": 224, "b": 752, "operator": "-", "result": -528}
{"question": "Solve (961 / 539)", "answer": "The result of (961 / 539) is 1.7829\n\n####1.7829", "a": 961, "b": 539, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7829}
{"question": "Solve (593 / 507)", "answer": "The result of (593 / 507) is 1.1696\n\n####1.1696", "a": 593, "b": 507, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1696}
{"question": "Solve (745 * 915)", "answer": "The result of (745 * 915) is 681675\n\n####681675", "a": 745, "b": 915, "operator": "*", "result": 681675}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 612)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 612) is 0.1438\n\n####0.1438", "a": 88, "b": 612, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1438}
{"question": "Solve (873 * 36)", "answer": "The result of (873 * 36) is 31428\n\n####31428", "a": 873, "b": 36, "operator": "*", "result": 31428}
{"question": "Solve (18 * 772)", "answer": "The result of (18 * 772) is 13896\n\n####13896", "a": 18, "b": 772, "operator": "*", "result": 13896}
{"question": "Solve (724 - 151)", "answer": "The result of (724 - 151) is 573\n\n####573", "a": 724, "b": 151, "operator": "-", "result": 573}
{"question": "Solve (158 + 409)", "answer": "The result of (158 + 409) is 567\n\n####567", "a": 158, "b": 409, "operator": "+", "result": 567}
{"question": "Solve (403 * 49)", "answer": "The result of (403 * 49) is 19747\n\n####19747", "a": 403, "b": 49, "operator": "*", "result": 19747}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 66)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 66) is 28\n\n####28", "a": 94, "b": 66, "operator": "-", "result": 28}
{"question": "Solve (375 / 866)", "answer": "The result of (375 / 866) is 0.433\n\n####0.433", "a": 375, "b": 866, "operator": "/", "result": 0.433}
{"question": "Solve (160 * 924)", "answer": "The result of (160 * 924) is 147840\n\n####147840", "a": 160, "b": 924, "operator": "*", "result": 147840}
{"question": "Solve (457 * 199)", "answer": "The result of (457 * 199) is 90943\n\n####90943", "a": 457, "b": 199, "operator": "*", "result": 90943}
{"question": "Solve (128 + 258)", "answer": "The result of (128 + 258) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 128, "b": 258, "operator": "+", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (983 - 199)", "answer": "The result of (983 - 199) is 784\n\n####784", "a": 983, "b": 199, "operator": "-", "result": 784}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 933)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 933) is 0.8146\n\n####0.8146", "a": 760, "b": 933, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8146}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 274)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 274) is 263588\n\n####263588", "a": 962, "b": 274, "operator": "*", "result": 263588}
{"question": "Solve (359 / 553)", "answer": "The result of (359 / 553) is 0.6492\n\n####0.6492", "a": 359, "b": 553, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6492}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 475)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 475) is 0.9684\n\n####0.9684", "a": 460, "b": 475, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9684}
{"question": "Solve (383 / 204)", "answer": "The result of (383 / 204) is 1.8775\n\n####1.8775", "a": 383, "b": 204, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8775}
{"question": "Solve (133 + 363)", "answer": "The result of (133 + 363) is 496\n\n####496", "a": 133, "b": 363, "operator": "+", "result": 496}
{"question": "Solve (79 * 451)", "answer": "The result of (79 * 451) is 35629\n\n####35629", "a": 79, "b": 451, "operator": "*", "result": 35629}
{"question": "Solve (76 * 388)", "answer": "The result of (76 * 388) is 29488\n\n####29488", "a": 76, "b": 388, "operator": "*", "result": 29488}
{"question": "Solve (885 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (885 - 647) is 238\n\n####238", "a": 885, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve (589 * 14)", "answer": "The result of (589 * 14) is 8246\n\n####8246", "a": 589, "b": 14, "operator": "*", "result": 8246}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 566)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 566) is 1012\n\n####1012", "a": 446, "b": 566, "operator": "+", "result": 1012}
{"question": "Solve (136 - 249)", "answer": "The result of (136 - 249) is -113\n\n####-113", "a": 136, "b": 249, "operator": "-", "result": -113}
{"question": "Solve (50 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (50 / 623) is 0.0803\n\n####0.0803", "a": 50, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0803}
{"question": "Solve (829 - 310)", "answer": "The result of (829 - 310) is 519\n\n####519", "a": 829, "b": 310, "operator": "-", "result": 519}
{"question": "Solve (585 * 44)", "answer": "The result of (585 * 44) is 25740\n\n####25740", "a": 585, "b": 44, "operator": "*", "result": 25740}
{"question": "Solve (693 / 875)", "answer": "The result of (693 / 875) is 0.792\n\n####0.792", "a": 693, "b": 875, "operator": "/", "result": 0.792}
{"question": "Solve (412 - 907)", "answer": "The result of (412 - 907) is -495\n\n####-495", "a": 412, "b": 907, "operator": "-", "result": -495}
{"question": "Solve (549 + 941)", "answer": "The result of (549 + 941) is 1490\n\n####1490", "a": 549, "b": 941, "operator": "+", "result": 1490}
{"question": "Solve (886 / 431)", "answer": "The result of (886 / 431) is 2.0557\n\n####2.0557", "a": 886, "b": 431, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0557}
{"question": "Solve (607 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (607 / 821) is 0.7393\n\n####0.7393", "a": 607, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7393}
{"question": "Solve (88 - 285)", "answer": "The result of (88 - 285) is -197\n\n####-197", "a": 88, "b": 285, "operator": "-", "result": -197}
{"question": "Solve (478 + 397)", "answer": "The result of (478 + 397) is 875\n\n####875", "a": 478, "b": 397, "operator": "+", "result": 875}
{"question": "Solve (751 / 181)", "answer": "The result of (751 / 181) is 4.1492\n\n####4.1492", "a": 751, "b": 181, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1492}
{"question": "Solve (892 + 357)", "answer": "The result of (892 + 357) is 1249\n\n####1249", "a": 892, "b": 357, "operator": "+", "result": 1249}
{"question": "Solve (188 - 771)", "answer": "The result of (188 - 771) is -583\n\n####-583", "a": 188, "b": 771, "operator": "-", "result": -583}
{"question": "Solve (514 / 818)", "answer": "The result of (514 / 818) is 0.6284\n\n####0.6284", "a": 514, "b": 818, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6284}
{"question": "Solve (915 + 594)", "answer": "The result of (915 + 594) is 1509\n\n####1509", "a": 915, "b": 594, "operator": "+", "result": 1509}
{"question": "Solve (689 - 608)", "answer": "The result of (689 - 608) is 81\n\n####81", "a": 689, "b": 608, "operator": "-", "result": 81}
{"question": "Solve (502 - 973)", "answer": "The result of (502 - 973) is -471\n\n####-471", "a": 502, "b": 973, "operator": "-", "result": -471}
{"question": "Solve (743 / 571)", "answer": "The result of (743 / 571) is 1.3012\n\n####1.3012", "a": 743, "b": 571, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3012}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 208)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 208) is 89\n\n####89", "a": 297, "b": 208, "operator": "-", "result": 89}
{"question": "Solve (110 / 750)", "answer": "The result of (110 / 750) is 0.1467\n\n####0.1467", "a": 110, "b": 750, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1467}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 361)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 361) is -162\n\n####-162", "a": 199, "b": 361, "operator": "-", "result": -162}
{"question": "Solve (50 / 423)", "answer": "The result of (50 / 423) is 0.1182\n\n####0.1182", "a": 50, "b": 423, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1182}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 54)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 54) is 2.5\n\n####2.5", "a": 135, "b": 54, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5}
{"question": "Solve (66 - 128)", "answer": "The result of (66 - 128) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 66, "b": 128, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (726 * 716)", "answer": "The result of (726 * 716) is 519816\n\n####519816", "a": 726, "b": 716, "operator": "*", "result": 519816}
{"question": "Solve (941 + 682)", "answer": "The result of (941 + 682) is 1623\n\n####1623", "a": 941, "b": 682, "operator": "+", "result": 1623}
{"question": "Solve (375 * 200)", "answer": "The result of (375 * 200) is 75000\n\n####75000", "a": 375, "b": 200, "operator": "*", "result": 75000}
{"question": "Solve (891 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (891 - 609) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 891, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (293 + 614)", "answer": "The result of (293 + 614) is 907\n\n####907", "a": 293, "b": 614, "operator": "+", "result": 907}
{"question": "Solve (689 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (689 - 45) is 644\n\n####644", "a": 689, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 644}
{"question": "Solve (35 + 75)", "answer": "The result of (35 + 75) is 110\n\n####110", "a": 35, "b": 75, "operator": "+", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 927) is -903\n\n####-903", "a": 24, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -903}
{"question": "Solve (754 / 160)", "answer": "The result of (754 / 160) is 4.7125\n\n####4.7125", "a": 754, "b": 160, "operator": "/", "result": 4.7125}
{"question": "Solve (841 - 391)", "answer": "The result of (841 - 391) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 841, "b": 391, "operator": "-", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (49 * 420)", "answer": "The result of (49 * 420) is 20580\n\n####20580", "a": 49, "b": 420, "operator": "*", "result": 20580}
{"question": "Solve (467 / 285)", "answer": "The result of (467 / 285) is 1.6386\n\n####1.6386", "a": 467, "b": 285, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6386}
{"question": "Solve (857 - 835)", "answer": "The result of (857 - 835) is 22\n\n####22", "a": 857, "b": 835, "operator": "-", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve (196 - 762)", "answer": "The result of (196 - 762) is -566\n\n####-566", "a": 196, "b": 762, "operator": "-", "result": -566}
{"question": "Solve (437 * 942)", "answer": "The result of (437 * 942) is 411654\n\n####411654", "a": 437, "b": 942, "operator": "*", "result": 411654}
{"question": "Solve (147 * 855)", "answer": "The result of (147 * 855) is 125685\n\n####125685", "a": 147, "b": 855, "operator": "*", "result": 125685}
{"question": "Solve (301 + 483)", "answer": "The result of (301 + 483) is 784\n\n####784", "a": 301, "b": 483, "operator": "+", "result": 784}
{"question": "Solve (207 - 141)", "answer": "The result of (207 - 141) is 66\n\n####66", "a": 207, "b": 141, "operator": "-", "result": 66}
{"question": "Solve (723 - 216)", "answer": "The result of (723 - 216) is 507\n\n####507", "a": 723, "b": 216, "operator": "-", "result": 507}
{"question": "Solve (404 - 165)", "answer": "The result of (404 - 165) is 239\n\n####239", "a": 404, "b": 165, "operator": "-", "result": 239}
{"question": "Solve (698 - 899)", "answer": "The result of (698 - 899) is -201\n\n####-201", "a": 698, "b": 899, "operator": "-", "result": -201}
{"question": "Solve (899 / 455)", "answer": "The result of (899 / 455) is 1.9758\n\n####1.9758", "a": 899, "b": 455, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9758}
{"question": "Solve (3 / 90)", "answer": "The result of (3 / 90) is 0.0333\n\n####0.0333", "a": 3, "b": 90, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0333}
{"question": "Solve (446 - 792)", "answer": "The result of (446 - 792) is -346\n\n####-346", "a": 446, "b": 792, "operator": "-", "result": -346}
{"question": "Solve (495 / 210)", "answer": "The result of (495 / 210) is 2.3571\n\n####2.3571", "a": 495, "b": 210, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3571}
{"question": "Solve (633 * 565)", "answer": "The result of (633 * 565) is 357645\n\n####357645", "a": 633, "b": 565, "operator": "*", "result": 357645}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 223)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 223) is 130678\n\n####130678", "a": 586, "b": 223, "operator": "*", "result": 130678}
{"question": "Solve (76 - 270)", "answer": "The result of (76 - 270) is -194\n\n####-194", "a": 76, "b": 270, "operator": "-", "result": -194}
{"question": "Solve (188 * 923)", "answer": "The result of (188 * 923) is 173524\n\n####173524", "a": 188, "b": 923, "operator": "*", "result": 173524}
{"question": "Solve (259 / 790)", "answer": "The result of (259 / 790) is 0.3278\n\n####0.3278", "a": 259, "b": 790, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3278}
{"question": "Solve (249 / 724)", "answer": "The result of (249 / 724) is 0.3439\n\n####0.3439", "a": 249, "b": 724, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3439}
{"question": "Solve (167 / 218)", "answer": "The result of (167 / 218) is 0.7661\n\n####0.7661", "a": 167, "b": 218, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7661}
{"question": "Solve (446 + 72)", "answer": "The result of (446 + 72) is 518\n\n####518", "a": 446, "b": 72, "operator": "+", "result": 518}
{"question": "Solve (816 - 871)", "answer": "The result of (816 - 871) is -55\n\n####-55", "a": 816, "b": 871, "operator": "-", "result": -55}
{"question": "Solve (56 - 363)", "answer": "The result of (56 - 363) is -307\n\n####-307", "a": 56, "b": 363, "operator": "-", "result": -307}
{"question": "Solve (838 / 981)", "answer": "The result of (838 / 981) is 0.8542\n\n####0.8542", "a": 838, "b": 981, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8542}
{"question": "Solve (641 / 760)", "answer": "The result of (641 / 760) is 0.8434\n\n####0.8434", "a": 641, "b": 760, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8434}
{"question": "Solve (362 * 311)", "answer": "The result of (362 * 311) is 112582\n\n####112582", "a": 362, "b": 311, "operator": "*", "result": 112582}
{"question": "Solve (803 + 592)", "answer": "The result of (803 + 592) is 1395\n\n####1395", "a": 803, "b": 592, "operator": "+", "result": 1395}
{"question": "Solve (27 + 238)", "answer": "The result of (27 + 238) is 265\n\n####265", "a": 27, "b": 238, "operator": "+", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve (127 + 535)", "answer": "The result of (127 + 535) is 662\n\n####662", "a": 127, "b": 535, "operator": "+", "result": 662}
{"question": "Solve (250 / 808)", "answer": "The result of (250 / 808) is 0.3094\n\n####0.3094", "a": 250, "b": 808, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3094}
{"question": "Solve (562 - 606)", "answer": "The result of (562 - 606) is -44\n\n####-44", "a": 562, "b": 606, "operator": "-", "result": -44}
{"question": "Solve (950 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (950 - 290) is 660\n\n####660", "a": 950, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 660}
{"question": "Solve (555 + 20)", "answer": "The result of (555 + 20) is 575\n\n####575", "a": 555, "b": 20, "operator": "+", "result": 575}
{"question": "Solve (632 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (632 - 661) is -29\n\n####-29", "a": 632, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -29}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 834)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 834) is 196824\n\n####196824", "a": 236, "b": 834, "operator": "*", "result": 196824}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 2) is 333\n\n####333", "a": 335, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 333}
{"question": "Solve (862 + 672)", "answer": "The result of (862 + 672) is 1534\n\n####1534", "a": 862, "b": 672, "operator": "+", "result": 1534}
{"question": "Solve (117 + 144)", "answer": "The result of (117 + 144) is 261\n\n####261", "a": 117, "b": 144, "operator": "+", "result": 261}
{"question": "Solve (341 + 176)", "answer": "The result of (341 + 176) is 517\n\n####517", "a": 341, "b": 176, "operator": "+", "result": 517}
{"question": "Solve (408 - 260)", "answer": "The result of (408 - 260) is 148\n\n####148", "a": 408, "b": 260, "operator": "-", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve (170 + 142)", "answer": "The result of (170 + 142) is 312\n\n####312", "a": 170, "b": 142, "operator": "+", "result": 312}
{"question": "Solve (481 / 576)", "answer": "The result of (481 / 576) is 0.8351\n\n####0.8351", "a": 481, "b": 576, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8351}
{"question": "Solve (51 - 886)", "answer": "The result of (51 - 886) is -835\n\n####-835", "a": 51, "b": 886, "operator": "-", "result": -835}
{"question": "Solve (98 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (98 - 210) is -112\n\n####-112", "a": 98, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": -112}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 302)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 302) is 0.4735\n\n####0.4735", "a": 143, "b": 302, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4735}
{"question": "Solve (197 * 664)", "answer": "The result of (197 * 664) is 130808\n\n####130808", "a": 197, "b": 664, "operator": "*", "result": 130808}
{"question": "Solve (658 + 739)", "answer": "The result of (658 + 739) is 1397\n\n####1397", "a": 658, "b": 739, "operator": "+", "result": 1397}
{"question": "Solve (352 - 316)", "answer": "The result of (352 - 316) is 36\n\n####36", "a": 352, "b": 316, "operator": "-", "result": 36}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 372)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 372) is -279\n\n####-279", "a": 93, "b": 372, "operator": "-", "result": -279}
{"question": "Solve (568 + 913)", "answer": "The result of (568 + 913) is 1481\n\n####1481", "a": 568, "b": 913, "operator": "+", "result": 1481}
{"question": "Solve (944 * 242)", "answer": "The result of (944 * 242) is 228448\n\n####228448", "a": 944, "b": 242, "operator": "*", "result": 228448}
{"question": "Solve (58 / 238)", "answer": "The result of (58 / 238) is 0.2437\n\n####0.2437", "a": 58, "b": 238, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2437}
{"question": "Solve (148 + 138)", "answer": "The result of (148 + 138) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 148, "b": 138, "operator": "+", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (363 - 339)", "answer": "The result of (363 - 339) is 24\n\n####24", "a": 363, "b": 339, "operator": "-", "result": 24}
{"question": "Solve (83 * 806)", "answer": "The result of (83 * 806) is 66898\n\n####66898", "a": 83, "b": 806, "operator": "*", "result": 66898}
{"question": "Solve (262 + 743)", "answer": "The result of (262 + 743) is 1005\n\n####1005", "a": 262, "b": 743, "operator": "+", "result": 1005}
{"question": "Solve (767 / 631)", "answer": "The result of (767 / 631) is 1.2155\n\n####1.2155", "a": 767, "b": 631, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2155}
{"question": "Solve (752 * 674)", "answer": "The result of (752 * 674) is 506848\n\n####506848", "a": 752, "b": 674, "operator": "*", "result": 506848}
{"question": "Solve (500 - 120)", "answer": "The result of (500 - 120) is 380\n\n####380", "a": 500, "b": 120, "operator": "-", "result": 380}
{"question": "Solve (560 + 303)", "answer": "The result of (560 + 303) is 863\n\n####863", "a": 560, "b": 303, "operator": "+", "result": 863}
{"question": "Solve (243 * 585)", "answer": "The result of (243 * 585) is 142155\n\n####142155", "a": 243, "b": 585, "operator": "*", "result": 142155}
{"question": "Solve (601 * 655)", "answer": "The result of (601 * 655) is 393655\n\n####393655", "a": 601, "b": 655, "operator": "*", "result": 393655}
{"question": "Solve (419 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (419 / 815) is 0.5141\n\n####0.5141", "a": 419, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5141}
{"question": "Solve (349 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (349 + 259) is 608\n\n####608", "a": 349, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 608}
{"question": "Solve (141 / 596)", "answer": "The result of (141 / 596) is 0.2366\n\n####0.2366", "a": 141, "b": 596, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2366}
{"question": "Solve (978 * 932)", "answer": "The result of (978 * 932) is 911496\n\n####911496", "a": 978, "b": 932, "operator": "*", "result": 911496}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 83)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 83) is 437\n\n####437", "a": 520, "b": 83, "operator": "-", "result": 437}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 80)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 80) is 506\n\n####506", "a": 586, "b": 80, "operator": "-", "result": 506}
{"question": "Solve (176 / 404)", "answer": "The result of (176 / 404) is 0.4356\n\n####0.4356", "a": 176, "b": 404, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4356}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 678)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 678) is 298\n\n####298", "a": 976, "b": 678, "operator": "-", "result": 298}
{"question": "Solve (429 * 437)", "answer": "The result of (429 * 437) is 187473\n\n####187473", "a": 429, "b": 437, "operator": "*", "result": 187473}
{"question": "Solve (822 * 618)", "answer": "The result of (822 * 618) is 507996\n\n####507996", "a": 822, "b": 618, "operator": "*", "result": 507996}
{"question": "Solve (341 * 353)", "answer": "The result of (341 * 353) is 120373\n\n####120373", "a": 341, "b": 353, "operator": "*", "result": 120373}
{"question": "Solve (660 + 530)", "answer": "The result of (660 + 530) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 660, "b": 530, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (959 * 757)", "answer": "The result of (959 * 757) is 725963\n\n####725963", "a": 959, "b": 757, "operator": "*", "result": 725963}
{"question": "Solve (551 * 31)", "answer": "The result of (551 * 31) is 17081\n\n####17081", "a": 551, "b": 31, "operator": "*", "result": 17081}
{"question": "Solve (79 - 889)", "answer": "The result of (79 - 889) is -810\n\n####-810", "a": 79, "b": 889, "operator": "-", "result": -810}
{"question": "Solve (269 * 539)", "answer": "The result of (269 * 539) is 144991\n\n####144991", "a": 269, "b": 539, "operator": "*", "result": 144991}
{"question": "Solve (80 - 489)", "answer": "The result of (80 - 489) is -409\n\n####-409", "a": 80, "b": 489, "operator": "-", "result": -409}
{"question": "Solve (476 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (476 - 261) is 215\n\n####215", "a": 476, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": 215}
{"question": "Solve (703 * 302)", "answer": "The result of (703 * 302) is 212306\n\n####212306", "a": 703, "b": 302, "operator": "*", "result": 212306}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 198)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 198) is 84\n\n####84", "a": 282, "b": 198, "operator": "-", "result": 84}
{"question": "Solve (905 * 800)", "answer": "The result of (905 * 800) is 724000\n\n####724000", "a": 905, "b": 800, "operator": "*", "result": 724000}
{"question": "Solve (915 * 789)", "answer": "The result of (915 * 789) is 721935\n\n####721935", "a": 915, "b": 789, "operator": "*", "result": 721935}
{"question": "Solve (951 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (951 * 780) is 741780\n\n####741780", "a": 951, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 741780}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 988)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 988) is -795\n\n####-795", "a": 193, "b": 988, "operator": "-", "result": -795}
{"question": "Solve (644 * 8)", "answer": "The result of (644 * 8) is 5152\n\n####5152", "a": 644, "b": 8, "operator": "*", "result": 5152}
{"question": "Solve (808 / 157)", "answer": "The result of (808 / 157) is 5.1465\n\n####5.1465", "a": 808, "b": 157, "operator": "/", "result": 5.1465}
{"question": "Solve (585 - 251)", "answer": "The result of (585 - 251) is 334\n\n####334", "a": 585, "b": 251, "operator": "-", "result": 334}
{"question": "Solve (686 + 676)", "answer": "The result of (686 + 676) is 1362\n\n####1362", "a": 686, "b": 676, "operator": "+", "result": 1362}
{"question": "Solve (122 + 197)", "answer": "The result of (122 + 197) is 319\n\n####319", "a": 122, "b": 197, "operator": "+", "result": 319}
{"question": "Solve (864 * 520)", "answer": "The result of (864 * 520) is 449280\n\n####449280", "a": 864, "b": 520, "operator": "*", "result": 449280}
{"question": "Solve (334 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (334 - 321) is 13\n\n####13", "a": 334, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": 13}
{"question": "Solve (95 * 960)", "answer": "The result of (95 * 960) is 91200\n\n####91200", "a": 95, "b": 960, "operator": "*", "result": 91200}
{"question": "Solve (317 / 608)", "answer": "The result of (317 / 608) is 0.5214\n\n####0.5214", "a": 317, "b": 608, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5214}
{"question": "Solve (443 / 257)", "answer": "The result of (443 / 257) is 1.7237\n\n####1.7237", "a": 443, "b": 257, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7237}
{"question": "Solve (219 + 75)", "answer": "The result of (219 + 75) is 294\n\n####294", "a": 219, "b": 75, "operator": "+", "result": 294}
{"question": "Solve (177 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (177 + 358) is 535\n\n####535", "a": 177, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 535}
{"question": "Solve (433 * 516)", "answer": "The result of (433 * 516) is 223428\n\n####223428", "a": 433, "b": 516, "operator": "*", "result": 223428}
{"question": "Solve (250 - 405)", "answer": "The result of (250 - 405) is -155\n\n####-155", "a": 250, "b": 405, "operator": "-", "result": -155}
{"question": "Solve (781 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (781 / 674) is 1.1588\n\n####1.1588", "a": 781, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1588}
{"question": "Solve (610 - 919)", "answer": "The result of (610 - 919) is -309\n\n####-309", "a": 610, "b": 919, "operator": "-", "result": -309}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 286)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 286) is 226\n\n####226", "a": 512, "b": 286, "operator": "-", "result": 226}
{"question": "Solve (187 / 380)", "answer": "The result of (187 / 380) is 0.4921\n\n####0.4921", "a": 187, "b": 380, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4921}
{"question": "Solve (806 / 308)", "answer": "The result of (806 / 308) is 2.6169\n\n####2.6169", "a": 806, "b": 308, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6169}
{"question": "Solve (807 * 34)", "answer": "The result of (807 * 34) is 27438\n\n####27438", "a": 807, "b": 34, "operator": "*", "result": 27438}
{"question": "Solve (279 / 341)", "answer": "The result of (279 / 341) is 0.8182\n\n####0.8182", "a": 279, "b": 341, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8182}
{"question": "Solve (553 - 103)", "answer": "The result of (553 - 103) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 553, "b": 103, "operator": "-", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (396 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (396 - 943) is -547\n\n####-547", "a": 396, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -547}
{"question": "Solve (10 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (10 / 674) is 0.0148\n\n####0.0148", "a": 10, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0148}
{"question": "Solve (961 - 566)", "answer": "The result of (961 - 566) is 395\n\n####395", "a": 961, "b": 566, "operator": "-", "result": 395}
{"question": "Solve (73 - 206)", "answer": "The result of (73 - 206) is -133\n\n####-133", "a": 73, "b": 206, "operator": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve (679 - 466)", "answer": "The result of (679 - 466) is 213\n\n####213", "a": 679, "b": 466, "operator": "-", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve (483 * 921)", "answer": "The result of (483 * 921) is 444843\n\n####444843", "a": 483, "b": 921, "operator": "*", "result": 444843}
{"question": "Solve (759 / 945)", "answer": "The result of (759 / 945) is 0.8032\n\n####0.8032", "a": 759, "b": 945, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8032}
{"question": "Solve (609 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (609 / 43) is 14.1628\n\n####14.1628", "a": 609, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 14.1628}
{"question": "Solve (95 + 234)", "answer": "The result of (95 + 234) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 95, "b": 234, "operator": "+", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (787 / 870)", "answer": "The result of (787 / 870) is 0.9046\n\n####0.9046", "a": 787, "b": 870, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9046}
{"question": "Solve (908 - 363)", "answer": "The result of (908 - 363) is 545\n\n####545", "a": 908, "b": 363, "operator": "-", "result": 545}
{"question": "Solve (854 * 161)", "answer": "The result of (854 * 161) is 137494\n\n####137494", "a": 854, "b": 161, "operator": "*", "result": 137494}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 541)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 541) is -348\n\n####-348", "a": 193, "b": 541, "operator": "-", "result": -348}
{"question": "Solve (660 / 702)", "answer": "The result of (660 / 702) is 0.9402\n\n####0.9402", "a": 660, "b": 702, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9402}
{"question": "Solve (240 * 779)", "answer": "The result of (240 * 779) is 186960\n\n####186960", "a": 240, "b": 779, "operator": "*", "result": 186960}
{"question": "Solve (122 * 454)", "answer": "The result of (122 * 454) is 55388\n\n####55388", "a": 122, "b": 454, "operator": "*", "result": 55388}
{"question": "Solve (670 * 162)", "answer": "The result of (670 * 162) is 108540\n\n####108540", "a": 670, "b": 162, "operator": "*", "result": 108540}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 407)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 407) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 204, "b": 407, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 342) is -143\n\n####-143", "a": 199, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": -143}
{"question": "Solve (672 - 560)", "answer": "The result of (672 - 560) is 112\n\n####112", "a": 672, "b": 560, "operator": "-", "result": 112}
{"question": "Solve (996 * 595)", "answer": "The result of (996 * 595) is 592620\n\n####592620", "a": 996, "b": 595, "operator": "*", "result": 592620}
{"question": "Solve (15 - 711)", "answer": "The result of (15 - 711) is -696\n\n####-696", "a": 15, "b": 711, "operator": "-", "result": -696}
{"question": "Solve (660 - 788)", "answer": "The result of (660 - 788) is -128\n\n####-128", "a": 660, "b": 788, "operator": "-", "result": -128}
{"question": "Solve (40 / 590)", "answer": "The result of (40 / 590) is 0.0678\n\n####0.0678", "a": 40, "b": 590, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0678}
{"question": "Solve (865 + 595)", "answer": "The result of (865 + 595) is 1460\n\n####1460", "a": 865, "b": 595, "operator": "+", "result": 1460}
{"question": "Solve (863 * 764)", "answer": "The result of (863 * 764) is 659332\n\n####659332", "a": 863, "b": 764, "operator": "*", "result": 659332}
{"question": "Solve (14 + 816)", "answer": "The result of (14 + 816) is 830\n\n####830", "a": 14, "b": 816, "operator": "+", "result": 830}
{"question": "Solve (62 - 578)", "answer": "The result of (62 - 578) is -516\n\n####-516", "a": 62, "b": 578, "operator": "-", "result": -516}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 274)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 274) is 108778\n\n####108778", "a": 397, "b": 274, "operator": "*", "result": 108778}
{"question": "Solve (143 - 215)", "answer": "The result of (143 - 215) is -72\n\n####-72", "a": 143, "b": 215, "operator": "-", "result": -72}
{"question": "Solve (217 / 91)", "answer": "The result of (217 / 91) is 2.3846\n\n####2.3846", "a": 217, "b": 91, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3846}
{"question": "Solve (789 * 489)", "answer": "The result of (789 * 489) is 385821\n\n####385821", "a": 789, "b": 489, "operator": "*", "result": 385821}
{"question": "Solve (375 - 341)", "answer": "The result of (375 - 341) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 375, "b": 341, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (709 / 730)", "answer": "The result of (709 / 730) is 0.9712\n\n####0.9712", "a": 709, "b": 730, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9712}
{"question": "Solve (856 + 685)", "answer": "The result of (856 + 685) is 1541\n\n####1541", "a": 856, "b": 685, "operator": "+", "result": 1541}
{"question": "Solve (369 / 584)", "answer": "The result of (369 / 584) is 0.6318\n\n####0.6318", "a": 369, "b": 584, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6318}
{"question": "Solve (323 + 51)", "answer": "The result of (323 + 51) is 374\n\n####374", "a": 323, "b": 51, "operator": "+", "result": 374}
{"question": "Solve (227 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (227 - 937) is -710\n\n####-710", "a": 227, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -710}
{"question": "Solve (367 / 731)", "answer": "The result of (367 / 731) is 0.5021\n\n####0.5021", "a": 367, "b": 731, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5021}
{"question": "Solve (883 / 458)", "answer": "The result of (883 / 458) is 1.9279\n\n####1.9279", "a": 883, "b": 458, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9279}
{"question": "Solve (909 - 12)", "answer": "The result of (909 - 12) is 897\n\n####897", "a": 909, "b": 12, "operator": "-", "result": 897}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 250)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 250) is 0.608\n\n####0.608", "a": 152, "b": 250, "operator": "/", "result": 0.608}
{"question": "Solve (51 * 718)", "answer": "The result of (51 * 718) is 36618\n\n####36618", "a": 51, "b": 718, "operator": "*", "result": 36618}
{"question": "Solve (536 / 789)", "answer": "The result of (536 / 789) is 0.6793\n\n####0.6793", "a": 536, "b": 789, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6793}
{"question": "Solve (991 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (991 - 609) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 991, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (31 + 304)", "answer": "The result of (31 + 304) is 335\n\n####335", "a": 31, "b": 304, "operator": "+", "result": 335}
{"question": "Solve (861 + 258)", "answer": "The result of (861 + 258) is 1119\n\n####1119", "a": 861, "b": 258, "operator": "+", "result": 1119}
{"question": "Solve (791 - 994)", "answer": "The result of (791 - 994) is -203\n\n####-203", "a": 791, "b": 994, "operator": "-", "result": -203}
{"question": "Solve (316 - 292)", "answer": "The result of (316 - 292) is 24\n\n####24", "a": 316, "b": 292, "operator": "-", "result": 24}
{"question": "Solve (31 + 98)", "answer": "The result of (31 + 98) is 129\n\n####129", "a": 31, "b": 98, "operator": "+", "result": 129}
{"question": "Solve (383 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (383 - 730) is -347\n\n####-347", "a": 383, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -347}
{"question": "Solve (391 / 735)", "answer": "The result of (391 / 735) is 0.532\n\n####0.532", "a": 391, "b": 735, "operator": "/", "result": 0.532}
{"question": "Solve (382 / 840)", "answer": "The result of (382 / 840) is 0.4548\n\n####0.4548", "a": 382, "b": 840, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4548}
{"question": "Solve (84 / 558)", "answer": "The result of (84 / 558) is 0.1505\n\n####0.1505", "a": 84, "b": 558, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1505}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 416)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 416) is 2.2115\n\n####2.2115", "a": 920, "b": 416, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2115}
{"question": "Solve (85 - 732)", "answer": "The result of (85 - 732) is -647\n\n####-647", "a": 85, "b": 732, "operator": "-", "result": -647}
{"question": "Solve (159 * 946)", "answer": "The result of (159 * 946) is 150414\n\n####150414", "a": 159, "b": 946, "operator": "*", "result": 150414}
{"question": "Solve (195 + 469)", "answer": "The result of (195 + 469) is 664\n\n####664", "a": 195, "b": 469, "operator": "+", "result": 664}
{"question": "Solve (338 - 906)", "answer": "The result of (338 - 906) is -568\n\n####-568", "a": 338, "b": 906, "operator": "-", "result": -568}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 290) is 2.9897\n\n####2.9897", "a": 867, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9897}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 996)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 996) is -566\n\n####-566", "a": 430, "b": 996, "operator": "-", "result": -566}
{"question": "Solve (541 + 713)", "answer": "The result of (541 + 713) is 1254\n\n####1254", "a": 541, "b": 713, "operator": "+", "result": 1254}
{"question": "Solve (604 * 238)", "answer": "The result of (604 * 238) is 143752\n\n####143752", "a": 604, "b": 238, "operator": "*", "result": 143752}
{"question": "Solve (746 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (746 - 354) is 392\n\n####392", "a": 746, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": 392}
{"question": "Solve (777 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (777 / 914) is 0.8501\n\n####0.8501", "a": 777, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8501}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 520) is -46\n\n####-46", "a": 474, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": -46}
{"question": "Solve (269 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (269 * 390) is 104910\n\n####104910", "a": 269, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 104910}
{"question": "Solve (703 * 535)", "answer": "The result of (703 * 535) is 376105\n\n####376105", "a": 703, "b": 535, "operator": "*", "result": 376105}
{"question": "Solve (849 + 505)", "answer": "The result of (849 + 505) is 1354\n\n####1354", "a": 849, "b": 505, "operator": "+", "result": 1354}
{"question": "Solve (271 / 823)", "answer": "The result of (271 / 823) is 0.3293\n\n####0.3293", "a": 271, "b": 823, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3293}
{"question": "Solve (334 / 942)", "answer": "The result of (334 / 942) is 0.3546\n\n####0.3546", "a": 334, "b": 942, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3546}
{"question": "Solve (591 / 786)", "answer": "The result of (591 / 786) is 0.7519\n\n####0.7519", "a": 591, "b": 786, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7519}
{"question": "Solve (814 * 37)", "answer": "The result of (814 * 37) is 30118\n\n####30118", "a": 814, "b": 37, "operator": "*", "result": 30118}
{"question": "Solve (477 + 898)", "answer": "The result of (477 + 898) is 1375\n\n####1375", "a": 477, "b": 898, "operator": "+", "result": 1375}
{"question": "Solve (497 - 397)", "answer": "The result of (497 - 397) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 497, "b": 397, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (506 / 889)", "answer": "The result of (506 / 889) is 0.5692\n\n####0.5692", "a": 506, "b": 889, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5692}
{"question": "Solve (261 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (261 / 504) is 0.5179\n\n####0.5179", "a": 261, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5179}
{"question": "Solve (237 - 897)", "answer": "The result of (237 - 897) is -660\n\n####-660", "a": 237, "b": 897, "operator": "-", "result": -660}
{"question": "Solve (222 - 122)", "answer": "The result of (222 - 122) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 222, "b": 122, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (848 * 927)", "answer": "The result of (848 * 927) is 786096\n\n####786096", "a": 848, "b": 927, "operator": "*", "result": 786096}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 249)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 249) is 618\n\n####618", "a": 867, "b": 249, "operator": "-", "result": 618}
{"question": "Solve (402 + 850)", "answer": "The result of (402 + 850) is 1252\n\n####1252", "a": 402, "b": 850, "operator": "+", "result": 1252}
{"question": "Solve (534 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (534 * 823) is 439482\n\n####439482", "a": 534, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 439482}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 203)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 203) is -6\n\n####-6", "a": 197, "b": 203, "operator": "-", "result": -6}
{"question": "Solve (32 * 86)", "answer": "The result of (32 * 86) is 2752\n\n####2752", "a": 32, "b": 86, "operator": "*", "result": 2752}
{"question": "Solve (732 * 659)", "answer": "The result of (732 * 659) is 482388\n\n####482388", "a": 732, "b": 659, "operator": "*", "result": 482388}
{"question": "Solve (418 + 440)", "answer": "The result of (418 + 440) is 858\n\n####858", "a": 418, "b": 440, "operator": "+", "result": 858}
{"question": "Solve (283 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (283 - 283) is 0\n\n####0", "a": 283, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": 0}
{"question": "Solve (744 - 392)", "answer": "The result of (744 - 392) is 352\n\n####352", "a": 744, "b": 392, "operator": "-", "result": 352}
{"question": "Solve (866 - 691)", "answer": "The result of (866 - 691) is 175\n\n####175", "a": 866, "b": 691, "operator": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve (851 - 504)", "answer": "The result of (851 - 504) is 347\n\n####347", "a": 851, "b": 504, "operator": "-", "result": 347}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 25)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 25) is 300\n\n####300", "a": 12, "b": 25, "operator": "*", "result": 300}
{"question": "Solve (597 * 105)", "answer": "The result of (597 * 105) is 62685\n\n####62685", "a": 597, "b": 105, "operator": "*", "result": 62685}
{"question": "Solve (760 + 13)", "answer": "The result of (760 + 13) is 773\n\n####773", "a": 760, "b": 13, "operator": "+", "result": 773}
{"question": "Solve (839 + 785)", "answer": "The result of (839 + 785) is 1624\n\n####1624", "a": 839, "b": 785, "operator": "+", "result": 1624}
{"question": "Solve (663 - 62)", "answer": "The result of (663 - 62) is 601\n\n####601", "a": 663, "b": 62, "operator": "-", "result": 601}
{"question": "Solve (214 + 426)", "answer": "The result of (214 + 426) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 214, "b": 426, "operator": "+", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (455 / 138)", "answer": "The result of (455 / 138) is 3.2971\n\n####3.2971", "a": 455, "b": 138, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2971}
{"question": "Solve (645 + 454)", "answer": "The result of (645 + 454) is 1099\n\n####1099", "a": 645, "b": 454, "operator": "+", "result": 1099}
{"question": "Solve (325 - 440)", "answer": "The result of (325 - 440) is -115\n\n####-115", "a": 325, "b": 440, "operator": "-", "result": -115}
{"question": "Solve (671 * 975)", "answer": "The result of (671 * 975) is 654225\n\n####654225", "a": 671, "b": 975, "operator": "*", "result": 654225}
{"question": "Solve (629 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (629 - 661) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 629, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (367 + 454)", "answer": "The result of (367 + 454) is 821\n\n####821", "a": 367, "b": 454, "operator": "+", "result": 821}
{"question": "Solve (881 / 274)", "answer": "The result of (881 / 274) is 3.2153\n\n####3.2153", "a": 881, "b": 274, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2153}
{"question": "Solve (783 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (783 - 876) is -93\n\n####-93", "a": 783, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -93}
{"question": "Solve (715 / 371)", "answer": "The result of (715 / 371) is 1.9272\n\n####1.9272", "a": 715, "b": 371, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9272}
{"question": "Solve (635 - 398)", "answer": "The result of (635 - 398) is 237\n\n####237", "a": 635, "b": 398, "operator": "-", "result": 237}
{"question": "Solve (396 - 64)", "answer": "The result of (396 - 64) is 332\n\n####332", "a": 396, "b": 64, "operator": "-", "result": 332}
{"question": "Solve (673 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (673 - 290) is 383\n\n####383", "a": 673, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 383}
{"question": "Solve (243 / 827)", "answer": "The result of (243 / 827) is 0.2938\n\n####0.2938", "a": 243, "b": 827, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2938}
{"question": "Solve (170 - 748)", "answer": "The result of (170 - 748) is -578\n\n####-578", "a": 170, "b": 748, "operator": "-", "result": -578}
{"question": "Solve (660 * 176)", "answer": "The result of (660 * 176) is 116160\n\n####116160", "a": 660, "b": 176, "operator": "*", "result": 116160}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 649)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 649) is -341\n\n####-341", "a": 308, "b": 649, "operator": "-", "result": -341}
{"question": "Solve (641 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (641 - 317) is 324\n\n####324", "a": 641, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 324}
{"question": "Solve (143 / 520)", "answer": "The result of (143 / 520) is 0.275\n\n####0.275", "a": 143, "b": 520, "operator": "/", "result": 0.275}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 725)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 725) is 0.7683\n\n####0.7683", "a": 557, "b": 725, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7683}
{"question": "Solve (761 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (761 + 245) is 1006\n\n####1006", "a": 761, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 1006}
{"question": "Solve (329 / 482)", "answer": "The result of (329 / 482) is 0.6826\n\n####0.6826", "a": 329, "b": 482, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6826}
{"question": "Solve (808 * 432)", "answer": "The result of (808 * 432) is 349056\n\n####349056", "a": 808, "b": 432, "operator": "*", "result": 349056}
{"question": "Solve (185 - 28)", "answer": "The result of (185 - 28) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 185, "b": 28, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (46 / 147)", "answer": "The result of (46 / 147) is 0.3129\n\n####0.3129", "a": 46, "b": 147, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3129}
{"question": "Solve (290 - 593)", "answer": "The result of (290 - 593) is -303\n\n####-303", "a": 290, "b": 593, "operator": "-", "result": -303}
{"question": "Solve (769 / 509)", "answer": "The result of (769 / 509) is 1.5108\n\n####1.5108", "a": 769, "b": 509, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5108}
{"question": "Solve (734 / 845)", "answer": "The result of (734 / 845) is 0.8686\n\n####0.8686", "a": 734, "b": 845, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8686}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 373)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 373) is -91\n\n####-91", "a": 282, "b": 373, "operator": "-", "result": -91}
{"question": "Solve (181 * 274)", "answer": "The result of (181 * 274) is 49594\n\n####49594", "a": 181, "b": 274, "operator": "*", "result": 49594}
{"question": "Solve (773 - 941)", "answer": "The result of (773 - 941) is -168\n\n####-168", "a": 773, "b": 941, "operator": "-", "result": -168}
{"question": "Solve (878 * 66)", "answer": "The result of (878 * 66) is 57948\n\n####57948", "a": 878, "b": 66, "operator": "*", "result": 57948}
{"question": "Solve (627 + 661)", "answer": "The result of (627 + 661) is 1288\n\n####1288", "a": 627, "b": 661, "operator": "+", "result": 1288}
{"question": "Solve (6 - 267)", "answer": "The result of (6 - 267) is -261\n\n####-261", "a": 6, "b": 267, "operator": "-", "result": -261}
{"question": "Solve (986 - 80)", "answer": "The result of (986 - 80) is 906\n\n####906", "a": 986, "b": 80, "operator": "-", "result": 906}
{"question": "Solve (440 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (440 - 700) is -260\n\n####-260", "a": 440, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -260}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 445) is 1.218\n\n####1.218", "a": 542, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 1.218}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 445) is 0.7303\n\n####0.7303", "a": 325, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7303}
{"question": "Solve (680 - 991)", "answer": "The result of (680 - 991) is -311\n\n####-311", "a": 680, "b": 991, "operator": "-", "result": -311}
{"question": "Solve (76 * 635)", "answer": "The result of (76 * 635) is 48260\n\n####48260", "a": 76, "b": 635, "operator": "*", "result": 48260}
{"question": "Solve (814 - 101)", "answer": "The result of (814 - 101) is 713\n\n####713", "a": 814, "b": 101, "operator": "-", "result": 713}
{"question": "Solve (314 / 514)", "answer": "The result of (314 / 514) is 0.6109\n\n####0.6109", "a": 314, "b": 514, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6109}
{"question": "Solve (549 - 107)", "answer": "The result of (549 - 107) is 442\n\n####442", "a": 549, "b": 107, "operator": "-", "result": 442}
{"question": "Solve (876 / 951)", "answer": "The result of (876 / 951) is 0.9211\n\n####0.9211", "a": 876, "b": 951, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9211}
{"question": "Solve (560 / 672)", "answer": "The result of (560 / 672) is 0.8333\n\n####0.8333", "a": 560, "b": 672, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8333}
{"question": "Solve (560 + 923)", "answer": "The result of (560 + 923) is 1483\n\n####1483", "a": 560, "b": 923, "operator": "+", "result": 1483}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 758)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 758) is -246\n\n####-246", "a": 512, "b": 758, "operator": "-", "result": -246}
{"question": "Solve (805 * 620)", "answer": "The result of (805 * 620) is 499100\n\n####499100", "a": 805, "b": 620, "operator": "*", "result": 499100}
{"question": "Solve (157 - 165)", "answer": "The result of (157 - 165) is -8\n\n####-8", "a": 157, "b": 165, "operator": "-", "result": -8}
{"question": "Solve (4 + 55)", "answer": "The result of (4 + 55) is 59\n\n####59", "a": 4, "b": 55, "operator": "+", "result": 59}
{"question": "Solve (313 + 69)", "answer": "The result of (313 + 69) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 313, "b": 69, "operator": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (857 * 561)", "answer": "The result of (857 * 561) is 480777\n\n####480777", "a": 857, "b": 561, "operator": "*", "result": 480777}
{"question": "Solve (42 - 948)", "answer": "The result of (42 - 948) is -906\n\n####-906", "a": 42, "b": 948, "operator": "-", "result": -906}
{"question": "Solve (61 / 682)", "answer": "The result of (61 / 682) is 0.0894\n\n####0.0894", "a": 61, "b": 682, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0894}
{"question": "Solve (417 * 924)", "answer": "The result of (417 * 924) is 385308\n\n####385308", "a": 417, "b": 924, "operator": "*", "result": 385308}
{"question": "Solve (805 - 989)", "answer": "The result of (805 - 989) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 805, "b": 989, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (429 - 66)", "answer": "The result of (429 - 66) is 363\n\n####363", "a": 429, "b": 66, "operator": "-", "result": 363}
{"question": "Solve (532 / 840)", "answer": "The result of (532 / 840) is 0.6333\n\n####0.6333", "a": 532, "b": 840, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6333}
{"question": "Solve (973 * 709)", "answer": "The result of (973 * 709) is 689857\n\n####689857", "a": 973, "b": 709, "operator": "*", "result": 689857}
{"question": "Solve (239 - 42)", "answer": "The result of (239 - 42) is 197\n\n####197", "a": 239, "b": 42, "operator": "-", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve (142 - 367)", "answer": "The result of (142 - 367) is -225\n\n####-225", "a": 142, "b": 367, "operator": "-", "result": -225}
{"question": "Solve (71 - 353)", "answer": "The result of (71 - 353) is -282\n\n####-282", "a": 71, "b": 353, "operator": "-", "result": -282}
{"question": "Solve (925 * 47)", "answer": "The result of (925 * 47) is 43475\n\n####43475", "a": 925, "b": 47, "operator": "*", "result": 43475}
{"question": "Solve (863 - 807)", "answer": "The result of (863 - 807) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 863, "b": 807, "operator": "-", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (20 / 825)", "answer": "The result of (20 / 825) is 0.0242\n\n####0.0242", "a": 20, "b": 825, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0242}
{"question": "Solve (215 / 444)", "answer": "The result of (215 / 444) is 0.4842\n\n####0.4842", "a": 215, "b": 444, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4842}
{"question": "Solve (592 - 558)", "answer": "The result of (592 - 558) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 592, "b": 558, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (284 * 960)", "answer": "The result of (284 * 960) is 272640\n\n####272640", "a": 284, "b": 960, "operator": "*", "result": 272640}
{"question": "Solve (571 / 594)", "answer": "The result of (571 / 594) is 0.9613\n\n####0.9613", "a": 571, "b": 594, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9613}
{"question": "Solve (230 * 350)", "answer": "The result of (230 * 350) is 80500\n\n####80500", "a": 230, "b": 350, "operator": "*", "result": 80500}
{"question": "Solve (313 / 103)", "answer": "The result of (313 / 103) is 3.0388\n\n####3.0388", "a": 313, "b": 103, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0388}
{"question": "Solve (314 * 115)", "answer": "The result of (314 * 115) is 36110\n\n####36110", "a": 314, "b": 115, "operator": "*", "result": 36110}
{"question": "Solve (941 / 449)", "answer": "The result of (941 / 449) is 2.0958\n\n####2.0958", "a": 941, "b": 449, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0958}
{"question": "Solve (499 - 562)", "answer": "The result of (499 - 562) is -63\n\n####-63", "a": 499, "b": 562, "operator": "-", "result": -63}
{"question": "Solve (781 - 666)", "answer": "The result of (781 - 666) is 115\n\n####115", "a": 781, "b": 666, "operator": "-", "result": 115}
{"question": "Solve (478 - 985)", "answer": "The result of (478 - 985) is -507\n\n####-507", "a": 478, "b": 985, "operator": "-", "result": -507}
{"question": "Solve (745 - 872)", "answer": "The result of (745 - 872) is -127\n\n####-127", "a": 745, "b": 872, "operator": "-", "result": -127}
{"question": "Solve (258 * 687)", "answer": "The result of (258 * 687) is 177246\n\n####177246", "a": 258, "b": 687, "operator": "*", "result": 177246}
{"question": "Solve (475 - 37)", "answer": "The result of (475 - 37) is 438\n\n####438", "a": 475, "b": 37, "operator": "-", "result": 438}
{"question": "Solve (681 / 232)", "answer": "The result of (681 / 232) is 2.9353\n\n####2.9353", "a": 681, "b": 232, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9353}
{"question": "Solve (199 + 57)", "answer": "The result of (199 + 57) is 256\n\n####256", "a": 199, "b": 57, "operator": "+", "result": 256}
{"question": "Solve (746 - 580)", "answer": "The result of (746 - 580) is 166\n\n####166", "a": 746, "b": 580, "operator": "-", "result": 166}
{"question": "Solve (447 * 686)", "answer": "The result of (447 * 686) is 306642\n\n####306642", "a": 447, "b": 686, "operator": "*", "result": 306642}
{"question": "Solve (840 - 20)", "answer": "The result of (840 - 20) is 820\n\n####820", "a": 840, "b": 20, "operator": "-", "result": 820}
{"question": "Solve (861 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (861 - 876) is -15\n\n####-15", "a": 861, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -15}
{"question": "Solve (839 * 940)", "answer": "The result of (839 * 940) is 788660\n\n####788660", "a": 839, "b": 940, "operator": "*", "result": 788660}
{"question": "Solve (91 * 15)", "answer": "The result of (91 * 15) is 1365\n\n####1365", "a": 91, "b": 15, "operator": "*", "result": 1365}
{"question": "Solve (204 * 615)", "answer": "The result of (204 * 615) is 125460\n\n####125460", "a": 204, "b": 615, "operator": "*", "result": 125460}
{"question": "Solve (717 + 58)", "answer": "The result of (717 + 58) is 775\n\n####775", "a": 717, "b": 58, "operator": "+", "result": 775}
{"question": "Solve (988 * 321)", "answer": "The result of (988 * 321) is 317148\n\n####317148", "a": 988, "b": 321, "operator": "*", "result": 317148}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 474)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 474) is 354\n\n####354", "a": 828, "b": 474, "operator": "-", "result": 354}
{"question": "Solve (423 + 629)", "answer": "The result of (423 + 629) is 1052\n\n####1052", "a": 423, "b": 629, "operator": "+", "result": 1052}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 758)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 758) is 733744\n\n####733744", "a": 968, "b": 758, "operator": "*", "result": 733744}
{"question": "Solve (72 * 465)", "answer": "The result of (72 * 465) is 33480\n\n####33480", "a": 72, "b": 465, "operator": "*", "result": 33480}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 267)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 267) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 923, "b": 267, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (659 / 821)", "answer": "The result of (659 / 821) is 0.8027\n\n####0.8027", "a": 659, "b": 821, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8027}
{"question": "Solve (394 * 6)", "answer": "The result of (394 * 6) is 2364\n\n####2364", "a": 394, "b": 6, "operator": "*", "result": 2364}
{"question": "Solve (286 + 582)", "answer": "The result of (286 + 582) is 868\n\n####868", "a": 286, "b": 582, "operator": "+", "result": 868}
{"question": "Solve (151 * 59)", "answer": "The result of (151 * 59) is 8909\n\n####8909", "a": 151, "b": 59, "operator": "*", "result": 8909}
{"question": "Solve (542 * 757)", "answer": "The result of (542 * 757) is 410294\n\n####410294", "a": 542, "b": 757, "operator": "*", "result": 410294}
{"question": "Solve (263 + 130)", "answer": "The result of (263 + 130) is 393\n\n####393", "a": 263, "b": 130, "operator": "+", "result": 393}
{"question": "Solve (486 + 887)", "answer": "The result of (486 + 887) is 1373\n\n####1373", "a": 486, "b": 887, "operator": "+", "result": 1373}
{"question": "Solve (499 * 977)", "answer": "The result of (499 * 977) is 487523\n\n####487523", "a": 499, "b": 977, "operator": "*", "result": 487523}
{"question": "Solve (447 - 110)", "answer": "The result of (447 - 110) is 337\n\n####337", "a": 447, "b": 110, "operator": "-", "result": 337}
{"question": "Solve (796 / 632)", "answer": "The result of (796 / 632) is 1.2595\n\n####1.2595", "a": 796, "b": 632, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2595}
{"question": "Solve (525 + 941)", "answer": "The result of (525 + 941) is 1466\n\n####1466", "a": 525, "b": 941, "operator": "+", "result": 1466}
{"question": "Solve (528 - 436)", "answer": "The result of (528 - 436) is 92\n\n####92", "a": 528, "b": 436, "operator": "-", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve (494 / 683)", "answer": "The result of (494 / 683) is 0.7233\n\n####0.7233", "a": 494, "b": 683, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7233}
{"question": "Solve (469 / 870)", "answer": "The result of (469 / 870) is 0.5391\n\n####0.5391", "a": 469, "b": 870, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5391}
{"question": "Solve (331 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (331 * 762) is 252222\n\n####252222", "a": 331, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 252222}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 435)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 435) is 57855\n\n####57855", "a": 133, "b": 435, "operator": "*", "result": 57855}
{"question": "Solve (667 + 56)", "answer": "The result of (667 + 56) is 723\n\n####723", "a": 667, "b": 56, "operator": "+", "result": 723}
{"question": "Solve (254 - 308)", "answer": "The result of (254 - 308) is -54\n\n####-54", "a": 254, "b": 308, "operator": "-", "result": -54}
{"question": "Solve (387 * 593)", "answer": "The result of (387 * 593) is 229491\n\n####229491", "a": 387, "b": 593, "operator": "*", "result": 229491}
{"question": "Solve (209 + 172)", "answer": "The result of (209 + 172) is 381\n\n####381", "a": 209, "b": 172, "operator": "+", "result": 381}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 751)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 751) is 582025\n\n####582025", "a": 775, "b": 751, "operator": "*", "result": 582025}
{"question": "Solve (945 + 33)", "answer": "The result of (945 + 33) is 978\n\n####978", "a": 945, "b": 33, "operator": "+", "result": 978}
{"question": "Solve (667 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (667 - 195) is 472\n\n####472", "a": 667, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": 472}
{"question": "Solve (570 / 381)", "answer": "The result of (570 / 381) is 1.4961\n\n####1.4961", "a": 570, "b": 381, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4961}
{"question": "Solve (659 * 832)", "answer": "The result of (659 * 832) is 548288\n\n####548288", "a": 659, "b": 832, "operator": "*", "result": 548288}
{"question": "Solve (561 * 848)", "answer": "The result of (561 * 848) is 475728\n\n####475728", "a": 561, "b": 848, "operator": "*", "result": 475728}
{"question": "Solve (790 - 562)", "answer": "The result of (790 - 562) is 228\n\n####228", "a": 790, "b": 562, "operator": "-", "result": 228}
{"question": "Solve (177 + 873)", "answer": "The result of (177 + 873) is 1050\n\n####1050", "a": 177, "b": 873, "operator": "+", "result": 1050}
{"question": "Solve (444 + 638)", "answer": "The result of (444 + 638) is 1082\n\n####1082", "a": 444, "b": 638, "operator": "+", "result": 1082}
{"question": "Solve (530 / 740)", "answer": "The result of (530 / 740) is 0.7162\n\n####0.7162", "a": 530, "b": 740, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7162}
{"question": "Solve (762 + 845)", "answer": "The result of (762 + 845) is 1607\n\n####1607", "a": 762, "b": 845, "operator": "+", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve (18 / 253)", "answer": "The result of (18 / 253) is 0.0711\n\n####0.0711", "a": 18, "b": 253, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0711}
{"question": "Solve (595 * 159)", "answer": "The result of (595 * 159) is 94605\n\n####94605", "a": 595, "b": 159, "operator": "*", "result": 94605}
{"question": "Solve (183 - 321)", "answer": "The result of (183 - 321) is -138\n\n####-138", "a": 183, "b": 321, "operator": "-", "result": -138}
{"question": "Solve (343 * 179)", "answer": "The result of (343 * 179) is 61397\n\n####61397", "a": 343, "b": 179, "operator": "*", "result": 61397}
{"question": "Solve (427 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (427 * 939) is 400953\n\n####400953", "a": 427, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 400953}
{"question": "Solve (99 - 692)", "answer": "The result of (99 - 692) is -593\n\n####-593", "a": 99, "b": 692, "operator": "-", "result": -593}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 752)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 752) is 0.9016\n\n####0.9016", "a": 678, "b": 752, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9016}
{"question": "Solve (761 + 443)", "answer": "The result of (761 + 443) is 1204\n\n####1204", "a": 761, "b": 443, "operator": "+", "result": 1204}
{"question": "Solve (304 - 118)", "answer": "The result of (304 - 118) is 186\n\n####186", "a": 304, "b": 118, "operator": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve (75 - 961)", "answer": "The result of (75 - 961) is -886\n\n####-886", "a": 75, "b": 961, "operator": "-", "result": -886}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 247)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 247) is 516\n\n####516", "a": 763, "b": 247, "operator": "-", "result": 516}
{"question": "Solve (327 / 281)", "answer": "The result of (327 / 281) is 1.1637\n\n####1.1637", "a": 327, "b": 281, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1637}
{"question": "Solve (928 + 443)", "answer": "The result of (928 + 443) is 1371\n\n####1371", "a": 928, "b": 443, "operator": "+", "result": 1371}
{"question": "Solve (560 / 850)", "answer": "The result of (560 / 850) is 0.6588\n\n####0.6588", "a": 560, "b": 850, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6588}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 296)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 296) is 2.3277\n\n####2.3277", "a": 689, "b": 296, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3277}
{"question": "Solve (225 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (225 - 342) is -117\n\n####-117", "a": 225, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": -117}
{"question": "Solve (216 / 73)", "answer": "The result of (216 / 73) is 2.9589\n\n####2.9589", "a": 216, "b": 73, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9589}
{"question": "Solve (870 - 272)", "answer": "The result of (870 - 272) is 598\n\n####598", "a": 870, "b": 272, "operator": "-", "result": 598}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 463)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 463) is 669\n\n####669", "a": 206, "b": 463, "operator": "+", "result": 669}
{"question": "Solve (40 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (40 / 206) is 0.1942\n\n####0.1942", "a": 40, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1942}
{"question": "Solve (645 - 49)", "answer": "The result of (645 - 49) is 596\n\n####596", "a": 645, "b": 49, "operator": "-", "result": 596}
{"question": "Solve (76 * 110)", "answer": "The result of (76 * 110) is 8360\n\n####8360", "a": 76, "b": 110, "operator": "*", "result": 8360}
{"question": "Solve (42 * 634)", "answer": "The result of (42 * 634) is 26628\n\n####26628", "a": 42, "b": 634, "operator": "*", "result": 26628}
{"question": "Solve (554 / 837)", "answer": "The result of (554 / 837) is 0.6619\n\n####0.6619", "a": 554, "b": 837, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6619}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 712)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 712) is 0.9522\n\n####0.9522", "a": 678, "b": 712, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9522}
{"question": "Solve (997 / 240)", "answer": "The result of (997 / 240) is 4.1542\n\n####4.1542", "a": 997, "b": 240, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1542}
{"question": "Solve (671 + 414)", "answer": "The result of (671 + 414) is 1085\n\n####1085", "a": 671, "b": 414, "operator": "+", "result": 1085}
{"question": "Solve (73 / 451)", "answer": "The result of (73 / 451) is 0.1619\n\n####0.1619", "a": 73, "b": 451, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1619}
{"question": "Solve (572 * 412)", "answer": "The result of (572 * 412) is 235664\n\n####235664", "a": 572, "b": 412, "operator": "*", "result": 235664}
{"question": "Solve (369 / 758)", "answer": "The result of (369 / 758) is 0.4868\n\n####0.4868", "a": 369, "b": 758, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4868}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 578)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 578) is 1.1903\n\n####1.1903", "a": 688, "b": 578, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1903}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 664)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 664) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 636, "b": 664, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (852 + 435)", "answer": "The result of (852 + 435) is 1287\n\n####1287", "a": 852, "b": 435, "operator": "+", "result": 1287}
{"question": "Solve (547 * 173)", "answer": "The result of (547 * 173) is 94631\n\n####94631", "a": 547, "b": 173, "operator": "*", "result": 94631}
{"question": "Solve (454 * 566)", "answer": "The result of (454 * 566) is 256964\n\n####256964", "a": 454, "b": 566, "operator": "*", "result": 256964}
{"question": "Solve (862 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (862 - 210) is 652\n\n####652", "a": 862, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": 652}
{"question": "Solve (473 * 664)", "answer": "The result of (473 * 664) is 314072\n\n####314072", "a": 473, "b": 664, "operator": "*", "result": 314072}
{"question": "Solve (339 - 87)", "answer": "The result of (339 - 87) is 252\n\n####252", "a": 339, "b": 87, "operator": "-", "result": 252}
{"question": "Solve (239 - 678)", "answer": "The result of (239 - 678) is -439\n\n####-439", "a": 239, "b": 678, "operator": "-", "result": -439}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 39)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 39) is 611\n\n####611", "a": 650, "b": 39, "operator": "-", "result": 611}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 204)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 204) is 0.7892\n\n####0.7892", "a": 161, "b": 204, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7892}
{"question": "Solve (274 / 168)", "answer": "The result of (274 / 168) is 1.631\n\n####1.631", "a": 274, "b": 168, "operator": "/", "result": 1.631}
{"question": "Solve (700 + 359)", "answer": "The result of (700 + 359) is 1059\n\n####1059", "a": 700, "b": 359, "operator": "+", "result": 1059}
{"question": "Solve (871 - 592)", "answer": "The result of (871 - 592) is 279\n\n####279", "a": 871, "b": 592, "operator": "-", "result": 279}
{"question": "Solve (606 * 528)", "answer": "The result of (606 * 528) is 319968\n\n####319968", "a": 606, "b": 528, "operator": "*", "result": 319968}
{"question": "Solve (825 - 518)", "answer": "The result of (825 - 518) is 307\n\n####307", "a": 825, "b": 518, "operator": "-", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve (1 + 892)", "answer": "The result of (1 + 892) is 893\n\n####893", "a": 1, "b": 892, "operator": "+", "result": 893}
{"question": "Solve (415 / 396)", "answer": "The result of (415 / 396) is 1.048\n\n####1.048", "a": 415, "b": 396, "operator": "/", "result": 1.048}
{"question": "Solve (132 * 632)", "answer": "The result of (132 * 632) is 83424\n\n####83424", "a": 132, "b": 632, "operator": "*", "result": 83424}
{"question": "Solve (810 * 537)", "answer": "The result of (810 * 537) is 434970\n\n####434970", "a": 810, "b": 537, "operator": "*", "result": 434970}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 862) is 534440\n\n####534440", "a": 620, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 534440}
{"question": "Solve (912 / 721)", "answer": "The result of (912 / 721) is 1.2649\n\n####1.2649", "a": 912, "b": 721, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2649}
{"question": "Solve (647 + 994)", "answer": "The result of (647 + 994) is 1641\n\n####1641", "a": 647, "b": 994, "operator": "+", "result": 1641}
{"question": "Solve (1 / 644)", "answer": "The result of (1 / 644) is 0.0016\n\n####0.0016", "a": 1, "b": 644, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0016}
{"question": "Solve (53 * 984)", "answer": "The result of (53 * 984) is 52152\n\n####52152", "a": 53, "b": 984, "operator": "*", "result": 52152}
{"question": "Solve (330 * 680)", "answer": "The result of (330 * 680) is 224400\n\n####224400", "a": 330, "b": 680, "operator": "*", "result": 224400}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 288)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 288) is 462\n\n####462", "a": 750, "b": 288, "operator": "-", "result": 462}
{"question": "Solve (57 + 301)", "answer": "The result of (57 + 301) is 358\n\n####358", "a": 57, "b": 301, "operator": "+", "result": 358}
{"question": "Solve (813 + 597)", "answer": "The result of (813 + 597) is 1410\n\n####1410", "a": 813, "b": 597, "operator": "+", "result": 1410}
{"question": "Solve (708 - 381)", "answer": "The result of (708 - 381) is 327\n\n####327", "a": 708, "b": 381, "operator": "-", "result": 327}
{"question": "Solve (592 * 566)", "answer": "The result of (592 * 566) is 335072\n\n####335072", "a": 592, "b": 566, "operator": "*", "result": 335072}
{"question": "Solve (449 + 585)", "answer": "The result of (449 + 585) is 1034\n\n####1034", "a": 449, "b": 585, "operator": "+", "result": 1034}
{"question": "Solve (70 / 519)", "answer": "The result of (70 / 519) is 0.1349\n\n####0.1349", "a": 70, "b": 519, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1349}
{"question": "Solve (829 - 879)", "answer": "The result of (829 - 879) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 829, "b": 879, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 1)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 1) is 511\n\n####511", "a": 512, "b": 1, "operator": "-", "result": 511}
{"question": "Solve (961 / 601)", "answer": "The result of (961 / 601) is 1.599\n\n####1.599", "a": 961, "b": 601, "operator": "/", "result": 1.599}
{"question": "Solve (153 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (153 * 897) is 137241\n\n####137241", "a": 153, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 137241}
{"question": "Solve (305 / 511)", "answer": "The result of (305 / 511) is 0.5969\n\n####0.5969", "a": 305, "b": 511, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5969}
{"question": "Solve (951 + 389)", "answer": "The result of (951 + 389) is 1340\n\n####1340", "a": 951, "b": 389, "operator": "+", "result": 1340}
{"question": "Solve (405 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (405 - 471) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 405, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (800 + 236)", "answer": "The result of (800 + 236) is 1036\n\n####1036", "a": 800, "b": 236, "operator": "+", "result": 1036}
{"question": "Solve (862 / 938)", "answer": "The result of (862 / 938) is 0.919\n\n####0.919", "a": 862, "b": 938, "operator": "/", "result": 0.919}
{"question": "Solve (364 / 211)", "answer": "The result of (364 / 211) is 1.7251\n\n####1.7251", "a": 364, "b": 211, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7251}
{"question": "Solve (14 + 301)", "answer": "The result of (14 + 301) is 315\n\n####315", "a": 14, "b": 301, "operator": "+", "result": 315}
{"question": "Solve (922 - 65)", "answer": "The result of (922 - 65) is 857\n\n####857", "a": 922, "b": 65, "operator": "-", "result": 857}
{"question": "Solve (582 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (582 * 884) is 514488\n\n####514488", "a": 582, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 514488}
{"question": "Solve (6 + 251)", "answer": "The result of (6 + 251) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 6, "b": 251, "operator": "+", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (317 / 612)", "answer": "The result of (317 / 612) is 0.518\n\n####0.518", "a": 317, "b": 612, "operator": "/", "result": 0.518}
{"question": "Solve (593 * 847)", "answer": "The result of (593 * 847) is 502271\n\n####502271", "a": 593, "b": 847, "operator": "*", "result": 502271}
{"question": "Solve (422 - 778)", "answer": "The result of (422 - 778) is -356\n\n####-356", "a": 422, "b": 778, "operator": "-", "result": -356}
{"question": "Solve (829 - 985)", "answer": "The result of (829 - 985) is -156\n\n####-156", "a": 829, "b": 985, "operator": "-", "result": -156}
{"question": "Solve (544 + 517)", "answer": "The result of (544 + 517) is 1061\n\n####1061", "a": 544, "b": 517, "operator": "+", "result": 1061}
{"question": "Solve (149 + 491)", "answer": "The result of (149 + 491) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 149, "b": 491, "operator": "+", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (343 + 297)", "answer": "The result of (343 + 297) is 640\n\n####640", "a": 343, "b": 297, "operator": "+", "result": 640}
{"question": "Solve (995 * 369)", "answer": "The result of (995 * 369) is 367155\n\n####367155", "a": 995, "b": 369, "operator": "*", "result": 367155}
{"question": "Solve (767 + 987)", "answer": "The result of (767 + 987) is 1754\n\n####1754", "a": 767, "b": 987, "operator": "+", "result": 1754}
{"question": "Solve (1 + 277)", "answer": "The result of (1 + 277) is 278\n\n####278", "a": 1, "b": 277, "operator": "+", "result": 278}
{"question": "Solve (728 - 465)", "answer": "The result of (728 - 465) is 263\n\n####263", "a": 728, "b": 465, "operator": "-", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve (782 / 608)", "answer": "The result of (782 / 608) is 1.2862\n\n####1.2862", "a": 782, "b": 608, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2862}
{"question": "Solve (656 * 604)", "answer": "The result of (656 * 604) is 396224\n\n####396224", "a": 656, "b": 604, "operator": "*", "result": 396224}
{"question": "Solve (740 - 338)", "answer": "The result of (740 - 338) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 740, "b": 338, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (985 + 319)", "answer": "The result of (985 + 319) is 1304\n\n####1304", "a": 985, "b": 319, "operator": "+", "result": 1304}
{"question": "Solve (23 + 875)", "answer": "The result of (23 + 875) is 898\n\n####898", "a": 23, "b": 875, "operator": "+", "result": 898}
{"question": "Solve (30 / 379)", "answer": "The result of (30 / 379) is 0.0792\n\n####0.0792", "a": 30, "b": 379, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0792}
{"question": "Solve (599 - 30)", "answer": "The result of (599 - 30) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 599, "b": 30, "operator": "-", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (43 - 562)", "answer": "The result of (43 - 562) is -519\n\n####-519", "a": 43, "b": 562, "operator": "-", "result": -519}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 397)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 397) is -364\n\n####-364", "a": 33, "b": 397, "operator": "-", "result": -364}
{"question": "Solve (992 * 739)", "answer": "The result of (992 * 739) is 733088\n\n####733088", "a": 992, "b": 739, "operator": "*", "result": 733088}
{"question": "Solve (775 - 555)", "answer": "The result of (775 - 555) is 220\n\n####220", "a": 775, "b": 555, "operator": "-", "result": 220}
{"question": "Solve (32 * 199)", "answer": "The result of (32 * 199) is 6368\n\n####6368", "a": 32, "b": 199, "operator": "*", "result": 6368}
{"question": "Solve (419 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (419 - 777) is -358\n\n####-358", "a": 419, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -358}
{"question": "Solve (570 / 215)", "answer": "The result of (570 / 215) is 2.6512\n\n####2.6512", "a": 570, "b": 215, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6512}
{"question": "Solve (130 / 42)", "answer": "The result of (130 / 42) is 3.0952\n\n####3.0952", "a": 130, "b": 42, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0952}
{"question": "Solve (422 + 387)", "answer": "The result of (422 + 387) is 809\n\n####809", "a": 422, "b": 387, "operator": "+", "result": 809}
{"question": "Solve (171 / 552)", "answer": "The result of (171 / 552) is 0.3098\n\n####0.3098", "a": 171, "b": 552, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3098}
{"question": "Solve (79 - 838)", "answer": "The result of (79 - 838) is -759\n\n####-759", "a": 79, "b": 838, "operator": "-", "result": -759}
{"question": "Solve (192 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (192 - 184) is 8\n\n####8", "a": 192, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 8}
{"question": "Solve (325 / 654)", "answer": "The result of (325 / 654) is 0.4969\n\n####0.4969", "a": 325, "b": 654, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4969}
{"question": "Solve (297 + 721)", "answer": "The result of (297 + 721) is 1018\n\n####1018", "a": 297, "b": 721, "operator": "+", "result": 1018}
{"question": "Solve (449 - 274)", "answer": "The result of (449 - 274) is 175\n\n####175", "a": 449, "b": 274, "operator": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve (824 * 201)", "answer": "The result of (824 * 201) is 165624\n\n####165624", "a": 824, "b": 201, "operator": "*", "result": 165624}
{"question": "Solve (653 / 355)", "answer": "The result of (653 / 355) is 1.8394\n\n####1.8394", "a": 653, "b": 355, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8394}
{"question": "Solve (452 - 572)", "answer": "The result of (452 - 572) is -120\n\n####-120", "a": 452, "b": 572, "operator": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve (348 / 424)", "answer": "The result of (348 / 424) is 0.8208\n\n####0.8208", "a": 348, "b": 424, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8208}
{"question": "Solve (736 / 400)", "answer": "The result of (736 / 400) is 1.84\n\n####1.84", "a": 736, "b": 400, "operator": "/", "result": 1.84}
{"question": "Solve (434 - 697)", "answer": "The result of (434 - 697) is -263\n\n####-263", "a": 434, "b": 697, "operator": "-", "result": -263}
{"question": "Solve (644 - 714)", "answer": "The result of (644 - 714) is -70\n\n####-70", "a": 644, "b": 714, "operator": "-", "result": -70}
{"question": "Solve (338 - 383)", "answer": "The result of (338 - 383) is -45\n\n####-45", "a": 338, "b": 383, "operator": "-", "result": -45}
{"question": "Solve (671 * 720)", "answer": "The result of (671 * 720) is 483120\n\n####483120", "a": 671, "b": 720, "operator": "*", "result": 483120}
{"question": "Solve (267 * 559)", "answer": "The result of (267 * 559) is 149253\n\n####149253", "a": 267, "b": 559, "operator": "*", "result": 149253}
{"question": "Solve (202 / 126)", "answer": "The result of (202 / 126) is 1.6032\n\n####1.6032", "a": 202, "b": 126, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6032}
{"question": "Solve (568 / 427)", "answer": "The result of (568 / 427) is 1.3302\n\n####1.3302", "a": 568, "b": 427, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3302}
{"question": "Solve (713 * 882)", "answer": "The result of (713 * 882) is 628866\n\n####628866", "a": 713, "b": 882, "operator": "*", "result": 628866}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 507)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 507) is -430\n\n####-430", "a": 77, "b": 507, "operator": "-", "result": -430}
{"question": "Solve (506 / 357)", "answer": "The result of (506 / 357) is 1.4174\n\n####1.4174", "a": 506, "b": 357, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4174}
{"question": "Solve (664 - 612)", "answer": "The result of (664 - 612) is 52\n\n####52", "a": 664, "b": 612, "operator": "-", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve (138 / 150)", "answer": "The result of (138 / 150) is 0.92\n\n####0.92", "a": 138, "b": 150, "operator": "/", "result": 0.92}
{"question": "Solve (374 * 182)", "answer": "The result of (374 * 182) is 68068\n\n####68068", "a": 374, "b": 182, "operator": "*", "result": 68068}
{"question": "Solve (577 - 566)", "answer": "The result of (577 - 566) is 11\n\n####11", "a": 577, "b": 566, "operator": "-", "result": 11}
{"question": "Solve (998 - 429)", "answer": "The result of (998 - 429) is 569\n\n####569", "a": 998, "b": 429, "operator": "-", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve (880 + 97)", "answer": "The result of (880 + 97) is 977\n\n####977", "a": 880, "b": 97, "operator": "+", "result": 977}
{"question": "Solve (604 * 526)", "answer": "The result of (604 * 526) is 317704\n\n####317704", "a": 604, "b": 526, "operator": "*", "result": 317704}
{"question": "Solve (824 / 364)", "answer": "The result of (824 / 364) is 2.2637\n\n####2.2637", "a": 824, "b": 364, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2637}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 896)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 896) is 555520\n\n####555520", "a": 620, "b": 896, "operator": "*", "result": 555520}
{"question": "Solve (94 - 569)", "answer": "The result of (94 - 569) is -475\n\n####-475", "a": 94, "b": 569, "operator": "-", "result": -475}
{"question": "Solve (857 + 590)", "answer": "The result of (857 + 590) is 1447\n\n####1447", "a": 857, "b": 590, "operator": "+", "result": 1447}
{"question": "Solve (460 - 58)", "answer": "The result of (460 - 58) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 460, "b": 58, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (195 * 831)", "answer": "The result of (195 * 831) is 162045\n\n####162045", "a": 195, "b": 831, "operator": "*", "result": 162045}
{"question": "Solve (69 / 351)", "answer": "The result of (69 / 351) is 0.1966\n\n####0.1966", "a": 69, "b": 351, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1966}
{"question": "Solve (552 * 535)", "answer": "The result of (552 * 535) is 295320\n\n####295320", "a": 552, "b": 535, "operator": "*", "result": 295320}
{"question": "Solve (725 - 445)", "answer": "The result of (725 - 445) is 280\n\n####280", "a": 725, "b": 445, "operator": "-", "result": 280}
{"question": "Solve (203 + 79)", "answer": "The result of (203 + 79) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 203, "b": 79, "operator": "+", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (267 - 355)", "answer": "The result of (267 - 355) is -88\n\n####-88", "a": 267, "b": 355, "operator": "-", "result": -88}
{"question": "Solve (485 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (485 / 623) is 0.7785\n\n####0.7785", "a": 485, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7785}
{"question": "Solve (890 + 338)", "answer": "The result of (890 + 338) is 1228\n\n####1228", "a": 890, "b": 338, "operator": "+", "result": 1228}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 863)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 863) is 0.0568\n\n####0.0568", "a": 49, "b": 863, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0568}
{"question": "Solve (723 * 719)", "answer": "The result of (723 * 719) is 519837\n\n####519837", "a": 723, "b": 719, "operator": "*", "result": 519837}
{"question": "Solve (780 * 197)", "answer": "The result of (780 * 197) is 153660\n\n####153660", "a": 780, "b": 197, "operator": "*", "result": 153660}
{"question": "Solve (769 + 710)", "answer": "The result of (769 + 710) is 1479\n\n####1479", "a": 769, "b": 710, "operator": "+", "result": 1479}
{"question": "Solve (824 - 741)", "answer": "The result of (824 - 741) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 824, "b": 741, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (713 * 807)", "answer": "The result of (713 * 807) is 575391\n\n####575391", "a": 713, "b": 807, "operator": "*", "result": 575391}
{"question": "Solve (257 / 2)", "answer": "The result of (257 / 2) is 128.5\n\n####128.5", "a": 257, "b": 2, "operator": "/", "result": 128.5}
{"question": "Solve (792 * 487)", "answer": "The result of (792 * 487) is 385704\n\n####385704", "a": 792, "b": 487, "operator": "*", "result": 385704}
{"question": "Solve (481 / 725)", "answer": "The result of (481 / 725) is 0.6634\n\n####0.6634", "a": 481, "b": 725, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6634}
{"question": "Solve (723 + 435)", "answer": "The result of (723 + 435) is 1158\n\n####1158", "a": 723, "b": 435, "operator": "+", "result": 1158}
{"question": "Solve (908 - 532)", "answer": "The result of (908 - 532) is 376\n\n####376", "a": 908, "b": 532, "operator": "-", "result": 376}
{"question": "Solve (619 * 62)", "answer": "The result of (619 * 62) is 38378\n\n####38378", "a": 619, "b": 62, "operator": "*", "result": 38378}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 308)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 308) is 300\n\n####300", "a": 608, "b": 308, "operator": "-", "result": 300}
{"question": "Solve (215 * 836)", "answer": "The result of (215 * 836) is 179740\n\n####179740", "a": 215, "b": 836, "operator": "*", "result": 179740}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 103)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 103) is 4.1165\n\n####4.1165", "a": 424, "b": 103, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1165}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 274)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 274) is 3.1642\n\n####3.1642", "a": 867, "b": 274, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1642}
{"question": "Solve (55 - 964)", "answer": "The result of (55 - 964) is -909\n\n####-909", "a": 55, "b": 964, "operator": "-", "result": -909}
{"question": "Solve (854 - 340)", "answer": "The result of (854 - 340) is 514\n\n####514", "a": 854, "b": 340, "operator": "-", "result": 514}
{"question": "Solve (628 / 882)", "answer": "The result of (628 / 882) is 0.712\n\n####0.712", "a": 628, "b": 882, "operator": "/", "result": 0.712}
{"question": "Solve (98 - 103)", "answer": "The result of (98 - 103) is -5\n\n####-5", "a": 98, "b": 103, "operator": "-", "result": -5}
{"question": "Solve (624 / 777)", "answer": "The result of (624 / 777) is 0.8031\n\n####0.8031", "a": 624, "b": 777, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8031}
{"question": "Solve (214 + 529)", "answer": "The result of (214 + 529) is 743\n\n####743", "a": 214, "b": 529, "operator": "+", "result": 743}
{"question": "Solve (872 * 985)", "answer": "The result of (872 * 985) is 858920\n\n####858920", "a": 872, "b": 985, "operator": "*", "result": 858920}
{"question": "Solve (168 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (168 / 686) is 0.2449\n\n####0.2449", "a": 168, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2449}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 153)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 153) is 5.2941\n\n####5.2941", "a": 810, "b": 153, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2941}
{"question": "Solve (278 + 322)", "answer": "The result of (278 + 322) is 600\n\n####600", "a": 278, "b": 322, "operator": "+", "result": 600}
{"question": "Solve (47 * 218)", "answer": "The result of (47 * 218) is 10246\n\n####10246", "a": 47, "b": 218, "operator": "*", "result": 10246}
{"question": "Solve (270 + 952)", "answer": "The result of (270 + 952) is 1222\n\n####1222", "a": 270, "b": 952, "operator": "+", "result": 1222}
{"question": "Solve (231 / 369)", "answer": "The result of (231 / 369) is 0.626\n\n####0.626", "a": 231, "b": 369, "operator": "/", "result": 0.626}
{"question": "Solve (23 + 392)", "answer": "The result of (23 + 392) is 415\n\n####415", "a": 23, "b": 392, "operator": "+", "result": 415}
{"question": "Solve (700 + 728)", "answer": "The result of (700 + 728) is 1428\n\n####1428", "a": 700, "b": 728, "operator": "+", "result": 1428}
{"question": "Solve (434 * 912)", "answer": "The result of (434 * 912) is 395808\n\n####395808", "a": 434, "b": 912, "operator": "*", "result": 395808}
{"question": "Solve (263 / 110)", "answer": "The result of (263 / 110) is 2.3909\n\n####2.3909", "a": 263, "b": 110, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3909}
{"question": "Solve (855 * 118)", "answer": "The result of (855 * 118) is 100890\n\n####100890", "a": 855, "b": 118, "operator": "*", "result": 100890}
{"question": "Solve (296 + 841)", "answer": "The result of (296 + 841) is 1137\n\n####1137", "a": 296, "b": 841, "operator": "+", "result": 1137}
{"question": "Solve (943 + 940)", "answer": "The result of (943 + 940) is 1883\n\n####1883", "a": 943, "b": 940, "operator": "+", "result": 1883}
{"question": "Solve (11 / 167)", "answer": "The result of (11 / 167) is 0.0659\n\n####0.0659", "a": 11, "b": 167, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0659}
{"question": "Solve (169 - 269)", "answer": "The result of (169 - 269) is -100\n\n####-100", "a": 169, "b": 269, "operator": "-", "result": -100}
{"question": "Solve (276 - 548)", "answer": "The result of (276 - 548) is -272\n\n####-272", "a": 276, "b": 548, "operator": "-", "result": -272}
{"question": "Solve (136 / 473)", "answer": "The result of (136 / 473) is 0.2875\n\n####0.2875", "a": 136, "b": 473, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2875}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 462)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 462) is 1.645\n\n####1.645", "a": 760, "b": 462, "operator": "/", "result": 1.645}
{"question": "Solve (801 * 377)", "answer": "The result of (801 * 377) is 301977\n\n####301977", "a": 801, "b": 377, "operator": "*", "result": 301977}
{"question": "Solve (636 + 679)", "answer": "The result of (636 + 679) is 1315\n\n####1315", "a": 636, "b": 679, "operator": "+", "result": 1315}
{"question": "Solve (320 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (320 - 604) is -284\n\n####-284", "a": 320, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -284}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 600)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 600) is 0.4867\n\n####0.4867", "a": 292, "b": 600, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4867}
{"question": "Solve (475 * 717)", "answer": "The result of (475 * 717) is 340575\n\n####340575", "a": 475, "b": 717, "operator": "*", "result": 340575}
{"question": "Solve (469 + 973)", "answer": "The result of (469 + 973) is 1442\n\n####1442", "a": 469, "b": 973, "operator": "+", "result": 1442}
{"question": "Solve (47 - 367)", "answer": "The result of (47 - 367) is -320\n\n####-320", "a": 47, "b": 367, "operator": "-", "result": -320}
{"question": "Solve (226 + 615)", "answer": "The result of (226 + 615) is 841\n\n####841", "a": 226, "b": 615, "operator": "+", "result": 841}
{"question": "Solve (979 * 324)", "answer": "The result of (979 * 324) is 317196\n\n####317196", "a": 979, "b": 324, "operator": "*", "result": 317196}
{"question": "Solve (58 / 125)", "answer": "The result of (58 / 125) is 0.464\n\n####0.464", "a": 58, "b": 125, "operator": "/", "result": 0.464}
{"question": "Solve (186 * 32)", "answer": "The result of (186 * 32) is 5952\n\n####5952", "a": 186, "b": 32, "operator": "*", "result": 5952}
{"question": "Solve (158 * 332)", "answer": "The result of (158 * 332) is 52456\n\n####52456", "a": 158, "b": 332, "operator": "*", "result": 52456}
{"question": "Solve (783 / 877)", "answer": "The result of (783 / 877) is 0.8928\n\n####0.8928", "a": 783, "b": 877, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8928}
{"question": "Solve (246 - 816)", "answer": "The result of (246 - 816) is -570\n\n####-570", "a": 246, "b": 816, "operator": "-", "result": -570}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 623)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 623) is 84105\n\n####84105", "a": 135, "b": 623, "operator": "*", "result": 84105}
{"question": "Solve (848 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (848 - 810) is 38\n\n####38", "a": 848, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": 38}
{"question": "Solve (298 + 337)", "answer": "The result of (298 + 337) is 635\n\n####635", "a": 298, "b": 337, "operator": "+", "result": 635}
{"question": "Solve (759 - 576)", "answer": "The result of (759 - 576) is 183\n\n####183", "a": 759, "b": 576, "operator": "-", "result": 183}
{"question": "Solve (205 + 984)", "answer": "The result of (205 + 984) is 1189\n\n####1189", "a": 205, "b": 984, "operator": "+", "result": 1189}
{"question": "Solve (725 / 896)", "answer": "The result of (725 / 896) is 0.8092\n\n####0.8092", "a": 725, "b": 896, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8092}
{"question": "Solve (416 + 358)", "answer": "The result of (416 + 358) is 774\n\n####774", "a": 416, "b": 358, "operator": "+", "result": 774}
{"question": "Solve (859 * 593)", "answer": "The result of (859 * 593) is 509387\n\n####509387", "a": 859, "b": 593, "operator": "*", "result": 509387}
{"question": "Solve (330 * 478)", "answer": "The result of (330 * 478) is 157740\n\n####157740", "a": 330, "b": 478, "operator": "*", "result": 157740}
{"question": "Solve (103 / 489)", "answer": "The result of (103 / 489) is 0.2106\n\n####0.2106", "a": 103, "b": 489, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2106}
{"question": "Solve (87 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (87 * 215) is 18705\n\n####18705", "a": 87, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 18705}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 408)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 408) is 2.0784\n\n####2.0784", "a": 848, "b": 408, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0784}
{"question": "Solve (368 - 657)", "answer": "The result of (368 - 657) is -289\n\n####-289", "a": 368, "b": 657, "operator": "-", "result": -289}
{"question": "Solve (162 - 670)", "answer": "The result of (162 - 670) is -508\n\n####-508", "a": 162, "b": 670, "operator": "-", "result": -508}
{"question": "Solve (912 * 311)", "answer": "The result of (912 * 311) is 283632\n\n####283632", "a": 912, "b": 311, "operator": "*", "result": 283632}
{"question": "Solve (602 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (602 / 300) is 2.0067\n\n####2.0067", "a": 602, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0067}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 500) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 127, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (379 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (379 - 751) is -372\n\n####-372", "a": 379, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": -372}
{"question": "Solve (964 * 387)", "answer": "The result of (964 * 387) is 373068\n\n####373068", "a": 964, "b": 387, "operator": "*", "result": 373068}
{"question": "Solve (236 / 900)", "answer": "The result of (236 / 900) is 0.2622\n\n####0.2622", "a": 236, "b": 900, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2622}
{"question": "Solve (888 * 207)", "answer": "The result of (888 * 207) is 183816\n\n####183816", "a": 888, "b": 207, "operator": "*", "result": 183816}
{"question": "Solve (587 - 719)", "answer": "The result of (587 - 719) is -132\n\n####-132", "a": 587, "b": 719, "operator": "-", "result": -132}
{"question": "Solve (566 / 366)", "answer": "The result of (566 / 366) is 1.5464\n\n####1.5464", "a": 566, "b": 366, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5464}
{"question": "Solve (791 + 267)", "answer": "The result of (791 + 267) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 791, "b": 267, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (263 / 910)", "answer": "The result of (263 / 910) is 0.289\n\n####0.289", "a": 263, "b": 910, "operator": "/", "result": 0.289}
{"question": "Solve (267 + 450)", "answer": "The result of (267 + 450) is 717\n\n####717", "a": 267, "b": 450, "operator": "+", "result": 717}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 698)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 698) is 1666\n\n####1666", "a": 968, "b": 698, "operator": "+", "result": 1666}
{"question": "Solve (84 / 315)", "answer": "The result of (84 / 315) is 0.2667\n\n####0.2667", "a": 84, "b": 315, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2667}
{"question": "Solve (267 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (267 - 992) is -725\n\n####-725", "a": 267, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -725}
{"question": "Solve (884 / 35)", "answer": "The result of (884 / 35) is 25.2571\n\n####25.2571", "a": 884, "b": 35, "operator": "/", "result": 25.2571}
{"question": "Solve (130 + 228)", "answer": "The result of (130 + 228) is 358\n\n####358", "a": 130, "b": 228, "operator": "+", "result": 358}
{"question": "Solve (455 - 413)", "answer": "The result of (455 - 413) is 42\n\n####42", "a": 455, "b": 413, "operator": "-", "result": 42}
{"question": "Solve (544 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (544 - 250) is 294\n\n####294", "a": 544, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": 294}
{"question": "Solve (320 / 141)", "answer": "The result of (320 / 141) is 2.2695\n\n####2.2695", "a": 320, "b": 141, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2695}
{"question": "Solve (682 - 715)", "answer": "The result of (682 - 715) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 682, "b": 715, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (281 * 465)", "answer": "The result of (281 * 465) is 130665\n\n####130665", "a": 281, "b": 465, "operator": "*", "result": 130665}
{"question": "Solve (558 / 476)", "answer": "The result of (558 / 476) is 1.1723\n\n####1.1723", "a": 558, "b": 476, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1723}
{"question": "Solve (414 + 498)", "answer": "The result of (414 + 498) is 912\n\n####912", "a": 414, "b": 498, "operator": "+", "result": 912}
{"question": "Solve (176 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (176 - 195) is -19\n\n####-19", "a": 176, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve (863 + 328)", "answer": "The result of (863 + 328) is 1191\n\n####1191", "a": 863, "b": 328, "operator": "+", "result": 1191}
{"question": "Solve (676 / 526)", "answer": "The result of (676 / 526) is 1.2852\n\n####1.2852", "a": 676, "b": 526, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2852}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 734)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 734) is 1.2316\n\n####1.2316", "a": 904, "b": 734, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2316}
{"question": "Solve (180 * 789)", "answer": "The result of (180 * 789) is 142020\n\n####142020", "a": 180, "b": 789, "operator": "*", "result": 142020}
{"question": "Solve (605 - 963)", "answer": "The result of (605 - 963) is -358\n\n####-358", "a": 605, "b": 963, "operator": "-", "result": -358}
{"question": "Solve (254 * 676)", "answer": "The result of (254 * 676) is 171704\n\n####171704", "a": 254, "b": 676, "operator": "*", "result": 171704}
{"question": "Solve (874 + 183)", "answer": "The result of (874 + 183) is 1057\n\n####1057", "a": 874, "b": 183, "operator": "+", "result": 1057}
{"question": "Solve (337 * 863)", "answer": "The result of (337 * 863) is 290831\n\n####290831", "a": 337, "b": 863, "operator": "*", "result": 290831}
{"question": "Solve (946 + 999)", "answer": "The result of (946 + 999) is 1945\n\n####1945", "a": 946, "b": 999, "operator": "+", "result": 1945}
{"question": "Solve (316 / 539)", "answer": "The result of (316 / 539) is 0.5863\n\n####0.5863", "a": 316, "b": 539, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5863}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 220)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 220) is 1.4136\n\n####1.4136", "a": 311, "b": 220, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4136}
{"question": "Solve (225 + 923)", "answer": "The result of (225 + 923) is 1148\n\n####1148", "a": 225, "b": 923, "operator": "+", "result": 1148}
{"question": "Solve (248 - 115)", "answer": "The result of (248 - 115) is 133\n\n####133", "a": 248, "b": 115, "operator": "-", "result": 133}
{"question": "Solve (457 / 161)", "answer": "The result of (457 / 161) is 2.8385\n\n####2.8385", "a": 457, "b": 161, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8385}
{"question": "Solve (558 - 110)", "answer": "The result of (558 - 110) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 558, "b": 110, "operator": "-", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (498 + 627)", "answer": "The result of (498 + 627) is 1125\n\n####1125", "a": 498, "b": 627, "operator": "+", "result": 1125}
{"question": "Solve (923 - 956)", "answer": "The result of (923 - 956) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 923, "b": 956, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (804 * 143)", "answer": "The result of (804 * 143) is 114972\n\n####114972", "a": 804, "b": 143, "operator": "*", "result": 114972}
{"question": "Solve (302 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (302 / 276) is 1.0942\n\n####1.0942", "a": 302, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0942}
{"question": "Solve (794 - 883)", "answer": "The result of (794 - 883) is -89\n\n####-89", "a": 794, "b": 883, "operator": "-", "result": -89}
{"question": "Solve (985 / 253)", "answer": "The result of (985 / 253) is 3.8933\n\n####3.8933", "a": 985, "b": 253, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8933}
{"question": "Solve (857 + 972)", "answer": "The result of (857 + 972) is 1829\n\n####1829", "a": 857, "b": 972, "operator": "+", "result": 1829}
{"question": "Solve (48 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (48 - 195) is -147\n\n####-147", "a": 48, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": -147}
{"question": "Solve (803 + 311)", "answer": "The result of (803 + 311) is 1114\n\n####1114", "a": 803, "b": 311, "operator": "+", "result": 1114}
{"question": "Solve (572 * 947)", "answer": "The result of (572 * 947) is 541684\n\n####541684", "a": 572, "b": 947, "operator": "*", "result": 541684}
{"question": "Solve (608 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (608 - 238) is 370\n\n####370", "a": 608, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 370}
{"question": "Solve (400 / 363)", "answer": "The result of (400 / 363) is 1.1019\n\n####1.1019", "a": 400, "b": 363, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1019}
{"question": "Solve (281 - 184)", "answer": "The result of (281 - 184) is 97\n\n####97", "a": 281, "b": 184, "operator": "-", "result": 97}
{"question": "Solve (842 / 104)", "answer": "The result of (842 / 104) is 8.0962\n\n####8.0962", "a": 842, "b": 104, "operator": "/", "result": 8.0962}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 198)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 198) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 598, "b": 198, "operator": "-", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 65)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 65) is 62920\n\n####62920", "a": 968, "b": 65, "operator": "*", "result": 62920}
{"question": "Solve (658 / 498)", "answer": "The result of (658 / 498) is 1.3213\n\n####1.3213", "a": 658, "b": 498, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3213}
{"question": "Solve (400 * 785)", "answer": "The result of (400 * 785) is 314000\n\n####314000", "a": 400, "b": 785, "operator": "*", "result": 314000}
{"question": "Solve (940 * 611)", "answer": "The result of (940 * 611) is 574340\n\n####574340", "a": 940, "b": 611, "operator": "*", "result": 574340}
{"question": "Solve (698 / 753)", "answer": "The result of (698 / 753) is 0.927\n\n####0.927", "a": 698, "b": 753, "operator": "/", "result": 0.927}
{"question": "Solve (16 / 409)", "answer": "The result of (16 / 409) is 0.0391\n\n####0.0391", "a": 16, "b": 409, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0391}
{"question": "Solve (35 + 795)", "answer": "The result of (35 + 795) is 830\n\n####830", "a": 35, "b": 795, "operator": "+", "result": 830}
{"question": "Solve (904 - 302)", "answer": "The result of (904 - 302) is 602\n\n####602", "a": 904, "b": 302, "operator": "-", "result": 602}
{"question": "Solve (799 + 298)", "answer": "The result of (799 + 298) is 1097\n\n####1097", "a": 799, "b": 298, "operator": "+", "result": 1097}
{"question": "Solve (438 + 922)", "answer": "The result of (438 + 922) is 1360\n\n####1360", "a": 438, "b": 922, "operator": "+", "result": 1360}
{"question": "Solve (547 / 864)", "answer": "The result of (547 / 864) is 0.6331\n\n####0.6331", "a": 547, "b": 864, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6331}
{"question": "Solve (163 - 883)", "answer": "The result of (163 - 883) is -720\n\n####-720", "a": 163, "b": 883, "operator": "-", "result": -720}
{"question": "Solve (780 * 17)", "answer": "The result of (780 * 17) is 13260\n\n####13260", "a": 780, "b": 17, "operator": "*", "result": 13260}
{"question": "Solve (718 * 751)", "answer": "The result of (718 * 751) is 539218\n\n####539218", "a": 718, "b": 751, "operator": "*", "result": 539218}
{"question": "Solve (751 / 494)", "answer": "The result of (751 / 494) is 1.5202\n\n####1.5202", "a": 751, "b": 494, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5202}
{"question": "Solve (285 * 573)", "answer": "The result of (285 * 573) is 163305\n\n####163305", "a": 285, "b": 573, "operator": "*", "result": 163305}
{"question": "Solve (183 * 210)", "answer": "The result of (183 * 210) is 38430\n\n####38430", "a": 183, "b": 210, "operator": "*", "result": 38430}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 830)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 830) is 9960\n\n####9960", "a": 12, "b": 830, "operator": "*", "result": 9960}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 390)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 390) is 25740\n\n####25740", "a": 66, "b": 390, "operator": "*", "result": 25740}
{"question": "Solve (885 - 844)", "answer": "The result of (885 - 844) is 41\n\n####41", "a": 885, "b": 844, "operator": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve (670 / 955)", "answer": "The result of (670 / 955) is 0.7016\n\n####0.7016", "a": 670, "b": 955, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7016}
{"question": "Solve (27 * 868)", "answer": "The result of (27 * 868) is 23436\n\n####23436", "a": 27, "b": 868, "operator": "*", "result": 23436}
{"question": "Solve (140 / 349)", "answer": "The result of (140 / 349) is 0.4011\n\n####0.4011", "a": 140, "b": 349, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4011}
{"question": "Solve (558 - 227)", "answer": "The result of (558 - 227) is 331\n\n####331", "a": 558, "b": 227, "operator": "-", "result": 331}
{"question": "Solve (505 + 974)", "answer": "The result of (505 + 974) is 1479\n\n####1479", "a": 505, "b": 974, "operator": "+", "result": 1479}
{"question": "Solve (77 + 65)", "answer": "The result of (77 + 65) is 142\n\n####142", "a": 77, "b": 65, "operator": "+", "result": 142}
{"question": "Solve (404 + 957)", "answer": "The result of (404 + 957) is 1361\n\n####1361", "a": 404, "b": 957, "operator": "+", "result": 1361}
{"question": "Solve (206 + 986)", "answer": "The result of (206 + 986) is 1192\n\n####1192", "a": 206, "b": 986, "operator": "+", "result": 1192}
{"question": "Solve (901 * 981)", "answer": "The result of (901 * 981) is 883881\n\n####883881", "a": 901, "b": 981, "operator": "*", "result": 883881}
{"question": "Solve (65 - 183)", "answer": "The result of (65 - 183) is -118\n\n####-118", "a": 65, "b": 183, "operator": "-", "result": -118}
{"question": "Solve (757 * 187)", "answer": "The result of (757 * 187) is 141559\n\n####141559", "a": 757, "b": 187, "operator": "*", "result": 141559}
{"question": "Solve (258 * 327)", "answer": "The result of (258 * 327) is 84366\n\n####84366", "a": 258, "b": 327, "operator": "*", "result": 84366}
{"question": "Solve (180 + 283)", "answer": "The result of (180 + 283) is 463\n\n####463", "a": 180, "b": 283, "operator": "+", "result": 463}
{"question": "Solve (323 / 582)", "answer": "The result of (323 / 582) is 0.555\n\n####0.555", "a": 323, "b": 582, "operator": "/", "result": 0.555}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 971)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 971) is 0.4737\n\n####0.4737", "a": 460, "b": 971, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4737}
{"question": "Solve (557 + 426)", "answer": "The result of (557 + 426) is 983\n\n####983", "a": 557, "b": 426, "operator": "+", "result": 983}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 288)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 288) is -31\n\n####-31", "a": 257, "b": 288, "operator": "-", "result": -31}
{"question": "Solve (115 - 460)", "answer": "The result of (115 - 460) is -345\n\n####-345", "a": 115, "b": 460, "operator": "-", "result": -345}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 207)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 207) is 469\n\n####469", "a": 676, "b": 207, "operator": "-", "result": 469}
{"question": "Solve (269 - 717)", "answer": "The result of (269 - 717) is -448\n\n####-448", "a": 269, "b": 717, "operator": "-", "result": -448}
{"question": "Solve (634 - 232)", "answer": "The result of (634 - 232) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 634, "b": 232, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (141 / 970)", "answer": "The result of (141 / 970) is 0.1454\n\n####0.1454", "a": 141, "b": 970, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1454}
{"question": "Solve (632 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (632 * 944) is 596608\n\n####596608", "a": 632, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 596608}
{"question": "Solve (936 + 737)", "answer": "The result of (936 + 737) is 1673\n\n####1673", "a": 936, "b": 737, "operator": "+", "result": 1673}
{"question": "Solve (331 - 182)", "answer": "The result of (331 - 182) is 149\n\n####149", "a": 331, "b": 182, "operator": "-", "result": 149}
{"question": "Solve (276 - 907)", "answer": "The result of (276 - 907) is -631\n\n####-631", "a": 276, "b": 907, "operator": "-", "result": -631}
{"question": "Solve (497 - 423)", "answer": "The result of (497 - 423) is 74\n\n####74", "a": 497, "b": 423, "operator": "-", "result": 74}
{"question": "Solve (244 * 41)", "answer": "The result of (244 * 41) is 10004\n\n####10004", "a": 244, "b": 41, "operator": "*", "result": 10004}
{"question": "Solve (696 * 235)", "answer": "The result of (696 * 235) is 163560\n\n####163560", "a": 696, "b": 235, "operator": "*", "result": 163560}
{"question": "Solve (372 - 680)", "answer": "The result of (372 - 680) is -308\n\n####-308", "a": 372, "b": 680, "operator": "-", "result": -308}
{"question": "Solve (899 / 653)", "answer": "The result of (899 / 653) is 1.3767\n\n####1.3767", "a": 899, "b": 653, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3767}
{"question": "Solve (302 - 403)", "answer": "The result of (302 - 403) is -101\n\n####-101", "a": 302, "b": 403, "operator": "-", "result": -101}
{"question": "Solve (522 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (522 + 245) is 767\n\n####767", "a": 522, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 767}
{"question": "Solve (5 + 443)", "answer": "The result of (5 + 443) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 5, "b": 443, "operator": "+", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 550)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 550) is -97\n\n####-97", "a": 453, "b": 550, "operator": "-", "result": -97}
{"question": "Solve (379 / 166)", "answer": "The result of (379 / 166) is 2.2831\n\n####2.2831", "a": 379, "b": 166, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2831}
{"question": "Solve (670 + 430)", "answer": "The result of (670 + 430) is 1100\n\n####1100", "a": 670, "b": 430, "operator": "+", "result": 1100}
{"question": "Solve (914 * 879)", "answer": "The result of (914 * 879) is 803406\n\n####803406", "a": 914, "b": 879, "operator": "*", "result": 803406}
{"question": "Solve (681 * 469)", "answer": "The result of (681 * 469) is 319389\n\n####319389", "a": 681, "b": 469, "operator": "*", "result": 319389}
{"question": "Solve (932 + 248)", "answer": "The result of (932 + 248) is 1180\n\n####1180", "a": 932, "b": 248, "operator": "+", "result": 1180}
{"question": "Solve (99 * 678)", "answer": "The result of (99 * 678) is 67122\n\n####67122", "a": 99, "b": 678, "operator": "*", "result": 67122}
{"question": "Solve (105 + 953)", "answer": "The result of (105 + 953) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 105, "b": 953, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (943 * 533)", "answer": "The result of (943 * 533) is 502619\n\n####502619", "a": 943, "b": 533, "operator": "*", "result": 502619}
{"question": "Solve (643 - 748)", "answer": "The result of (643 - 748) is -105\n\n####-105", "a": 643, "b": 748, "operator": "-", "result": -105}
{"question": "Solve (513 + 519)", "answer": "The result of (513 + 519) is 1032\n\n####1032", "a": 513, "b": 519, "operator": "+", "result": 1032}
{"question": "Solve (857 + 331)", "answer": "The result of (857 + 331) is 1188\n\n####1188", "a": 857, "b": 331, "operator": "+", "result": 1188}
{"question": "Solve (883 - 111)", "answer": "The result of (883 - 111) is 772\n\n####772", "a": 883, "b": 111, "operator": "-", "result": 772}
{"question": "Solve (901 / 502)", "answer": "The result of (901 / 502) is 1.7948\n\n####1.7948", "a": 901, "b": 502, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7948}
{"question": "Solve (335 + 955)", "answer": "The result of (335 + 955) is 1290\n\n####1290", "a": 335, "b": 955, "operator": "+", "result": 1290}
{"question": "Solve (949 + 253)", "answer": "The result of (949 + 253) is 1202\n\n####1202", "a": 949, "b": 253, "operator": "+", "result": 1202}
{"question": "Solve (462 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (462 / 236) is 1.9576\n\n####1.9576", "a": 462, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9576}
{"question": "Solve (778 * 15)", "answer": "The result of (778 * 15) is 11670\n\n####11670", "a": 778, "b": 15, "operator": "*", "result": 11670}
{"question": "Solve (380 / 806)", "answer": "The result of (380 / 806) is 0.4715\n\n####0.4715", "a": 380, "b": 806, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4715}
{"question": "Solve (108 + 411)", "answer": "The result of (108 + 411) is 519\n\n####519", "a": 108, "b": 411, "operator": "+", "result": 519}
{"question": "Solve (600 / 523)", "answer": "The result of (600 / 523) is 1.1472\n\n####1.1472", "a": 600, "b": 523, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1472}
{"question": "Solve (188 - 918)", "answer": "The result of (188 - 918) is -730\n\n####-730", "a": 188, "b": 918, "operator": "-", "result": -730}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 411)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 411) is 519\n\n####519", "a": 930, "b": 411, "operator": "-", "result": 519}
{"question": "Solve (899 * 253)", "answer": "The result of (899 * 253) is 227447\n\n####227447", "a": 899, "b": 253, "operator": "*", "result": 227447}
{"question": "Solve (416 / 893)", "answer": "The result of (416 / 893) is 0.4658\n\n####0.4658", "a": 416, "b": 893, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4658}
{"question": "Solve (473 / 428)", "answer": "The result of (473 / 428) is 1.1051\n\n####1.1051", "a": 473, "b": 428, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1051}
{"question": "Solve (58 / 315)", "answer": "The result of (58 / 315) is 0.1841\n\n####0.1841", "a": 58, "b": 315, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1841}
{"question": "Solve (137 * 741)", "answer": "The result of (137 * 741) is 101517\n\n####101517", "a": 137, "b": 741, "operator": "*", "result": 101517}
{"question": "Solve (503 - 258)", "answer": "The result of (503 - 258) is 245\n\n####245", "a": 503, "b": 258, "operator": "-", "result": 245}
{"question": "Solve (72 * 426)", "answer": "The result of (72 * 426) is 30672\n\n####30672", "a": 72, "b": 426, "operator": "*", "result": 30672}
{"question": "Solve (877 / 248)", "answer": "The result of (877 / 248) is 3.5363\n\n####3.5363", "a": 877, "b": 248, "operator": "/", "result": 3.5363}
{"question": "Solve (446 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (446 - 943) is -497\n\n####-497", "a": 446, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -497}
{"question": "Solve (90 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (90 / 206) is 0.4369\n\n####0.4369", "a": 90, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4369}
{"question": "Solve (657 - 812)", "answer": "The result of (657 - 812) is -155\n\n####-155", "a": 657, "b": 812, "operator": "-", "result": -155}
{"question": "Solve (235 - 812)", "answer": "The result of (235 - 812) is -577\n\n####-577", "a": 235, "b": 812, "operator": "-", "result": -577}
{"question": "Solve (268 + 51)", "answer": "The result of (268 + 51) is 319\n\n####319", "a": 268, "b": 51, "operator": "+", "result": 319}
{"question": "Solve (857 - 574)", "answer": "The result of (857 - 574) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 857, "b": 574, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (160 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (160 * 548) is 87680\n\n####87680", "a": 160, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 87680}
{"question": "Solve (855 - 772)", "answer": "The result of (855 - 772) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 855, "b": 772, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (817 - 858)", "answer": "The result of (817 - 858) is -41\n\n####-41", "a": 817, "b": 858, "operator": "-", "result": -41}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 896)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 896) is 0.3002\n\n####0.3002", "a": 269, "b": 896, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3002}
{"question": "Solve (248 - 502)", "answer": "The result of (248 - 502) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 248, "b": 502, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (514 - 211)", "answer": "The result of (514 - 211) is 303\n\n####303", "a": 514, "b": 211, "operator": "-", "result": 303}
{"question": "Solve (100 * 98)", "answer": "The result of (100 * 98) is 9800\n\n####9800", "a": 100, "b": 98, "operator": "*", "result": 9800}
{"question": "Solve (43 + 976)", "answer": "The result of (43 + 976) is 1019\n\n####1019", "a": 43, "b": 976, "operator": "+", "result": 1019}
{"question": "Solve (337 - 943)", "answer": "The result of (337 - 943) is -606\n\n####-606", "a": 337, "b": 943, "operator": "-", "result": -606}
{"question": "Solve (113 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (113 - 937) is -824\n\n####-824", "a": 113, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -824}
{"question": "Solve (741 + 307)", "answer": "The result of (741 + 307) is 1048\n\n####1048", "a": 741, "b": 307, "operator": "+", "result": 1048}
{"question": "Solve (187 - 331)", "answer": "The result of (187 - 331) is -144\n\n####-144", "a": 187, "b": 331, "operator": "-", "result": -144}
{"question": "Solve (199 + 821)", "answer": "The result of (199 + 821) is 1020\n\n####1020", "a": 199, "b": 821, "operator": "+", "result": 1020}
{"question": "Solve (963 / 868)", "answer": "The result of (963 / 868) is 1.1094\n\n####1.1094", "a": 963, "b": 868, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1094}
{"question": "Solve (690 / 414)", "answer": "The result of (690 / 414) is 1.6667\n\n####1.6667", "a": 690, "b": 414, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6667}
{"question": "Solve (950 - 69)", "answer": "The result of (950 - 69) is 881\n\n####881", "a": 950, "b": 69, "operator": "-", "result": 881}
{"question": "Solve (370 / 883)", "answer": "The result of (370 / 883) is 0.419\n\n####0.419", "a": 370, "b": 883, "operator": "/", "result": 0.419}
{"question": "Solve (665 - 415)", "answer": "The result of (665 - 415) is 250\n\n####250", "a": 665, "b": 415, "operator": "-", "result": 250}
{"question": "Solve (847 / 70)", "answer": "The result of (847 / 70) is 12.1\n\n####12.1", "a": 847, "b": 70, "operator": "/", "result": 12.1}
{"question": "Solve (251 * 728)", "answer": "The result of (251 * 728) is 182728\n\n####182728", "a": 251, "b": 728, "operator": "*", "result": 182728}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 84)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 84) is 19824\n\n####19824", "a": 236, "b": 84, "operator": "*", "result": 19824}
{"question": "Solve (758 * 635)", "answer": "The result of (758 * 635) is 481330\n\n####481330", "a": 758, "b": 635, "operator": "*", "result": 481330}
{"question": "Solve (878 + 784)", "answer": "The result of (878 + 784) is 1662\n\n####1662", "a": 878, "b": 784, "operator": "+", "result": 1662}
{"question": "Solve (989 / 934)", "answer": "The result of (989 / 934) is 1.0589\n\n####1.0589", "a": 989, "b": 934, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0589}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 161)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 161) is 174\n\n####174", "a": 335, "b": 161, "operator": "-", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 104)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 104) is 1768\n\n####1768", "a": 17, "b": 104, "operator": "*", "result": 1768}
{"question": "Solve (473 * 644)", "answer": "The result of (473 * 644) is 304612\n\n####304612", "a": 473, "b": 644, "operator": "*", "result": 304612}
{"question": "Solve (527 - 561)", "answer": "The result of (527 - 561) is -34\n\n####-34", "a": 527, "b": 561, "operator": "-", "result": -34}
{"question": "Solve (303 - 268)", "answer": "The result of (303 - 268) is 35\n\n####35", "a": 303, "b": 268, "operator": "-", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve (212 * 241)", "answer": "The result of (212 * 241) is 51092\n\n####51092", "a": 212, "b": 241, "operator": "*", "result": 51092}
{"question": "Solve (312 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (312 * 485) is 151320\n\n####151320", "a": 312, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 151320}
{"question": "Solve (146 + 207)", "answer": "The result of (146 + 207) is 353\n\n####353", "a": 146, "b": 207, "operator": "+", "result": 353}
{"question": "Solve (936 * 2)", "answer": "The result of (936 * 2) is 1872\n\n####1872", "a": 936, "b": 2, "operator": "*", "result": 1872}
{"question": "Solve (893 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (893 / 390) is 2.2897\n\n####2.2897", "a": 893, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2897}
{"question": "Solve (792 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (792 * 485) is 384120\n\n####384120", "a": 792, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 384120}
{"question": "Solve (170 - 774)", "answer": "The result of (170 - 774) is -604\n\n####-604", "a": 170, "b": 774, "operator": "-", "result": -604}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 512)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 512) is -194\n\n####-194", "a": 318, "b": 512, "operator": "-", "result": -194}
{"question": "Solve (57 - 762)", "answer": "The result of (57 - 762) is -705\n\n####-705", "a": 57, "b": 762, "operator": "-", "result": -705}
{"question": "Solve (178 - 21)", "answer": "The result of (178 - 21) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 178, "b": 21, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 590)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 590) is -100\n\n####-100", "a": 490, "b": 590, "operator": "-", "result": -100}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 790)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 790) is -573\n\n####-573", "a": 217, "b": 790, "operator": "-", "result": -573}
{"question": "Solve (865 - 76)", "answer": "The result of (865 - 76) is 789\n\n####789", "a": 865, "b": 76, "operator": "-", "result": 789}
{"question": "Solve (128 - 939)", "answer": "The result of (128 - 939) is -811\n\n####-811", "a": 128, "b": 939, "operator": "-", "result": -811}
{"question": "Solve (740 / 334)", "answer": "The result of (740 / 334) is 2.2156\n\n####2.2156", "a": 740, "b": 334, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2156}
{"question": "Solve (401 - 63)", "answer": "The result of (401 - 63) is 338\n\n####338", "a": 401, "b": 63, "operator": "-", "result": 338}
{"question": "Solve (908 / 603)", "answer": "The result of (908 / 603) is 1.5058\n\n####1.5058", "a": 908, "b": 603, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5058}
{"question": "Solve (216 + 20)", "answer": "The result of (216 + 20) is 236\n\n####236", "a": 216, "b": 20, "operator": "+", "result": 236}
{"question": "Solve (412 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (412 * 637) is 262444\n\n####262444", "a": 412, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 262444}
{"question": "Solve (878 * 431)", "answer": "The result of (878 * 431) is 378418\n\n####378418", "a": 878, "b": 431, "operator": "*", "result": 378418}
{"question": "Solve (136 * 556)", "answer": "The result of (136 * 556) is 75616\n\n####75616", "a": 136, "b": 556, "operator": "*", "result": 75616}
{"question": "Solve (691 - 72)", "answer": "The result of (691 - 72) is 619\n\n####619", "a": 691, "b": 72, "operator": "-", "result": 619}
{"question": "Solve (586 * 334)", "answer": "The result of (586 * 334) is 195724\n\n####195724", "a": 586, "b": 334, "operator": "*", "result": 195724}
{"question": "Solve (692 / 848)", "answer": "The result of (692 / 848) is 0.816\n\n####0.816", "a": 692, "b": 848, "operator": "/", "result": 0.816}
{"question": "Solve (504 + 163)", "answer": "The result of (504 + 163) is 667\n\n####667", "a": 504, "b": 163, "operator": "+", "result": 667}
{"question": "Solve (17 + 247)", "answer": "The result of (17 + 247) is 264\n\n####264", "a": 17, "b": 247, "operator": "+", "result": 264}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 395)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 395) is 666\n\n####666", "a": 271, "b": 395, "operator": "+", "result": 666}
{"question": "Solve (160 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (160 - 45) is 115\n\n####115", "a": 160, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 115}
{"question": "Solve (204 / 464)", "answer": "The result of (204 / 464) is 0.4397\n\n####0.4397", "a": 204, "b": 464, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4397}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 294) is 1.1769\n\n####1.1769", "a": 346, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1769}
{"question": "Solve (947 * 903)", "answer": "The result of (947 * 903) is 855141\n\n####855141", "a": 947, "b": 903, "operator": "*", "result": 855141}
{"question": "Solve (705 * 666)", "answer": "The result of (705 * 666) is 469530\n\n####469530", "a": 705, "b": 666, "operator": "*", "result": 469530}
{"question": "Solve (18 * 517)", "answer": "The result of (18 * 517) is 9306\n\n####9306", "a": 18, "b": 517, "operator": "*", "result": 9306}
{"question": "Solve (983 / 809)", "answer": "The result of (983 / 809) is 1.2151\n\n####1.2151", "a": 983, "b": 809, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2151}
{"question": "Solve (561 - 511)", "answer": "The result of (561 - 511) is 50\n\n####50", "a": 561, "b": 511, "operator": "-", "result": 50}
{"question": "Solve (160 * 429)", "answer": "The result of (160 * 429) is 68640\n\n####68640", "a": 160, "b": 429, "operator": "*", "result": 68640}
{"question": "Solve (739 + 621)", "answer": "The result of (739 + 621) is 1360\n\n####1360", "a": 739, "b": 621, "operator": "+", "result": 1360}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 974)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 974) is -259\n\n####-259", "a": 715, "b": 974, "operator": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 260)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 260) is 1.1423\n\n####1.1423", "a": 297, "b": 260, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1423}
{"question": "Solve (344 / 643)", "answer": "The result of (344 / 643) is 0.535\n\n####0.535", "a": 344, "b": 643, "operator": "/", "result": 0.535}
{"question": "Solve (534 * 383)", "answer": "The result of (534 * 383) is 204522\n\n####204522", "a": 534, "b": 383, "operator": "*", "result": 204522}
{"question": "Solve (267 * 545)", "answer": "The result of (267 * 545) is 145515\n\n####145515", "a": 267, "b": 545, "operator": "*", "result": 145515}
{"question": "Solve (207 * 728)", "answer": "The result of (207 * 728) is 150696\n\n####150696", "a": 207, "b": 728, "operator": "*", "result": 150696}
{"question": "Solve (388 * 256)", "answer": "The result of (388 * 256) is 99328\n\n####99328", "a": 388, "b": 256, "operator": "*", "result": 99328}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 573)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 573) is 76209\n\n####76209", "a": 133, "b": 573, "operator": "*", "result": 76209}
{"question": "Solve (758 / 898)", "answer": "The result of (758 / 898) is 0.8441\n\n####0.8441", "a": 758, "b": 898, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8441}
{"question": "Solve (607 / 748)", "answer": "The result of (607 / 748) is 0.8115\n\n####0.8115", "a": 607, "b": 748, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8115}
{"question": "Solve (923 / 418)", "answer": "The result of (923 / 418) is 2.2081\n\n####2.2081", "a": 923, "b": 418, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2081}
{"question": "Solve (957 + 93)", "answer": "The result of (957 + 93) is 1050\n\n####1050", "a": 957, "b": 93, "operator": "+", "result": 1050}
{"question": "Solve (885 + 590)", "answer": "The result of (885 + 590) is 1475\n\n####1475", "a": 885, "b": 590, "operator": "+", "result": 1475}
{"question": "Solve (244 / 11)", "answer": "The result of (244 / 11) is 22.1818\n\n####22.1818", "a": 244, "b": 11, "operator": "/", "result": 22.1818}
{"question": "Solve (684 / 798)", "answer": "The result of (684 / 798) is 0.8571\n\n####0.8571", "a": 684, "b": 798, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8571}
{"question": "Solve (588 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (588 / 87) is 6.7586\n\n####6.7586", "a": 588, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 6.7586}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 466)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 466) is 284726\n\n####284726", "a": 611, "b": 466, "operator": "*", "result": 284726}
{"question": "Solve (740 * 562)", "answer": "The result of (740 * 562) is 415880\n\n####415880", "a": 740, "b": 562, "operator": "*", "result": 415880}
{"question": "Solve (280 / 222)", "answer": "The result of (280 / 222) is 1.2613\n\n####1.2613", "a": 280, "b": 222, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2613}
{"question": "Solve (989 - 69)", "answer": "The result of (989 - 69) is 920\n\n####920", "a": 989, "b": 69, "operator": "-", "result": 920}
{"question": "Solve (11 * 752)", "answer": "The result of (11 * 752) is 8272\n\n####8272", "a": 11, "b": 752, "operator": "*", "result": 8272}
{"question": "Solve (246 / 162)", "answer": "The result of (246 / 162) is 1.5185\n\n####1.5185", "a": 246, "b": 162, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5185}
{"question": "Solve (401 - 995)", "answer": "The result of (401 - 995) is -594\n\n####-594", "a": 401, "b": 995, "operator": "-", "result": -594}
{"question": "Solve (673 / 306)", "answer": "The result of (673 / 306) is 2.1993\n\n####2.1993", "a": 673, "b": 306, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1993}
{"question": "Solve (701 * 451)", "answer": "The result of (701 * 451) is 316151\n\n####316151", "a": 701, "b": 451, "operator": "*", "result": 316151}
{"question": "Solve (518 + 909)", "answer": "The result of (518 + 909) is 1427\n\n####1427", "a": 518, "b": 909, "operator": "+", "result": 1427}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 914) is 0.8862\n\n####0.8862", "a": 810, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8862}
{"question": "Solve (232 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (232 - 344) is -112\n\n####-112", "a": 232, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": -112}
{"question": "Solve (357 / 251)", "answer": "The result of (357 / 251) is 1.4223\n\n####1.4223", "a": 357, "b": 251, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4223}
{"question": "Solve (811 - 629)", "answer": "The result of (811 - 629) is 182\n\n####182", "a": 811, "b": 629, "operator": "-", "result": 182}
{"question": "Solve (297 + 95)", "answer": "The result of (297 + 95) is 392\n\n####392", "a": 297, "b": 95, "operator": "+", "result": 392}
{"question": "Solve (895 - 325)", "answer": "The result of (895 - 325) is 570\n\n####570", "a": 895, "b": 325, "operator": "-", "result": 570}
{"question": "Solve (380 - 92)", "answer": "The result of (380 - 92) is 288\n\n####288", "a": 380, "b": 92, "operator": "-", "result": 288}
{"question": "Solve (60 + 95)", "answer": "The result of (60 + 95) is 155\n\n####155", "a": 60, "b": 95, "operator": "+", "result": 155}
{"question": "Solve (663 + 607)", "answer": "The result of (663 + 607) is 1270\n\n####1270", "a": 663, "b": 607, "operator": "+", "result": 1270}
{"question": "Solve (212 + 583)", "answer": "The result of (212 + 583) is 795\n\n####795", "a": 212, "b": 583, "operator": "+", "result": 795}
{"question": "Solve (747 * 991)", "answer": "The result of (747 * 991) is 740277\n\n####740277", "a": 747, "b": 991, "operator": "*", "result": 740277}
{"question": "Solve (690 - 19)", "answer": "The result of (690 - 19) is 671\n\n####671", "a": 690, "b": 19, "operator": "-", "result": 671}
{"question": "Solve (226 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (226 - 295) is -69\n\n####-69", "a": 226, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": -69}
{"question": "Solve (769 / 588)", "answer": "The result of (769 / 588) is 1.3078\n\n####1.3078", "a": 769, "b": 588, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3078}
{"question": "Solve (649 * 241)", "answer": "The result of (649 * 241) is 156409\n\n####156409", "a": 649, "b": 241, "operator": "*", "result": 156409}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 519)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 519) is -196\n\n####-196", "a": 323, "b": 519, "operator": "-", "result": -196}
{"question": "Solve (891 / 352)", "answer": "The result of (891 / 352) is 2.5312\n\n####2.5312", "a": 891, "b": 352, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5312}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 857)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 857) is -371\n\n####-371", "a": 486, "b": 857, "operator": "-", "result": -371}
{"question": "Solve (747 - 780)", "answer": "The result of (747 - 780) is -33\n\n####-33", "a": 747, "b": 780, "operator": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve (79 / 562)", "answer": "The result of (79 / 562) is 0.1406\n\n####0.1406", "a": 79, "b": 562, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1406}
{"question": "Solve (193 / 209)", "answer": "The result of (193 / 209) is 0.9234\n\n####0.9234", "a": 193, "b": 209, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9234}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 480)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 480) is 0.6188\n\n####0.6188", "a": 297, "b": 480, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6188}
{"question": "Solve (152 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (152 / 388) is 0.3918\n\n####0.3918", "a": 152, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3918}
{"question": "Solve (835 + 361)", "answer": "The result of (835 + 361) is 1196\n\n####1196", "a": 835, "b": 361, "operator": "+", "result": 1196}
{"question": "Solve (398 * 683)", "answer": "The result of (398 * 683) is 271834\n\n####271834", "a": 398, "b": 683, "operator": "*", "result": 271834}
{"question": "Solve (924 - 930)", "answer": "The result of (924 - 930) is -6\n\n####-6", "a": 924, "b": 930, "operator": "-", "result": -6}
{"question": "Solve (262 - 865)", "answer": "The result of (262 - 865) is -603\n\n####-603", "a": 262, "b": 865, "operator": "-", "result": -603}
{"question": "Solve (163 / 282)", "answer": "The result of (163 / 282) is 0.578\n\n####0.578", "a": 163, "b": 282, "operator": "/", "result": 0.578}
{"question": "Solve (888 * 181)", "answer": "The result of (888 * 181) is 160728\n\n####160728", "a": 888, "b": 181, "operator": "*", "result": 160728}
{"question": "Solve (475 / 425)", "answer": "The result of (475 / 425) is 1.1176\n\n####1.1176", "a": 475, "b": 425, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1176}
{"question": "Solve (20 * 739)", "answer": "The result of (20 * 739) is 14780\n\n####14780", "a": 20, "b": 739, "operator": "*", "result": 14780}
{"question": "Solve (743 + 879)", "answer": "The result of (743 + 879) is 1622\n\n####1622", "a": 743, "b": 879, "operator": "+", "result": 1622}
{"question": "Solve (491 - 928)", "answer": "The result of (491 - 928) is -437\n\n####-437", "a": 491, "b": 928, "operator": "-", "result": -437}
{"question": "Solve (953 - 467)", "answer": "The result of (953 - 467) is 486\n\n####486", "a": 953, "b": 467, "operator": "-", "result": 486}
{"question": "Solve (100 - 36)", "answer": "The result of (100 - 36) is 64\n\n####64", "a": 100, "b": 36, "operator": "-", "result": 64}
{"question": "Solve (102 + 227)", "answer": "The result of (102 + 227) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 102, "b": 227, "operator": "+", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (385 + 50)", "answer": "The result of (385 + 50) is 435\n\n####435", "a": 385, "b": 50, "operator": "+", "result": 435}
{"question": "Solve (508 - 149)", "answer": "The result of (508 - 149) is 359\n\n####359", "a": 508, "b": 149, "operator": "-", "result": 359}
{"question": "Solve (666 - 67)", "answer": "The result of (666 - 67) is 599\n\n####599", "a": 666, "b": 67, "operator": "-", "result": 599}
{"question": "Solve (414 - 315)", "answer": "The result of (414 - 315) is 99\n\n####99", "a": 414, "b": 315, "operator": "-", "result": 99}
{"question": "Solve (516 / 500)", "answer": "The result of (516 / 500) is 1.032\n\n####1.032", "a": 516, "b": 500, "operator": "/", "result": 1.032}
{"question": "Solve (559 - 111)", "answer": "The result of (559 - 111) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 559, "b": 111, "operator": "-", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (228 - 104)", "answer": "The result of (228 - 104) is 124\n\n####124", "a": 228, "b": 104, "operator": "-", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 802)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 802) is 0.0262\n\n####0.0262", "a": 21, "b": 802, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0262}
{"question": "Solve (715 / 809)", "answer": "The result of (715 / 809) is 0.8838\n\n####0.8838", "a": 715, "b": 809, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8838}
{"question": "Solve (521 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (521 - 238) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 521, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (763 - 24)", "answer": "The result of (763 - 24) is 739\n\n####739", "a": 763, "b": 24, "operator": "-", "result": 739}
{"question": "Solve (107 + 274)", "answer": "The result of (107 + 274) is 381\n\n####381", "a": 107, "b": 274, "operator": "+", "result": 381}
{"question": "Solve (142 - 716)", "answer": "The result of (142 - 716) is -574\n\n####-574", "a": 142, "b": 716, "operator": "-", "result": -574}
{"question": "Solve (818 / 826)", "answer": "The result of (818 / 826) is 0.9903\n\n####0.9903", "a": 818, "b": 826, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9903}
{"question": "Solve (897 * 79)", "answer": "The result of (897 * 79) is 70863\n\n####70863", "a": 897, "b": 79, "operator": "*", "result": 70863}
{"question": "Solve (170 + 212)", "answer": "The result of (170 + 212) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 170, "b": 212, "operator": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (688 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (688 - 449) is 239\n\n####239", "a": 688, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": 239}
{"question": "Solve (19 + 164)", "answer": "The result of (19 + 164) is 183\n\n####183", "a": 19, "b": 164, "operator": "+", "result": 183}
{"question": "Solve (189 - 350)", "answer": "The result of (189 - 350) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 189, "b": 350, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (306 + 177)", "answer": "The result of (306 + 177) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 306, "b": 177, "operator": "+", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 82)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 82) is 167\n\n####167", "a": 249, "b": 82, "operator": "-", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve (851 * 802)", "answer": "The result of (851 * 802) is 682502\n\n####682502", "a": 851, "b": 802, "operator": "*", "result": 682502}
{"question": "Solve (752 + 394)", "answer": "The result of (752 + 394) is 1146\n\n####1146", "a": 752, "b": 394, "operator": "+", "result": 1146}
{"question": "Solve (851 / 280)", "answer": "The result of (851 / 280) is 3.0393\n\n####3.0393", "a": 851, "b": 280, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0393}
{"question": "Solve (261 + 963)", "answer": "The result of (261 + 963) is 1224\n\n####1224", "a": 261, "b": 963, "operator": "+", "result": 1224}
{"question": "Solve (625 - 378)", "answer": "The result of (625 - 378) is 247\n\n####247", "a": 625, "b": 378, "operator": "-", "result": 247}
{"question": "Solve (211 / 824)", "answer": "The result of (211 / 824) is 0.2561\n\n####0.2561", "a": 211, "b": 824, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2561}
{"question": "Solve (419 - 166)", "answer": "The result of (419 - 166) is 253\n\n####253", "a": 419, "b": 166, "operator": "-", "result": 253}
{"question": "Solve (405 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (405 / 390) is 1.0385\n\n####1.0385", "a": 405, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0385}
{"question": "Solve (983 * 959)", "answer": "The result of (983 * 959) is 942697\n\n####942697", "a": 983, "b": 959, "operator": "*", "result": 942697}
{"question": "Solve (458 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (458 * 690) is 316020\n\n####316020", "a": 458, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 316020}
{"question": "Solve (279 + 82)", "answer": "The result of (279 + 82) is 361\n\n####361", "a": 279, "b": 82, "operator": "+", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve (933 * 455)", "answer": "The result of (933 * 455) is 424515\n\n####424515", "a": 933, "b": 455, "operator": "*", "result": 424515}
{"question": "Solve (495 * 572)", "answer": "The result of (495 * 572) is 283140\n\n####283140", "a": 495, "b": 572, "operator": "*", "result": 283140}
{"question": "Solve (573 * 853)", "answer": "The result of (573 * 853) is 488769\n\n####488769", "a": 573, "b": 853, "operator": "*", "result": 488769}
{"question": "Solve (821 * 48)", "answer": "The result of (821 * 48) is 39408\n\n####39408", "a": 821, "b": 48, "operator": "*", "result": 39408}
{"question": "Solve (998 / 616)", "answer": "The result of (998 / 616) is 1.6201\n\n####1.6201", "a": 998, "b": 616, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6201}
{"question": "Solve (106 * 383)", "answer": "The result of (106 * 383) is 40598\n\n####40598", "a": 106, "b": 383, "operator": "*", "result": 40598}
{"question": "Solve (39 / 555)", "answer": "The result of (39 / 555) is 0.0703\n\n####0.0703", "a": 39, "b": 555, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0703}
{"question": "Solve (209 / 777)", "answer": "The result of (209 / 777) is 0.269\n\n####0.269", "a": 209, "b": 777, "operator": "/", "result": 0.269}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 539)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 539) is 33957\n\n####33957", "a": 63, "b": 539, "operator": "*", "result": 33957}
{"question": "Solve (123 / 10)", "answer": "The result of (123 / 10) is 12.3\n\n####12.3", "a": 123, "b": 10, "operator": "/", "result": 12.3}
{"question": "Solve (902 * 483)", "answer": "The result of (902 * 483) is 435666\n\n####435666", "a": 902, "b": 483, "operator": "*", "result": 435666}
{"question": "Solve (505 + 571)", "answer": "The result of (505 + 571) is 1076\n\n####1076", "a": 505, "b": 571, "operator": "+", "result": 1076}
{"question": "Solve (38 + 534)", "answer": "The result of (38 + 534) is 572\n\n####572", "a": 38, "b": 534, "operator": "+", "result": 572}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 407)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 407) is 1.6904\n\n####1.6904", "a": 688, "b": 407, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6904}
{"question": "Solve (169 - 299)", "answer": "The result of (169 - 299) is -130\n\n####-130", "a": 169, "b": 299, "operator": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve (737 * 739)", "answer": "The result of (737 * 739) is 544643\n\n####544643", "a": 737, "b": 739, "operator": "*", "result": 544643}
{"question": "Solve (52 - 454)", "answer": "The result of (52 - 454) is -402\n\n####-402", "a": 52, "b": 454, "operator": "-", "result": -402}
{"question": "Solve (988 / 547)", "answer": "The result of (988 / 547) is 1.8062\n\n####1.8062", "a": 988, "b": 547, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8062}
{"question": "Solve (31 * 205)", "answer": "The result of (31 * 205) is 6355\n\n####6355", "a": 31, "b": 205, "operator": "*", "result": 6355}
{"question": "Solve (260 - 862)", "answer": "The result of (260 - 862) is -602\n\n####-602", "a": 260, "b": 862, "operator": "-", "result": -602}
{"question": "Solve (843 + 8)", "answer": "The result of (843 + 8) is 851\n\n####851", "a": 843, "b": 8, "operator": "+", "result": 851}
{"question": "Solve (17 - 505)", "answer": "The result of (17 - 505) is -488\n\n####-488", "a": 17, "b": 505, "operator": "-", "result": -488}
{"question": "Solve (923 + 31)", "answer": "The result of (923 + 31) is 954\n\n####954", "a": 923, "b": 31, "operator": "+", "result": 954}
{"question": "Solve (726 * 482)", "answer": "The result of (726 * 482) is 349932\n\n####349932", "a": 726, "b": 482, "operator": "*", "result": 349932}
{"question": "Solve (910 + 35)", "answer": "The result of (910 + 35) is 945\n\n####945", "a": 910, "b": 35, "operator": "+", "result": 945}
{"question": "Solve (280 - 21)", "answer": "The result of (280 - 21) is 259\n\n####259", "a": 280, "b": 21, "operator": "-", "result": 259}
{"question": "Solve (419 - 526)", "answer": "The result of (419 - 526) is -107\n\n####-107", "a": 419, "b": 526, "operator": "-", "result": -107}
{"question": "Solve (802 / 53)", "answer": "The result of (802 / 53) is 15.1321\n\n####15.1321", "a": 802, "b": 53, "operator": "/", "result": 15.1321}
{"question": "Solve (17 - 654)", "answer": "The result of (17 - 654) is -637\n\n####-637", "a": 17, "b": 654, "operator": "-", "result": -637}
{"question": "Solve (406 * 667)", "answer": "The result of (406 * 667) is 270802\n\n####270802", "a": 406, "b": 667, "operator": "*", "result": 270802}
{"question": "Solve (328 / 169)", "answer": "The result of (328 / 169) is 1.9408\n\n####1.9408", "a": 328, "b": 169, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9408}
{"question": "Solve (802 + 506)", "answer": "The result of (802 + 506) is 1308\n\n####1308", "a": 802, "b": 506, "operator": "+", "result": 1308}
{"question": "Solve (927 / 23)", "answer": "The result of (927 / 23) is 40.3043\n\n####40.3043", "a": 927, "b": 23, "operator": "/", "result": 40.3043}
{"question": "Solve (884 + 24)", "answer": "The result of (884 + 24) is 908\n\n####908", "a": 884, "b": 24, "operator": "+", "result": 908}
{"question": "Solve (933 / 359)", "answer": "The result of (933 / 359) is 2.5989\n\n####2.5989", "a": 933, "b": 359, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5989}
{"question": "Solve (742 / 836)", "answer": "The result of (742 / 836) is 0.8876\n\n####0.8876", "a": 742, "b": 836, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8876}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 578)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 578) is 325992\n\n####325992", "a": 564, "b": 578, "operator": "*", "result": 325992}
{"question": "Solve (981 - 780)", "answer": "The result of (981 - 780) is 201\n\n####201", "a": 981, "b": 780, "operator": "-", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve (583 / 199)", "answer": "The result of (583 / 199) is 2.9296\n\n####2.9296", "a": 583, "b": 199, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9296}
{"question": "Solve (619 - 78)", "answer": "The result of (619 - 78) is 541\n\n####541", "a": 619, "b": 78, "operator": "-", "result": 541}
{"question": "Solve (271 + 919)", "answer": "The result of (271 + 919) is 1190\n\n####1190", "a": 271, "b": 919, "operator": "+", "result": 1190}
{"question": "Solve (986 + 682)", "answer": "The result of (986 + 682) is 1668\n\n####1668", "a": 986, "b": 682, "operator": "+", "result": 1668}
{"question": "Solve (936 + 982)", "answer": "The result of (936 + 982) is 1918\n\n####1918", "a": 936, "b": 982, "operator": "+", "result": 1918}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 371)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 371) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 318, "b": 371, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (276 * 491)", "answer": "The result of (276 * 491) is 135516\n\n####135516", "a": 276, "b": 491, "operator": "*", "result": 135516}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 175) is 23275\n\n####23275", "a": 133, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 23275}
{"question": "Solve (930 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (930 - 849) is 81\n\n####81", "a": 930, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": 81}
{"question": "Solve (661 - 50)", "answer": "The result of (661 - 50) is 611\n\n####611", "a": 661, "b": 50, "operator": "-", "result": 611}
{"question": "Solve (813 / 527)", "answer": "The result of (813 / 527) is 1.5427\n\n####1.5427", "a": 813, "b": 527, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5427}
{"question": "Solve (208 / 653)", "answer": "The result of (208 / 653) is 0.3185\n\n####0.3185", "a": 208, "b": 653, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3185}
{"question": "Solve (318 / 611)", "answer": "The result of (318 / 611) is 0.5205\n\n####0.5205", "a": 318, "b": 611, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5205}
{"question": "Solve (960 - 776)", "answer": "The result of (960 - 776) is 184\n\n####184", "a": 960, "b": 776, "operator": "-", "result": 184}
{"question": "Solve (591 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (591 / 294) is 2.0102\n\n####2.0102", "a": 591, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0102}
{"question": "Solve (188 + 424)", "answer": "The result of (188 + 424) is 612\n\n####612", "a": 188, "b": 424, "operator": "+", "result": 612}
{"question": "Solve (316 * 146)", "answer": "The result of (316 * 146) is 46136\n\n####46136", "a": 316, "b": 146, "operator": "*", "result": 46136}
{"question": "Solve (614 * 159)", "answer": "The result of (614 * 159) is 97626\n\n####97626", "a": 614, "b": 159, "operator": "*", "result": 97626}
{"question": "Solve (772 + 594)", "answer": "The result of (772 + 594) is 1366\n\n####1366", "a": 772, "b": 594, "operator": "+", "result": 1366}
{"question": "Solve (410 - 252)", "answer": "The result of (410 - 252) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 410, "b": 252, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (32 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (32 - 822) is -790\n\n####-790", "a": 32, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": -790}
{"question": "Solve (626 + 566)", "answer": "The result of (626 + 566) is 1192\n\n####1192", "a": 626, "b": 566, "operator": "+", "result": 1192}
{"question": "Solve (772 * 480)", "answer": "The result of (772 * 480) is 370560\n\n####370560", "a": 772, "b": 480, "operator": "*", "result": 370560}
{"question": "Solve (669 + 745)", "answer": "The result of (669 + 745) is 1414\n\n####1414", "a": 669, "b": 745, "operator": "+", "result": 1414}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 231)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 231) is 179025\n\n####179025", "a": 775, "b": 231, "operator": "*", "result": 179025}
{"question": "Solve (21 - 373)", "answer": "The result of (21 - 373) is -352\n\n####-352", "a": 21, "b": 373, "operator": "-", "result": -352}
{"question": "Solve (494 + 649)", "answer": "The result of (494 + 649) is 1143\n\n####1143", "a": 494, "b": 649, "operator": "+", "result": 1143}
{"question": "Solve (553 * 116)", "answer": "The result of (553 * 116) is 64148\n\n####64148", "a": 553, "b": 116, "operator": "*", "result": 64148}
{"question": "Solve (230 * 231)", "answer": "The result of (230 * 231) is 53130\n\n####53130", "a": 230, "b": 231, "operator": "*", "result": 53130}
{"question": "Solve (502 - 467)", "answer": "The result of (502 - 467) is 35\n\n####35", "a": 502, "b": 467, "operator": "-", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve (244 * 540)", "answer": "The result of (244 * 540) is 131760\n\n####131760", "a": 244, "b": 540, "operator": "*", "result": 131760}
{"question": "Solve (522 - 186)", "answer": "The result of (522 - 186) is 336\n\n####336", "a": 522, "b": 186, "operator": "-", "result": 336}
{"question": "Solve (610 + 706)", "answer": "The result of (610 + 706) is 1316\n\n####1316", "a": 610, "b": 706, "operator": "+", "result": 1316}
{"question": "Solve (195 - 615)", "answer": "The result of (195 - 615) is -420\n\n####-420", "a": 195, "b": 615, "operator": "-", "result": -420}
{"question": "Solve (669 + 940)", "answer": "The result of (669 + 940) is 1609\n\n####1609", "a": 669, "b": 940, "operator": "+", "result": 1609}
{"question": "Solve (16 - 209)", "answer": "The result of (16 - 209) is -193\n\n####-193", "a": 16, "b": 209, "operator": "-", "result": -193}
{"question": "Solve (455 / 297)", "answer": "The result of (455 / 297) is 1.532\n\n####1.532", "a": 455, "b": 297, "operator": "/", "result": 1.532}
{"question": "Solve (542 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (542 - 256) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 542, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (601 * 726)", "answer": "The result of (601 * 726) is 436326\n\n####436326", "a": 601, "b": 726, "operator": "*", "result": 436326}
{"question": "Solve (989 / 550)", "answer": "The result of (989 / 550) is 1.7982\n\n####1.7982", "a": 989, "b": 550, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7982}
{"question": "Solve (310 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (310 - 471) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 310, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (156 + 792)", "answer": "The result of (156 + 792) is 948\n\n####948", "a": 156, "b": 792, "operator": "+", "result": 948}
{"question": "Solve (633 * 54)", "answer": "The result of (633 * 54) is 34182\n\n####34182", "a": 633, "b": 54, "operator": "*", "result": 34182}
{"question": "Solve (701 + 590)", "answer": "The result of (701 + 590) is 1291\n\n####1291", "a": 701, "b": 590, "operator": "+", "result": 1291}
{"question": "Solve (815 * 598)", "answer": "The result of (815 * 598) is 487370\n\n####487370", "a": 815, "b": 598, "operator": "*", "result": 487370}
{"question": "Solve (813 - 799)", "answer": "The result of (813 - 799) is 14\n\n####14", "a": 813, "b": 799, "operator": "-", "result": 14}
{"question": "Solve (567 * 44)", "answer": "The result of (567 * 44) is 24948\n\n####24948", "a": 567, "b": 44, "operator": "*", "result": 24948}
{"question": "Solve (715 * 308)", "answer": "The result of (715 * 308) is 220220\n\n####220220", "a": 715, "b": 308, "operator": "*", "result": 220220}
{"question": "Solve (906 - 698)", "answer": "The result of (906 - 698) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 906, "b": 698, "operator": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (619 / 189)", "answer": "The result of (619 / 189) is 3.2751\n\n####3.2751", "a": 619, "b": 189, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2751}
{"question": "Solve (280 - 167)", "answer": "The result of (280 - 167) is 113\n\n####113", "a": 280, "b": 167, "operator": "-", "result": 113}
{"question": "Solve (879 - 801)", "answer": "The result of (879 - 801) is 78\n\n####78", "a": 879, "b": 801, "operator": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve (843 - 180)", "answer": "The result of (843 - 180) is 663\n\n####663", "a": 843, "b": 180, "operator": "-", "result": 663}
{"question": "Solve (912 * 845)", "answer": "The result of (912 * 845) is 770640\n\n####770640", "a": 912, "b": 845, "operator": "*", "result": 770640}
{"question": "Solve (322 + 260)", "answer": "The result of (322 + 260) is 582\n\n####582", "a": 322, "b": 260, "operator": "+", "result": 582}
{"question": "Solve (911 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (911 / 623) is 1.4623\n\n####1.4623", "a": 911, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4623}
{"question": "Solve (543 + 49)", "answer": "The result of (543 + 49) is 592\n\n####592", "a": 543, "b": 49, "operator": "+", "result": 592}
{"question": "Solve (131 * 264)", "answer": "The result of (131 * 264) is 34584\n\n####34584", "a": 131, "b": 264, "operator": "*", "result": 34584}
{"question": "Solve (831 / 270)", "answer": "The result of (831 / 270) is 3.0778\n\n####3.0778", "a": 831, "b": 270, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0778}
{"question": "Solve (301 + 284)", "answer": "The result of (301 + 284) is 585\n\n####585", "a": 301, "b": 284, "operator": "+", "result": 585}
{"question": "Solve (341 + 632)", "answer": "The result of (341 + 632) is 973\n\n####973", "a": 341, "b": 632, "operator": "+", "result": 973}
{"question": "Solve (484 / 174)", "answer": "The result of (484 / 174) is 2.7816\n\n####2.7816", "a": 484, "b": 174, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7816}
{"question": "Solve (847 - 991)", "answer": "The result of (847 - 991) is -144\n\n####-144", "a": 847, "b": 991, "operator": "-", "result": -144}
{"question": "Solve (640 / 676)", "answer": "The result of (640 / 676) is 0.9467\n\n####0.9467", "a": 640, "b": 676, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9467}
{"question": "Solve (483 / 802)", "answer": "The result of (483 / 802) is 0.6022\n\n####0.6022", "a": 483, "b": 802, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6022}
{"question": "Solve (108 + 237)", "answer": "The result of (108 + 237) is 345\n\n####345", "a": 108, "b": 237, "operator": "+", "result": 345}
{"question": "Solve (348 - 171)", "answer": "The result of (348 - 171) is 177\n\n####177", "a": 348, "b": 171, "operator": "-", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve (70 * 160)", "answer": "The result of (70 * 160) is 11200\n\n####11200", "a": 70, "b": 160, "operator": "*", "result": 11200}
{"question": "Solve (319 - 187)", "answer": "The result of (319 - 187) is 132\n\n####132", "a": 319, "b": 187, "operator": "-", "result": 132}
{"question": "Solve (146 / 897)", "answer": "The result of (146 / 897) is 0.1628\n\n####0.1628", "a": 146, "b": 897, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1628}
{"question": "Solve (228 * 136)", "answer": "The result of (228 * 136) is 31008\n\n####31008", "a": 228, "b": 136, "operator": "*", "result": 31008}
{"question": "Solve (379 * 381)", "answer": "The result of (379 * 381) is 144399\n\n####144399", "a": 379, "b": 381, "operator": "*", "result": 144399}
{"question": "Solve (821 - 656)", "answer": "The result of (821 - 656) is 165\n\n####165", "a": 821, "b": 656, "operator": "-", "result": 165}
{"question": "Solve (584 + 109)", "answer": "The result of (584 + 109) is 693\n\n####693", "a": 584, "b": 109, "operator": "+", "result": 693}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 993)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 993) is 0.3635\n\n####0.3635", "a": 361, "b": 993, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3635}
{"question": "Solve (198 - 561)", "answer": "The result of (198 - 561) is -363\n\n####-363", "a": 198, "b": 561, "operator": "-", "result": -363}
{"question": "Solve (331 * 717)", "answer": "The result of (331 * 717) is 237327\n\n####237327", "a": 331, "b": 717, "operator": "*", "result": 237327}
{"question": "Solve (474 - 242)", "answer": "The result of (474 - 242) is 232\n\n####232", "a": 474, "b": 242, "operator": "-", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve (13 + 901)", "answer": "The result of (13 + 901) is 914\n\n####914", "a": 13, "b": 901, "operator": "+", "result": 914}
{"question": "Solve (608 / 6)", "answer": "The result of (608 / 6) is 101.3333\n\n####101.3333", "a": 608, "b": 6, "operator": "/", "result": 101.3333}
{"question": "Solve (836 / 624)", "answer": "The result of (836 / 624) is 1.3397\n\n####1.3397", "a": 836, "b": 624, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3397}
{"question": "Solve (129 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (129 - 647) is -518\n\n####-518", "a": 129, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": -518}
{"question": "Solve (581 - 507)", "answer": "The result of (581 - 507) is 74\n\n####74", "a": 581, "b": 507, "operator": "-", "result": 74}
{"question": "Solve (109 / 645)", "answer": "The result of (109 / 645) is 0.169\n\n####0.169", "a": 109, "b": 645, "operator": "/", "result": 0.169}
{"question": "Solve (589 - 117)", "answer": "The result of (589 - 117) is 472\n\n####472", "a": 589, "b": 117, "operator": "-", "result": 472}
{"question": "Solve (314 / 754)", "answer": "The result of (314 / 754) is 0.4164\n\n####0.4164", "a": 314, "b": 754, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4164}
{"question": "Solve (70 - 714)", "answer": "The result of (70 - 714) is -644\n\n####-644", "a": 70, "b": 714, "operator": "-", "result": -644}
{"question": "Solve (679 / 1)", "answer": "The result of (679 / 1) is 679.0\n\n####679.0", "a": 679, "b": 1, "operator": "/", "result": 679.0}
{"question": "Solve (477 * 344)", "answer": "The result of (477 * 344) is 164088\n\n####164088", "a": 477, "b": 344, "operator": "*", "result": 164088}
{"question": "Solve (897 * 107)", "answer": "The result of (897 * 107) is 95979\n\n####95979", "a": 897, "b": 107, "operator": "*", "result": 95979}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 97)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 97) is 94187\n\n####94187", "a": 971, "b": 97, "operator": "*", "result": 94187}
{"question": "Solve (358 * 793)", "answer": "The result of (358 * 793) is 283894\n\n####283894", "a": 358, "b": 793, "operator": "*", "result": 283894}
{"question": "Solve (665 / 564)", "answer": "The result of (665 / 564) is 1.1791\n\n####1.1791", "a": 665, "b": 564, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1791}
{"question": "Solve (743 * 580)", "answer": "The result of (743 * 580) is 430940\n\n####430940", "a": 743, "b": 580, "operator": "*", "result": 430940}
{"question": "Solve (914 * 561)", "answer": "The result of (914 * 561) is 512754\n\n####512754", "a": 914, "b": 561, "operator": "*", "result": 512754}
{"question": "Solve (675 + 249)", "answer": "The result of (675 + 249) is 924\n\n####924", "a": 675, "b": 249, "operator": "+", "result": 924}
{"question": "Solve (918 + 417)", "answer": "The result of (918 + 417) is 1335\n\n####1335", "a": 918, "b": 417, "operator": "+", "result": 1335}
{"question": "Solve (710 / 157)", "answer": "The result of (710 / 157) is 4.5223\n\n####4.5223", "a": 710, "b": 157, "operator": "/", "result": 4.5223}
{"question": "Solve (210 - 947)", "answer": "The result of (210 - 947) is -737\n\n####-737", "a": 210, "b": 947, "operator": "-", "result": -737}
{"question": "Solve (365 + 21)", "answer": "The result of (365 + 21) is 386\n\n####386", "a": 365, "b": 21, "operator": "+", "result": 386}
{"question": "Solve (208 * 831)", "answer": "The result of (208 * 831) is 172848\n\n####172848", "a": 208, "b": 831, "operator": "*", "result": 172848}
{"question": "Solve (699 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (699 * 22) is 15378\n\n####15378", "a": 699, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 15378}
{"question": "Solve (908 * 288)", "answer": "The result of (908 * 288) is 261504\n\n####261504", "a": 908, "b": 288, "operator": "*", "result": 261504}
{"question": "Solve (630 / 467)", "answer": "The result of (630 / 467) is 1.349\n\n####1.349", "a": 630, "b": 467, "operator": "/", "result": 1.349}
{"question": "Solve (712 - 744)", "answer": "The result of (712 - 744) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 712, "b": 744, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (627 / 691)", "answer": "The result of (627 / 691) is 0.9074\n\n####0.9074", "a": 627, "b": 691, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9074}
{"question": "Solve (20 + 204)", "answer": "The result of (20 + 204) is 224\n\n####224", "a": 20, "b": 204, "operator": "+", "result": 224}
{"question": "Solve (719 / 794)", "answer": "The result of (719 / 794) is 0.9055\n\n####0.9055", "a": 719, "b": 794, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9055}
{"question": "Solve (875 - 675)", "answer": "The result of (875 - 675) is 200\n\n####200", "a": 875, "b": 675, "operator": "-", "result": 200}
{"question": "Solve (734 + 981)", "answer": "The result of (734 + 981) is 1715\n\n####1715", "a": 734, "b": 981, "operator": "+", "result": 1715}
{"question": "Solve (424 * 217)", "answer": "The result of (424 * 217) is 92008\n\n####92008", "a": 424, "b": 217, "operator": "*", "result": 92008}
{"question": "Solve (785 / 855)", "answer": "The result of (785 / 855) is 0.9181\n\n####0.9181", "a": 785, "b": 855, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9181}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 937)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 937) is -740\n\n####-740", "a": 197, "b": 937, "operator": "-", "result": -740}
{"question": "Solve (82 - 15)", "answer": "The result of (82 - 15) is 67\n\n####67", "a": 82, "b": 15, "operator": "-", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve (898 - 342)", "answer": "The result of (898 - 342) is 556\n\n####556", "a": 898, "b": 342, "operator": "-", "result": 556}
{"question": "Solve (787 + 425)", "answer": "The result of (787 + 425) is 1212\n\n####1212", "a": 787, "b": 425, "operator": "+", "result": 1212}
{"question": "Solve (644 / 842)", "answer": "The result of (644 / 842) is 0.7648\n\n####0.7648", "a": 644, "b": 842, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7648}
{"question": "Solve (116 + 139)", "answer": "The result of (116 + 139) is 255\n\n####255", "a": 116, "b": 139, "operator": "+", "result": 255}
{"question": "Solve (27 + 409)", "answer": "The result of (27 + 409) is 436\n\n####436", "a": 27, "b": 409, "operator": "+", "result": 436}
{"question": "Solve (98 / 630)", "answer": "The result of (98 / 630) is 0.1556\n\n####0.1556", "a": 98, "b": 630, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1556}
{"question": "Solve (22 * 381)", "answer": "The result of (22 * 381) is 8382\n\n####8382", "a": 22, "b": 381, "operator": "*", "result": 8382}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 254)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 254) is 461\n\n####461", "a": 715, "b": 254, "operator": "-", "result": 461}
{"question": "Solve (272 * 308)", "answer": "The result of (272 * 308) is 83776\n\n####83776", "a": 272, "b": 308, "operator": "*", "result": 83776}
{"question": "Solve (506 + 441)", "answer": "The result of (506 + 441) is 947\n\n####947", "a": 506, "b": 441, "operator": "+", "result": 947}
{"question": "Solve (905 + 816)", "answer": "The result of (905 + 816) is 1721\n\n####1721", "a": 905, "b": 816, "operator": "+", "result": 1721}
{"question": "Solve (620 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (620 - 537) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 620, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (12 / 277)", "answer": "The result of (12 / 277) is 0.0433\n\n####0.0433", "a": 12, "b": 277, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0433}
{"question": "Solve (907 / 145)", "answer": "The result of (907 / 145) is 6.2552\n\n####6.2552", "a": 907, "b": 145, "operator": "/", "result": 6.2552}
{"question": "Solve (334 / 544)", "answer": "The result of (334 / 544) is 0.614\n\n####0.614", "a": 334, "b": 544, "operator": "/", "result": 0.614}
{"question": "Solve (866 / 520)", "answer": "The result of (866 / 520) is 1.6654\n\n####1.6654", "a": 866, "b": 520, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6654}
{"question": "Solve (26 / 7)", "answer": "The result of (26 / 7) is 3.7143\n\n####3.7143", "a": 26, "b": 7, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7143}
{"question": "Solve (337 - 571)", "answer": "The result of (337 - 571) is -234\n\n####-234", "a": 337, "b": 571, "operator": "-", "result": -234}
{"question": "Solve (852 / 35)", "answer": "The result of (852 / 35) is 24.3429\n\n####24.3429", "a": 852, "b": 35, "operator": "/", "result": 24.3429}
{"question": "Solve (888 - 79)", "answer": "The result of (888 - 79) is 809\n\n####809", "a": 888, "b": 79, "operator": "-", "result": 809}
{"question": "Solve (817 / 859)", "answer": "The result of (817 / 859) is 0.9511\n\n####0.9511", "a": 817, "b": 859, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9511}
{"question": "Solve (212 / 160)", "answer": "The result of (212 / 160) is 1.325\n\n####1.325", "a": 212, "b": 160, "operator": "/", "result": 1.325}
{"question": "Solve (144 * 677)", "answer": "The result of (144 * 677) is 97488\n\n####97488", "a": 144, "b": 677, "operator": "*", "result": 97488}
{"question": "Solve (955 - 870)", "answer": "The result of (955 - 870) is 85\n\n####85", "a": 955, "b": 870, "operator": "-", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve (654 / 974)", "answer": "The result of (654 / 974) is 0.6715\n\n####0.6715", "a": 654, "b": 974, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6715}
{"question": "Solve (490 - 172)", "answer": "The result of (490 - 172) is 318\n\n####318", "a": 490, "b": 172, "operator": "-", "result": 318}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 383)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 383) is 200692\n\n####200692", "a": 524, "b": 383, "operator": "*", "result": 200692}
{"question": "Solve (354 / 530)", "answer": "The result of (354 / 530) is 0.6679\n\n####0.6679", "a": 354, "b": 530, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6679}
{"question": "Solve (642 + 425)", "answer": "The result of (642 + 425) is 1067\n\n####1067", "a": 642, "b": 425, "operator": "+", "result": 1067}
{"question": "Solve (44 * 816)", "answer": "The result of (44 * 816) is 35904\n\n####35904", "a": 44, "b": 816, "operator": "*", "result": 35904}
{"question": "Solve (923 / 675)", "answer": "The result of (923 / 675) is 1.3674\n\n####1.3674", "a": 923, "b": 675, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3674}
{"question": "Solve (934 * 320)", "answer": "The result of (934 * 320) is 298880\n\n####298880", "a": 934, "b": 320, "operator": "*", "result": 298880}
{"question": "Solve (254 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (254 * 423) is 107442\n\n####107442", "a": 254, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 107442}
{"question": "Solve (858 / 735)", "answer": "The result of (858 / 735) is 1.1673\n\n####1.1673", "a": 858, "b": 735, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1673}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 198)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 198) is 31\n\n####31", "a": 229, "b": 198, "operator": "-", "result": 31}
{"question": "Solve (12 + 541)", "answer": "The result of (12 + 541) is 553\n\n####553", "a": 12, "b": 541, "operator": "+", "result": 553}
{"question": "Solve (412 + 386)", "answer": "The result of (412 + 386) is 798\n\n####798", "a": 412, "b": 386, "operator": "+", "result": 798}
{"question": "Solve (206 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (206 / 322) is 0.6398\n\n####0.6398", "a": 206, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6398}
{"question": "Solve (862 + 323)", "answer": "The result of (862 + 323) is 1185\n\n####1185", "a": 862, "b": 323, "operator": "+", "result": 1185}
{"question": "Solve (21 * 204)", "answer": "The result of (21 * 204) is 4284\n\n####4284", "a": 21, "b": 204, "operator": "*", "result": 4284}
{"question": "Solve (892 - 402)", "answer": "The result of (892 - 402) is 490\n\n####490", "a": 892, "b": 402, "operator": "-", "result": 490}
{"question": "Solve (99 / 783)", "answer": "The result of (99 / 783) is 0.1264\n\n####0.1264", "a": 99, "b": 783, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1264}
{"question": "Solve (169 + 661)", "answer": "The result of (169 + 661) is 830\n\n####830", "a": 169, "b": 661, "operator": "+", "result": 830}
{"question": "Solve (474 / 83)", "answer": "The result of (474 / 83) is 5.7108\n\n####5.7108", "a": 474, "b": 83, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7108}
{"question": "Solve (557 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (557 + 487) is 1044\n\n####1044", "a": 557, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 1044}
{"question": "Solve (463 / 538)", "answer": "The result of (463 / 538) is 0.8606\n\n####0.8606", "a": 463, "b": 538, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8606}
{"question": "Solve (720 - 190)", "answer": "The result of (720 - 190) is 530\n\n####530", "a": 720, "b": 190, "operator": "-", "result": 530}
{"question": "Solve (837 * 306)", "answer": "The result of (837 * 306) is 256122\n\n####256122", "a": 837, "b": 306, "operator": "*", "result": 256122}
{"question": "Solve (372 / 570)", "answer": "The result of (372 / 570) is 0.6526\n\n####0.6526", "a": 372, "b": 570, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6526}
{"question": "Solve (935 - 32)", "answer": "The result of (935 - 32) is 903\n\n####903", "a": 935, "b": 32, "operator": "-", "result": 903}
{"question": "Solve (63 * 344)", "answer": "The result of (63 * 344) is 21672\n\n####21672", "a": 63, "b": 344, "operator": "*", "result": 21672}
{"question": "Solve (444 - 985)", "answer": "The result of (444 - 985) is -541\n\n####-541", "a": 444, "b": 985, "operator": "-", "result": -541}
{"question": "Solve (493 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (493 / 453) is 1.0883\n\n####1.0883", "a": 493, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0883}
{"question": "Solve (543 - 380)", "answer": "The result of (543 - 380) is 163\n\n####163", "a": 543, "b": 380, "operator": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve (567 / 991)", "answer": "The result of (567 / 991) is 0.5721\n\n####0.5721", "a": 567, "b": 991, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5721}
{"question": "Solve (842 / 223)", "answer": "The result of (842 / 223) is 3.7758\n\n####3.7758", "a": 842, "b": 223, "operator": "/", "result": 3.7758}
{"question": "Solve (886 * 836)", "answer": "The result of (886 * 836) is 740696\n\n####740696", "a": 886, "b": 836, "operator": "*", "result": 740696}
{"question": "Solve (297 / 330)", "answer": "The result of (297 / 330) is 0.9\n\n####0.9", "a": 297, "b": 330, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9}
{"question": "Solve (147 / 543)", "answer": "The result of (147 / 543) is 0.2707\n\n####0.2707", "a": 147, "b": 543, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2707}
{"question": "Solve (184 * 728)", "answer": "The result of (184 * 728) is 133952\n\n####133952", "a": 184, "b": 728, "operator": "*", "result": 133952}
{"question": "Solve (589 * 522)", "answer": "The result of (589 * 522) is 307458\n\n####307458", "a": 589, "b": 522, "operator": "*", "result": 307458}
{"question": "Solve (339 * 171)", "answer": "The result of (339 * 171) is 57969\n\n####57969", "a": 339, "b": 171, "operator": "*", "result": 57969}
{"question": "Solve (130 * 249)", "answer": "The result of (130 * 249) is 32370\n\n####32370", "a": 130, "b": 249, "operator": "*", "result": 32370}
{"question": "Solve (193 / 680)", "answer": "The result of (193 / 680) is 0.2838\n\n####0.2838", "a": 193, "b": 680, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2838}
{"question": "Solve (491 + 655)", "answer": "The result of (491 + 655) is 1146\n\n####1146", "a": 491, "b": 655, "operator": "+", "result": 1146}
{"question": "Solve (535 - 369)", "answer": "The result of (535 - 369) is 166\n\n####166", "a": 535, "b": 369, "operator": "-", "result": 166}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 231)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 231) is 92\n\n####92", "a": 323, "b": 231, "operator": "-", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve (128 + 426)", "answer": "The result of (128 + 426) is 554\n\n####554", "a": 128, "b": 426, "operator": "+", "result": 554}
{"question": "Solve (99 - 283)", "answer": "The result of (99 - 283) is -184\n\n####-184", "a": 99, "b": 283, "operator": "-", "result": -184}
{"question": "Solve (603 - 87)", "answer": "The result of (603 - 87) is 516\n\n####516", "a": 603, "b": 87, "operator": "-", "result": 516}
{"question": "Solve (4 * 378)", "answer": "The result of (4 * 378) is 1512\n\n####1512", "a": 4, "b": 378, "operator": "*", "result": 1512}
{"question": "Solve (67 - 985)", "answer": "The result of (67 - 985) is -918\n\n####-918", "a": 67, "b": 985, "operator": "-", "result": -918}
{"question": "Solve (388 + 338)", "answer": "The result of (388 + 338) is 726\n\n####726", "a": 388, "b": 338, "operator": "+", "result": 726}
{"question": "Solve (261 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (261 / 504) is 0.5179\n\n####0.5179", "a": 261, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5179}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 168) is -124\n\n####-124", "a": 44, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": -124}
{"question": "Solve (503 + 286)", "answer": "The result of (503 + 286) is 789\n\n####789", "a": 503, "b": 286, "operator": "+", "result": 789}
{"question": "Solve (760 / 261)", "answer": "The result of (760 / 261) is 2.9119\n\n####2.9119", "a": 760, "b": 261, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9119}
{"question": "Solve (679 - 881)", "answer": "The result of (679 - 881) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 679, "b": 881, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (87 + 754)", "answer": "The result of (87 + 754) is 841\n\n####841", "a": 87, "b": 754, "operator": "+", "result": 841}
{"question": "Solve (965 / 553)", "answer": "The result of (965 / 553) is 1.745\n\n####1.745", "a": 965, "b": 553, "operator": "/", "result": 1.745}
{"question": "Solve (40 / 526)", "answer": "The result of (40 / 526) is 0.076\n\n####0.076", "a": 40, "b": 526, "operator": "/", "result": 0.076}
{"question": "Solve (146 - 307)", "answer": "The result of (146 - 307) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 146, "b": 307, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (914 - 124)", "answer": "The result of (914 - 124) is 790\n\n####790", "a": 914, "b": 124, "operator": "-", "result": 790}
{"question": "Solve (542 + 788)", "answer": "The result of (542 + 788) is 1330\n\n####1330", "a": 542, "b": 788, "operator": "+", "result": 1330}
{"question": "Solve (956 / 218)", "answer": "The result of (956 / 218) is 4.3853\n\n####4.3853", "a": 956, "b": 218, "operator": "/", "result": 4.3853}
{"question": "Solve (436 - 84)", "answer": "The result of (436 - 84) is 352\n\n####352", "a": 436, "b": 84, "operator": "-", "result": 352}
{"question": "Solve (34 / 630)", "answer": "The result of (34 / 630) is 0.054\n\n####0.054", "a": 34, "b": 630, "operator": "/", "result": 0.054}
{"question": "Solve (67 / 761)", "answer": "The result of (67 / 761) is 0.088\n\n####0.088", "a": 67, "b": 761, "operator": "/", "result": 0.088}
{"question": "Solve (98 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (98 - 354) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 98, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (590 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (590 - 825) is -235\n\n####-235", "a": 590, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": -235}
{"question": "Solve (56 + 381)", "answer": "The result of (56 + 381) is 437\n\n####437", "a": 56, "b": 381, "operator": "+", "result": 437}
{"question": "Solve (959 * 762)", "answer": "The result of (959 * 762) is 730758\n\n####730758", "a": 959, "b": 762, "operator": "*", "result": 730758}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 48)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 48) is 270\n\n####270", "a": 318, "b": 48, "operator": "-", "result": 270}
{"question": "Solve (530 - 163)", "answer": "The result of (530 - 163) is 367\n\n####367", "a": 530, "b": 163, "operator": "-", "result": 367}
{"question": "Solve (795 + 997)", "answer": "The result of (795 + 997) is 1792\n\n####1792", "a": 795, "b": 997, "operator": "+", "result": 1792}
{"question": "Solve (924 * 327)", "answer": "The result of (924 * 327) is 302148\n\n####302148", "a": 924, "b": 327, "operator": "*", "result": 302148}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 597)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 597) is 1.5377\n\n####1.5377", "a": 918, "b": 597, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5377}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 168)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 168) is 681\n\n####681", "a": 849, "b": 168, "operator": "-", "result": 681}
{"question": "Solve (3 * 785)", "answer": "The result of (3 * 785) is 2355\n\n####2355", "a": 3, "b": 785, "operator": "*", "result": 2355}
{"question": "Solve (604 / 719)", "answer": "The result of (604 / 719) is 0.8401\n\n####0.8401", "a": 604, "b": 719, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8401}
{"question": "Solve (799 - 145)", "answer": "The result of (799 - 145) is 654\n\n####654", "a": 799, "b": 145, "operator": "-", "result": 654}
{"question": "Solve (487 / 354)", "answer": "The result of (487 / 354) is 1.3757\n\n####1.3757", "a": 487, "b": 354, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3757}
{"question": "Solve (578 / 435)", "answer": "The result of (578 / 435) is 1.3287\n\n####1.3287", "a": 578, "b": 435, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3287}
{"question": "Solve (487 - 133)", "answer": "The result of (487 - 133) is 354\n\n####354", "a": 487, "b": 133, "operator": "-", "result": 354}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 748)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 748) is 2\n\n####2", "a": 750, "b": 748, "operator": "-", "result": 2}
{"question": "Solve (261 * 152)", "answer": "The result of (261 * 152) is 39672\n\n####39672", "a": 261, "b": 152, "operator": "*", "result": 39672}
{"question": "Solve (254 - 604)", "answer": "The result of (254 - 604) is -350\n\n####-350", "a": 254, "b": 604, "operator": "-", "result": -350}
{"question": "Solve (31 + 912)", "answer": "The result of (31 + 912) is 943\n\n####943", "a": 31, "b": 912, "operator": "+", "result": 943}
{"question": "Solve (196 + 493)", "answer": "The result of (196 + 493) is 689\n\n####689", "a": 196, "b": 493, "operator": "+", "result": 689}
{"question": "Solve (982 * 828)", "answer": "The result of (982 * 828) is 813096\n\n####813096", "a": 982, "b": 828, "operator": "*", "result": 813096}
{"question": "Solve (716 / 87)", "answer": "The result of (716 / 87) is 8.2299\n\n####8.2299", "a": 716, "b": 87, "operator": "/", "result": 8.2299}
{"question": "Solve (491 / 543)", "answer": "The result of (491 / 543) is 0.9042\n\n####0.9042", "a": 491, "b": 543, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9042}
{"question": "Solve (846 - 928)", "answer": "The result of (846 - 928) is -82\n\n####-82", "a": 846, "b": 928, "operator": "-", "result": -82}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 589)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 589) is 411122\n\n####411122", "a": 698, "b": 589, "operator": "*", "result": 411122}
{"question": "Solve (206 * 13)", "answer": "The result of (206 * 13) is 2678\n\n####2678", "a": 206, "b": 13, "operator": "*", "result": 2678}
{"question": "Solve (266 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (266 * 698) is 185668\n\n####185668", "a": 266, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 185668}
{"question": "Solve (252 + 160)", "answer": "The result of (252 + 160) is 412\n\n####412", "a": 252, "b": 160, "operator": "+", "result": 412}
{"question": "Solve (402 + 847)", "answer": "The result of (402 + 847) is 1249\n\n####1249", "a": 402, "b": 847, "operator": "+", "result": 1249}
{"question": "Solve (831 - 610)", "answer": "The result of (831 - 610) is 221\n\n####221", "a": 831, "b": 610, "operator": "-", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve (270 / 541)", "answer": "The result of (270 / 541) is 0.4991\n\n####0.4991", "a": 270, "b": 541, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4991}
{"question": "Solve (664 / 317)", "answer": "The result of (664 / 317) is 2.0946\n\n####2.0946", "a": 664, "b": 317, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0946}
{"question": "Solve (796 + 408)", "answer": "The result of (796 + 408) is 1204\n\n####1204", "a": 796, "b": 408, "operator": "+", "result": 1204}
{"question": "Solve (338 / 253)", "answer": "The result of (338 / 253) is 1.336\n\n####1.336", "a": 338, "b": 253, "operator": "/", "result": 1.336}
{"question": "Solve (33 / 317)", "answer": "The result of (33 / 317) is 0.1041\n\n####0.1041", "a": 33, "b": 317, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1041}
{"question": "Solve (323 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (323 * 215) is 69445\n\n####69445", "a": 323, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 69445}
{"question": "Solve (844 / 524)", "answer": "The result of (844 / 524) is 1.6107\n\n####1.6107", "a": 844, "b": 524, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6107}
{"question": "Solve (356 / 978)", "answer": "The result of (356 / 978) is 0.364\n\n####0.364", "a": 356, "b": 978, "operator": "/", "result": 0.364}
{"question": "Solve (753 * 439)", "answer": "The result of (753 * 439) is 330567\n\n####330567", "a": 753, "b": 439, "operator": "*", "result": 330567}
{"question": "Solve (776 / 921)", "answer": "The result of (776 / 921) is 0.8426\n\n####0.8426", "a": 776, "b": 921, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8426}
{"question": "Solve (975 * 47)", "answer": "The result of (975 * 47) is 45825\n\n####45825", "a": 975, "b": 47, "operator": "*", "result": 45825}
{"question": "Solve (37 - 756)", "answer": "The result of (37 - 756) is -719\n\n####-719", "a": 37, "b": 756, "operator": "-", "result": -719}
{"question": "Solve (810 + 907)", "answer": "The result of (810 + 907) is 1717\n\n####1717", "a": 810, "b": 907, "operator": "+", "result": 1717}
{"question": "Solve (408 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (408 - 358) is 50\n\n####50", "a": 408, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 50}
{"question": "Solve (561 + 971)", "answer": "The result of (561 + 971) is 1532\n\n####1532", "a": 561, "b": 971, "operator": "+", "result": 1532}
{"question": "Solve (41 * 699)", "answer": "The result of (41 * 699) is 28659\n\n####28659", "a": 41, "b": 699, "operator": "*", "result": 28659}
{"question": "Solve (5 + 879)", "answer": "The result of (5 + 879) is 884\n\n####884", "a": 5, "b": 879, "operator": "+", "result": 884}
{"question": "Solve (336 - 906)", "answer": "The result of (336 - 906) is -570\n\n####-570", "a": 336, "b": 906, "operator": "-", "result": -570}
{"question": "Solve (673 + 273)", "answer": "The result of (673 + 273) is 946\n\n####946", "a": 673, "b": 273, "operator": "+", "result": 946}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 862)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 862) is -421\n\n####-421", "a": 441, "b": 862, "operator": "-", "result": -421}
{"question": "Solve (37 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (37 - 276) is -239\n\n####-239", "a": 37, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": -239}
{"question": "Solve (946 / 603)", "answer": "The result of (946 / 603) is 1.5688\n\n####1.5688", "a": 946, "b": 603, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5688}
{"question": "Solve (338 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (338 * 251) is 84838\n\n####84838", "a": 338, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 84838}
{"question": "Solve (401 * 402)", "answer": "The result of (401 * 402) is 161202\n\n####161202", "a": 401, "b": 402, "operator": "*", "result": 161202}
{"question": "Solve (937 + 304)", "answer": "The result of (937 + 304) is 1241\n\n####1241", "a": 937, "b": 304, "operator": "+", "result": 1241}
{"question": "Solve (721 / 721)", "answer": "The result of (721 / 721) is 1.0\n\n####1.0", "a": 721, "b": 721, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0}
{"question": "Solve (823 + 55)", "answer": "The result of (823 + 55) is 878\n\n####878", "a": 823, "b": 55, "operator": "+", "result": 878}
{"question": "Solve (322 - 939)", "answer": "The result of (322 - 939) is -617\n\n####-617", "a": 322, "b": 939, "operator": "-", "result": -617}
{"question": "Solve (228 / 868)", "answer": "The result of (228 / 868) is 0.2627\n\n####0.2627", "a": 228, "b": 868, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2627}
{"question": "Solve (127 * 402)", "answer": "The result of (127 * 402) is 51054\n\n####51054", "a": 127, "b": 402, "operator": "*", "result": 51054}
{"question": "Solve (84 - 782)", "answer": "The result of (84 - 782) is -698\n\n####-698", "a": 84, "b": 782, "operator": "-", "result": -698}
{"question": "Solve (728 + 690)", "answer": "The result of (728 + 690) is 1418\n\n####1418", "a": 728, "b": 690, "operator": "+", "result": 1418}
{"question": "Solve (426 - 705)", "answer": "The result of (426 - 705) is -279\n\n####-279", "a": 426, "b": 705, "operator": "-", "result": -279}
{"question": "Solve (455 - 334)", "answer": "The result of (455 - 334) is 121\n\n####121", "a": 455, "b": 334, "operator": "-", "result": 121}
{"question": "Solve (306 - 606)", "answer": "The result of (306 - 606) is -300\n\n####-300", "a": 306, "b": 606, "operator": "-", "result": -300}
{"question": "Solve (758 - 957)", "answer": "The result of (758 - 957) is -199\n\n####-199", "a": 758, "b": 957, "operator": "-", "result": -199}
{"question": "Solve (564 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (564 - 933) is -369\n\n####-369", "a": 564, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -369}
{"question": "Solve (290 + 802)", "answer": "The result of (290 + 802) is 1092\n\n####1092", "a": 290, "b": 802, "operator": "+", "result": 1092}
{"question": "Solve (762 - 526)", "answer": "The result of (762 - 526) is 236\n\n####236", "a": 762, "b": 526, "operator": "-", "result": 236}
{"question": "Solve (688 / 731)", "answer": "The result of (688 / 731) is 0.9412\n\n####0.9412", "a": 688, "b": 731, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9412}
{"question": "Solve (222 / 950)", "answer": "The result of (222 / 950) is 0.2337\n\n####0.2337", "a": 222, "b": 950, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2337}
{"question": "Solve (337 / 652)", "answer": "The result of (337 / 652) is 0.5169\n\n####0.5169", "a": 337, "b": 652, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5169}
{"question": "Solve (708 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (708 - 567) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 708, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (402 + 118)", "answer": "The result of (402 + 118) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 402, "b": 118, "operator": "+", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (804 / 415)", "answer": "The result of (804 / 415) is 1.9373\n\n####1.9373", "a": 804, "b": 415, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9373}
{"question": "Solve (619 + 956)", "answer": "The result of (619 + 956) is 1575\n\n####1575", "a": 619, "b": 956, "operator": "+", "result": 1575}
{"question": "Solve (814 - 542)", "answer": "The result of (814 - 542) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 814, "b": 542, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (649 - 626)", "answer": "The result of (649 - 626) is 23\n\n####23", "a": 649, "b": 626, "operator": "-", "result": 23}
{"question": "Solve (121 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (121 - 700) is -579\n\n####-579", "a": 121, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -579}
{"question": "Solve (477 - 193)", "answer": "The result of (477 - 193) is 284\n\n####284", "a": 477, "b": 193, "operator": "-", "result": 284}
{"question": "Solve (87 / 929)", "answer": "The result of (87 / 929) is 0.0936\n\n####0.0936", "a": 87, "b": 929, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0936}
{"question": "Solve (389 + 175)", "answer": "The result of (389 + 175) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 389, "b": 175, "operator": "+", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (905 / 50)", "answer": "The result of (905 / 50) is 18.1\n\n####18.1", "a": 905, "b": 50, "operator": "/", "result": 18.1}
{"question": "Solve (261 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (261 * 884) is 230724\n\n####230724", "a": 261, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 230724}
{"question": "Solve (75 * 838)", "answer": "The result of (75 * 838) is 62850\n\n####62850", "a": 75, "b": 838, "operator": "*", "result": 62850}
{"question": "Solve (679 * 903)", "answer": "The result of (679 * 903) is 613137\n\n####613137", "a": 679, "b": 903, "operator": "*", "result": 613137}
{"question": "Solve (774 * 260)", "answer": "The result of (774 * 260) is 201240\n\n####201240", "a": 774, "b": 260, "operator": "*", "result": 201240}
{"question": "Solve (513 - 727)", "answer": "The result of (513 - 727) is -214\n\n####-214", "a": 513, "b": 727, "operator": "-", "result": -214}
{"question": "Solve (892 - 422)", "answer": "The result of (892 - 422) is 470\n\n####470", "a": 892, "b": 422, "operator": "-", "result": 470}
{"question": "Solve (867 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (867 - 547) is 320\n\n####320", "a": 867, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": 320}
{"question": "Solve (101 * 262)", "answer": "The result of (101 * 262) is 26462\n\n####26462", "a": 101, "b": 262, "operator": "*", "result": 26462}
{"question": "Solve (970 + 214)", "answer": "The result of (970 + 214) is 1184\n\n####1184", "a": 970, "b": 214, "operator": "+", "result": 1184}
{"question": "Solve (419 / 587)", "answer": "The result of (419 / 587) is 0.7138\n\n####0.7138", "a": 419, "b": 587, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7138}
{"question": "Solve (538 + 844)", "answer": "The result of (538 + 844) is 1382\n\n####1382", "a": 538, "b": 844, "operator": "+", "result": 1382}
{"question": "Solve (53 - 717)", "answer": "The result of (53 - 717) is -664\n\n####-664", "a": 53, "b": 717, "operator": "-", "result": -664}
{"question": "Solve (44 + 46)", "answer": "The result of (44 + 46) is 90\n\n####90", "a": 44, "b": 46, "operator": "+", "result": 90}
{"question": "Solve (926 / 78)", "answer": "The result of (926 / 78) is 11.8718\n\n####11.8718", "a": 926, "b": 78, "operator": "/", "result": 11.8718}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 756)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 756) is 468720\n\n####468720", "a": 620, "b": 756, "operator": "*", "result": 468720}
{"question": "Solve (838 * 34)", "answer": "The result of (838 * 34) is 28492\n\n####28492", "a": 838, "b": 34, "operator": "*", "result": 28492}
{"question": "Solve (417 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (417 - 706) is -289\n\n####-289", "a": 417, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -289}
{"question": "Solve (948 - 374)", "answer": "The result of (948 - 374) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 948, "b": 374, "operator": "-", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (979 - 401)", "answer": "The result of (979 - 401) is 578\n\n####578", "a": 979, "b": 401, "operator": "-", "result": 578}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 127)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 127) is 670\n\n####670", "a": 797, "b": 127, "operator": "-", "result": 670}
{"question": "Solve (38 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (38 / 453) is 0.0839\n\n####0.0839", "a": 38, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0839}
{"question": "Solve (427 - 857)", "answer": "The result of (427 - 857) is -430\n\n####-430", "a": 427, "b": 857, "operator": "-", "result": -430}
{"question": "Solve (817 * 256)", "answer": "The result of (817 * 256) is 209152\n\n####209152", "a": 817, "b": 256, "operator": "*", "result": 209152}
{"question": "Solve (125 - 412)", "answer": "The result of (125 - 412) is -287\n\n####-287", "a": 125, "b": 412, "operator": "-", "result": -287}
{"question": "Solve (909 / 410)", "answer": "The result of (909 / 410) is 2.2171\n\n####2.2171", "a": 909, "b": 410, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2171}
{"question": "Solve (100 + 51)", "answer": "The result of (100 + 51) is 151\n\n####151", "a": 100, "b": 51, "operator": "+", "result": 151}
{"question": "Solve (54 + 161)", "answer": "The result of (54 + 161) is 215\n\n####215", "a": 54, "b": 161, "operator": "+", "result": 215}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 50)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 50) is 917\n\n####917", "a": 867, "b": 50, "operator": "+", "result": 917}
{"question": "Solve (832 - 983)", "answer": "The result of (832 - 983) is -151\n\n####-151", "a": 832, "b": 983, "operator": "-", "result": -151}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 453)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 453) is 1280\n\n####1280", "a": 827, "b": 453, "operator": "+", "result": 1280}
{"question": "Solve (773 / 439)", "answer": "The result of (773 / 439) is 1.7608\n\n####1.7608", "a": 773, "b": 439, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7608}
{"question": "Solve (918 - 344)", "answer": "The result of (918 - 344) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 918, "b": 344, "operator": "-", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (71 * 505)", "answer": "The result of (71 * 505) is 35855\n\n####35855", "a": 71, "b": 505, "operator": "*", "result": 35855}
{"question": "Solve (600 + 492)", "answer": "The result of (600 + 492) is 1092\n\n####1092", "a": 600, "b": 492, "operator": "+", "result": 1092}
{"question": "Solve (417 + 867)", "answer": "The result of (417 + 867) is 1284\n\n####1284", "a": 417, "b": 867, "operator": "+", "result": 1284}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 675)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 675) is -458\n\n####-458", "a": 217, "b": 675, "operator": "-", "result": -458}
{"question": "Solve (86 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (86 / 390) is 0.2205\n\n####0.2205", "a": 86, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2205}
{"question": "Solve (659 / 181)", "answer": "The result of (659 / 181) is 3.6409\n\n####3.6409", "a": 659, "b": 181, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6409}
{"question": "Solve (466 - 664)", "answer": "The result of (466 - 664) is -198\n\n####-198", "a": 466, "b": 664, "operator": "-", "result": -198}
{"question": "Solve (108 - 86)", "answer": "The result of (108 - 86) is 22\n\n####22", "a": 108, "b": 86, "operator": "-", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve (296 / 876)", "answer": "The result of (296 / 876) is 0.3379\n\n####0.3379", "a": 296, "b": 876, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3379}
{"question": "Solve (768 * 64)", "answer": "The result of (768 * 64) is 49152\n\n####49152", "a": 768, "b": 64, "operator": "*", "result": 49152}
{"question": "Solve (329 - 744)", "answer": "The result of (329 - 744) is -415\n\n####-415", "a": 329, "b": 744, "operator": "-", "result": -415}
{"question": "Solve (882 / 740)", "answer": "The result of (882 / 740) is 1.1919\n\n####1.1919", "a": 882, "b": 740, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1919}
{"question": "Solve (880 * 615)", "answer": "The result of (880 * 615) is 541200\n\n####541200", "a": 880, "b": 615, "operator": "*", "result": 541200}
{"question": "Solve (619 - 160)", "answer": "The result of (619 - 160) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 619, "b": 160, "operator": "-", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (399 * 378)", "answer": "The result of (399 * 378) is 150822\n\n####150822", "a": 399, "b": 378, "operator": "*", "result": 150822}
{"question": "Solve (847 * 308)", "answer": "The result of (847 * 308) is 260876\n\n####260876", "a": 847, "b": 308, "operator": "*", "result": 260876}
{"question": "Solve (699 - 639)", "answer": "The result of (699 - 639) is 60\n\n####60", "a": 699, "b": 639, "operator": "-", "result": 60}
{"question": "Solve (911 * 867)", "answer": "The result of (911 * 867) is 789837\n\n####789837", "a": 911, "b": 867, "operator": "*", "result": 789837}
{"question": "Solve (826 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (826 - 452) is 374\n\n####374", "a": 826, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": 374}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 3)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 3) is 190\n\n####190", "a": 193, "b": 3, "operator": "-", "result": 190}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 180)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 180) is 77\n\n####77", "a": 257, "b": 180, "operator": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve (237 / 84)", "answer": "The result of (237 / 84) is 2.8214\n\n####2.8214", "a": 237, "b": 84, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8214}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 823)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 823) is 1.1312\n\n####1.1312", "a": 931, "b": 823, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1312}
{"question": "Solve (270 + 249)", "answer": "The result of (270 + 249) is 519\n\n####519", "a": 270, "b": 249, "operator": "+", "result": 519}
{"question": "Solve (9 / 146)", "answer": "The result of (9 / 146) is 0.0616\n\n####0.0616", "a": 9, "b": 146, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0616}
{"question": "Solve (742 + 399)", "answer": "The result of (742 + 399) is 1141\n\n####1141", "a": 742, "b": 399, "operator": "+", "result": 1141}
{"question": "Solve (68 / 280)", "answer": "The result of (68 / 280) is 0.2429\n\n####0.2429", "a": 68, "b": 280, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2429}
{"question": "Solve (775 * 744)", "answer": "The result of (775 * 744) is 576600\n\n####576600", "a": 775, "b": 744, "operator": "*", "result": 576600}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 617)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 617) is -187\n\n####-187", "a": 430, "b": 617, "operator": "-", "result": -187}
{"question": "Solve (190 - 449)", "answer": "The result of (190 - 449) is -259\n\n####-259", "a": 190, "b": 449, "operator": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve (914 - 179)", "answer": "The result of (914 - 179) is 735\n\n####735", "a": 914, "b": 179, "operator": "-", "result": 735}
{"question": "Solve (92 - 301)", "answer": "The result of (92 - 301) is -209\n\n####-209", "a": 92, "b": 301, "operator": "-", "result": -209}
{"question": "Solve (782 - 814)", "answer": "The result of (782 - 814) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 782, "b": 814, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 15)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 15) is 692\n\n####692", "a": 677, "b": 15, "operator": "+", "result": 692}
{"question": "Solve (702 + 899)", "answer": "The result of (702 + 899) is 1601\n\n####1601", "a": 702, "b": 899, "operator": "+", "result": 1601}
{"question": "Solve (788 - 590)", "answer": "The result of (788 - 590) is 198\n\n####198", "a": 788, "b": 590, "operator": "-", "result": 198}
{"question": "Solve (234 / 574)", "answer": "The result of (234 / 574) is 0.4077\n\n####0.4077", "a": 234, "b": 574, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4077}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 668)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 668) is 0.8338\n\n####0.8338", "a": 557, "b": 668, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8338}
{"question": "Solve (863 + 287)", "answer": "The result of (863 + 287) is 1150\n\n####1150", "a": 863, "b": 287, "operator": "+", "result": 1150}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 977)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 977) is 676084\n\n####676084", "a": 692, "b": 977, "operator": "*", "result": 676084}
{"question": "Solve (689 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (689 / 504) is 1.3671\n\n####1.3671", "a": 689, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3671}
{"question": "Solve (660 - 750)", "answer": "The result of (660 - 750) is -90\n\n####-90", "a": 660, "b": 750, "operator": "-", "result": -90}
{"question": "Solve (966 / 841)", "answer": "The result of (966 / 841) is 1.1486\n\n####1.1486", "a": 966, "b": 841, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1486}
{"question": "Solve (855 + 249)", "answer": "The result of (855 + 249) is 1104\n\n####1104", "a": 855, "b": 249, "operator": "+", "result": 1104}
{"question": "Solve (878 + 66)", "answer": "The result of (878 + 66) is 944\n\n####944", "a": 878, "b": 66, "operator": "+", "result": 944}
{"question": "Solve (404 - 440)", "answer": "The result of (404 - 440) is -36\n\n####-36", "a": 404, "b": 440, "operator": "-", "result": -36}
{"question": "Solve (858 / 924)", "answer": "The result of (858 / 924) is 0.9286\n\n####0.9286", "a": 858, "b": 924, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9286}
{"question": "Solve (899 * 110)", "answer": "The result of (899 * 110) is 98890\n\n####98890", "a": 899, "b": 110, "operator": "*", "result": 98890}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 48)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 48) is 405\n\n####405", "a": 453, "b": 48, "operator": "-", "result": 405}
{"question": "Solve (562 / 444)", "answer": "The result of (562 / 444) is 1.2658\n\n####1.2658", "a": 562, "b": 444, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2658}
{"question": "Solve (109 * 688)", "answer": "The result of (109 * 688) is 74992\n\n####74992", "a": 109, "b": 688, "operator": "*", "result": 74992}
{"question": "Solve (938 + 487)", "answer": "The result of (938 + 487) is 1425\n\n####1425", "a": 938, "b": 487, "operator": "+", "result": 1425}
{"question": "Solve (792 / 139)", "answer": "The result of (792 / 139) is 5.6978\n\n####5.6978", "a": 792, "b": 139, "operator": "/", "result": 5.6978}
{"question": "Solve (794 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (794 * 145) is 115130\n\n####115130", "a": 794, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 115130}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 933)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 933) is -441\n\n####-441", "a": 492, "b": 933, "operator": "-", "result": -441}
{"question": "Solve (894 * 29)", "answer": "The result of (894 * 29) is 25926\n\n####25926", "a": 894, "b": 29, "operator": "*", "result": 25926}
{"question": "Solve (411 * 165)", "answer": "The result of (411 * 165) is 67815\n\n####67815", "a": 411, "b": 165, "operator": "*", "result": 67815}
{"question": "Solve (38 + 245)", "answer": "The result of (38 + 245) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 38, "b": 245, "operator": "+", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (41 * 775)", "answer": "The result of (41 * 775) is 31775\n\n####31775", "a": 41, "b": 775, "operator": "*", "result": 31775}
{"question": "Solve (967 / 726)", "answer": "The result of (967 / 726) is 1.332\n\n####1.332", "a": 967, "b": 726, "operator": "/", "result": 1.332}
{"question": "Solve (412 + 881)", "answer": "The result of (412 + 881) is 1293\n\n####1293", "a": 412, "b": 881, "operator": "+", "result": 1293}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 227)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 227) is 488\n\n####488", "a": 715, "b": 227, "operator": "-", "result": 488}
{"question": "Solve (159 - 651)", "answer": "The result of (159 - 651) is -492\n\n####-492", "a": 159, "b": 651, "operator": "-", "result": -492}
{"question": "Solve (998 + 599)", "answer": "The result of (998 + 599) is 1597\n\n####1597", "a": 998, "b": 599, "operator": "+", "result": 1597}
{"question": "Solve (132 + 837)", "answer": "The result of (132 + 837) is 969\n\n####969", "a": 132, "b": 837, "operator": "+", "result": 969}
{"question": "Solve (140 / 394)", "answer": "The result of (140 / 394) is 0.3553\n\n####0.3553", "a": 140, "b": 394, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3553}
{"question": "Solve (102 - 659)", "answer": "The result of (102 - 659) is -557\n\n####-557", "a": 102, "b": 659, "operator": "-", "result": -557}
{"question": "Solve (443 / 776)", "answer": "The result of (443 / 776) is 0.5709\n\n####0.5709", "a": 443, "b": 776, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5709}
{"question": "Solve (210 - 790)", "answer": "The result of (210 - 790) is -580\n\n####-580", "a": 210, "b": 790, "operator": "-", "result": -580}
{"question": "Solve (592 * 286)", "answer": "The result of (592 * 286) is 169312\n\n####169312", "a": 592, "b": 286, "operator": "*", "result": 169312}
{"question": "Solve (176 + 772)", "answer": "The result of (176 + 772) is 948\n\n####948", "a": 176, "b": 772, "operator": "+", "result": 948}
{"question": "Solve (634 - 888)", "answer": "The result of (634 - 888) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 634, "b": 888, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (196 * 485)", "answer": "The result of (196 * 485) is 95060\n\n####95060", "a": 196, "b": 485, "operator": "*", "result": 95060}
{"question": "Solve (217 / 389)", "answer": "The result of (217 / 389) is 0.5578\n\n####0.5578", "a": 217, "b": 389, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5578}
{"question": "Solve (469 * 377)", "answer": "The result of (469 * 377) is 176813\n\n####176813", "a": 469, "b": 377, "operator": "*", "result": 176813}
{"question": "Solve (178 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (178 - 431) is -253\n\n####-253", "a": 178, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": -253}
{"question": "Solve (660 * 821)", "answer": "The result of (660 * 821) is 541860\n\n####541860", "a": 660, "b": 821, "operator": "*", "result": 541860}
{"question": "Solve (507 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (507 + 239) is 746\n\n####746", "a": 507, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 746}
{"question": "Solve (987 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (987 - 724) is 263\n\n####263", "a": 987, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve (84 / 861)", "answer": "The result of (84 / 861) is 0.0976\n\n####0.0976", "a": 84, "b": 861, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0976}
{"question": "Solve (639 - 425)", "answer": "The result of (639 - 425) is 214\n\n####214", "a": 639, "b": 425, "operator": "-", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve (65 + 392)", "answer": "The result of (65 + 392) is 457\n\n####457", "a": 65, "b": 392, "operator": "+", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve (225 - 624)", "answer": "The result of (225 - 624) is -399\n\n####-399", "a": 225, "b": 624, "operator": "-", "result": -399}
{"question": "Solve (374 + 874)", "answer": "The result of (374 + 874) is 1248\n\n####1248", "a": 374, "b": 874, "operator": "+", "result": 1248}
{"question": "Solve (572 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (572 / 289) is 1.9792\n\n####1.9792", "a": 572, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9792}
{"question": "Solve (382 / 45)", "answer": "The result of (382 / 45) is 8.4889\n\n####8.4889", "a": 382, "b": 45, "operator": "/", "result": 8.4889}
{"question": "Solve (407 / 856)", "answer": "The result of (407 / 856) is 0.4755\n\n####0.4755", "a": 407, "b": 856, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4755}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 173)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 173) is -66\n\n####-66", "a": 107, "b": 173, "operator": "-", "result": -66}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 662)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 662) is 299224\n\n####299224", "a": 452, "b": 662, "operator": "*", "result": 299224}
{"question": "Solve (756 / 144)", "answer": "The result of (756 / 144) is 5.25\n\n####5.25", "a": 756, "b": 144, "operator": "/", "result": 5.25}
{"question": "Solve (554 / 631)", "answer": "The result of (554 / 631) is 0.878\n\n####0.878", "a": 554, "b": 631, "operator": "/", "result": 0.878}
{"question": "Solve (653 / 470)", "answer": "The result of (653 / 470) is 1.3894\n\n####1.3894", "a": 653, "b": 470, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3894}
{"question": "Solve (311 / 442)", "answer": "The result of (311 / 442) is 0.7036\n\n####0.7036", "a": 311, "b": 442, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7036}
{"question": "Solve (670 - 264)", "answer": "The result of (670 - 264) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 670, "b": 264, "operator": "-", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (908 + 708)", "answer": "The result of (908 + 708) is 1616\n\n####1616", "a": 908, "b": 708, "operator": "+", "result": 1616}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 299) is 0.9766\n\n####0.9766", "a": 292, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9766}
{"question": "Solve (864 - 416)", "answer": "The result of (864 - 416) is 448\n\n####448", "a": 864, "b": 416, "operator": "-", "result": 448}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 233)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 233) is 161236\n\n####161236", "a": 692, "b": 233, "operator": "*", "result": 161236}
{"question": "Solve (462 - 101)", "answer": "The result of (462 - 101) is 361\n\n####361", "a": 462, "b": 101, "operator": "-", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve (249 * 260)", "answer": "The result of (249 * 260) is 64740\n\n####64740", "a": 249, "b": 260, "operator": "*", "result": 64740}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 538)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 538) is 1.2955\n\n####1.2955", "a": 697, "b": 538, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2955}
{"question": "Solve (306 + 368)", "answer": "The result of (306 + 368) is 674\n\n####674", "a": 306, "b": 368, "operator": "+", "result": 674}
{"question": "Solve (453 * 221)", "answer": "The result of (453 * 221) is 100113\n\n####100113", "a": 453, "b": 221, "operator": "*", "result": 100113}
{"question": "Solve (78 - 427)", "answer": "The result of (78 - 427) is -349\n\n####-349", "a": 78, "b": 427, "operator": "-", "result": -349}
{"question": "Solve (512 / 545)", "answer": "The result of (512 / 545) is 0.9394\n\n####0.9394", "a": 512, "b": 545, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9394}
{"question": "Solve (794 * 350)", "answer": "The result of (794 * 350) is 277900\n\n####277900", "a": 794, "b": 350, "operator": "*", "result": 277900}
{"question": "Solve (739 - 582)", "answer": "The result of (739 - 582) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 739, "b": 582, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 143)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 143) is 61\n\n####61", "a": 204, "b": 143, "operator": "-", "result": 61}
{"question": "Solve (34 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (34 / 768) is 0.0443\n\n####0.0443", "a": 34, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0443}
{"question": "Solve (864 + 850)", "answer": "The result of (864 + 850) is 1714\n\n####1714", "a": 864, "b": 850, "operator": "+", "result": 1714}
{"question": "Solve (973 / 565)", "answer": "The result of (973 / 565) is 1.7221\n\n####1.7221", "a": 973, "b": 565, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7221}
{"question": "Solve (655 + 557)", "answer": "The result of (655 + 557) is 1212\n\n####1212", "a": 655, "b": 557, "operator": "+", "result": 1212}
{"question": "Solve (395 - 380)", "answer": "The result of (395 - 380) is 15\n\n####15", "a": 395, "b": 380, "operator": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve (647 + 624)", "answer": "The result of (647 + 624) is 1271\n\n####1271", "a": 647, "b": 624, "operator": "+", "result": 1271}
{"question": "Solve (116 / 671)", "answer": "The result of (116 / 671) is 0.1729\n\n####0.1729", "a": 116, "b": 671, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1729}
{"question": "Solve (799 / 18)", "answer": "The result of (799 / 18) is 44.3889\n\n####44.3889", "a": 799, "b": 18, "operator": "/", "result": 44.3889}
{"question": "Solve (373 - 855)", "answer": "The result of (373 - 855) is -482\n\n####-482", "a": 373, "b": 855, "operator": "-", "result": -482}
{"question": "Solve (431 / 252)", "answer": "The result of (431 / 252) is 1.7103\n\n####1.7103", "a": 431, "b": 252, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7103}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 294)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 294) is 1.8435\n\n####1.8435", "a": 542, "b": 294, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8435}
{"question": "Solve (652 * 203)", "answer": "The result of (652 * 203) is 132356\n\n####132356", "a": 652, "b": 203, "operator": "*", "result": 132356}
{"question": "Solve (549 - 979)", "answer": "The result of (549 - 979) is -430\n\n####-430", "a": 549, "b": 979, "operator": "-", "result": -430}
{"question": "Solve (224 + 194)", "answer": "The result of (224 + 194) is 418\n\n####418", "a": 224, "b": 194, "operator": "+", "result": 418}
{"question": "Solve (541 - 299)", "answer": "The result of (541 - 299) is 242\n\n####242", "a": 541, "b": 299, "operator": "-", "result": 242}
{"question": "Solve (662 + 483)", "answer": "The result of (662 + 483) is 1145\n\n####1145", "a": 662, "b": 483, "operator": "+", "result": 1145}
{"question": "Solve (485 - 646)", "answer": "The result of (485 - 646) is -161\n\n####-161", "a": 485, "b": 646, "operator": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve (88 + 81)", "answer": "The result of (88 + 81) is 169\n\n####169", "a": 88, "b": 81, "operator": "+", "result": 169}
{"question": "Solve (160 / 311)", "answer": "The result of (160 / 311) is 0.5145\n\n####0.5145", "a": 160, "b": 311, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5145}
{"question": "Solve (480 * 493)", "answer": "The result of (480 * 493) is 236640\n\n####236640", "a": 480, "b": 493, "operator": "*", "result": 236640}
{"question": "Solve (916 - 687)", "answer": "The result of (916 - 687) is 229\n\n####229", "a": 916, "b": 687, "operator": "-", "result": 229}
{"question": "Solve (743 * 593)", "answer": "The result of (743 * 593) is 440599\n\n####440599", "a": 743, "b": 593, "operator": "*", "result": 440599}
{"question": "Solve (257 - 794)", "answer": "The result of (257 - 794) is -537\n\n####-537", "a": 257, "b": 794, "operator": "-", "result": -537}
{"question": "Solve (451 - 641)", "answer": "The result of (451 - 641) is -190\n\n####-190", "a": 451, "b": 641, "operator": "-", "result": -190}
{"question": "Solve (662 / 422)", "answer": "The result of (662 / 422) is 1.5687\n\n####1.5687", "a": 662, "b": 422, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5687}
{"question": "Solve (796 * 283)", "answer": "The result of (796 * 283) is 225268\n\n####225268", "a": 796, "b": 283, "operator": "*", "result": 225268}
{"question": "Solve (976 / 306)", "answer": "The result of (976 / 306) is 3.1895\n\n####3.1895", "a": 976, "b": 306, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1895}
{"question": "Solve (866 + 846)", "answer": "The result of (866 + 846) is 1712\n\n####1712", "a": 866, "b": 846, "operator": "+", "result": 1712}
{"question": "Solve (990 - 453)", "answer": "The result of (990 - 453) is 537\n\n####537", "a": 990, "b": 453, "operator": "-", "result": 537}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 186)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 186) is 4.9462\n\n####4.9462", "a": 920, "b": 186, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9462}
{"question": "Solve (638 + 241)", "answer": "The result of (638 + 241) is 879\n\n####879", "a": 638, "b": 241, "operator": "+", "result": 879}
{"question": "Solve (190 / 687)", "answer": "The result of (190 / 687) is 0.2766\n\n####0.2766", "a": 190, "b": 687, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2766}
{"question": "Solve (77 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (77 - 992) is -915\n\n####-915", "a": 77, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -915}
{"question": "Solve (600 - 458)", "answer": "The result of (600 - 458) is 142\n\n####142", "a": 600, "b": 458, "operator": "-", "result": 142}
{"question": "Solve (762 + 16)", "answer": "The result of (762 + 16) is 778\n\n####778", "a": 762, "b": 16, "operator": "+", "result": 778}
{"question": "Solve (324 - 186)", "answer": "The result of (324 - 186) is 138\n\n####138", "a": 324, "b": 186, "operator": "-", "result": 138}
{"question": "Solve (558 * 335)", "answer": "The result of (558 * 335) is 186930\n\n####186930", "a": 558, "b": 335, "operator": "*", "result": 186930}
{"question": "Solve (164 - 222)", "answer": "The result of (164 - 222) is -58\n\n####-58", "a": 164, "b": 222, "operator": "-", "result": -58}
{"question": "Solve (162 - 259)", "answer": "The result of (162 - 259) is -97\n\n####-97", "a": 162, "b": 259, "operator": "-", "result": -97}
{"question": "Solve (926 + 54)", "answer": "The result of (926 + 54) is 980\n\n####980", "a": 926, "b": 54, "operator": "+", "result": 980}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 290) is 7\n\n####7", "a": 297, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve (94 + 766)", "answer": "The result of (94 + 766) is 860\n\n####860", "a": 94, "b": 766, "operator": "+", "result": 860}
{"question": "Solve (916 + 404)", "answer": "The result of (916 + 404) is 1320\n\n####1320", "a": 916, "b": 404, "operator": "+", "result": 1320}
{"question": "Solve (871 + 187)", "answer": "The result of (871 + 187) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 871, "b": 187, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (21 * 628)", "answer": "The result of (21 * 628) is 13188\n\n####13188", "a": 21, "b": 628, "operator": "*", "result": 13188}
{"question": "Solve (591 / 175)", "answer": "The result of (591 / 175) is 3.3771\n\n####3.3771", "a": 591, "b": 175, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3771}
{"question": "Solve (684 - 386)", "answer": "The result of (684 - 386) is 298\n\n####298", "a": 684, "b": 386, "operator": "-", "result": 298}
{"question": "Solve (91 - 966)", "answer": "The result of (91 - 966) is -875\n\n####-875", "a": 91, "b": 966, "operator": "-", "result": -875}
{"question": "Solve (237 + 738)", "answer": "The result of (237 + 738) is 975\n\n####975", "a": 237, "b": 738, "operator": "+", "result": 975}
{"question": "Solve (335 - 408)", "answer": "The result of (335 - 408) is -73\n\n####-73", "a": 335, "b": 408, "operator": "-", "result": -73}
{"question": "Solve (270 / 455)", "answer": "The result of (270 / 455) is 0.5934\n\n####0.5934", "a": 270, "b": 455, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5934}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 410)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 410) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 654, "b": 410, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (545 * 42)", "answer": "The result of (545 * 42) is 22890\n\n####22890", "a": 545, "b": 42, "operator": "*", "result": 22890}
{"question": "Solve (741 - 564)", "answer": "The result of (741 - 564) is 177\n\n####177", "a": 741, "b": 564, "operator": "-", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve (9 * 315)", "answer": "The result of (9 * 315) is 2835\n\n####2835", "a": 9, "b": 315, "operator": "*", "result": 2835}
{"question": "Solve (506 - 908)", "answer": "The result of (506 - 908) is -402\n\n####-402", "a": 506, "b": 908, "operator": "-", "result": -402}
{"question": "Solve (407 * 583)", "answer": "The result of (407 * 583) is 237281\n\n####237281", "a": 407, "b": 583, "operator": "*", "result": 237281}
{"question": "Solve (574 / 661)", "answer": "The result of (574 / 661) is 0.8684\n\n####0.8684", "a": 574, "b": 661, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8684}
{"question": "Solve (147 - 4)", "answer": "The result of (147 - 4) is 143\n\n####143", "a": 147, "b": 4, "operator": "-", "result": 143}
{"question": "Solve (997 * 131)", "answer": "The result of (997 * 131) is 130607\n\n####130607", "a": 997, "b": 131, "operator": "*", "result": 130607}
{"question": "Solve (909 * 804)", "answer": "The result of (909 * 804) is 730836\n\n####730836", "a": 909, "b": 804, "operator": "*", "result": 730836}
{"question": "Solve (582 + 470)", "answer": "The result of (582 + 470) is 1052\n\n####1052", "a": 582, "b": 470, "operator": "+", "result": 1052}
{"question": "Solve (244 * 99)", "answer": "The result of (244 * 99) is 24156\n\n####24156", "a": 244, "b": 99, "operator": "*", "result": 24156}
{"question": "Solve (303 / 493)", "answer": "The result of (303 / 493) is 0.6146\n\n####0.6146", "a": 303, "b": 493, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6146}
{"question": "Solve (286 * 793)", "answer": "The result of (286 * 793) is 226798\n\n####226798", "a": 286, "b": 793, "operator": "*", "result": 226798}
{"question": "Solve (796 / 434)", "answer": "The result of (796 / 434) is 1.8341\n\n####1.8341", "a": 796, "b": 434, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8341}
{"question": "Solve (380 * 309)", "answer": "The result of (380 * 309) is 117420\n\n####117420", "a": 380, "b": 309, "operator": "*", "result": 117420}
{"question": "Solve (614 / 800)", "answer": "The result of (614 / 800) is 0.7675\n\n####0.7675", "a": 614, "b": 800, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7675}
{"question": "Solve (912 + 973)", "answer": "The result of (912 + 973) is 1885\n\n####1885", "a": 912, "b": 973, "operator": "+", "result": 1885}
{"question": "Solve (267 / 498)", "answer": "The result of (267 / 498) is 0.5361\n\n####0.5361", "a": 267, "b": 498, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5361}
{"question": "Solve (951 - 468)", "answer": "The result of (951 - 468) is 483\n\n####483", "a": 951, "b": 468, "operator": "-", "result": 483}
{"question": "Solve (854 / 564)", "answer": "The result of (854 / 564) is 1.5142\n\n####1.5142", "a": 854, "b": 564, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5142}
{"question": "Solve (850 - 7)", "answer": "The result of (850 - 7) is 843\n\n####843", "a": 850, "b": 7, "operator": "-", "result": 843}
{"question": "Solve (380 * 94)", "answer": "The result of (380 * 94) is 35720\n\n####35720", "a": 380, "b": 94, "operator": "*", "result": 35720}
{"question": "Solve (252 + 465)", "answer": "The result of (252 + 465) is 717\n\n####717", "a": 252, "b": 465, "operator": "+", "result": 717}
{"question": "Solve (286 - 472)", "answer": "The result of (286 - 472) is -186\n\n####-186", "a": 286, "b": 472, "operator": "-", "result": -186}
{"question": "Solve (313 / 717)", "answer": "The result of (313 / 717) is 0.4365\n\n####0.4365", "a": 313, "b": 717, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4365}
{"question": "Solve (750 * 214)", "answer": "The result of (750 * 214) is 160500\n\n####160500", "a": 750, "b": 214, "operator": "*", "result": 160500}
{"question": "Solve (201 / 982)", "answer": "The result of (201 / 982) is 0.2047\n\n####0.2047", "a": 201, "b": 982, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2047}
{"question": "Solve (849 / 670)", "answer": "The result of (849 / 670) is 1.2672\n\n####1.2672", "a": 849, "b": 670, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2672}
{"question": "Solve (17 * 447)", "answer": "The result of (17 * 447) is 7599\n\n####7599", "a": 17, "b": 447, "operator": "*", "result": 7599}
{"question": "Solve (891 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (891 - 261) is 630\n\n####630", "a": 891, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": 630}
{"question": "Solve (739 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (739 / 914) is 0.8085\n\n####0.8085", "a": 739, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8085}
{"question": "Solve (534 * 38)", "answer": "The result of (534 * 38) is 20292\n\n####20292", "a": 534, "b": 38, "operator": "*", "result": 20292}
{"question": "Solve (8 / 879)", "answer": "The result of (8 / 879) is 0.0091\n\n####0.0091", "a": 8, "b": 879, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0091}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 878)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 878) is -163\n\n####-163", "a": 715, "b": 878, "operator": "-", "result": -163}
{"question": "Solve (405 * 828)", "answer": "The result of (405 * 828) is 335340\n\n####335340", "a": 405, "b": 828, "operator": "*", "result": 335340}
{"question": "Solve (956 / 20)", "answer": "The result of (956 / 20) is 47.8\n\n####47.8", "a": 956, "b": 20, "operator": "/", "result": 47.8}
{"question": "Solve (298 - 291)", "answer": "The result of (298 - 291) is 7\n\n####7", "a": 298, "b": 291, "operator": "-", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve (507 / 479)", "answer": "The result of (507 / 479) is 1.0585\n\n####1.0585", "a": 507, "b": 479, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0585}
{"question": "Solve (461 * 766)", "answer": "The result of (461 * 766) is 353126\n\n####353126", "a": 461, "b": 766, "operator": "*", "result": 353126}
{"question": "Solve (28 + 647)", "answer": "The result of (28 + 647) is 675\n\n####675", "a": 28, "b": 647, "operator": "+", "result": 675}
{"question": "Solve (566 * 784)", "answer": "The result of (566 * 784) is 443744\n\n####443744", "a": 566, "b": 784, "operator": "*", "result": 443744}
{"question": "Solve (992 - 51)", "answer": "The result of (992 - 51) is 941\n\n####941", "a": 992, "b": 51, "operator": "-", "result": 941}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 237)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 237) is 3.8819\n\n####3.8819", "a": 920, "b": 237, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8819}
{"question": "Solve (962 - 442)", "answer": "The result of (962 - 442) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 962, "b": 442, "operator": "-", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (761 * 32)", "answer": "The result of (761 * 32) is 24352\n\n####24352", "a": 761, "b": 32, "operator": "*", "result": 24352}
{"question": "Solve (917 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (917 * 637) is 584129\n\n####584129", "a": 917, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 584129}
{"question": "Solve (378 + 190)", "answer": "The result of (378 + 190) is 568\n\n####568", "a": 378, "b": 190, "operator": "+", "result": 568}
{"question": "Solve (931 * 974)", "answer": "The result of (931 * 974) is 906794\n\n####906794", "a": 931, "b": 974, "operator": "*", "result": 906794}
{"question": "Solve (815 + 437)", "answer": "The result of (815 + 437) is 1252\n\n####1252", "a": 815, "b": 437, "operator": "+", "result": 1252}
{"question": "Solve (161 / 279)", "answer": "The result of (161 / 279) is 0.5771\n\n####0.5771", "a": 161, "b": 279, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5771}
{"question": "Solve (879 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (879 * 400) is 351600\n\n####351600", "a": 879, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 351600}
{"question": "Solve (140 - 892)", "answer": "The result of (140 - 892) is -752\n\n####-752", "a": 140, "b": 892, "operator": "-", "result": -752}
{"question": "Solve (979 + 329)", "answer": "The result of (979 + 329) is 1308\n\n####1308", "a": 979, "b": 329, "operator": "+", "result": 1308}
{"question": "Solve (813 / 405)", "answer": "The result of (813 / 405) is 2.0074\n\n####2.0074", "a": 813, "b": 405, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0074}
{"question": "Solve (305 + 182)", "answer": "The result of (305 + 182) is 487\n\n####487", "a": 305, "b": 182, "operator": "+", "result": 487}
{"question": "Solve (713 + 486)", "answer": "The result of (713 + 486) is 1199\n\n####1199", "a": 713, "b": 486, "operator": "+", "result": 1199}
{"question": "Solve (733 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (733 * 823) is 603259\n\n####603259", "a": 733, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 603259}
{"question": "Solve (520 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (520 * 524) is 272480\n\n####272480", "a": 520, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 272480}
{"question": "Solve (662 - 739)", "answer": "The result of (662 - 739) is -77\n\n####-77", "a": 662, "b": 739, "operator": "-", "result": -77}
{"question": "Solve (137 / 274)", "answer": "The result of (137 / 274) is 0.5\n\n####0.5", "a": 137, "b": 274, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5}
{"question": "Solve (595 + 761)", "answer": "The result of (595 + 761) is 1356\n\n####1356", "a": 595, "b": 761, "operator": "+", "result": 1356}
{"question": "Solve (678 / 493)", "answer": "The result of (678 / 493) is 1.3753\n\n####1.3753", "a": 678, "b": 493, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3753}
{"question": "Solve (525 - 823)", "answer": "The result of (525 - 823) is -298\n\n####-298", "a": 525, "b": 823, "operator": "-", "result": -298}
{"question": "Solve (933 - 402)", "answer": "The result of (933 - 402) is 531\n\n####531", "a": 933, "b": 402, "operator": "-", "result": 531}
{"question": "Solve (367 * 291)", "answer": "The result of (367 * 291) is 106797\n\n####106797", "a": 367, "b": 291, "operator": "*", "result": 106797}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 701) is 0.9943\n\n####0.9943", "a": 697, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9943}
{"question": "Solve (150 - 530)", "answer": "The result of (150 - 530) is -380\n\n####-380", "a": 150, "b": 530, "operator": "-", "result": -380}
{"question": "Solve (885 * 399)", "answer": "The result of (885 * 399) is 353115\n\n####353115", "a": 885, "b": 399, "operator": "*", "result": 353115}
{"question": "Solve (997 + 404)", "answer": "The result of (997 + 404) is 1401\n\n####1401", "a": 997, "b": 404, "operator": "+", "result": 1401}
{"question": "Solve (675 * 375)", "answer": "The result of (675 * 375) is 253125\n\n####253125", "a": 675, "b": 375, "operator": "*", "result": 253125}
{"question": "Solve (904 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (904 - 551) is 353\n\n####353", "a": 904, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": 353}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 537) is 138\n\n####138", "a": 675, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": 138}
{"question": "Solve (13 + 974)", "answer": "The result of (13 + 974) is 987\n\n####987", "a": 13, "b": 974, "operator": "+", "result": 987}
{"question": "Solve (920 / 51)", "answer": "The result of (920 / 51) is 18.0392\n\n####18.0392", "a": 920, "b": 51, "operator": "/", "result": 18.0392}
{"question": "Solve (115 / 212)", "answer": "The result of (115 / 212) is 0.5425\n\n####0.5425", "a": 115, "b": 212, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5425}
{"question": "Solve (459 * 107)", "answer": "The result of (459 * 107) is 49113\n\n####49113", "a": 459, "b": 107, "operator": "*", "result": 49113}
{"question": "Solve (272 * 637)", "answer": "The result of (272 * 637) is 173264\n\n####173264", "a": 272, "b": 637, "operator": "*", "result": 173264}
{"question": "Solve (816 * 26)", "answer": "The result of (816 * 26) is 21216\n\n####21216", "a": 816, "b": 26, "operator": "*", "result": 21216}
{"question": "Solve (509 * 100)", "answer": "The result of (509 * 100) is 50900\n\n####50900", "a": 509, "b": 100, "operator": "*", "result": 50900}
{"question": "Solve (244 + 42)", "answer": "The result of (244 + 42) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 244, "b": 42, "operator": "+", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (267 / 127)", "answer": "The result of (267 / 127) is 2.1024\n\n####2.1024", "a": 267, "b": 127, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1024}
{"question": "Solve (337 - 552)", "answer": "The result of (337 - 552) is -215\n\n####-215", "a": 337, "b": 552, "operator": "-", "result": -215}
{"question": "Solve (110 * 190)", "answer": "The result of (110 * 190) is 20900\n\n####20900", "a": 110, "b": 190, "operator": "*", "result": 20900}
{"question": "Solve (678 - 249)", "answer": "The result of (678 - 249) is 429\n\n####429", "a": 678, "b": 249, "operator": "-", "result": 429}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 76)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 76) is 416\n\n####416", "a": 492, "b": 76, "operator": "-", "result": 416}
{"question": "Solve (885 * 765)", "answer": "The result of (885 * 765) is 677025\n\n####677025", "a": 885, "b": 765, "operator": "*", "result": 677025}
{"question": "Solve (76 * 493)", "answer": "The result of (76 * 493) is 37468\n\n####37468", "a": 76, "b": 493, "operator": "*", "result": 37468}
{"question": "Solve (141 * 325)", "answer": "The result of (141 * 325) is 45825\n\n####45825", "a": 141, "b": 325, "operator": "*", "result": 45825}
{"question": "Solve (29 / 959)", "answer": "The result of (29 / 959) is 0.0302\n\n####0.0302", "a": 29, "b": 959, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0302}
{"question": "Solve (610 / 801)", "answer": "The result of (610 / 801) is 0.7615\n\n####0.7615", "a": 610, "b": 801, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7615}
{"question": "Solve (385 + 154)", "answer": "The result of (385 + 154) is 539\n\n####539", "a": 385, "b": 154, "operator": "+", "result": 539}
{"question": "Solve (460 / 298)", "answer": "The result of (460 / 298) is 1.5436\n\n####1.5436", "a": 460, "b": 298, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5436}
{"question": "Solve (170 * 685)", "answer": "The result of (170 * 685) is 116450\n\n####116450", "a": 170, "b": 685, "operator": "*", "result": 116450}
{"question": "Solve (679 * 857)", "answer": "The result of (679 * 857) is 581903\n\n####581903", "a": 679, "b": 857, "operator": "*", "result": 581903}
{"question": "Solve (392 - 148)", "answer": "The result of (392 - 148) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 392, "b": 148, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (544 - 935)", "answer": "The result of (544 - 935) is -391\n\n####-391", "a": 544, "b": 935, "operator": "-", "result": -391}
{"question": "Solve (561 * 457)", "answer": "The result of (561 * 457) is 256377\n\n####256377", "a": 561, "b": 457, "operator": "*", "result": 256377}
{"question": "Solve (246 + 540)", "answer": "The result of (246 + 540) is 786\n\n####786", "a": 246, "b": 540, "operator": "+", "result": 786}
{"question": "Solve (226 - 40)", "answer": "The result of (226 - 40) is 186\n\n####186", "a": 226, "b": 40, "operator": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve (733 / 859)", "answer": "The result of (733 / 859) is 0.8533\n\n####0.8533", "a": 733, "b": 859, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8533}
{"question": "Solve (205 / 258)", "answer": "The result of (205 / 258) is 0.7946\n\n####0.7946", "a": 205, "b": 258, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7946}
{"question": "Solve (889 / 506)", "answer": "The result of (889 / 506) is 1.7569\n\n####1.7569", "a": 889, "b": 506, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7569}
{"question": "Solve (452 + 26)", "answer": "The result of (452 + 26) is 478\n\n####478", "a": 452, "b": 26, "operator": "+", "result": 478}
{"question": "Solve (865 / 949)", "answer": "The result of (865 / 949) is 0.9115\n\n####0.9115", "a": 865, "b": 949, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9115}
{"question": "Solve (606 / 511)", "answer": "The result of (606 / 511) is 1.1859\n\n####1.1859", "a": 606, "b": 511, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1859}
{"question": "Solve (207 - 907)", "answer": "The result of (207 - 907) is -700\n\n####-700", "a": 207, "b": 907, "operator": "-", "result": -700}
{"question": "Solve (436 / 231)", "answer": "The result of (436 / 231) is 1.8874\n\n####1.8874", "a": 436, "b": 231, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8874}
{"question": "Solve (355 + 135)", "answer": "The result of (355 + 135) is 490\n\n####490", "a": 355, "b": 135, "operator": "+", "result": 490}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 299) is 0.9264\n\n####0.9264", "a": 277, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9264}
{"question": "Solve (789 / 564)", "answer": "The result of (789 / 564) is 1.3989\n\n####1.3989", "a": 789, "b": 564, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3989}
{"question": "Solve (675 * 968)", "answer": "The result of (675 * 968) is 653400\n\n####653400", "a": 675, "b": 968, "operator": "*", "result": 653400}
{"question": "Solve (256 / 236)", "answer": "The result of (256 / 236) is 1.0847\n\n####1.0847", "a": 256, "b": 236, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0847}
{"question": "Solve (78 + 960)", "answer": "The result of (78 + 960) is 1038\n\n####1038", "a": 78, "b": 960, "operator": "+", "result": 1038}
{"question": "Solve (820 - 345)", "answer": "The result of (820 - 345) is 475\n\n####475", "a": 820, "b": 345, "operator": "-", "result": 475}
{"question": "Solve (104 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (104 - 846) is -742\n\n####-742", "a": 104, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -742}
{"question": "Solve (308 + 853)", "answer": "The result of (308 + 853) is 1161\n\n####1161", "a": 308, "b": 853, "operator": "+", "result": 1161}
{"question": "Solve (147 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (147 - 485) is -338\n\n####-338", "a": 147, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": -338}
{"question": "Solve (788 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (788 - 567) is 221\n\n####221", "a": 788, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve (678 - 419)", "answer": "The result of (678 - 419) is 259\n\n####259", "a": 678, "b": 419, "operator": "-", "result": 259}
{"question": "Solve (512 + 951)", "answer": "The result of (512 + 951) is 1463\n\n####1463", "a": 512, "b": 951, "operator": "+", "result": 1463}
{"question": "Solve (8 * 597)", "answer": "The result of (8 * 597) is 4776\n\n####4776", "a": 8, "b": 597, "operator": "*", "result": 4776}
{"question": "Solve (785 - 517)", "answer": "The result of (785 - 517) is 268\n\n####268", "a": 785, "b": 517, "operator": "-", "result": 268}
{"question": "Solve (335 / 346)", "answer": "The result of (335 / 346) is 0.9682\n\n####0.9682", "a": 335, "b": 346, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9682}
{"question": "Solve (460 + 455)", "answer": "The result of (460 + 455) is 915\n\n####915", "a": 460, "b": 455, "operator": "+", "result": 915}
{"question": "Solve (961 * 194)", "answer": "The result of (961 * 194) is 186434\n\n####186434", "a": 961, "b": 194, "operator": "*", "result": 186434}
{"question": "Solve (270 * 611)", "answer": "The result of (270 * 611) is 164970\n\n####164970", "a": 270, "b": 611, "operator": "*", "result": 164970}
{"question": "Solve (338 + 725)", "answer": "The result of (338 + 725) is 1063\n\n####1063", "a": 338, "b": 725, "operator": "+", "result": 1063}
{"question": "Solve (144 - 50)", "answer": "The result of (144 - 50) is 94\n\n####94", "a": 144, "b": 50, "operator": "-", "result": 94}
{"question": "Solve (143 + 263)", "answer": "The result of (143 + 263) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 143, "b": 263, "operator": "+", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (274 - 341)", "answer": "The result of (274 - 341) is -67\n\n####-67", "a": 274, "b": 341, "operator": "-", "result": -67}
{"question": "Solve (228 - 404)", "answer": "The result of (228 - 404) is -176\n\n####-176", "a": 228, "b": 404, "operator": "-", "result": -176}
{"question": "Solve (696 / 868)", "answer": "The result of (696 / 868) is 0.8018\n\n####0.8018", "a": 696, "b": 868, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8018}
{"question": "Solve (280 + 347)", "answer": "The result of (280 + 347) is 627\n\n####627", "a": 280, "b": 347, "operator": "+", "result": 627}
{"question": "Solve (626 - 949)", "answer": "The result of (626 - 949) is -323\n\n####-323", "a": 626, "b": 949, "operator": "-", "result": -323}
{"question": "Solve (234 + 722)", "answer": "The result of (234 + 722) is 956\n\n####956", "a": 234, "b": 722, "operator": "+", "result": 956}
{"question": "Solve (481 * 585)", "answer": "The result of (481 * 585) is 281385\n\n####281385", "a": 481, "b": 585, "operator": "*", "result": 281385}
{"question": "Solve (340 + 572)", "answer": "The result of (340 + 572) is 912\n\n####912", "a": 340, "b": 572, "operator": "+", "result": 912}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 302)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 302) is 2.3079\n\n####2.3079", "a": 697, "b": 302, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3079}
{"question": "Solve (627 * 548)", "answer": "The result of (627 * 548) is 343596\n\n####343596", "a": 627, "b": 548, "operator": "*", "result": 343596}
{"question": "Solve (87 * 153)", "answer": "The result of (87 * 153) is 13311\n\n####13311", "a": 87, "b": 153, "operator": "*", "result": 13311}
{"question": "Solve (550 * 965)", "answer": "The result of (550 * 965) is 530750\n\n####530750", "a": 550, "b": 965, "operator": "*", "result": 530750}
{"question": "Solve (841 / 244)", "answer": "The result of (841 / 244) is 3.4467\n\n####3.4467", "a": 841, "b": 244, "operator": "/", "result": 3.4467}
{"question": "Solve (475 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (475 - 358) is 117\n\n####117", "a": 475, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve (683 / 936)", "answer": "The result of (683 / 936) is 0.7297\n\n####0.7297", "a": 683, "b": 936, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7297}
{"question": "Solve (784 * 538)", "answer": "The result of (784 * 538) is 421792\n\n####421792", "a": 784, "b": 538, "operator": "*", "result": 421792}
{"question": "Solve (958 + 411)", "answer": "The result of (958 + 411) is 1369\n\n####1369", "a": 958, "b": 411, "operator": "+", "result": 1369}
{"question": "Solve (145 - 771)", "answer": "The result of (145 - 771) is -626\n\n####-626", "a": 145, "b": 771, "operator": "-", "result": -626}
{"question": "Solve (857 / 611)", "answer": "The result of (857 / 611) is 1.4026\n\n####1.4026", "a": 857, "b": 611, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4026}
{"question": "Solve (26 - 472)", "answer": "The result of (26 - 472) is -446\n\n####-446", "a": 26, "b": 472, "operator": "-", "result": -446}
{"question": "Solve (208 / 639)", "answer": "The result of (208 / 639) is 0.3255\n\n####0.3255", "a": 208, "b": 639, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3255}
{"question": "Solve (844 / 883)", "answer": "The result of (844 / 883) is 0.9558\n\n####0.9558", "a": 844, "b": 883, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9558}
{"question": "Solve (670 - 387)", "answer": "The result of (670 - 387) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 670, "b": 387, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (792 * 783)", "answer": "The result of (792 * 783) is 620136\n\n####620136", "a": 792, "b": 783, "operator": "*", "result": 620136}
{"question": "Solve (832 * 192)", "answer": "The result of (832 * 192) is 159744\n\n####159744", "a": 832, "b": 192, "operator": "*", "result": 159744}
{"question": "Solve (167 * 741)", "answer": "The result of (167 * 741) is 123747\n\n####123747", "a": 167, "b": 741, "operator": "*", "result": 123747}
{"question": "Solve (712 * 276)", "answer": "The result of (712 * 276) is 196512\n\n####196512", "a": 712, "b": 276, "operator": "*", "result": 196512}
{"question": "Solve (381 * 144)", "answer": "The result of (381 * 144) is 54864\n\n####54864", "a": 381, "b": 144, "operator": "*", "result": 54864}
{"question": "Solve (843 - 894)", "answer": "The result of (843 - 894) is -51\n\n####-51", "a": 843, "b": 894, "operator": "-", "result": -51}
{"question": "Solve (370 / 40)", "answer": "The result of (370 / 40) is 9.25\n\n####9.25", "a": 370, "b": 40, "operator": "/", "result": 9.25}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 861)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 861) is -657\n\n####-657", "a": 204, "b": 861, "operator": "-", "result": -657}
{"question": "Solve (350 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (350 / 290) is 1.2069\n\n####1.2069", "a": 350, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2069}
{"question": "Solve (422 + 419)", "answer": "The result of (422 + 419) is 841\n\n####841", "a": 422, "b": 419, "operator": "+", "result": 841}
{"question": "Solve (786 / 136)", "answer": "The result of (786 / 136) is 5.7794\n\n####5.7794", "a": 786, "b": 136, "operator": "/", "result": 5.7794}
{"question": "Solve (879 * 867)", "answer": "The result of (879 * 867) is 762093\n\n####762093", "a": 879, "b": 867, "operator": "*", "result": 762093}
{"question": "Solve (424 - 843)", "answer": "The result of (424 - 843) is -419\n\n####-419", "a": 424, "b": 843, "operator": "-", "result": -419}
{"question": "Solve (102 * 320)", "answer": "The result of (102 * 320) is 32640\n\n####32640", "a": 102, "b": 320, "operator": "*", "result": 32640}
{"question": "Solve (421 * 665)", "answer": "The result of (421 * 665) is 279965\n\n####279965", "a": 421, "b": 665, "operator": "*", "result": 279965}
{"question": "Solve (600 - 671)", "answer": "The result of (600 - 671) is -71\n\n####-71", "a": 600, "b": 671, "operator": "-", "result": -71}
{"question": "Solve (380 + 428)", "answer": "The result of (380 + 428) is 808\n\n####808", "a": 380, "b": 428, "operator": "+", "result": 808}
{"question": "Solve (788 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (788 - 498) is 290\n\n####290", "a": 788, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 536)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 536) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 486, "b": 536, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (96 - 888)", "answer": "The result of (96 - 888) is -792\n\n####-792", "a": 96, "b": 888, "operator": "-", "result": -792}
{"question": "Solve (212 - 403)", "answer": "The result of (212 - 403) is -191\n\n####-191", "a": 212, "b": 403, "operator": "-", "result": -191}
{"question": "Solve (63 - 981)", "answer": "The result of (63 - 981) is -918\n\n####-918", "a": 63, "b": 981, "operator": "-", "result": -918}
{"question": "Solve (545 + 274)", "answer": "The result of (545 + 274) is 819\n\n####819", "a": 545, "b": 274, "operator": "+", "result": 819}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 897) is 677235\n\n####677235", "a": 755, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 677235}
{"question": "Solve (321 + 549)", "answer": "The result of (321 + 549) is 870\n\n####870", "a": 321, "b": 549, "operator": "+", "result": 870}
{"question": "Solve (560 / 680)", "answer": "The result of (560 / 680) is 0.8235\n\n####0.8235", "a": 560, "b": 680, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8235}
{"question": "Solve (985 / 764)", "answer": "The result of (985 / 764) is 1.2893\n\n####1.2893", "a": 985, "b": 764, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2893}
{"question": "Solve (593 * 917)", "answer": "The result of (593 * 917) is 543781\n\n####543781", "a": 593, "b": 917, "operator": "*", "result": 543781}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 570)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 570) is -247\n\n####-247", "a": 323, "b": 570, "operator": "-", "result": -247}
{"question": "Solve (24 * 616)", "answer": "The result of (24 * 616) is 14784\n\n####14784", "a": 24, "b": 616, "operator": "*", "result": 14784}
{"question": "Solve (353 / 206)", "answer": "The result of (353 / 206) is 1.7136\n\n####1.7136", "a": 353, "b": 206, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7136}
{"question": "Solve (725 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (725 * 22) is 15950\n\n####15950", "a": 725, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 15950}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 920)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 920) is 242880\n\n####242880", "a": 264, "b": 920, "operator": "*", "result": 242880}
{"question": "Solve (3 - 257)", "answer": "The result of (3 - 257) is -254\n\n####-254", "a": 3, "b": 257, "operator": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve (720 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (720 / 385) is 1.8701\n\n####1.8701", "a": 720, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8701}
{"question": "Solve (609 * 184)", "answer": "The result of (609 * 184) is 112056\n\n####112056", "a": 609, "b": 184, "operator": "*", "result": 112056}
{"question": "Solve (21 - 840)", "answer": "The result of (21 - 840) is -819\n\n####-819", "a": 21, "b": 840, "operator": "-", "result": -819}
{"question": "Solve (737 * 180)", "answer": "The result of (737 * 180) is 132660\n\n####132660", "a": 737, "b": 180, "operator": "*", "result": 132660}
{"question": "Solve (520 * 491)", "answer": "The result of (520 * 491) is 255320\n\n####255320", "a": 520, "b": 491, "operator": "*", "result": 255320}
{"question": "Solve (587 / 193)", "answer": "The result of (587 / 193) is 3.0415\n\n####3.0415", "a": 587, "b": 193, "operator": "/", "result": 3.0415}
{"question": "Solve (540 / 271)", "answer": "The result of (540 / 271) is 1.9926\n\n####1.9926", "a": 540, "b": 271, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9926}
{"question": "Solve (431 - 997)", "answer": "The result of (431 - 997) is -566\n\n####-566", "a": 431, "b": 997, "operator": "-", "result": -566}
{"question": "Solve (945 / 299)", "answer": "The result of (945 / 299) is 3.1605\n\n####3.1605", "a": 945, "b": 299, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1605}
{"question": "Solve (877 - 271)", "answer": "The result of (877 - 271) is 606\n\n####606", "a": 877, "b": 271, "operator": "-", "result": 606}
{"question": "Solve (865 / 713)", "answer": "The result of (865 / 713) is 1.2132\n\n####1.2132", "a": 865, "b": 713, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2132}
{"question": "Solve (939 / 660)", "answer": "The result of (939 / 660) is 1.4227\n\n####1.4227", "a": 939, "b": 660, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4227}
{"question": "Solve (757 - 652)", "answer": "The result of (757 - 652) is 105\n\n####105", "a": 757, "b": 652, "operator": "-", "result": 105}
{"question": "Solve (153 * 748)", "answer": "The result of (153 * 748) is 114444\n\n####114444", "a": 153, "b": 748, "operator": "*", "result": 114444}
{"question": "Solve (119 - 135)", "answer": "The result of (119 - 135) is -16\n\n####-16", "a": 119, "b": 135, "operator": "-", "result": -16}
{"question": "Solve (205 / 415)", "answer": "The result of (205 / 415) is 0.494\n\n####0.494", "a": 205, "b": 415, "operator": "/", "result": 0.494}
{"question": "Solve (925 * 739)", "answer": "The result of (925 * 739) is 683575\n\n####683575", "a": 925, "b": 739, "operator": "*", "result": 683575}
{"question": "Solve (332 + 208)", "answer": "The result of (332 + 208) is 540\n\n####540", "a": 332, "b": 208, "operator": "+", "result": 540}
{"question": "Solve (970 - 104)", "answer": "The result of (970 - 104) is 866\n\n####866", "a": 970, "b": 104, "operator": "-", "result": 866}
{"question": "Solve (228 / 941)", "answer": "The result of (228 / 941) is 0.2423\n\n####0.2423", "a": 228, "b": 941, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2423}
{"question": "Solve (906 / 858)", "answer": "The result of (906 / 858) is 1.0559\n\n####1.0559", "a": 906, "b": 858, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0559}
{"question": "Solve (732 + 976)", "answer": "The result of (732 + 976) is 1708\n\n####1708", "a": 732, "b": 976, "operator": "+", "result": 1708}
{"question": "Solve (694 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (694 * 870) is 603780\n\n####603780", "a": 694, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 603780}
{"question": "Solve (778 + 656)", "answer": "The result of (778 + 656) is 1434\n\n####1434", "a": 778, "b": 656, "operator": "+", "result": 1434}
{"question": "Solve (614 + 62)", "answer": "The result of (614 + 62) is 676\n\n####676", "a": 614, "b": 62, "operator": "+", "result": 676}
{"question": "Solve (558 - 956)", "answer": "The result of (558 - 956) is -398\n\n####-398", "a": 558, "b": 956, "operator": "-", "result": -398}
{"question": "Solve (902 - 286)", "answer": "The result of (902 - 286) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 902, "b": 286, "operator": "-", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (579 / 894)", "answer": "The result of (579 / 894) is 0.6477\n\n####0.6477", "a": 579, "b": 894, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6477}
{"question": "Solve (322 * 740)", "answer": "The result of (322 * 740) is 238280\n\n####238280", "a": 322, "b": 740, "operator": "*", "result": 238280}
{"question": "Solve (797 / 486)", "answer": "The result of (797 / 486) is 1.6399\n\n####1.6399", "a": 797, "b": 486, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6399}
{"question": "Solve (10 + 332)", "answer": "The result of (10 + 332) is 342\n\n####342", "a": 10, "b": 332, "operator": "+", "result": 342}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 276)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 276) is 192648\n\n####192648", "a": 698, "b": 276, "operator": "*", "result": 192648}
{"question": "Solve (468 + 828)", "answer": "The result of (468 + 828) is 1296\n\n####1296", "a": 468, "b": 828, "operator": "+", "result": 1296}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 781)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 781) is 1753\n\n####1753", "a": 972, "b": 781, "operator": "+", "result": 1753}
{"question": "Solve (394 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (394 - 210) is 184\n\n####184", "a": 394, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": 184}
{"question": "Solve (617 + 793)", "answer": "The result of (617 + 793) is 1410\n\n####1410", "a": 617, "b": 793, "operator": "+", "result": 1410}
{"question": "Solve (961 + 784)", "answer": "The result of (961 + 784) is 1745\n\n####1745", "a": 961, "b": 784, "operator": "+", "result": 1745}
{"question": "Solve (247 - 397)", "answer": "The result of (247 - 397) is -150\n\n####-150", "a": 247, "b": 397, "operator": "-", "result": -150}
{"question": "Solve (769 + 117)", "answer": "The result of (769 + 117) is 886\n\n####886", "a": 769, "b": 117, "operator": "+", "result": 886}
{"question": "Solve (566 + 558)", "answer": "The result of (566 + 558) is 1124\n\n####1124", "a": 566, "b": 558, "operator": "+", "result": 1124}
{"question": "Solve (468 * 708)", "answer": "The result of (468 * 708) is 331344\n\n####331344", "a": 468, "b": 708, "operator": "*", "result": 331344}
{"question": "Solve (798 / 326)", "answer": "The result of (798 / 326) is 2.4479\n\n####2.4479", "a": 798, "b": 326, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4479}
{"question": "Solve (949 * 395)", "answer": "The result of (949 * 395) is 374855\n\n####374855", "a": 949, "b": 395, "operator": "*", "result": 374855}
{"question": "Solve (963 / 772)", "answer": "The result of (963 / 772) is 1.2474\n\n####1.2474", "a": 963, "b": 772, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2474}
{"question": "Solve (936 - 385)", "answer": "The result of (936 - 385) is 551\n\n####551", "a": 936, "b": 385, "operator": "-", "result": 551}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 92)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 92) is 65688\n\n####65688", "a": 714, "b": 92, "operator": "*", "result": 65688}
{"question": "Solve (874 * 4)", "answer": "The result of (874 * 4) is 3496\n\n####3496", "a": 874, "b": 4, "operator": "*", "result": 3496}
{"question": "Solve (318 - 379)", "answer": "The result of (318 - 379) is -61\n\n####-61", "a": 318, "b": 379, "operator": "-", "result": -61}
{"question": "Solve (892 - 180)", "answer": "The result of (892 - 180) is 712\n\n####712", "a": 892, "b": 180, "operator": "-", "result": 712}
{"question": "Solve (607 / 961)", "answer": "The result of (607 / 961) is 0.6316\n\n####0.6316", "a": 607, "b": 961, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6316}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 995)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 995) is -137\n\n####-137", "a": 858, "b": 995, "operator": "-", "result": -137}
{"question": "Solve (519 + 36)", "answer": "The result of (519 + 36) is 555\n\n####555", "a": 519, "b": 36, "operator": "+", "result": 555}
{"question": "Solve (294 - 376)", "answer": "The result of (294 - 376) is -82\n\n####-82", "a": 294, "b": 376, "operator": "-", "result": -82}
{"question": "Solve (844 / 300)", "answer": "The result of (844 / 300) is 2.8133\n\n####2.8133", "a": 844, "b": 300, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8133}
{"question": "Solve (949 + 787)", "answer": "The result of (949 + 787) is 1736\n\n####1736", "a": 949, "b": 787, "operator": "+", "result": 1736}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 745)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 745) is 83\n\n####83", "a": 828, "b": 745, "operator": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve (423 / 435)", "answer": "The result of (423 / 435) is 0.9724\n\n####0.9724", "a": 423, "b": 435, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9724}
{"question": "Solve (582 / 850)", "answer": "The result of (582 / 850) is 0.6847\n\n####0.6847", "a": 582, "b": 850, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6847}
{"question": "Solve (241 - 485)", "answer": "The result of (241 - 485) is -244\n\n####-244", "a": 241, "b": 485, "operator": "-", "result": -244}
{"question": "Solve (746 / 513)", "answer": "The result of (746 / 513) is 1.4542\n\n####1.4542", "a": 746, "b": 513, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4542}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 988)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 988) is -881\n\n####-881", "a": 107, "b": 988, "operator": "-", "result": -881}
{"question": "Solve (278 / 991)", "answer": "The result of (278 / 991) is 0.2805\n\n####0.2805", "a": 278, "b": 991, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2805}
{"question": "Solve (390 - 846)", "answer": "The result of (390 - 846) is -456\n\n####-456", "a": 390, "b": 846, "operator": "-", "result": -456}
{"question": "Solve (895 / 829)", "answer": "The result of (895 / 829) is 1.0796\n\n####1.0796", "a": 895, "b": 829, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0796}
{"question": "Solve (334 - 948)", "answer": "The result of (334 - 948) is -614\n\n####-614", "a": 334, "b": 948, "operator": "-", "result": -614}
{"question": "Solve (1 * 56)", "answer": "The result of (1 * 56) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 1, "b": 56, "operator": "*", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (853 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (853 + 843) is 1696\n\n####1696", "a": 853, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 1696}
{"question": "Solve (873 / 998)", "answer": "The result of (873 / 998) is 0.8747\n\n####0.8747", "a": 873, "b": 998, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8747}
{"question": "Solve (732 * 964)", "answer": "The result of (732 * 964) is 705648\n\n####705648", "a": 732, "b": 964, "operator": "*", "result": 705648}
{"question": "Solve (728 * 996)", "answer": "The result of (728 * 996) is 725088\n\n####725088", "a": 728, "b": 996, "operator": "*", "result": 725088}
{"question": "Solve (615 - 332)", "answer": "The result of (615 - 332) is 283\n\n####283", "a": 615, "b": 332, "operator": "-", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve (996 + 151)", "answer": "The result of (996 + 151) is 1147\n\n####1147", "a": 996, "b": 151, "operator": "+", "result": 1147}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 552)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 552) is 6624\n\n####6624", "a": 12, "b": 552, "operator": "*", "result": 6624}
{"question": "Solve (524 - 997)", "answer": "The result of (524 - 997) is -473\n\n####-473", "a": 524, "b": 997, "operator": "-", "result": -473}
{"question": "Solve (123 - 96)", "answer": "The result of (123 - 96) is 27\n\n####27", "a": 123, "b": 96, "operator": "-", "result": 27}
{"question": "Solve (148 - 799)", "answer": "The result of (148 - 799) is -651\n\n####-651", "a": 148, "b": 799, "operator": "-", "result": -651}
{"question": "Solve (595 * 937)", "answer": "The result of (595 * 937) is 557515\n\n####557515", "a": 595, "b": 937, "operator": "*", "result": 557515}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 520)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 520) is 503360\n\n####503360", "a": 968, "b": 520, "operator": "*", "result": 503360}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 124)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 124) is 4.4919\n\n####4.4919", "a": 557, "b": 124, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4919}
{"question": "Solve (613 * 679)", "answer": "The result of (613 * 679) is 416227\n\n####416227", "a": 613, "b": 679, "operator": "*", "result": 416227}
{"question": "Solve (770 - 250)", "answer": "The result of (770 - 250) is 520\n\n####520", "a": 770, "b": 250, "operator": "-", "result": 520}
{"question": "Solve (518 + 605)", "answer": "The result of (518 + 605) is 1123\n\n####1123", "a": 518, "b": 605, "operator": "+", "result": 1123}
{"question": "Solve (867 + 239)", "answer": "The result of (867 + 239) is 1106\n\n####1106", "a": 867, "b": 239, "operator": "+", "result": 1106}
{"question": "Solve (405 / 961)", "answer": "The result of (405 / 961) is 0.4214\n\n####0.4214", "a": 405, "b": 961, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4214}
{"question": "Solve (140 * 57)", "answer": "The result of (140 * 57) is 7980\n\n####7980", "a": 140, "b": 57, "operator": "*", "result": 7980}
{"question": "Solve (41 * 746)", "answer": "The result of (41 * 746) is 30586\n\n####30586", "a": 41, "b": 746, "operator": "*", "result": 30586}
{"question": "Solve (181 / 322)", "answer": "The result of (181 / 322) is 0.5621\n\n####0.5621", "a": 181, "b": 322, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5621}
{"question": "Solve (662 + 564)", "answer": "The result of (662 + 564) is 1226\n\n####1226", "a": 662, "b": 564, "operator": "+", "result": 1226}
{"question": "Solve (975 * 643)", "answer": "The result of (975 * 643) is 626925\n\n####626925", "a": 975, "b": 643, "operator": "*", "result": 626925}
{"question": "Solve (616 + 70)", "answer": "The result of (616 + 70) is 686\n\n####686", "a": 616, "b": 70, "operator": "+", "result": 686}
{"question": "Solve (534 - 581)", "answer": "The result of (534 - 581) is -47\n\n####-47", "a": 534, "b": 581, "operator": "-", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve (211 * 732)", "answer": "The result of (211 * 732) is 154452\n\n####154452", "a": 211, "b": 732, "operator": "*", "result": 154452}
{"question": "Solve (848 - 284)", "answer": "The result of (848 - 284) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 848, "b": 284, "operator": "-", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (56 * 372)", "answer": "The result of (56 * 372) is 20832\n\n####20832", "a": 56, "b": 372, "operator": "*", "result": 20832}
{"question": "Solve (694 / 598)", "answer": "The result of (694 / 598) is 1.1605\n\n####1.1605", "a": 694, "b": 598, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1605}
{"question": "Solve (250 / 117)", "answer": "The result of (250 / 117) is 2.1368\n\n####2.1368", "a": 250, "b": 117, "operator": "/", "result": 2.1368}
{"question": "Solve (794 - 608)", "answer": "The result of (794 - 608) is 186\n\n####186", "a": 794, "b": 608, "operator": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve (756 + 926)", "answer": "The result of (756 + 926) is 1682\n\n####1682", "a": 756, "b": 926, "operator": "+", "result": 1682}
{"question": "Solve (310 / 669)", "answer": "The result of (310 / 669) is 0.4634\n\n####0.4634", "a": 310, "b": 669, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4634}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 730) is -623\n\n####-623", "a": 107, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -623}
{"question": "Solve (993 - 271)", "answer": "The result of (993 - 271) is 722\n\n####722", "a": 993, "b": 271, "operator": "-", "result": 722}
{"question": "Solve (87 + 386)", "answer": "The result of (87 + 386) is 473\n\n####473", "a": 87, "b": 386, "operator": "+", "result": 473}
{"question": "Solve (731 + 88)", "answer": "The result of (731 + 88) is 819\n\n####819", "a": 731, "b": 88, "operator": "+", "result": 819}
{"question": "Solve (704 - 939)", "answer": "The result of (704 - 939) is -235\n\n####-235", "a": 704, "b": 939, "operator": "-", "result": -235}
{"question": "Solve (3 - 259)", "answer": "The result of (3 - 259) is -256\n\n####-256", "a": 3, "b": 259, "operator": "-", "result": -256}
{"question": "Solve (265 * 587)", "answer": "The result of (265 * 587) is 155555\n\n####155555", "a": 265, "b": 587, "operator": "*", "result": 155555}
{"question": "Solve (982 / 752)", "answer": "The result of (982 / 752) is 1.3059\n\n####1.3059", "a": 982, "b": 752, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3059}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 175) is 500\n\n####500", "a": 675, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 500}
{"question": "Solve (18 / 984)", "answer": "The result of (18 / 984) is 0.0183\n\n####0.0183", "a": 18, "b": 984, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0183}
{"question": "Solve (101 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (101 / 701) is 0.1441\n\n####0.1441", "a": 101, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1441}
{"question": "Solve (910 - 590)", "answer": "The result of (910 - 590) is 320\n\n####320", "a": 910, "b": 590, "operator": "-", "result": 320}
{"question": "Solve (746 * 345)", "answer": "The result of (746 * 345) is 257370\n\n####257370", "a": 746, "b": 345, "operator": "*", "result": 257370}
{"question": "Solve (61 - 275)", "answer": "The result of (61 - 275) is -214\n\n####-214", "a": 61, "b": 275, "operator": "-", "result": -214}
{"question": "Solve (970 - 157)", "answer": "The result of (970 - 157) is 813\n\n####813", "a": 970, "b": 157, "operator": "-", "result": 813}
{"question": "Solve (662 * 278)", "answer": "The result of (662 * 278) is 184036\n\n####184036", "a": 662, "b": 278, "operator": "*", "result": 184036}
{"question": "Solve (44 * 975)", "answer": "The result of (44 * 975) is 42900\n\n####42900", "a": 44, "b": 975, "operator": "*", "result": 42900}
{"question": "Solve (804 - 920)", "answer": "The result of (804 - 920) is -116\n\n####-116", "a": 804, "b": 920, "operator": "-", "result": -116}
{"question": "Solve (496 * 411)", "answer": "The result of (496 * 411) is 203856\n\n####203856", "a": 496, "b": 411, "operator": "*", "result": 203856}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 632)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 632) is 497384\n\n####497384", "a": 787, "b": 632, "operator": "*", "result": 497384}
{"question": "Solve (63 / 621)", "answer": "The result of (63 / 621) is 0.1014\n\n####0.1014", "a": 63, "b": 621, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1014}
{"question": "Solve (853 * 575)", "answer": "The result of (853 * 575) is 490475\n\n####490475", "a": 853, "b": 575, "operator": "*", "result": 490475}
{"question": "Solve (972 - 126)", "answer": "The result of (972 - 126) is 846\n\n####846", "a": 972, "b": 126, "operator": "-", "result": 846}
{"question": "Solve (586 + 326)", "answer": "The result of (586 + 326) is 912\n\n####912", "a": 586, "b": 326, "operator": "+", "result": 912}
{"question": "Solve (133 * 12)", "answer": "The result of (133 * 12) is 1596\n\n####1596", "a": 133, "b": 12, "operator": "*", "result": 1596}
{"question": "Solve (353 * 6)", "answer": "The result of (353 * 6) is 2118\n\n####2118", "a": 353, "b": 6, "operator": "*", "result": 2118}
{"question": "Solve (32 - 75)", "answer": "The result of (32 - 75) is -43\n\n####-43", "a": 32, "b": 75, "operator": "-", "result": -43}
{"question": "Solve (843 + 379)", "answer": "The result of (843 + 379) is 1222\n\n####1222", "a": 843, "b": 379, "operator": "+", "result": 1222}
{"question": "Solve (888 / 68)", "answer": "The result of (888 / 68) is 13.0588\n\n####13.0588", "a": 888, "b": 68, "operator": "/", "result": 13.0588}
{"question": "Solve (553 / 271)", "answer": "The result of (553 / 271) is 2.0406\n\n####2.0406", "a": 553, "b": 271, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0406}
{"question": "Solve (187 * 267)", "answer": "The result of (187 * 267) is 49929\n\n####49929", "a": 187, "b": 267, "operator": "*", "result": 49929}
{"question": "Solve (809 / 50)", "answer": "The result of (809 / 50) is 16.18\n\n####16.18", "a": 809, "b": 50, "operator": "/", "result": 16.18}
{"question": "Solve (17 / 600)", "answer": "The result of (17 / 600) is 0.0283\n\n####0.0283", "a": 17, "b": 600, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0283}
{"question": "Solve (171 - 699)", "answer": "The result of (171 - 699) is -528\n\n####-528", "a": 171, "b": 699, "operator": "-", "result": -528}
{"question": "Solve (1 / 261)", "answer": "The result of (1 / 261) is 0.0038\n\n####0.0038", "a": 1, "b": 261, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0038}
{"question": "Solve (529 - 689)", "answer": "The result of (529 - 689) is -160\n\n####-160", "a": 529, "b": 689, "operator": "-", "result": -160}
{"question": "Solve (324 + 267)", "answer": "The result of (324 + 267) is 591\n\n####591", "a": 324, "b": 267, "operator": "+", "result": 591}
{"question": "Solve (465 + 747)", "answer": "The result of (465 + 747) is 1212\n\n####1212", "a": 465, "b": 747, "operator": "+", "result": 1212}
{"question": "Solve (901 - 394)", "answer": "The result of (901 - 394) is 507\n\n####507", "a": 901, "b": 394, "operator": "-", "result": 507}
{"question": "Solve (190 / 994)", "answer": "The result of (190 / 994) is 0.1911\n\n####0.1911", "a": 190, "b": 994, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1911}
{"question": "Solve (714 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (714 - 514) is 200\n\n####200", "a": 714, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": 200}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 553)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 553) is 1.3056\n\n####1.3056", "a": 722, "b": 553, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3056}
{"question": "Solve (49 / 280)", "answer": "The result of (49 / 280) is 0.175\n\n####0.175", "a": 49, "b": 280, "operator": "/", "result": 0.175}
{"question": "Solve (162 / 445)", "answer": "The result of (162 / 445) is 0.364\n\n####0.364", "a": 162, "b": 445, "operator": "/", "result": 0.364}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 558)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 558) is -379\n\n####-379", "a": 179, "b": 558, "operator": "-", "result": -379}
{"question": "Solve (987 - 514)", "answer": "The result of (987 - 514) is 473\n\n####473", "a": 987, "b": 514, "operator": "-", "result": 473}
{"question": "Solve (458 / 579)", "answer": "The result of (458 / 579) is 0.791\n\n####0.791", "a": 458, "b": 579, "operator": "/", "result": 0.791}
{"question": "Solve (261 * 122)", "answer": "The result of (261 * 122) is 31842\n\n####31842", "a": 261, "b": 122, "operator": "*", "result": 31842}
{"question": "Solve (519 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (519 - 701) is -182\n\n####-182", "a": 519, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": -182}
{"question": "Solve (240 + 70)", "answer": "The result of (240 + 70) is 310\n\n####310", "a": 240, "b": 70, "operator": "+", "result": 310}
{"question": "Solve (507 - 105)", "answer": "The result of (507 - 105) is 402\n\n####402", "a": 507, "b": 105, "operator": "-", "result": 402}
{"question": "Solve (492 * 889)", "answer": "The result of (492 * 889) is 437388\n\n####437388", "a": 492, "b": 889, "operator": "*", "result": 437388}
{"question": "Solve (48 + 687)", "answer": "The result of (48 + 687) is 735\n\n####735", "a": 48, "b": 687, "operator": "+", "result": 735}
{"question": "Solve (488 - 640)", "answer": "The result of (488 - 640) is -152\n\n####-152", "a": 488, "b": 640, "operator": "-", "result": -152}
{"question": "Solve (878 - 202)", "answer": "The result of (878 - 202) is 676\n\n####676", "a": 878, "b": 202, "operator": "-", "result": 676}
{"question": "Solve (191 / 326)", "answer": "The result of (191 / 326) is 0.5859\n\n####0.5859", "a": 191, "b": 326, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5859}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 551) is -518\n\n####-518", "a": 33, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": -518}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 586)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 586) is -278\n\n####-278", "a": 308, "b": 586, "operator": "-", "result": -278}
{"question": "Solve (849 - 914)", "answer": "The result of (849 - 914) is -65\n\n####-65", "a": 849, "b": 914, "operator": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve (134 + 141)", "answer": "The result of (134 + 141) is 275\n\n####275", "a": 134, "b": 141, "operator": "+", "result": 275}
{"question": "Solve (687 - 547)", "answer": "The result of (687 - 547) is 140\n\n####140", "a": 687, "b": 547, "operator": "-", "result": 140}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 107)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 107) is 385\n\n####385", "a": 492, "b": 107, "operator": "-", "result": 385}
{"question": "Solve (920 + 987)", "answer": "The result of (920 + 987) is 1907\n\n####1907", "a": 920, "b": 987, "operator": "+", "result": 1907}
{"question": "Solve (450 / 371)", "answer": "The result of (450 / 371) is 1.2129\n\n####1.2129", "a": 450, "b": 371, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2129}
{"question": "Solve (327 - 318)", "answer": "The result of (327 - 318) is 9\n\n####9", "a": 327, "b": 318, "operator": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve (541 - 591)", "answer": "The result of (541 - 591) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 541, "b": 591, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (985 - 352)", "answer": "The result of (985 - 352) is 633\n\n####633", "a": 985, "b": 352, "operator": "-", "result": 633}
{"question": "Solve (15 - 154)", "answer": "The result of (15 - 154) is -139\n\n####-139", "a": 15, "b": 154, "operator": "-", "result": -139}
{"question": "Solve (940 - 232)", "answer": "The result of (940 - 232) is 708\n\n####708", "a": 940, "b": 232, "operator": "-", "result": 708}
{"question": "Solve (677 - 788)", "answer": "The result of (677 - 788) is -111\n\n####-111", "a": 677, "b": 788, "operator": "-", "result": -111}
{"question": "Solve (514 - 701)", "answer": "The result of (514 - 701) is -187\n\n####-187", "a": 514, "b": 701, "operator": "-", "result": -187}
{"question": "Solve (630 - 178)", "answer": "The result of (630 - 178) is 452\n\n####452", "a": 630, "b": 178, "operator": "-", "result": 452}
{"question": "Solve (343 * 575)", "answer": "The result of (343 * 575) is 197225\n\n####197225", "a": 343, "b": 575, "operator": "*", "result": 197225}
{"question": "Solve (680 / 881)", "answer": "The result of (680 / 881) is 0.7719\n\n####0.7719", "a": 680, "b": 881, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7719}
{"question": "Solve (395 - 235)", "answer": "The result of (395 - 235) is 160\n\n####160", "a": 395, "b": 235, "operator": "-", "result": 160}
{"question": "Solve (254 - 603)", "answer": "The result of (254 - 603) is -349\n\n####-349", "a": 254, "b": 603, "operator": "-", "result": -349}
{"question": "Solve (236 - 102)", "answer": "The result of (236 - 102) is 134\n\n####134", "a": 236, "b": 102, "operator": "-", "result": 134}
{"question": "Solve (854 - 12)", "answer": "The result of (854 - 12) is 842\n\n####842", "a": 854, "b": 12, "operator": "-", "result": 842}
{"question": "Solve (842 - 473)", "answer": "The result of (842 - 473) is 369\n\n####369", "a": 842, "b": 473, "operator": "-", "result": 369}
{"question": "Solve (705 * 433)", "answer": "The result of (705 * 433) is 305265\n\n####305265", "a": 705, "b": 433, "operator": "*", "result": 305265}
{"question": "Solve (535 * 695)", "answer": "The result of (535 * 695) is 371825\n\n####371825", "a": 535, "b": 695, "operator": "*", "result": 371825}
{"question": "Solve (291 / 178)", "answer": "The result of (291 / 178) is 1.6348\n\n####1.6348", "a": 291, "b": 178, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6348}
{"question": "Solve (178 / 678)", "answer": "The result of (178 / 678) is 0.2625\n\n####0.2625", "a": 178, "b": 678, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2625}
{"question": "Solve (878 / 357)", "answer": "The result of (878 / 357) is 2.4594\n\n####2.4594", "a": 878, "b": 357, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4594}
{"question": "Solve (856 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (856 - 822) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 856, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (347 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (347 - 810) is -463\n\n####-463", "a": 347, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": -463}
{"question": "Solve (775 / 5)", "answer": "The result of (775 / 5) is 155.0\n\n####155.0", "a": 775, "b": 5, "operator": "/", "result": 155.0}
{"question": "Solve (222 / 668)", "answer": "The result of (222 / 668) is 0.3323\n\n####0.3323", "a": 222, "b": 668, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3323}
{"question": "Solve (203 + 929)", "answer": "The result of (203 + 929) is 1132\n\n####1132", "a": 203, "b": 929, "operator": "+", "result": 1132}
{"question": "Solve (951 * 595)", "answer": "The result of (951 * 595) is 565845\n\n####565845", "a": 951, "b": 595, "operator": "*", "result": 565845}
{"question": "Solve (936 / 612)", "answer": "The result of (936 / 612) is 1.5294\n\n####1.5294", "a": 936, "b": 612, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5294}
{"question": "Solve (99 / 563)", "answer": "The result of (99 / 563) is 0.1758\n\n####0.1758", "a": 99, "b": 563, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1758}
{"question": "Solve (336 * 82)", "answer": "The result of (336 * 82) is 27552\n\n####27552", "a": 336, "b": 82, "operator": "*", "result": 27552}
{"question": "Solve (881 + 122)", "answer": "The result of (881 + 122) is 1003\n\n####1003", "a": 881, "b": 122, "operator": "+", "result": 1003}
{"question": "Solve (494 - 271)", "answer": "The result of (494 - 271) is 223\n\n####223", "a": 494, "b": 271, "operator": "-", "result": 223}
{"question": "Solve (996 + 823)", "answer": "The result of (996 + 823) is 1819\n\n####1819", "a": 996, "b": 823, "operator": "+", "result": 1819}
{"question": "Solve (873 / 278)", "answer": "The result of (873 / 278) is 3.1403\n\n####3.1403", "a": 873, "b": 278, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1403}
{"question": "Solve (348 + 882)", "answer": "The result of (348 + 882) is 1230\n\n####1230", "a": 348, "b": 882, "operator": "+", "result": 1230}
{"question": "Solve (300 + 427)", "answer": "The result of (300 + 427) is 727\n\n####727", "a": 300, "b": 427, "operator": "+", "result": 727}
{"question": "Solve (135 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (135 / 504) is 0.2679\n\n####0.2679", "a": 135, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2679}
{"question": "Solve (317 - 809)", "answer": "The result of (317 - 809) is -492\n\n####-492", "a": 317, "b": 809, "operator": "-", "result": -492}
{"question": "Solve (363 / 460)", "answer": "The result of (363 / 460) is 0.7891\n\n####0.7891", "a": 363, "b": 460, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7891}
{"question": "Solve (873 / 710)", "answer": "The result of (873 / 710) is 1.2296\n\n####1.2296", "a": 873, "b": 710, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2296}
{"question": "Solve (468 - 649)", "answer": "The result of (468 - 649) is -181\n\n####-181", "a": 468, "b": 649, "operator": "-", "result": -181}
{"question": "Solve (988 + 166)", "answer": "The result of (988 + 166) is 1154\n\n####1154", "a": 988, "b": 166, "operator": "+", "result": 1154}
{"question": "Solve (411 - 634)", "answer": "The result of (411 - 634) is -223\n\n####-223", "a": 411, "b": 634, "operator": "-", "result": -223}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 874)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 874) is -577\n\n####-577", "a": 297, "b": 874, "operator": "-", "result": -577}
{"question": "Solve (882 - 553)", "answer": "The result of (882 - 553) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 882, "b": 553, "operator": "-", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (20 - 710)", "answer": "The result of (20 - 710) is -690\n\n####-690", "a": 20, "b": 710, "operator": "-", "result": -690}
{"question": "Solve (447 / 421)", "answer": "The result of (447 / 421) is 1.0618\n\n####1.0618", "a": 447, "b": 421, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0618}
{"question": "Solve (397 / 198)", "answer": "The result of (397 / 198) is 2.0051\n\n####2.0051", "a": 397, "b": 198, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0051}
{"question": "Solve (990 / 922)", "answer": "The result of (990 / 922) is 1.0738\n\n####1.0738", "a": 990, "b": 922, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0738}
{"question": "Solve (861 * 581)", "answer": "The result of (861 * 581) is 500241\n\n####500241", "a": 861, "b": 581, "operator": "*", "result": 500241}
{"question": "Solve (398 + 461)", "answer": "The result of (398 + 461) is 859\n\n####859", "a": 398, "b": 461, "operator": "+", "result": 859}
{"question": "Solve (193 / 670)", "answer": "The result of (193 / 670) is 0.2881\n\n####0.2881", "a": 193, "b": 670, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2881}
{"question": "Solve (792 / 853)", "answer": "The result of (792 / 853) is 0.9285\n\n####0.9285", "a": 792, "b": 853, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9285}
{"question": "Solve (733 - 478)", "answer": "The result of (733 - 478) is 255\n\n####255", "a": 733, "b": 478, "operator": "-", "result": 255}
{"question": "Solve (850 / 384)", "answer": "The result of (850 / 384) is 2.2135\n\n####2.2135", "a": 850, "b": 384, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2135}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 983)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 983) is 390251\n\n####390251", "a": 397, "b": 983, "operator": "*", "result": 390251}
{"question": "Solve (274 + 616)", "answer": "The result of (274 + 616) is 890\n\n####890", "a": 274, "b": 616, "operator": "+", "result": 890}
{"question": "Solve (602 - 22)", "answer": "The result of (602 - 22) is 580\n\n####580", "a": 602, "b": 22, "operator": "-", "result": 580}
{"question": "Solve (550 - 964)", "answer": "The result of (550 - 964) is -414\n\n####-414", "a": 550, "b": 964, "operator": "-", "result": -414}
{"question": "Solve (166 - 287)", "answer": "The result of (166 - 287) is -121\n\n####-121", "a": 166, "b": 287, "operator": "-", "result": -121}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 778)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 778) is -685\n\n####-685", "a": 93, "b": 778, "operator": "-", "result": -685}
{"question": "Solve (57 + 645)", "answer": "The result of (57 + 645) is 702\n\n####702", "a": 57, "b": 645, "operator": "+", "result": 702}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 643)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 643) is 362652\n\n####362652", "a": 564, "b": 643, "operator": "*", "result": 362652}
{"question": "Solve (843 * 749)", "answer": "The result of (843 * 749) is 631407\n\n####631407", "a": 843, "b": 749, "operator": "*", "result": 631407}
{"question": "Solve (246 + 706)", "answer": "The result of (246 + 706) is 952\n\n####952", "a": 246, "b": 706, "operator": "+", "result": 952}
{"question": "Solve (865 - 45)", "answer": "The result of (865 - 45) is 820\n\n####820", "a": 865, "b": 45, "operator": "-", "result": 820}
{"question": "Solve (488 + 479)", "answer": "The result of (488 + 479) is 967\n\n####967", "a": 488, "b": 479, "operator": "+", "result": 967}
{"question": "Solve (285 + 26)", "answer": "The result of (285 + 26) is 311\n\n####311", "a": 285, "b": 26, "operator": "+", "result": 311}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 886)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 886) is 1713\n\n####1713", "a": 827, "b": 886, "operator": "+", "result": 1713}
{"question": "Solve (298 - 4)", "answer": "The result of (298 - 4) is 294\n\n####294", "a": 298, "b": 4, "operator": "-", "result": 294}
{"question": "Solve (807 + 766)", "answer": "The result of (807 + 766) is 1573\n\n####1573", "a": 807, "b": 766, "operator": "+", "result": 1573}
{"question": "Solve (389 - 334)", "answer": "The result of (389 - 334) is 55\n\n####55", "a": 389, "b": 334, "operator": "-", "result": 55}
{"question": "Solve (819 * 659)", "answer": "The result of (819 * 659) is 539721\n\n####539721", "a": 819, "b": 659, "operator": "*", "result": 539721}
{"question": "Solve (968 / 195)", "answer": "The result of (968 / 195) is 4.9641\n\n####4.9641", "a": 968, "b": 195, "operator": "/", "result": 4.9641}
{"question": "Solve (417 - 826)", "answer": "The result of (417 - 826) is -409\n\n####-409", "a": 417, "b": 826, "operator": "-", "result": -409}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 697)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 697) is 1.297\n\n####1.297", "a": 904, "b": 697, "operator": "/", "result": 1.297}
{"question": "Solve (360 + 783)", "answer": "The result of (360 + 783) is 1143\n\n####1143", "a": 360, "b": 783, "operator": "+", "result": 1143}
{"question": "Solve (395 - 200)", "answer": "The result of (395 - 200) is 195\n\n####195", "a": 395, "b": 200, "operator": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve (516 + 472)", "answer": "The result of (516 + 472) is 988\n\n####988", "a": 516, "b": 472, "operator": "+", "result": 988}
{"question": "Solve (160 * 397)", "answer": "The result of (160 * 397) is 63520\n\n####63520", "a": 160, "b": 397, "operator": "*", "result": 63520}
{"question": "Solve (960 - 500)", "answer": "The result of (960 - 500) is 460\n\n####460", "a": 960, "b": 500, "operator": "-", "result": 460}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 244)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 244) is 127856\n\n####127856", "a": 524, "b": 244, "operator": "*", "result": 127856}
{"question": "Solve (980 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (980 / 815) is 1.2025\n\n####1.2025", "a": 980, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2025}
{"question": "Solve (71 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (71 / 453) is 0.1567\n\n####0.1567", "a": 71, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1567}
{"question": "Solve (62 / 934)", "answer": "The result of (62 / 934) is 0.0664\n\n####0.0664", "a": 62, "b": 934, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0664}
{"question": "Solve (444 + 688)", "answer": "The result of (444 + 688) is 1132\n\n####1132", "a": 444, "b": 688, "operator": "+", "result": 1132}
{"question": "Solve (312 + 734)", "answer": "The result of (312 + 734) is 1046\n\n####1046", "a": 312, "b": 734, "operator": "+", "result": 1046}
{"question": "Solve (283 - 43)", "answer": "The result of (283 - 43) is 240\n\n####240", "a": 283, "b": 43, "operator": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve (729 * 389)", "answer": "The result of (729 * 389) is 283581\n\n####283581", "a": 729, "b": 389, "operator": "*", "result": 283581}
{"question": "Solve (161 + 860)", "answer": "The result of (161 + 860) is 1021\n\n####1021", "a": 161, "b": 860, "operator": "+", "result": 1021}
{"question": "Solve (386 / 373)", "answer": "The result of (386 / 373) is 1.0349\n\n####1.0349", "a": 386, "b": 373, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0349}
{"question": "Solve (692 - 438)", "answer": "The result of (692 - 438) is 254\n\n####254", "a": 692, "b": 438, "operator": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve (599 * 522)", "answer": "The result of (599 * 522) is 312678\n\n####312678", "a": 599, "b": 522, "operator": "*", "result": 312678}
{"question": "Solve (894 + 545)", "answer": "The result of (894 + 545) is 1439\n\n####1439", "a": 894, "b": 545, "operator": "+", "result": 1439}
{"question": "Solve (724 * 850)", "answer": "The result of (724 * 850) is 615400\n\n####615400", "a": 724, "b": 850, "operator": "*", "result": 615400}
{"question": "Solve (493 * 204)", "answer": "The result of (493 * 204) is 100572\n\n####100572", "a": 493, "b": 204, "operator": "*", "result": 100572}
{"question": "Solve (808 - 2)", "answer": "The result of (808 - 2) is 806\n\n####806", "a": 808, "b": 2, "operator": "-", "result": 806}
{"question": "Solve (348 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (348 - 175) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 348, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (160 + 169)", "answer": "The result of (160 + 169) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 160, "b": 169, "operator": "+", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (996 * 507)", "answer": "The result of (996 * 507) is 504972\n\n####504972", "a": 996, "b": 507, "operator": "*", "result": 504972}
{"question": "Solve (732 / 947)", "answer": "The result of (732 / 947) is 0.773\n\n####0.773", "a": 732, "b": 947, "operator": "/", "result": 0.773}
{"question": "Solve (312 - 582)", "answer": "The result of (312 - 582) is -270\n\n####-270", "a": 312, "b": 582, "operator": "-", "result": -270}
{"question": "Solve (394 - 704)", "answer": "The result of (394 - 704) is -310\n\n####-310", "a": 394, "b": 704, "operator": "-", "result": -310}
{"question": "Solve (786 / 914)", "answer": "The result of (786 / 914) is 0.86\n\n####0.86", "a": 786, "b": 914, "operator": "/", "result": 0.86}
{"question": "Solve (931 / 603)", "answer": "The result of (931 / 603) is 1.5439\n\n####1.5439", "a": 931, "b": 603, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5439}
{"question": "Solve (403 - 236)", "answer": "The result of (403 - 236) is 167\n\n####167", "a": 403, "b": 236, "operator": "-", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve (432 / 169)", "answer": "The result of (432 / 169) is 2.5562\n\n####2.5562", "a": 432, "b": 169, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5562}
{"question": "Solve (651 / 392)", "answer": "The result of (651 / 392) is 1.6607\n\n####1.6607", "a": 651, "b": 392, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6607}
{"question": "Solve (530 - 130)", "answer": "The result of (530 - 130) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 530, "b": 130, "operator": "-", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (938 * 502)", "answer": "The result of (938 * 502) is 470876\n\n####470876", "a": 938, "b": 502, "operator": "*", "result": 470876}
{"question": "Solve (198 * 514)", "answer": "The result of (198 * 514) is 101772\n\n####101772", "a": 198, "b": 514, "operator": "*", "result": 101772}
{"question": "Solve (762 / 337)", "answer": "The result of (762 / 337) is 2.2611\n\n####2.2611", "a": 762, "b": 337, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2611}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 730)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 730) is -537\n\n####-537", "a": 193, "b": 730, "operator": "-", "result": -537}
{"question": "Solve (599 + 928)", "answer": "The result of (599 + 928) is 1527\n\n####1527", "a": 599, "b": 928, "operator": "+", "result": 1527}
{"question": "Solve (14 - 785)", "answer": "The result of (14 - 785) is -771\n\n####-771", "a": 14, "b": 785, "operator": "-", "result": -771}
{"question": "Solve (622 + 604)", "answer": "The result of (622 + 604) is 1226\n\n####1226", "a": 622, "b": 604, "operator": "+", "result": 1226}
{"question": "Solve (924 + 873)", "answer": "The result of (924 + 873) is 1797\n\n####1797", "a": 924, "b": 873, "operator": "+", "result": 1797}
{"question": "Solve (793 - 506)", "answer": "The result of (793 - 506) is 287\n\n####287", "a": 793, "b": 506, "operator": "-", "result": 287}
{"question": "Solve (832 + 432)", "answer": "The result of (832 + 432) is 1264\n\n####1264", "a": 832, "b": 432, "operator": "+", "result": 1264}
{"question": "Solve (972 + 611)", "answer": "The result of (972 + 611) is 1583\n\n####1583", "a": 972, "b": 611, "operator": "+", "result": 1583}
{"question": "Solve (800 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (800 - 409) is 391\n\n####391", "a": 800, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": 391}
{"question": "Solve (788 - 616)", "answer": "The result of (788 - 616) is 172\n\n####172", "a": 788, "b": 616, "operator": "-", "result": 172}
{"question": "Solve (795 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (795 / 623) is 1.2761\n\n####1.2761", "a": 795, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2761}
{"question": "Solve (370 * 893)", "answer": "The result of (370 * 893) is 330410\n\n####330410", "a": 370, "b": 893, "operator": "*", "result": 330410}
{"question": "Solve (842 / 511)", "answer": "The result of (842 / 511) is 1.6477\n\n####1.6477", "a": 842, "b": 511, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6477}
{"question": "Solve (96 / 130)", "answer": "The result of (96 / 130) is 0.7385\n\n####0.7385", "a": 96, "b": 130, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7385}
{"question": "Solve (364 + 110)", "answer": "The result of (364 + 110) is 474\n\n####474", "a": 364, "b": 110, "operator": "+", "result": 474}
{"question": "Solve (808 / 101)", "answer": "The result of (808 / 101) is 8.0\n\n####8.0", "a": 808, "b": 101, "operator": "/", "result": 8.0}
{"question": "Solve (712 - 17)", "answer": "The result of (712 - 17) is 695\n\n####695", "a": 712, "b": 17, "operator": "-", "result": 695}
{"question": "Solve (122 / 497)", "answer": "The result of (122 / 497) is 0.2455\n\n####0.2455", "a": 122, "b": 497, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2455}
{"question": "Solve (151 - 416)", "answer": "The result of (151 - 416) is -265\n\n####-265", "a": 151, "b": 416, "operator": "-", "result": -265}
{"question": "Solve (962 - 660)", "answer": "The result of (962 - 660) is 302\n\n####302", "a": 962, "b": 660, "operator": "-", "result": 302}
{"question": "Solve (608 / 339)", "answer": "The result of (608 / 339) is 1.7935\n\n####1.7935", "a": 608, "b": 339, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7935}
{"question": "Solve (679 / 727)", "answer": "The result of (679 / 727) is 0.934\n\n####0.934", "a": 679, "b": 727, "operator": "/", "result": 0.934}
{"question": "Solve (322 * 194)", "answer": "The result of (322 * 194) is 62468\n\n####62468", "a": 322, "b": 194, "operator": "*", "result": 62468}
{"question": "Solve (129 / 920)", "answer": "The result of (129 / 920) is 0.1402\n\n####0.1402", "a": 129, "b": 920, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1402}
{"question": "Solve (152 * 463)", "answer": "The result of (152 * 463) is 70376\n\n####70376", "a": 152, "b": 463, "operator": "*", "result": 70376}
{"question": "Solve (438 * 549)", "answer": "The result of (438 * 549) is 240462\n\n####240462", "a": 438, "b": 549, "operator": "*", "result": 240462}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 62)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 62) is 142\n\n####142", "a": 204, "b": 62, "operator": "-", "result": 142}
{"question": "Solve (738 / 950)", "answer": "The result of (738 / 950) is 0.7768\n\n####0.7768", "a": 738, "b": 950, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7768}
{"question": "Solve (642 / 46)", "answer": "The result of (642 / 46) is 13.9565\n\n####13.9565", "a": 642, "b": 46, "operator": "/", "result": 13.9565}
{"question": "Solve (464 * 361)", "answer": "The result of (464 * 361) is 167504\n\n####167504", "a": 464, "b": 361, "operator": "*", "result": 167504}
{"question": "Solve (299 / 91)", "answer": "The result of (299 / 91) is 3.2857\n\n####3.2857", "a": 299, "b": 91, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2857}
{"question": "Solve (333 - 717)", "answer": "The result of (333 - 717) is -384\n\n####-384", "a": 333, "b": 717, "operator": "-", "result": -384}
{"question": "Solve (87 / 436)", "answer": "The result of (87 / 436) is 0.1995\n\n####0.1995", "a": 87, "b": 436, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1995}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 623)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 623) is 0.5554\n\n####0.5554", "a": 346, "b": 623, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5554}
{"question": "Solve (36 * 768)", "answer": "The result of (36 * 768) is 27648\n\n####27648", "a": 36, "b": 768, "operator": "*", "result": 27648}
{"question": "Solve (424 + 624)", "answer": "The result of (424 + 624) is 1048\n\n####1048", "a": 424, "b": 624, "operator": "+", "result": 1048}
{"question": "Solve (654 - 979)", "answer": "The result of (654 - 979) is -325\n\n####-325", "a": 654, "b": 979, "operator": "-", "result": -325}
{"question": "Solve (145 / 207)", "answer": "The result of (145 / 207) is 0.7005\n\n####0.7005", "a": 145, "b": 207, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7005}
{"question": "Solve (835 + 587)", "answer": "The result of (835 + 587) is 1422\n\n####1422", "a": 835, "b": 587, "operator": "+", "result": 1422}
{"question": "Solve (950 - 684)", "answer": "The result of (950 - 684) is 266\n\n####266", "a": 950, "b": 684, "operator": "-", "result": 266}
{"question": "Solve (177 * 924)", "answer": "The result of (177 * 924) is 163548\n\n####163548", "a": 177, "b": 924, "operator": "*", "result": 163548}
{"question": "Solve (606 * 925)", "answer": "The result of (606 * 925) is 560550\n\n####560550", "a": 606, "b": 925, "operator": "*", "result": 560550}
{"question": "Solve (259 + 30)", "answer": "The result of (259 + 30) is 289\n\n####289", "a": 259, "b": 30, "operator": "+", "result": 289}
{"question": "Solve (571 - 493)", "answer": "The result of (571 - 493) is 78\n\n####78", "a": 571, "b": 493, "operator": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve (703 - 422)", "answer": "The result of (703 - 422) is 281\n\n####281", "a": 703, "b": 422, "operator": "-", "result": 281}
{"question": "Solve (543 / 901)", "answer": "The result of (543 / 901) is 0.6027\n\n####0.6027", "a": 543, "b": 901, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6027}
{"question": "Solve (568 / 783)", "answer": "The result of (568 / 783) is 0.7254\n\n####0.7254", "a": 568, "b": 783, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7254}
{"question": "Solve (384 / 997)", "answer": "The result of (384 / 997) is 0.3852\n\n####0.3852", "a": 384, "b": 997, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3852}
{"question": "Solve (812 * 326)", "answer": "The result of (812 * 326) is 264712\n\n####264712", "a": 812, "b": 326, "operator": "*", "result": 264712}
{"question": "Solve (180 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (180 / 411) is 0.438\n\n####0.438", "a": 180, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 0.438}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 409)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 409) is 157\n\n####157", "a": 566, "b": 409, "operator": "-", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve (580 * 678)", "answer": "The result of (580 * 678) is 393240\n\n####393240", "a": 580, "b": 678, "operator": "*", "result": 393240}
{"question": "Solve (113 + 596)", "answer": "The result of (113 + 596) is 709\n\n####709", "a": 113, "b": 596, "operator": "+", "result": 709}
{"question": "Solve (61 + 689)", "answer": "The result of (61 + 689) is 750\n\n####750", "a": 61, "b": 689, "operator": "+", "result": 750}
{"question": "Solve (748 / 314)", "answer": "The result of (748 / 314) is 2.3822\n\n####2.3822", "a": 748, "b": 314, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3822}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 361)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 361) is 1038\n\n####1038", "a": 677, "b": 361, "operator": "+", "result": 1038}
{"question": "Solve (984 - 502)", "answer": "The result of (984 - 502) is 482\n\n####482", "a": 984, "b": 502, "operator": "-", "result": 482}
{"question": "Solve (971 * 764)", "answer": "The result of (971 * 764) is 741844\n\n####741844", "a": 971, "b": 764, "operator": "*", "result": 741844}
{"question": "Solve (762 * 779)", "answer": "The result of (762 * 779) is 593598\n\n####593598", "a": 762, "b": 779, "operator": "*", "result": 593598}
{"question": "Solve (219 - 421)", "answer": "The result of (219 - 421) is -202\n\n####-202", "a": 219, "b": 421, "operator": "-", "result": -202}
{"question": "Solve (466 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (466 * 862) is 401692\n\n####401692", "a": 466, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 401692}
{"question": "Solve (415 + 799)", "answer": "The result of (415 + 799) is 1214\n\n####1214", "a": 415, "b": 799, "operator": "+", "result": 1214}
{"question": "Solve (966 + 381)", "answer": "The result of (966 + 381) is 1347\n\n####1347", "a": 966, "b": 381, "operator": "+", "result": 1347}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 839)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 839) is 620021\n\n####620021", "a": 739, "b": 839, "operator": "*", "result": 620021}
{"question": "Solve (768 / 88)", "answer": "The result of (768 / 88) is 8.7273\n\n####8.7273", "a": 768, "b": 88, "operator": "/", "result": 8.7273}
{"question": "Solve (36 * 354)", "answer": "The result of (36 * 354) is 12744\n\n####12744", "a": 36, "b": 354, "operator": "*", "result": 12744}
{"question": "Solve (206 - 984)", "answer": "The result of (206 - 984) is -778\n\n####-778", "a": 206, "b": 984, "operator": "-", "result": -778}
{"question": "Solve (77 / 25)", "answer": "The result of (77 / 25) is 3.08\n\n####3.08", "a": 77, "b": 25, "operator": "/", "result": 3.08}
{"question": "Solve (564 * 292)", "answer": "The result of (564 * 292) is 164688\n\n####164688", "a": 564, "b": 292, "operator": "*", "result": 164688}
{"question": "Solve (984 - 968)", "answer": "The result of (984 - 968) is 16\n\n####16", "a": 984, "b": 968, "operator": "-", "result": 16}
{"question": "Solve (620 * 329)", "answer": "The result of (620 * 329) is 203980\n\n####203980", "a": 620, "b": 329, "operator": "*", "result": 203980}
{"question": "Solve (980 + 815)", "answer": "The result of (980 + 815) is 1795\n\n####1795", "a": 980, "b": 815, "operator": "+", "result": 1795}
{"question": "Solve (503 * 897)", "answer": "The result of (503 * 897) is 451191\n\n####451191", "a": 503, "b": 897, "operator": "*", "result": 451191}
{"question": "Solve (411 * 863)", "answer": "The result of (411 * 863) is 354693\n\n####354693", "a": 411, "b": 863, "operator": "*", "result": 354693}
{"question": "Solve (931 * 784)", "answer": "The result of (931 * 784) is 729904\n\n####729904", "a": 931, "b": 784, "operator": "*", "result": 729904}
{"question": "Solve (811 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (811 + 11) is 822\n\n####822", "a": 811, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 822}
{"question": "Solve (831 + 309)", "answer": "The result of (831 + 309) is 1140\n\n####1140", "a": 831, "b": 309, "operator": "+", "result": 1140}
{"question": "Solve (288 + 286)", "answer": "The result of (288 + 286) is 574\n\n####574", "a": 288, "b": 286, "operator": "+", "result": 574}
{"question": "Solve (503 / 978)", "answer": "The result of (503 / 978) is 0.5143\n\n####0.5143", "a": 503, "b": 978, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5143}
{"question": "Solve (274 + 35)", "answer": "The result of (274 + 35) is 309\n\n####309", "a": 274, "b": 35, "operator": "+", "result": 309}
{"question": "Solve (178 - 865)", "answer": "The result of (178 - 865) is -687\n\n####-687", "a": 178, "b": 865, "operator": "-", "result": -687}
{"question": "Solve (740 + 131)", "answer": "The result of (740 + 131) is 871\n\n####871", "a": 740, "b": 131, "operator": "+", "result": 871}
{"question": "Solve (324 * 708)", "answer": "The result of (324 * 708) is 229392\n\n####229392", "a": 324, "b": 708, "operator": "*", "result": 229392}
{"question": "Solve (469 + 770)", "answer": "The result of (469 + 770) is 1239\n\n####1239", "a": 469, "b": 770, "operator": "+", "result": 1239}
{"question": "Solve (273 + 855)", "answer": "The result of (273 + 855) is 1128\n\n####1128", "a": 273, "b": 855, "operator": "+", "result": 1128}
{"question": "Solve (461 / 22)", "answer": "The result of (461 / 22) is 20.9545\n\n####20.9545", "a": 461, "b": 22, "operator": "/", "result": 20.9545}
{"question": "Solve (392 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (392 - 354) is 38\n\n####38", "a": 392, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": 38}
{"question": "Solve (593 - 802)", "answer": "The result of (593 - 802) is -209\n\n####-209", "a": 593, "b": 802, "operator": "-", "result": -209}
{"question": "Solve (995 - 202)", "answer": "The result of (995 - 202) is 793\n\n####793", "a": 995, "b": 202, "operator": "-", "result": 793}
{"question": "Solve (756 / 662)", "answer": "The result of (756 / 662) is 1.142\n\n####1.142", "a": 756, "b": 662, "operator": "/", "result": 1.142}
{"question": "Solve (671 / 105)", "answer": "The result of (671 / 105) is 6.3905\n\n####6.3905", "a": 671, "b": 105, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3905}
{"question": "Solve (203 - 352)", "answer": "The result of (203 - 352) is -149\n\n####-149", "a": 203, "b": 352, "operator": "-", "result": -149}
{"question": "Solve (978 * 788)", "answer": "The result of (978 * 788) is 770664\n\n####770664", "a": 978, "b": 788, "operator": "*", "result": 770664}
{"question": "Solve (308 - 902)", "answer": "The result of (308 - 902) is -594\n\n####-594", "a": 308, "b": 902, "operator": "-", "result": -594}
{"question": "Solve (448 - 381)", "answer": "The result of (448 - 381) is 67\n\n####67", "a": 448, "b": 381, "operator": "-", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 246)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 246) is 16236\n\n####16236", "a": 66, "b": 246, "operator": "*", "result": 16236}
{"question": "Solve (154 + 844)", "answer": "The result of (154 + 844) is 998\n\n####998", "a": 154, "b": 844, "operator": "+", "result": 998}
{"question": "Solve (556 / 671)", "answer": "The result of (556 / 671) is 0.8286\n\n####0.8286", "a": 556, "b": 671, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8286}
{"question": "Solve (177 * 568)", "answer": "The result of (177 * 568) is 100536\n\n####100536", "a": 177, "b": 568, "operator": "*", "result": 100536}
{"question": "Solve (717 - 202)", "answer": "The result of (717 - 202) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 717, "b": 202, "operator": "-", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (40 - 989)", "answer": "The result of (40 - 989) is -949\n\n####-949", "a": 40, "b": 989, "operator": "-", "result": -949}
{"question": "Solve (492 / 305)", "answer": "The result of (492 / 305) is 1.6131\n\n####1.6131", "a": 492, "b": 305, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6131}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 526)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 526) is 275624\n\n####275624", "a": 524, "b": 526, "operator": "*", "result": 275624}
{"question": "Solve (303 + 212)", "answer": "The result of (303 + 212) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 303, "b": 212, "operator": "+", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 358)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 358) is 72\n\n####72", "a": 430, "b": 358, "operator": "-", "result": 72}
{"question": "Solve (917 - 253)", "answer": "The result of (917 - 253) is 664\n\n####664", "a": 917, "b": 253, "operator": "-", "result": 664}
{"question": "Solve (3 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (3 + 259) is 262\n\n####262", "a": 3, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve (846 * 681)", "answer": "The result of (846 * 681) is 576126\n\n####576126", "a": 846, "b": 681, "operator": "*", "result": 576126}
{"question": "Solve (700 - 351)", "answer": "The result of (700 - 351) is 349\n\n####349", "a": 700, "b": 351, "operator": "-", "result": 349}
{"question": "Solve (905 / 717)", "answer": "The result of (905 / 717) is 1.2622\n\n####1.2622", "a": 905, "b": 717, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2622}
{"question": "Solve (959 - 954)", "answer": "The result of (959 - 954) is 5\n\n####5", "a": 959, "b": 954, "operator": "-", "result": 5}
{"question": "Solve (30 / 648)", "answer": "The result of (30 / 648) is 0.0463\n\n####0.0463", "a": 30, "b": 648, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0463}
{"question": "Solve (66 * 688)", "answer": "The result of (66 * 688) is 45408\n\n####45408", "a": 66, "b": 688, "operator": "*", "result": 45408}
{"question": "Solve (93 / 560)", "answer": "The result of (93 / 560) is 0.1661\n\n####0.1661", "a": 93, "b": 560, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1661}
{"question": "Solve (982 + 95)", "answer": "The result of (982 + 95) is 1077\n\n####1077", "a": 982, "b": 95, "operator": "+", "result": 1077}
{"question": "Solve (329 * 73)", "answer": "The result of (329 * 73) is 24017\n\n####24017", "a": 329, "b": 73, "operator": "*", "result": 24017}
{"question": "Solve (37 - 304)", "answer": "The result of (37 - 304) is -267\n\n####-267", "a": 37, "b": 304, "operator": "-", "result": -267}
{"question": "Solve (687 + 637)", "answer": "The result of (687 + 637) is 1324\n\n####1324", "a": 687, "b": 637, "operator": "+", "result": 1324}
{"question": "Solve (201 - 53)", "answer": "The result of (201 - 53) is 148\n\n####148", "a": 201, "b": 53, "operator": "-", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve (856 / 163)", "answer": "The result of (856 / 163) is 5.2515\n\n####5.2515", "a": 856, "b": 163, "operator": "/", "result": 5.2515}
{"question": "Solve (927 + 825)", "answer": "The result of (927 + 825) is 1752\n\n####1752", "a": 927, "b": 825, "operator": "+", "result": 1752}
{"question": "Solve (905 + 516)", "answer": "The result of (905 + 516) is 1421\n\n####1421", "a": 905, "b": 516, "operator": "+", "result": 1421}
{"question": "Solve (273 - 440)", "answer": "The result of (273 - 440) is -167\n\n####-167", "a": 273, "b": 440, "operator": "-", "result": -167}
{"question": "Solve (244 - 380)", "answer": "The result of (244 - 380) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 244, "b": 380, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (940 + 728)", "answer": "The result of (940 + 728) is 1668\n\n####1668", "a": 940, "b": 728, "operator": "+", "result": 1668}
{"question": "Solve (271 / 729)", "answer": "The result of (271 / 729) is 0.3717\n\n####0.3717", "a": 271, "b": 729, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3717}
{"question": "Solve (414 + 808)", "answer": "The result of (414 + 808) is 1222\n\n####1222", "a": 414, "b": 808, "operator": "+", "result": 1222}
{"question": "Solve (336 / 93)", "answer": "The result of (336 / 93) is 3.6129\n\n####3.6129", "a": 336, "b": 93, "operator": "/", "result": 3.6129}
{"question": "Solve (589 - 630)", "answer": "The result of (589 - 630) is -41\n\n####-41", "a": 589, "b": 630, "operator": "-", "result": -41}
{"question": "Solve (859 * 582)", "answer": "The result of (859 * 582) is 499938\n\n####499938", "a": 859, "b": 582, "operator": "*", "result": 499938}
{"question": "Solve (496 - 925)", "answer": "The result of (496 - 925) is -429\n\n####-429", "a": 496, "b": 925, "operator": "-", "result": -429}
{"question": "Solve (479 + 959)", "answer": "The result of (479 + 959) is 1438\n\n####1438", "a": 479, "b": 959, "operator": "+", "result": 1438}
{"question": "Solve (413 - 746)", "answer": "The result of (413 - 746) is -333\n\n####-333", "a": 413, "b": 746, "operator": "-", "result": -333}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 846)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 846) is 1673\n\n####1673", "a": 827, "b": 846, "operator": "+", "result": 1673}
{"question": "Solve (770 + 418)", "answer": "The result of (770 + 418) is 1188\n\n####1188", "a": 770, "b": 418, "operator": "+", "result": 1188}
{"question": "Solve (256 + 650)", "answer": "The result of (256 + 650) is 906\n\n####906", "a": 256, "b": 650, "operator": "+", "result": 906}
{"question": "Solve (643 * 473)", "answer": "The result of (643 * 473) is 304139\n\n####304139", "a": 643, "b": 473, "operator": "*", "result": 304139}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 29)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 29) is 463\n\n####463", "a": 492, "b": 29, "operator": "-", "result": 463}
{"question": "Solve (889 * 554)", "answer": "The result of (889 * 554) is 492506\n\n####492506", "a": 889, "b": 554, "operator": "*", "result": 492506}
{"question": "Solve (746 / 450)", "answer": "The result of (746 / 450) is 1.6578\n\n####1.6578", "a": 746, "b": 450, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6578}
{"question": "Solve (423 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (423 - 724) is -301\n\n####-301", "a": 423, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -301}
{"question": "Solve (955 - 656)", "answer": "The result of (955 - 656) is 299\n\n####299", "a": 955, "b": 656, "operator": "-", "result": 299}
{"question": "Solve (289 - 508)", "answer": "The result of (289 - 508) is -219\n\n####-219", "a": 289, "b": 508, "operator": "-", "result": -219}
{"question": "Solve (733 / 503)", "answer": "The result of (733 / 503) is 1.4573\n\n####1.4573", "a": 733, "b": 503, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4573}
{"question": "Solve (828 - 687)", "answer": "The result of (828 - 687) is 141\n\n####141", "a": 828, "b": 687, "operator": "-", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve (691 - 27)", "answer": "The result of (691 - 27) is 664\n\n####664", "a": 691, "b": 27, "operator": "-", "result": 664}
{"question": "Solve (196 / 263)", "answer": "The result of (196 / 263) is 0.7452\n\n####0.7452", "a": 196, "b": 263, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7452}
{"question": "Solve (15 - 889)", "answer": "The result of (15 - 889) is -874\n\n####-874", "a": 15, "b": 889, "operator": "-", "result": -874}
{"question": "Solve (64 - 385)", "answer": "The result of (64 - 385) is -321\n\n####-321", "a": 64, "b": 385, "operator": "-", "result": -321}
{"question": "Solve (617 / 534)", "answer": "The result of (617 / 534) is 1.1554\n\n####1.1554", "a": 617, "b": 534, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1554}
{"question": "Solve (765 + 981)", "answer": "The result of (765 + 981) is 1746\n\n####1746", "a": 765, "b": 981, "operator": "+", "result": 1746}
{"question": "Solve (113 + 69)", "answer": "The result of (113 + 69) is 182\n\n####182", "a": 113, "b": 69, "operator": "+", "result": 182}
{"question": "Solve (224 - 369)", "answer": "The result of (224 - 369) is -145\n\n####-145", "a": 224, "b": 369, "operator": "-", "result": -145}
{"question": "Solve (642 * 28)", "answer": "The result of (642 * 28) is 17976\n\n####17976", "a": 642, "b": 28, "operator": "*", "result": 17976}
{"question": "Solve (633 * 79)", "answer": "The result of (633 * 79) is 50007\n\n####50007", "a": 633, "b": 79, "operator": "*", "result": 50007}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 637)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 637) is 329\n\n####329", "a": 966, "b": 637, "operator": "-", "result": 329}
{"question": "Solve (553 - 860)", "answer": "The result of (553 - 860) is -307\n\n####-307", "a": 553, "b": 860, "operator": "-", "result": -307}
{"question": "Solve (150 * 785)", "answer": "The result of (150 * 785) is 117750\n\n####117750", "a": 150, "b": 785, "operator": "*", "result": 117750}
{"question": "Solve (347 / 55)", "answer": "The result of (347 / 55) is 6.3091\n\n####6.3091", "a": 347, "b": 55, "operator": "/", "result": 6.3091}
{"question": "Solve (534 * 603)", "answer": "The result of (534 * 603) is 322002\n\n####322002", "a": 534, "b": 603, "operator": "*", "result": 322002}
{"question": "Solve (61 + 345)", "answer": "The result of (61 + 345) is 406\n\n####406", "a": 61, "b": 345, "operator": "+", "result": 406}
{"question": "Solve (253 - 762)", "answer": "The result of (253 - 762) is -509\n\n####-509", "a": 253, "b": 762, "operator": "-", "result": -509}
{"question": "Solve (592 * 145)", "answer": "The result of (592 * 145) is 85840\n\n####85840", "a": 592, "b": 145, "operator": "*", "result": 85840}
{"question": "Solve (344 * 510)", "answer": "The result of (344 * 510) is 175440\n\n####175440", "a": 344, "b": 510, "operator": "*", "result": 175440}
{"question": "Solve (647 * 829)", "answer": "The result of (647 * 829) is 536363\n\n####536363", "a": 647, "b": 829, "operator": "*", "result": 536363}
{"question": "Solve (544 * 512)", "answer": "The result of (544 * 512) is 278528\n\n####278528", "a": 544, "b": 512, "operator": "*", "result": 278528}
{"question": "Solve (430 - 429)", "answer": "The result of (430 - 429) is 1\n\n####1", "a": 430, "b": 429, "operator": "-", "result": 1}
{"question": "Solve (316 * 386)", "answer": "The result of (316 * 386) is 121976\n\n####121976", "a": 316, "b": 386, "operator": "*", "result": 121976}
{"question": "Solve (982 - 942)", "answer": "The result of (982 - 942) is 40\n\n####40", "a": 982, "b": 942, "operator": "-", "result": 40}
{"question": "Solve (808 / 948)", "answer": "The result of (808 / 948) is 0.8523\n\n####0.8523", "a": 808, "b": 948, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8523}
{"question": "Solve (182 / 195)", "answer": "The result of (182 / 195) is 0.9333\n\n####0.9333", "a": 182, "b": 195, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9333}
{"question": "Solve (471 - 740)", "answer": "The result of (471 - 740) is -269\n\n####-269", "a": 471, "b": 740, "operator": "-", "result": -269}
{"question": "Solve (409 - 22)", "answer": "The result of (409 - 22) is 387\n\n####387", "a": 409, "b": 22, "operator": "-", "result": 387}
{"question": "Solve (260 + 278)", "answer": "The result of (260 + 278) is 538\n\n####538", "a": 260, "b": 278, "operator": "+", "result": 538}
{"question": "Solve (697 * 306)", "answer": "The result of (697 * 306) is 213282\n\n####213282", "a": 697, "b": 306, "operator": "*", "result": 213282}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 968)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 968) is -686\n\n####-686", "a": 282, "b": 968, "operator": "-", "result": -686}
{"question": "Solve (655 - 567)", "answer": "The result of (655 - 567) is 88\n\n####88", "a": 655, "b": 567, "operator": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve (892 * 559)", "answer": "The result of (892 * 559) is 498628\n\n####498628", "a": 892, "b": 559, "operator": "*", "result": 498628}
{"question": "Solve (294 + 428)", "answer": "The result of (294 + 428) is 722\n\n####722", "a": 294, "b": 428, "operator": "+", "result": 722}
{"question": "Solve (44 / 860)", "answer": "The result of (44 / 860) is 0.0512\n\n####0.0512", "a": 44, "b": 860, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0512}
{"question": "Solve (339 - 560)", "answer": "The result of (339 - 560) is -221\n\n####-221", "a": 339, "b": 560, "operator": "-", "result": -221}
{"question": "Solve (750 / 214)", "answer": "The result of (750 / 214) is 3.5047\n\n####3.5047", "a": 750, "b": 214, "operator": "/", "result": 3.5047}
{"question": "Solve (664 / 992)", "answer": "The result of (664 / 992) is 0.6694\n\n####0.6694", "a": 664, "b": 992, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6694}
{"question": "Solve (894 / 142)", "answer": "The result of (894 / 142) is 6.2958\n\n####6.2958", "a": 894, "b": 142, "operator": "/", "result": 6.2958}
{"question": "Solve (243 + 917)", "answer": "The result of (243 + 917) is 1160\n\n####1160", "a": 243, "b": 917, "operator": "+", "result": 1160}
{"question": "Solve (908 / 768)", "answer": "The result of (908 / 768) is 1.1823\n\n####1.1823", "a": 908, "b": 768, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1823}
{"question": "Solve (85 + 728)", "answer": "The result of (85 + 728) is 813\n\n####813", "a": 85, "b": 728, "operator": "+", "result": 813}
{"question": "Solve (706 - 306)", "answer": "The result of (706 - 306) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 706, "b": 306, "operator": "-", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (478 + 905)", "answer": "The result of (478 + 905) is 1383\n\n####1383", "a": 478, "b": 905, "operator": "+", "result": 1383}
{"question": "Solve (56 - 58)", "answer": "The result of (56 - 58) is -2\n\n####-2", "a": 56, "b": 58, "operator": "-", "result": -2}
{"question": "Solve (44 - 945)", "answer": "The result of (44 - 945) is -901\n\n####-901", "a": 44, "b": 945, "operator": "-", "result": -901}
{"question": "Solve (787 * 205)", "answer": "The result of (787 * 205) is 161335\n\n####161335", "a": 787, "b": 205, "operator": "*", "result": 161335}
{"question": "Solve (799 * 991)", "answer": "The result of (799 * 991) is 791809\n\n####791809", "a": 799, "b": 991, "operator": "*", "result": 791809}
{"question": "Solve (737 / 466)", "answer": "The result of (737 / 466) is 1.5815\n\n####1.5815", "a": 737, "b": 466, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5815}
{"question": "Solve (501 / 710)", "answer": "The result of (501 / 710) is 0.7056\n\n####0.7056", "a": 501, "b": 710, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7056}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 264)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 264) is 23496\n\n####23496", "a": 89, "b": 264, "operator": "*", "result": 23496}
{"question": "Solve (550 + 108)", "answer": "The result of (550 + 108) is 658\n\n####658", "a": 550, "b": 108, "operator": "+", "result": 658}
{"question": "Solve (458 / 632)", "answer": "The result of (458 / 632) is 0.7247\n\n####0.7247", "a": 458, "b": 632, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7247}
{"question": "Solve (466 - 87)", "answer": "The result of (466 - 87) is 379\n\n####379", "a": 466, "b": 87, "operator": "-", "result": 379}
{"question": "Solve (783 + 183)", "answer": "The result of (783 + 183) is 966\n\n####966", "a": 783, "b": 183, "operator": "+", "result": 966}
{"question": "Solve (518 - 665)", "answer": "The result of (518 - 665) is -147\n\n####-147", "a": 518, "b": 665, "operator": "-", "result": -147}
{"question": "Solve (37 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (37 + 19) is 56\n\n####56", "a": 37, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 624)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 624) is -26\n\n####-26", "a": 598, "b": 624, "operator": "-", "result": -26}
{"question": "Solve (753 + 445)", "answer": "The result of (753 + 445) is 1198\n\n####1198", "a": 753, "b": 445, "operator": "+", "result": 1198}
{"question": "Solve (547 / 310)", "answer": "The result of (547 / 310) is 1.7645\n\n####1.7645", "a": 547, "b": 310, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7645}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 647)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 647) is 103\n\n####103", "a": 750, "b": 647, "operator": "-", "result": 103}
{"question": "Solve (792 / 734)", "answer": "The result of (792 / 734) is 1.079\n\n####1.079", "a": 792, "b": 734, "operator": "/", "result": 1.079}
{"question": "Solve (971 / 813)", "answer": "The result of (971 / 813) is 1.1943\n\n####1.1943", "a": 971, "b": 813, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1943}
{"question": "Solve (822 - 107)", "answer": "The result of (822 - 107) is 715\n\n####715", "a": 822, "b": 107, "operator": "-", "result": 715}
{"question": "Solve (425 + 181)", "answer": "The result of (425 + 181) is 606\n\n####606", "a": 425, "b": 181, "operator": "+", "result": 606}
{"question": "Solve (694 / 510)", "answer": "The result of (694 / 510) is 1.3608\n\n####1.3608", "a": 694, "b": 510, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3608}
{"question": "Solve (201 + 787)", "answer": "The result of (201 + 787) is 988\n\n####988", "a": 201, "b": 787, "operator": "+", "result": 988}
{"question": "Solve (937 * 4)", "answer": "The result of (937 * 4) is 3748\n\n####3748", "a": 937, "b": 4, "operator": "*", "result": 3748}
{"question": "Solve (230 - 142)", "answer": "The result of (230 - 142) is 88\n\n####88", "a": 230, "b": 142, "operator": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve (600 / 486)", "answer": "The result of (600 / 486) is 1.2346\n\n####1.2346", "a": 600, "b": 486, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2346}
{"question": "Solve (417 + 586)", "answer": "The result of (417 + 586) is 1003\n\n####1003", "a": 417, "b": 586, "operator": "+", "result": 1003}
{"question": "Solve (9 + 49)", "answer": "The result of (9 + 49) is 58\n\n####58", "a": 9, "b": 49, "operator": "+", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve (448 - 292)", "answer": "The result of (448 - 292) is 156\n\n####156", "a": 448, "b": 292, "operator": "-", "result": 156}
{"question": "Solve (686 + 390)", "answer": "The result of (686 + 390) is 1076\n\n####1076", "a": 686, "b": 390, "operator": "+", "result": 1076}
{"question": "Solve (967 * 829)", "answer": "The result of (967 * 829) is 801643\n\n####801643", "a": 967, "b": 829, "operator": "*", "result": 801643}
{"question": "Solve (635 / 940)", "answer": "The result of (635 / 940) is 0.6755\n\n####0.6755", "a": 635, "b": 940, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6755}
{"question": "Solve (361 / 266)", "answer": "The result of (361 / 266) is 1.3571\n\n####1.3571", "a": 361, "b": 266, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3571}
{"question": "Solve (871 - 266)", "answer": "The result of (871 - 266) is 605\n\n####605", "a": 871, "b": 266, "operator": "-", "result": 605}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 616)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 616) is -583\n\n####-583", "a": 33, "b": 616, "operator": "-", "result": -583}
{"question": "Solve (327 - 141)", "answer": "The result of (327 - 141) is 186\n\n####186", "a": 327, "b": 141, "operator": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve (910 * 600)", "answer": "The result of (910 * 600) is 546000\n\n####546000", "a": 910, "b": 600, "operator": "*", "result": 546000}
{"question": "Solve (972 - 369)", "answer": "The result of (972 - 369) is 603\n\n####603", "a": 972, "b": 369, "operator": "-", "result": 603}
{"question": "Solve (650 / 227)", "answer": "The result of (650 / 227) is 2.8634\n\n####2.8634", "a": 650, "b": 227, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8634}
{"question": "Solve (839 / 373)", "answer": "The result of (839 / 373) is 2.2493\n\n####2.2493", "a": 839, "b": 373, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2493}
{"question": "Solve (104 * 216)", "answer": "The result of (104 * 216) is 22464\n\n####22464", "a": 104, "b": 216, "operator": "*", "result": 22464}
{"question": "Solve (914 * 791)", "answer": "The result of (914 * 791) is 722974\n\n####722974", "a": 914, "b": 791, "operator": "*", "result": 722974}
{"question": "Solve (191 / 753)", "answer": "The result of (191 / 753) is 0.2537\n\n####0.2537", "a": 191, "b": 753, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2537}
{"question": "Solve (590 * 632)", "answer": "The result of (590 * 632) is 372880\n\n####372880", "a": 590, "b": 632, "operator": "*", "result": 372880}
{"question": "Solve (954 + 772)", "answer": "The result of (954 + 772) is 1726\n\n####1726", "a": 954, "b": 772, "operator": "+", "result": 1726}
{"question": "Solve (750 / 527)", "answer": "The result of (750 / 527) is 1.4231\n\n####1.4231", "a": 750, "b": 527, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4231}
{"question": "Solve (709 + 671)", "answer": "The result of (709 + 671) is 1380\n\n####1380", "a": 709, "b": 671, "operator": "+", "result": 1380}
{"question": "Solve (496 + 529)", "answer": "The result of (496 + 529) is 1025\n\n####1025", "a": 496, "b": 529, "operator": "+", "result": 1025}
{"question": "Solve (918 / 136)", "answer": "The result of (918 / 136) is 6.75\n\n####6.75", "a": 918, "b": 136, "operator": "/", "result": 6.75}
{"question": "Solve (974 * 319)", "answer": "The result of (974 * 319) is 310706\n\n####310706", "a": 974, "b": 319, "operator": "*", "result": 310706}
{"question": "Solve (5 - 311)", "answer": "The result of (5 - 311) is -306\n\n####-306", "a": 5, "b": 311, "operator": "-", "result": -306}
{"question": "Solve (995 / 477)", "answer": "The result of (995 / 477) is 2.086\n\n####2.086", "a": 995, "b": 477, "operator": "/", "result": 2.086}
{"question": "Solve (167 / 272)", "answer": "The result of (167 / 272) is 0.614\n\n####0.614", "a": 167, "b": 272, "operator": "/", "result": 0.614}
{"question": "Solve (72 * 503)", "answer": "The result of (72 * 503) is 36216\n\n####36216", "a": 72, "b": 503, "operator": "*", "result": 36216}
{"question": "Solve (875 / 433)", "answer": "The result of (875 / 433) is 2.0208\n\n####2.0208", "a": 875, "b": 433, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0208}
{"question": "Solve (141 - 871)", "answer": "The result of (141 - 871) is -730\n\n####-730", "a": 141, "b": 871, "operator": "-", "result": -730}
{"question": "Solve (576 / 695)", "answer": "The result of (576 / 695) is 0.8288\n\n####0.8288", "a": 576, "b": 695, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8288}
{"question": "Solve (932 * 178)", "answer": "The result of (932 * 178) is 165896\n\n####165896", "a": 932, "b": 178, "operator": "*", "result": 165896}
{"question": "Solve (454 + 259)", "answer": "The result of (454 + 259) is 713\n\n####713", "a": 454, "b": 259, "operator": "+", "result": 713}
{"question": "Solve (771 / 402)", "answer": "The result of (771 / 402) is 1.9179\n\n####1.9179", "a": 771, "b": 402, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9179}
{"question": "Solve (605 * 526)", "answer": "The result of (605 * 526) is 318230\n\n####318230", "a": 605, "b": 526, "operator": "*", "result": 318230}
{"question": "Solve (342 - 763)", "answer": "The result of (342 - 763) is -421\n\n####-421", "a": 342, "b": 763, "operator": "-", "result": -421}
{"question": "Solve (427 - 434)", "answer": "The result of (427 - 434) is -7\n\n####-7", "a": 427, "b": 434, "operator": "-", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve (660 / 352)", "answer": "The result of (660 / 352) is 1.875\n\n####1.875", "a": 660, "b": 352, "operator": "/", "result": 1.875}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 498)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 498) is 152\n\n####152", "a": 650, "b": 498, "operator": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve (469 - 286)", "answer": "The result of (469 - 286) is 183\n\n####183", "a": 469, "b": 286, "operator": "-", "result": 183}
{"question": "Solve (332 / 536)", "answer": "The result of (332 / 536) is 0.6194\n\n####0.6194", "a": 332, "b": 536, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6194}
{"question": "Solve (136 - 592)", "answer": "The result of (136 - 592) is -456\n\n####-456", "a": 136, "b": 592, "operator": "-", "result": -456}
{"question": "Solve (923 * 59)", "answer": "The result of (923 * 59) is 54457\n\n####54457", "a": 923, "b": 59, "operator": "*", "result": 54457}
{"question": "Solve (727 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (727 + 11) is 738\n\n####738", "a": 727, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 738}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 22)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 22) is 16258\n\n####16258", "a": 739, "b": 22, "operator": "*", "result": 16258}
{"question": "Solve (620 - 462)", "answer": "The result of (620 - 462) is 158\n\n####158", "a": 620, "b": 462, "operator": "-", "result": 158}
{"question": "Solve (320 + 843)", "answer": "The result of (320 + 843) is 1163\n\n####1163", "a": 320, "b": 843, "operator": "+", "result": 1163}
{"question": "Solve (976 * 81)", "answer": "The result of (976 * 81) is 79056\n\n####79056", "a": 976, "b": 81, "operator": "*", "result": 79056}
{"question": "Solve (2 + 821)", "answer": "The result of (2 + 821) is 823\n\n####823", "a": 2, "b": 821, "operator": "+", "result": 823}
{"question": "Solve (29 * 807)", "answer": "The result of (29 * 807) is 23403\n\n####23403", "a": 29, "b": 807, "operator": "*", "result": 23403}
{"question": "Solve (546 * 175)", "answer": "The result of (546 * 175) is 95550\n\n####95550", "a": 546, "b": 175, "operator": "*", "result": 95550}
{"question": "Solve (486 - 85)", "answer": "The result of (486 - 85) is 401\n\n####401", "a": 486, "b": 85, "operator": "-", "result": 401}
{"question": "Solve (292 + 279)", "answer": "The result of (292 + 279) is 571\n\n####571", "a": 292, "b": 279, "operator": "+", "result": 571}
{"question": "Solve (628 + 725)", "answer": "The result of (628 + 725) is 1353\n\n####1353", "a": 628, "b": 725, "operator": "+", "result": 1353}
{"question": "Solve (163 - 531)", "answer": "The result of (163 - 531) is -368\n\n####-368", "a": 163, "b": 531, "operator": "-", "result": -368}
{"question": "Solve (631 * 314)", "answer": "The result of (631 * 314) is 198134\n\n####198134", "a": 631, "b": 314, "operator": "*", "result": 198134}
{"question": "Solve (17 / 996)", "answer": "The result of (17 / 996) is 0.0171\n\n####0.0171", "a": 17, "b": 996, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0171}
{"question": "Solve (505 + 205)", "answer": "The result of (505 + 205) is 710\n\n####710", "a": 505, "b": 205, "operator": "+", "result": 710}
{"question": "Solve (21 + 763)", "answer": "The result of (21 + 763) is 784\n\n####784", "a": 21, "b": 763, "operator": "+", "result": 784}
{"question": "Solve (67 - 419)", "answer": "The result of (67 - 419) is -352\n\n####-352", "a": 67, "b": 419, "operator": "-", "result": -352}
{"question": "Solve (448 / 76)", "answer": "The result of (448 / 76) is 5.8947\n\n####5.8947", "a": 448, "b": 76, "operator": "/", "result": 5.8947}
{"question": "Solve (500 - 499)", "answer": "The result of (500 - 499) is 1\n\n####1", "a": 500, "b": 499, "operator": "-", "result": 1}
{"question": "Solve (48 - 210)", "answer": "The result of (48 - 210) is -162\n\n####-162", "a": 48, "b": 210, "operator": "-", "result": -162}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 831)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 831) is -614\n\n####-614", "a": 217, "b": 831, "operator": "-", "result": -614}
{"question": "Solve (323 + 651)", "answer": "The result of (323 + 651) is 974\n\n####974", "a": 323, "b": 651, "operator": "+", "result": 974}
{"question": "Solve (474 * 421)", "answer": "The result of (474 * 421) is 199554\n\n####199554", "a": 474, "b": 421, "operator": "*", "result": 199554}
{"question": "Solve (582 / 182)", "answer": "The result of (582 / 182) is 3.1978\n\n####3.1978", "a": 582, "b": 182, "operator": "/", "result": 3.1978}
{"question": "Solve (485 + 573)", "answer": "The result of (485 + 573) is 1058\n\n####1058", "a": 485, "b": 573, "operator": "+", "result": 1058}
{"question": "Solve (431 * 484)", "answer": "The result of (431 * 484) is 208604\n\n####208604", "a": 431, "b": 484, "operator": "*", "result": 208604}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 57)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 57) is 6.0702\n\n####6.0702", "a": 346, "b": 57, "operator": "/", "result": 6.0702}
{"question": "Solve (945 / 858)", "answer": "The result of (945 / 858) is 1.1014\n\n####1.1014", "a": 945, "b": 858, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1014}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 257)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 257) is -28\n\n####-28", "a": 229, "b": 257, "operator": "-", "result": -28}
{"question": "Solve (787 + 326)", "answer": "The result of (787 + 326) is 1113\n\n####1113", "a": 787, "b": 326, "operator": "+", "result": 1113}
{"question": "Solve (791 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (791 / 504) is 1.5694\n\n####1.5694", "a": 791, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5694}
{"question": "Solve (666 - 17)", "answer": "The result of (666 - 17) is 649\n\n####649", "a": 666, "b": 17, "operator": "-", "result": 649}
{"question": "Solve (439 + 859)", "answer": "The result of (439 + 859) is 1298\n\n####1298", "a": 439, "b": 859, "operator": "+", "result": 1298}
{"question": "Solve (107 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (107 - 169) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 107, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 286)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 286) is 2.8322\n\n####2.8322", "a": 810, "b": 286, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8322}
{"question": "Solve (194 + 878)", "answer": "The result of (194 + 878) is 1072\n\n####1072", "a": 194, "b": 878, "operator": "+", "result": 1072}
{"question": "Solve (391 / 916)", "answer": "The result of (391 / 916) is 0.4269\n\n####0.4269", "a": 391, "b": 916, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4269}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 46)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 46) is 1.913\n\n####1.913", "a": 88, "b": 46, "operator": "/", "result": 1.913}
{"question": "Solve (753 * 596)", "answer": "The result of (753 * 596) is 448788\n\n####448788", "a": 753, "b": 596, "operator": "*", "result": 448788}
{"question": "Solve (292 * 676)", "answer": "The result of (292 * 676) is 197392\n\n####197392", "a": 292, "b": 676, "operator": "*", "result": 197392}
{"question": "Solve (262 / 219)", "answer": "The result of (262 / 219) is 1.1963\n\n####1.1963", "a": 262, "b": 219, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1963}
{"question": "Solve (727 / 880)", "answer": "The result of (727 / 880) is 0.8261\n\n####0.8261", "a": 727, "b": 880, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8261}
{"question": "Solve (320 / 243)", "answer": "The result of (320 / 243) is 1.3169\n\n####1.3169", "a": 320, "b": 243, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3169}
{"question": "Solve (274 / 930)", "answer": "The result of (274 / 930) is 0.2946\n\n####0.2946", "a": 274, "b": 930, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2946}
{"question": "Solve (113 - 924)", "answer": "The result of (113 - 924) is -811\n\n####-811", "a": 113, "b": 924, "operator": "-", "result": -811}
{"question": "Solve (690 - 436)", "answer": "The result of (690 - 436) is 254\n\n####254", "a": 690, "b": 436, "operator": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve (722 / 102)", "answer": "The result of (722 / 102) is 7.0784\n\n####7.0784", "a": 722, "b": 102, "operator": "/", "result": 7.0784}
{"question": "Solve (507 / 109)", "answer": "The result of (507 / 109) is 4.6514\n\n####4.6514", "a": 507, "b": 109, "operator": "/", "result": 4.6514}
{"question": "Solve (976 - 313)", "answer": "The result of (976 - 313) is 663\n\n####663", "a": 976, "b": 313, "operator": "-", "result": 663}
{"question": "Solve (240 * 251)", "answer": "The result of (240 * 251) is 60240\n\n####60240", "a": 240, "b": 251, "operator": "*", "result": 60240}
{"question": "Solve (208 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (208 - 256) is -48\n\n####-48", "a": 208, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": -48}
{"question": "Solve (287 + 874)", "answer": "The result of (287 + 874) is 1161\n\n####1161", "a": 287, "b": 874, "operator": "+", "result": 1161}
{"question": "Solve (108 - 609)", "answer": "The result of (108 - 609) is -501\n\n####-501", "a": 108, "b": 609, "operator": "-", "result": -501}
{"question": "Solve (8 - 194)", "answer": "The result of (8 - 194) is -186\n\n####-186", "a": 8, "b": 194, "operator": "-", "result": -186}
{"question": "Solve (292 / 820)", "answer": "The result of (292 / 820) is 0.3561\n\n####0.3561", "a": 292, "b": 820, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3561}
{"question": "Solve (190 / 685)", "answer": "The result of (190 / 685) is 0.2774\n\n####0.2774", "a": 190, "b": 685, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2774}
{"question": "Solve (833 + 624)", "answer": "The result of (833 + 624) is 1457\n\n####1457", "a": 833, "b": 624, "operator": "+", "result": 1457}
{"question": "Solve (566 * 250)", "answer": "The result of (566 * 250) is 141500\n\n####141500", "a": 566, "b": 250, "operator": "*", "result": 141500}
{"question": "Solve (609 - 151)", "answer": "The result of (609 - 151) is 458\n\n####458", "a": 609, "b": 151, "operator": "-", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve (942 + 455)", "answer": "The result of (942 + 455) is 1397\n\n####1397", "a": 942, "b": 455, "operator": "+", "result": 1397}
{"question": "Solve (357 / 269)", "answer": "The result of (357 / 269) is 1.3271\n\n####1.3271", "a": 357, "b": 269, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3271}
{"question": "Solve (584 - 874)", "answer": "The result of (584 - 874) is -290\n\n####-290", "a": 584, "b": 874, "operator": "-", "result": -290}
{"question": "Solve (504 / 111)", "answer": "The result of (504 / 111) is 4.5405\n\n####4.5405", "a": 504, "b": 111, "operator": "/", "result": 4.5405}
{"question": "Solve (194 * 526)", "answer": "The result of (194 * 526) is 102044\n\n####102044", "a": 194, "b": 526, "operator": "*", "result": 102044}
{"question": "Solve (898 / 701)", "answer": "The result of (898 / 701) is 1.281\n\n####1.281", "a": 898, "b": 701, "operator": "/", "result": 1.281}
{"question": "Solve (104 / 617)", "answer": "The result of (104 / 617) is 0.1686\n\n####0.1686", "a": 104, "b": 617, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1686}
{"question": "Solve (569 + 47)", "answer": "The result of (569 + 47) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 569, "b": 47, "operator": "+", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (657 / 155)", "answer": "The result of (657 / 155) is 4.2387\n\n####4.2387", "a": 657, "b": 155, "operator": "/", "result": 4.2387}
{"question": "Solve (454 * 720)", "answer": "The result of (454 * 720) is 326880\n\n####326880", "a": 454, "b": 720, "operator": "*", "result": 326880}
{"question": "Solve (257 / 446)", "answer": "The result of (257 / 446) is 0.5762\n\n####0.5762", "a": 257, "b": 446, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5762}
{"question": "Solve (936 / 830)", "answer": "The result of (936 / 830) is 1.1277\n\n####1.1277", "a": 936, "b": 830, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1277}
{"question": "Solve (867 / 132)", "answer": "The result of (867 / 132) is 6.5682\n\n####6.5682", "a": 867, "b": 132, "operator": "/", "result": 6.5682}
{"question": "Solve (764 / 235)", "answer": "The result of (764 / 235) is 3.2511\n\n####3.2511", "a": 764, "b": 235, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2511}
{"question": "Solve (804 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (804 * 61) is 49044\n\n####49044", "a": 804, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 49044}
{"question": "Solve (627 - 680)", "answer": "The result of (627 - 680) is -53\n\n####-53", "a": 627, "b": 680, "operator": "-", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve (732 + 357)", "answer": "The result of (732 + 357) is 1089\n\n####1089", "a": 732, "b": 357, "operator": "+", "result": 1089}
{"question": "Solve (715 - 53)", "answer": "The result of (715 - 53) is 662\n\n####662", "a": 715, "b": 53, "operator": "-", "result": 662}
{"question": "Solve (893 + 93)", "answer": "The result of (893 + 93) is 986\n\n####986", "a": 893, "b": 93, "operator": "+", "result": 986}
{"question": "Solve (286 - 907)", "answer": "The result of (286 - 907) is -621\n\n####-621", "a": 286, "b": 907, "operator": "-", "result": -621}
{"question": "Solve (170 / 38)", "answer": "The result of (170 / 38) is 4.4737\n\n####4.4737", "a": 170, "b": 38, "operator": "/", "result": 4.4737}
{"question": "Solve (825 / 934)", "answer": "The result of (825 / 934) is 0.8833\n\n####0.8833", "a": 825, "b": 934, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8833}
{"question": "Solve (590 + 761)", "answer": "The result of (590 + 761) is 1351\n\n####1351", "a": 590, "b": 761, "operator": "+", "result": 1351}
{"question": "Solve (687 * 782)", "answer": "The result of (687 * 782) is 537234\n\n####537234", "a": 687, "b": 782, "operator": "*", "result": 537234}
{"question": "Solve (643 / 961)", "answer": "The result of (643 / 961) is 0.6691\n\n####0.6691", "a": 643, "b": 961, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6691}
{"question": "Solve (184 - 559)", "answer": "The result of (184 - 559) is -375\n\n####-375", "a": 184, "b": 559, "operator": "-", "result": -375}
{"question": "Solve (751 / 504)", "answer": "The result of (751 / 504) is 1.4901\n\n####1.4901", "a": 751, "b": 504, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4901}
{"question": "Solve (977 + 23)", "answer": "The result of (977 + 23) is 1000\n\n####1000", "a": 977, "b": 23, "operator": "+", "result": 1000}
{"question": "Solve (424 / 767)", "answer": "The result of (424 / 767) is 0.5528\n\n####0.5528", "a": 424, "b": 767, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5528}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 662)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 662) is 89370\n\n####89370", "a": 135, "b": 662, "operator": "*", "result": 89370}
{"question": "Solve (794 / 491)", "answer": "The result of (794 / 491) is 1.6171\n\n####1.6171", "a": 794, "b": 491, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6171}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 774)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 774) is 207432\n\n####207432", "a": 268, "b": 774, "operator": "*", "result": 207432}
{"question": "Solve (895 / 704)", "answer": "The result of (895 / 704) is 1.2713\n\n####1.2713", "a": 895, "b": 704, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2713}
{"question": "Solve (718 - 942)", "answer": "The result of (718 - 942) is -224\n\n####-224", "a": 718, "b": 942, "operator": "-", "result": -224}
{"question": "Solve (406 + 805)", "answer": "The result of (406 + 805) is 1211\n\n####1211", "a": 406, "b": 805, "operator": "+", "result": 1211}
{"question": "Solve (401 / 188)", "answer": "The result of (401 / 188) is 2.133\n\n####2.133", "a": 401, "b": 188, "operator": "/", "result": 2.133}
{"question": "Solve (260 * 760)", "answer": "The result of (260 * 760) is 197600\n\n####197600", "a": 260, "b": 760, "operator": "*", "result": 197600}
{"question": "Solve (301 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (301 - 276) is 25\n\n####25", "a": 301, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": 25}
{"question": "Solve (317 / 681)", "answer": "The result of (317 / 681) is 0.4655\n\n####0.4655", "a": 317, "b": 681, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4655}
{"question": "Solve (724 * 71)", "answer": "The result of (724 * 71) is 51404\n\n####51404", "a": 724, "b": 71, "operator": "*", "result": 51404}
{"question": "Solve (816 / 598)", "answer": "The result of (816 / 598) is 1.3645\n\n####1.3645", "a": 816, "b": 598, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3645}
{"question": "Solve (981 * 862)", "answer": "The result of (981 * 862) is 845622\n\n####845622", "a": 981, "b": 862, "operator": "*", "result": 845622}
{"question": "Solve (733 - 557)", "answer": "The result of (733 - 557) is 176\n\n####176", "a": 733, "b": 557, "operator": "-", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 883)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 883) is 0.6138\n\n####0.6138", "a": 542, "b": 883, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6138}
{"question": "Solve (537 * 654)", "answer": "The result of (537 * 654) is 351198\n\n####351198", "a": 537, "b": 654, "operator": "*", "result": 351198}
{"question": "Solve (237 / 594)", "answer": "The result of (237 / 594) is 0.399\n\n####0.399", "a": 237, "b": 594, "operator": "/", "result": 0.399}
{"question": "Solve (408 / 917)", "answer": "The result of (408 / 917) is 0.4449\n\n####0.4449", "a": 408, "b": 917, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4449}
{"question": "Solve (675 - 505)", "answer": "The result of (675 - 505) is 170\n\n####170", "a": 675, "b": 505, "operator": "-", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve (325 * 463)", "answer": "The result of (325 * 463) is 150475\n\n####150475", "a": 325, "b": 463, "operator": "*", "result": 150475}
{"question": "Solve (860 * 952)", "answer": "The result of (860 * 952) is 818720\n\n####818720", "a": 860, "b": 952, "operator": "*", "result": 818720}
{"question": "Solve (4 / 871)", "answer": "The result of (4 / 871) is 0.0046\n\n####0.0046", "a": 4, "b": 871, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0046}
{"question": "Solve (240 * 720)", "answer": "The result of (240 * 720) is 172800\n\n####172800", "a": 240, "b": 720, "operator": "*", "result": 172800}
{"question": "Solve (930 / 63)", "answer": "The result of (930 / 63) is 14.7619\n\n####14.7619", "a": 930, "b": 63, "operator": "/", "result": 14.7619}
{"question": "Solve (127 - 804)", "answer": "The result of (127 - 804) is -677\n\n####-677", "a": 127, "b": 804, "operator": "-", "result": -677}
{"question": "Solve (255 / 382)", "answer": "The result of (255 / 382) is 0.6675\n\n####0.6675", "a": 255, "b": 382, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6675}
{"question": "Solve (76 * 258)", "answer": "The result of (76 * 258) is 19608\n\n####19608", "a": 76, "b": 258, "operator": "*", "result": 19608}
{"question": "Solve (198 / 585)", "answer": "The result of (198 / 585) is 0.3385\n\n####0.3385", "a": 198, "b": 585, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3385}
{"question": "Solve (847 * 150)", "answer": "The result of (847 * 150) is 127050\n\n####127050", "a": 847, "b": 150, "operator": "*", "result": 127050}
{"question": "Solve (446 / 255)", "answer": "The result of (446 / 255) is 1.749\n\n####1.749", "a": 446, "b": 255, "operator": "/", "result": 1.749}
{"question": "Solve (113 + 121)", "answer": "The result of (113 + 121) is 234\n\n####234", "a": 113, "b": 121, "operator": "+", "result": 234}
{"question": "Solve (611 * 552)", "answer": "The result of (611 * 552) is 337272\n\n####337272", "a": 611, "b": 552, "operator": "*", "result": 337272}
{"question": "Solve (871 + 786)", "answer": "The result of (871 + 786) is 1657\n\n####1657", "a": 871, "b": 786, "operator": "+", "result": 1657}
{"question": "Solve (398 * 269)", "answer": "The result of (398 * 269) is 107062\n\n####107062", "a": 398, "b": 269, "operator": "*", "result": 107062}
{"question": "Solve (723 / 291)", "answer": "The result of (723 / 291) is 2.4845\n\n####2.4845", "a": 723, "b": 291, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4845}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 626)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 626) is -422\n\n####-422", "a": 204, "b": 626, "operator": "-", "result": -422}
{"question": "Solve (426 + 602)", "answer": "The result of (426 + 602) is 1028\n\n####1028", "a": 426, "b": 602, "operator": "+", "result": 1028}
{"question": "Solve (60 - 914)", "answer": "The result of (60 - 914) is -854\n\n####-854", "a": 60, "b": 914, "operator": "-", "result": -854}
{"question": "Solve (73 / 902)", "answer": "The result of (73 / 902) is 0.0809\n\n####0.0809", "a": 73, "b": 902, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0809}
{"question": "Solve (12 - 901)", "answer": "The result of (12 - 901) is -889\n\n####-889", "a": 12, "b": 901, "operator": "-", "result": -889}
{"question": "Solve (356 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (356 - 492) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 356, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (517 + 227)", "answer": "The result of (517 + 227) is 744\n\n####744", "a": 517, "b": 227, "operator": "+", "result": 744}
{"question": "Solve (437 + 185)", "answer": "The result of (437 + 185) is 622\n\n####622", "a": 437, "b": 185, "operator": "+", "result": 622}
{"question": "Solve (400 / 797)", "answer": "The result of (400 / 797) is 0.5019\n\n####0.5019", "a": 400, "b": 797, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5019}
{"question": "Solve (88 / 538)", "answer": "The result of (88 / 538) is 0.1636\n\n####0.1636", "a": 88, "b": 538, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1636}
{"question": "Solve (850 * 723)", "answer": "The result of (850 * 723) is 614550\n\n####614550", "a": 850, "b": 723, "operator": "*", "result": 614550}
{"question": "Solve (452 / 842)", "answer": "The result of (452 / 842) is 0.5368\n\n####0.5368", "a": 452, "b": 842, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5368}
{"question": "Solve (646 * 188)", "answer": "The result of (646 * 188) is 121448\n\n####121448", "a": 646, "b": 188, "operator": "*", "result": 121448}
{"question": "Solve (792 + 453)", "answer": "The result of (792 + 453) is 1245\n\n####1245", "a": 792, "b": 453, "operator": "+", "result": 1245}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 237)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 237) is 169218\n\n####169218", "a": 714, "b": 237, "operator": "*", "result": 169218}
{"question": "Solve (863 / 356)", "answer": "The result of (863 / 356) is 2.4242\n\n####2.4242", "a": 863, "b": 356, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4242}
{"question": "Solve (841 * 423)", "answer": "The result of (841 * 423) is 355743\n\n####355743", "a": 841, "b": 423, "operator": "*", "result": 355743}
{"question": "Solve (740 + 803)", "answer": "The result of (740 + 803) is 1543\n\n####1543", "a": 740, "b": 803, "operator": "+", "result": 1543}
{"question": "Solve (73 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (73 - 520) is -447\n\n####-447", "a": 73, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": -447}
{"question": "Solve (323 - 421)", "answer": "The result of (323 - 421) is -98\n\n####-98", "a": 323, "b": 421, "operator": "-", "result": -98}
{"question": "Solve (916 * 374)", "answer": "The result of (916 * 374) is 342584\n\n####342584", "a": 916, "b": 374, "operator": "*", "result": 342584}
{"question": "Solve (35 - 655)", "answer": "The result of (35 - 655) is -620\n\n####-620", "a": 35, "b": 655, "operator": "-", "result": -620}
{"question": "Solve (514 * 17)", "answer": "The result of (514 * 17) is 8738\n\n####8738", "a": 514, "b": 17, "operator": "*", "result": 8738}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 53)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 53) is 244\n\n####244", "a": 297, "b": 53, "operator": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve (469 * 891)", "answer": "The result of (469 * 891) is 417879\n\n####417879", "a": 469, "b": 891, "operator": "*", "result": 417879}
{"question": "Solve (364 * 54)", "answer": "The result of (364 * 54) is 19656\n\n####19656", "a": 364, "b": 54, "operator": "*", "result": 19656}
{"question": "Solve (419 / 718)", "answer": "The result of (419 / 718) is 0.5836\n\n####0.5836", "a": 419, "b": 718, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5836}
{"question": "Solve (440 / 955)", "answer": "The result of (440 / 955) is 0.4607\n\n####0.4607", "a": 440, "b": 955, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4607}
{"question": "Solve (941 - 473)", "answer": "The result of (941 - 473) is 468\n\n####468", "a": 941, "b": 473, "operator": "-", "result": 468}
{"question": "Solve (67 / 531)", "answer": "The result of (67 / 531) is 0.1262\n\n####0.1262", "a": 67, "b": 531, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1262}
{"question": "Solve (277 * 296)", "answer": "The result of (277 * 296) is 81992\n\n####81992", "a": 277, "b": 296, "operator": "*", "result": 81992}
{"question": "Solve (955 + 440)", "answer": "The result of (955 + 440) is 1395\n\n####1395", "a": 955, "b": 440, "operator": "+", "result": 1395}
{"question": "Solve (13 - 261)", "answer": "The result of (13 - 261) is -248\n\n####-248", "a": 13, "b": 261, "operator": "-", "result": -248}
{"question": "Solve (846 - 395)", "answer": "The result of (846 - 395) is 451\n\n####451", "a": 846, "b": 395, "operator": "-", "result": 451}
{"question": "Solve (105 * 888)", "answer": "The result of (105 * 888) is 93240\n\n####93240", "a": 105, "b": 888, "operator": "*", "result": 93240}
{"question": "Solve (697 / 500)", "answer": "The result of (697 / 500) is 1.394\n\n####1.394", "a": 697, "b": 500, "operator": "/", "result": 1.394}
{"question": "Solve (805 / 285)", "answer": "The result of (805 / 285) is 2.8246\n\n####2.8246", "a": 805, "b": 285, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8246}
{"question": "Solve (588 + 184)", "answer": "The result of (588 + 184) is 772\n\n####772", "a": 588, "b": 184, "operator": "+", "result": 772}
{"question": "Solve (750 - 838)", "answer": "The result of (750 - 838) is -88\n\n####-88", "a": 750, "b": 838, "operator": "-", "result": -88}
{"question": "Solve (705 - 777)", "answer": "The result of (705 - 777) is -72\n\n####-72", "a": 705, "b": 777, "operator": "-", "result": -72}
{"question": "Solve (85 / 438)", "answer": "The result of (85 / 438) is 0.1941\n\n####0.1941", "a": 85, "b": 438, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1941}
{"question": "Solve (394 + 892)", "answer": "The result of (394 + 892) is 1286\n\n####1286", "a": 394, "b": 892, "operator": "+", "result": 1286}
{"question": "Solve (316 - 870)", "answer": "The result of (316 - 870) is -554\n\n####-554", "a": 316, "b": 870, "operator": "-", "result": -554}
{"question": "Solve (672 * 398)", "answer": "The result of (672 * 398) is 267456\n\n####267456", "a": 672, "b": 398, "operator": "*", "result": 267456}
{"question": "Solve (349 - 150)", "answer": "The result of (349 - 150) is 199\n\n####199", "a": 349, "b": 150, "operator": "-", "result": 199}
{"question": "Solve (806 * 838)", "answer": "The result of (806 * 838) is 675428\n\n####675428", "a": 806, "b": 838, "operator": "*", "result": 675428}
{"question": "Solve (79 * 518)", "answer": "The result of (79 * 518) is 40922\n\n####40922", "a": 79, "b": 518, "operator": "*", "result": 40922}
{"question": "Solve (538 * 537)", "answer": "The result of (538 * 537) is 288906\n\n####288906", "a": 538, "b": 537, "operator": "*", "result": 288906}
{"question": "Solve (583 * 466)", "answer": "The result of (583 * 466) is 271678\n\n####271678", "a": 583, "b": 466, "operator": "*", "result": 271678}
{"question": "Solve (26 - 177)", "answer": "The result of (26 - 177) is -151\n\n####-151", "a": 26, "b": 177, "operator": "-", "result": -151}
{"question": "Solve (631 / 566)", "answer": "The result of (631 / 566) is 1.1148\n\n####1.1148", "a": 631, "b": 566, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1148}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 464)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 464) is 235712\n\n####235712", "a": 508, "b": 464, "operator": "*", "result": 235712}
{"question": "Solve (600 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (600 - 520) is 80\n\n####80", "a": 600, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve (791 * 845)", "answer": "The result of (791 * 845) is 668395\n\n####668395", "a": 791, "b": 845, "operator": "*", "result": 668395}
{"question": "Solve (964 - 34)", "answer": "The result of (964 - 34) is 930\n\n####930", "a": 964, "b": 34, "operator": "-", "result": 930}
{"question": "Solve (237 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (237 / 327) is 0.7248\n\n####0.7248", "a": 237, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7248}
{"question": "Solve (179 + 829)", "answer": "The result of (179 + 829) is 1008\n\n####1008", "a": 179, "b": 829, "operator": "+", "result": 1008}
{"question": "Solve (544 + 144)", "answer": "The result of (544 + 144) is 688\n\n####688", "a": 544, "b": 144, "operator": "+", "result": 688}
{"question": "Solve (840 / 512)", "answer": "The result of (840 / 512) is 1.6406\n\n####1.6406", "a": 840, "b": 512, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6406}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 4)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 4) is 2792\n\n####2792", "a": 698, "b": 4, "operator": "*", "result": 2792}
{"question": "Solve (827 - 570)", "answer": "The result of (827 - 570) is 257\n\n####257", "a": 827, "b": 570, "operator": "-", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 834)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 834) is 0.9712\n\n####0.9712", "a": 810, "b": 834, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9712}
{"question": "Solve (269 / 288)", "answer": "The result of (269 / 288) is 0.934\n\n####0.934", "a": 269, "b": 288, "operator": "/", "result": 0.934}
{"question": "Solve (622 - 491)", "answer": "The result of (622 - 491) is 131\n\n####131", "a": 622, "b": 491, "operator": "-", "result": 131}
{"question": "Solve (686 * 680)", "answer": "The result of (686 * 680) is 466480\n\n####466480", "a": 686, "b": 680, "operator": "*", "result": 466480}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 113)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 113) is 80682\n\n####80682", "a": 714, "b": 113, "operator": "*", "result": 80682}
{"question": "Solve (503 + 318)", "answer": "The result of (503 + 318) is 821\n\n####821", "a": 503, "b": 318, "operator": "+", "result": 821}
{"question": "Solve (25 / 707)", "answer": "The result of (25 / 707) is 0.0354\n\n####0.0354", "a": 25, "b": 707, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0354}
{"question": "Solve (962 / 643)", "answer": "The result of (962 / 643) is 1.4961\n\n####1.4961", "a": 962, "b": 643, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4961}
{"question": "Solve (306 - 20)", "answer": "The result of (306 - 20) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 306, "b": 20, "operator": "-", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (790 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (790 - 822) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 790, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 479)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 479) is 334342\n\n####334342", "a": 698, "b": 479, "operator": "*", "result": 334342}
{"question": "Solve (827 * 975)", "answer": "The result of (827 * 975) is 806325\n\n####806325", "a": 827, "b": 975, "operator": "*", "result": 806325}
{"question": "Solve (460 - 962)", "answer": "The result of (460 - 962) is -502\n\n####-502", "a": 460, "b": 962, "operator": "-", "result": -502}
{"question": "Solve (849 * 125)", "answer": "The result of (849 * 125) is 106125\n\n####106125", "a": 849, "b": 125, "operator": "*", "result": 106125}
{"question": "Solve (525 / 736)", "answer": "The result of (525 / 736) is 0.7133\n\n####0.7133", "a": 525, "b": 736, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7133}
{"question": "Solve (598 + 228)", "answer": "The result of (598 + 228) is 826\n\n####826", "a": 598, "b": 228, "operator": "+", "result": 826}
{"question": "Solve (188 / 594)", "answer": "The result of (188 / 594) is 0.3165\n\n####0.3165", "a": 188, "b": 594, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3165}
{"question": "Solve (354 - 758)", "answer": "The result of (354 - 758) is -404\n\n####-404", "a": 354, "b": 758, "operator": "-", "result": -404}
{"question": "Solve (227 * 409)", "answer": "The result of (227 * 409) is 92843\n\n####92843", "a": 227, "b": 409, "operator": "*", "result": 92843}
{"question": "Solve (428 + 312)", "answer": "The result of (428 + 312) is 740\n\n####740", "a": 428, "b": 312, "operator": "+", "result": 740}
{"question": "Solve (409 / 806)", "answer": "The result of (409 / 806) is 0.5074\n\n####0.5074", "a": 409, "b": 806, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5074}
{"question": "Solve (991 + 393)", "answer": "The result of (991 + 393) is 1384\n\n####1384", "a": 991, "b": 393, "operator": "+", "result": 1384}
{"question": "Solve (560 / 691)", "answer": "The result of (560 / 691) is 0.8104\n\n####0.8104", "a": 560, "b": 691, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8104}
{"question": "Solve (861 / 891)", "answer": "The result of (861 / 891) is 0.9663\n\n####0.9663", "a": 861, "b": 891, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9663}
{"question": "Solve (482 / 199)", "answer": "The result of (482 / 199) is 2.4221\n\n####2.4221", "a": 482, "b": 199, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4221}
{"question": "Solve (766 * 247)", "answer": "The result of (766 * 247) is 189202\n\n####189202", "a": 766, "b": 247, "operator": "*", "result": 189202}
{"question": "Solve (315 - 768)", "answer": "The result of (315 - 768) is -453\n\n####-453", "a": 315, "b": 768, "operator": "-", "result": -453}
{"question": "Solve (824 - 527)", "answer": "The result of (824 - 527) is 297\n\n####297", "a": 824, "b": 527, "operator": "-", "result": 297}
{"question": "Solve (560 * 910)", "answer": "The result of (560 * 910) is 509600\n\n####509600", "a": 560, "b": 910, "operator": "*", "result": 509600}
{"question": "Solve (368 + 752)", "answer": "The result of (368 + 752) is 1120\n\n####1120", "a": 368, "b": 752, "operator": "+", "result": 1120}
{"question": "Solve (723 + 949)", "answer": "The result of (723 + 949) is 1672\n\n####1672", "a": 723, "b": 949, "operator": "+", "result": 1672}
{"question": "Solve (216 / 210)", "answer": "The result of (216 / 210) is 1.0286\n\n####1.0286", "a": 216, "b": 210, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0286}
{"question": "Solve (902 - 520)", "answer": "The result of (902 - 520) is 382\n\n####382", "a": 902, "b": 520, "operator": "-", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve (3 - 50)", "answer": "The result of (3 - 50) is -47\n\n####-47", "a": 3, "b": 50, "operator": "-", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve (570 + 906)", "answer": "The result of (570 + 906) is 1476\n\n####1476", "a": 570, "b": 906, "operator": "+", "result": 1476}
{"question": "Solve (597 / 385)", "answer": "The result of (597 / 385) is 1.5506\n\n####1.5506", "a": 597, "b": 385, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5506}
{"question": "Solve (820 - 539)", "answer": "The result of (820 - 539) is 281\n\n####281", "a": 820, "b": 539, "operator": "-", "result": 281}
{"question": "Solve (938 + 173)", "answer": "The result of (938 + 173) is 1111\n\n####1111", "a": 938, "b": 173, "operator": "+", "result": 1111}
{"question": "Solve (832 / 608)", "answer": "The result of (832 / 608) is 1.3684\n\n####1.3684", "a": 832, "b": 608, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3684}
{"question": "Solve (706 + 552)", "answer": "The result of (706 + 552) is 1258\n\n####1258", "a": 706, "b": 552, "operator": "+", "result": 1258}
{"question": "Solve (471 - 713)", "answer": "The result of (471 - 713) is -242\n\n####-242", "a": 471, "b": 713, "operator": "-", "result": -242}
{"question": "Solve (839 - 301)", "answer": "The result of (839 - 301) is 538\n\n####538", "a": 839, "b": 301, "operator": "-", "result": 538}
{"question": "Solve (478 / 55)", "answer": "The result of (478 / 55) is 8.6909\n\n####8.6909", "a": 478, "b": 55, "operator": "/", "result": 8.6909}
{"question": "Solve (433 * 947)", "answer": "The result of (433 * 947) is 410051\n\n####410051", "a": 433, "b": 947, "operator": "*", "result": 410051}
{"question": "Solve (423 / 254)", "answer": "The result of (423 / 254) is 1.6654\n\n####1.6654", "a": 423, "b": 254, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6654}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 554)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 554) is 32\n\n####32", "a": 586, "b": 554, "operator": "-", "result": 32}
{"question": "Solve (225 - 551)", "answer": "The result of (225 - 551) is -326\n\n####-326", "a": 225, "b": 551, "operator": "-", "result": -326}
{"question": "Solve (303 + 36)", "answer": "The result of (303 + 36) is 339\n\n####339", "a": 303, "b": 36, "operator": "+", "result": 339}
{"question": "Solve (839 * 186)", "answer": "The result of (839 * 186) is 156054\n\n####156054", "a": 839, "b": 186, "operator": "*", "result": 156054}
{"question": "Solve (523 * 443)", "answer": "The result of (523 * 443) is 231689\n\n####231689", "a": 523, "b": 443, "operator": "*", "result": 231689}
{"question": "Solve (336 + 321)", "answer": "The result of (336 + 321) is 657\n\n####657", "a": 336, "b": 321, "operator": "+", "result": 657}
{"question": "Solve (565 * 989)", "answer": "The result of (565 * 989) is 558785\n\n####558785", "a": 565, "b": 989, "operator": "*", "result": 558785}
{"question": "Solve (968 * 532)", "answer": "The result of (968 * 532) is 514976\n\n####514976", "a": 968, "b": 532, "operator": "*", "result": 514976}
{"question": "Solve (331 - 276)", "answer": "The result of (331 - 276) is 55\n\n####55", "a": 331, "b": 276, "operator": "-", "result": 55}
{"question": "Solve (488 / 48)", "answer": "The result of (488 / 48) is 10.1667\n\n####10.1667", "a": 488, "b": 48, "operator": "/", "result": 10.1667}
{"question": "Solve (428 - 925)", "answer": "The result of (428 - 925) is -497\n\n####-497", "a": 428, "b": 925, "operator": "-", "result": -497}
{"question": "Solve (512 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (512 - 496) is 16\n\n####16", "a": 512, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": 16}
{"question": "Solve (949 / 889)", "answer": "The result of (949 / 889) is 1.0675\n\n####1.0675", "a": 949, "b": 889, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0675}
{"question": "Solve (385 - 511)", "answer": "The result of (385 - 511) is -126\n\n####-126", "a": 385, "b": 511, "operator": "-", "result": -126}
{"question": "Solve (638 * 163)", "answer": "The result of (638 * 163) is 103994\n\n####103994", "a": 638, "b": 163, "operator": "*", "result": 103994}
{"question": "Solve (766 + 233)", "answer": "The result of (766 + 233) is 999\n\n####999", "a": 766, "b": 233, "operator": "+", "result": 999}
{"question": "Solve (174 * 271)", "answer": "The result of (174 * 271) is 47154\n\n####47154", "a": 174, "b": 271, "operator": "*", "result": 47154}
{"question": "Solve (738 - 528)", "answer": "The result of (738 - 528) is 210\n\n####210", "a": 738, "b": 528, "operator": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 753)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 753) is 0.0279\n\n####0.0279", "a": 21, "b": 753, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0279}
{"question": "Solve (272 - 960)", "answer": "The result of (272 - 960) is -688\n\n####-688", "a": 272, "b": 960, "operator": "-", "result": -688}
{"question": "Solve (705 * 998)", "answer": "The result of (705 * 998) is 703590\n\n####703590", "a": 705, "b": 998, "operator": "*", "result": 703590}
{"question": "Solve (127 / 134)", "answer": "The result of (127 / 134) is 0.9478\n\n####0.9478", "a": 127, "b": 134, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9478}
{"question": "Solve (125 / 723)", "answer": "The result of (125 / 723) is 0.1729\n\n####0.1729", "a": 125, "b": 723, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1729}
{"question": "Solve (384 / 828)", "answer": "The result of (384 / 828) is 0.4638\n\n####0.4638", "a": 384, "b": 828, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4638}
{"question": "Solve (662 - 390)", "answer": "The result of (662 - 390) is 272\n\n####272", "a": 662, "b": 390, "operator": "-", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve (501 / 919)", "answer": "The result of (501 / 919) is 0.5452\n\n####0.5452", "a": 501, "b": 919, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5452}
{"question": "Solve (380 + 13)", "answer": "The result of (380 + 13) is 393\n\n####393", "a": 380, "b": 13, "operator": "+", "result": 393}
{"question": "Solve (952 * 837)", "answer": "The result of (952 * 837) is 796824\n\n####796824", "a": 952, "b": 837, "operator": "*", "result": 796824}
{"question": "Solve (852 + 631)", "answer": "The result of (852 + 631) is 1483\n\n####1483", "a": 852, "b": 631, "operator": "+", "result": 1483}
{"question": "Solve (788 - 580)", "answer": "The result of (788 - 580) is 208\n\n####208", "a": 788, "b": 580, "operator": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve (632 / 879)", "answer": "The result of (632 / 879) is 0.719\n\n####0.719", "a": 632, "b": 879, "operator": "/", "result": 0.719}
{"question": "Solve (926 - 536)", "answer": "The result of (926 - 536) is 390\n\n####390", "a": 926, "b": 536, "operator": "-", "result": 390}
{"question": "Solve (925 * 339)", "answer": "The result of (925 * 339) is 313575\n\n####313575", "a": 925, "b": 339, "operator": "*", "result": 313575}
{"question": "Solve (236 * 911)", "answer": "The result of (236 * 911) is 214996\n\n####214996", "a": 236, "b": 911, "operator": "*", "result": 214996}
{"question": "Solve (577 + 827)", "answer": "The result of (577 + 827) is 1404\n\n####1404", "a": 577, "b": 827, "operator": "+", "result": 1404}
{"question": "Solve (366 - 950)", "answer": "The result of (366 - 950) is -584\n\n####-584", "a": 366, "b": 950, "operator": "-", "result": -584}
{"question": "Solve (429 - 751)", "answer": "The result of (429 - 751) is -322\n\n####-322", "a": 429, "b": 751, "operator": "-", "result": -322}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 926)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 926) is 890812\n\n####890812", "a": 962, "b": 926, "operator": "*", "result": 890812}
{"question": "Solve (600 * 729)", "answer": "The result of (600 * 729) is 437400\n\n####437400", "a": 600, "b": 729, "operator": "*", "result": 437400}
{"question": "Solve (577 * 848)", "answer": "The result of (577 * 848) is 489296\n\n####489296", "a": 577, "b": 848, "operator": "*", "result": 489296}
{"question": "Solve (578 - 434)", "answer": "The result of (578 - 434) is 144\n\n####144", "a": 578, "b": 434, "operator": "-", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve (226 + 347)", "answer": "The result of (226 + 347) is 573\n\n####573", "a": 226, "b": 347, "operator": "+", "result": 573}
{"question": "Solve (209 / 686)", "answer": "The result of (209 / 686) is 0.3047\n\n####0.3047", "a": 209, "b": 686, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3047}
{"question": "Solve (241 / 233)", "answer": "The result of (241 / 233) is 1.0343\n\n####1.0343", "a": 241, "b": 233, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0343}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 537)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 537) is -340\n\n####-340", "a": 197, "b": 537, "operator": "-", "result": -340}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 124)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 124) is 1488\n\n####1488", "a": 12, "b": 124, "operator": "*", "result": 1488}
{"question": "Solve (687 - 175)", "answer": "The result of (687 - 175) is 512\n\n####512", "a": 687, "b": 175, "operator": "-", "result": 512}
{"question": "Solve (606 * 186)", "answer": "The result of (606 * 186) is 112716\n\n####112716", "a": 606, "b": 186, "operator": "*", "result": 112716}
{"question": "Solve (859 + 46)", "answer": "The result of (859 + 46) is 905\n\n####905", "a": 859, "b": 46, "operator": "+", "result": 905}
{"question": "Solve (314 + 785)", "answer": "The result of (314 + 785) is 1099\n\n####1099", "a": 314, "b": 785, "operator": "+", "result": 1099}
{"question": "Solve (707 * 570)", "answer": "The result of (707 * 570) is 402990\n\n####402990", "a": 707, "b": 570, "operator": "*", "result": 402990}
{"question": "Solve (391 + 998)", "answer": "The result of (391 + 998) is 1389\n\n####1389", "a": 391, "b": 998, "operator": "+", "result": 1389}
{"question": "Solve (623 + 454)", "answer": "The result of (623 + 454) is 1077\n\n####1077", "a": 623, "b": 454, "operator": "+", "result": 1077}
{"question": "Solve (833 / 860)", "answer": "The result of (833 / 860) is 0.9686\n\n####0.9686", "a": 833, "b": 860, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9686}
{"question": "Solve (165 / 805)", "answer": "The result of (165 / 805) is 0.205\n\n####0.205", "a": 165, "b": 805, "operator": "/", "result": 0.205}
{"question": "Solve (848 / 354)", "answer": "The result of (848 / 354) is 2.3955\n\n####2.3955", "a": 848, "b": 354, "operator": "/", "result": 2.3955}
{"question": "Solve (903 + 646)", "answer": "The result of (903 + 646) is 1549\n\n####1549", "a": 903, "b": 646, "operator": "+", "result": 1549}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 26)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 26) is 20800\n\n####20800", "a": 800, "b": 26, "operator": "*", "result": 20800}
{"question": "Solve (196 + 346)", "answer": "The result of (196 + 346) is 542\n\n####542", "a": 196, "b": 346, "operator": "+", "result": 542}
{"question": "Solve (660 / 56)", "answer": "The result of (660 / 56) is 11.7857\n\n####11.7857", "a": 660, "b": 56, "operator": "/", "result": 11.7857}
{"question": "Solve (981 * 698)", "answer": "The result of (981 * 698) is 684738\n\n####684738", "a": 981, "b": 698, "operator": "*", "result": 684738}
{"question": "Solve (75 - 81)", "answer": "The result of (75 - 81) is -6\n\n####-6", "a": 75, "b": 81, "operator": "-", "result": -6}
{"question": "Solve (686 - 958)", "answer": "The result of (686 - 958) is -272\n\n####-272", "a": 686, "b": 958, "operator": "-", "result": -272}
{"question": "Solve (992 * 651)", "answer": "The result of (992 * 651) is 645792\n\n####645792", "a": 992, "b": 651, "operator": "*", "result": 645792}
{"question": "Solve (764 - 112)", "answer": "The result of (764 - 112) is 652\n\n####652", "a": 764, "b": 112, "operator": "-", "result": 652}
{"question": "Solve (360 - 43)", "answer": "The result of (360 - 43) is 317\n\n####317", "a": 360, "b": 43, "operator": "-", "result": 317}
{"question": "Solve (946 / 31)", "answer": "The result of (946 / 31) is 30.5161\n\n####30.5161", "a": 946, "b": 31, "operator": "/", "result": 30.5161}
{"question": "Solve (714 / 775)", "answer": "The result of (714 / 775) is 0.9213\n\n####0.9213", "a": 714, "b": 775, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9213}
{"question": "Solve (321 / 350)", "answer": "The result of (321 / 350) is 0.9171\n\n####0.9171", "a": 321, "b": 350, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9171}
{"question": "Solve (581 - 810)", "answer": "The result of (581 - 810) is -229\n\n####-229", "a": 581, "b": 810, "operator": "-", "result": -229}
{"question": "Solve (817 / 710)", "answer": "The result of (817 / 710) is 1.1507\n\n####1.1507", "a": 817, "b": 710, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1507}
{"question": "Solve (514 / 186)", "answer": "The result of (514 / 186) is 2.7634\n\n####2.7634", "a": 514, "b": 186, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7634}
{"question": "Solve (217 - 90)", "answer": "The result of (217 - 90) is 127\n\n####127", "a": 217, "b": 90, "operator": "-", "result": 127}
{"question": "Solve (456 * 143)", "answer": "The result of (456 * 143) is 65208\n\n####65208", "a": 456, "b": 143, "operator": "*", "result": 65208}
{"question": "Solve (535 * 541)", "answer": "The result of (535 * 541) is 289435\n\n####289435", "a": 535, "b": 541, "operator": "*", "result": 289435}
{"question": "Solve (455 * 823)", "answer": "The result of (455 * 823) is 374465\n\n####374465", "a": 455, "b": 823, "operator": "*", "result": 374465}
{"question": "Solve (731 * 276)", "answer": "The result of (731 * 276) is 201756\n\n####201756", "a": 731, "b": 276, "operator": "*", "result": 201756}
{"question": "Solve (957 / 637)", "answer": "The result of (957 / 637) is 1.5024\n\n####1.5024", "a": 957, "b": 637, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5024}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 724)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 724) is -545\n\n####-545", "a": 179, "b": 724, "operator": "-", "result": -545}
{"question": "Solve (775 / 972)", "answer": "The result of (775 / 972) is 0.7973\n\n####0.7973", "a": 775, "b": 972, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7973}
{"question": "Solve (965 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (965 - 992) is -27\n\n####-27", "a": 965, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -27}
{"question": "Solve (433 / 276)", "answer": "The result of (433 / 276) is 1.5688\n\n####1.5688", "a": 433, "b": 276, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5688}
{"question": "Solve (257 / 421)", "answer": "The result of (257 / 421) is 0.6105\n\n####0.6105", "a": 257, "b": 421, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6105}
{"question": "Solve (574 - 170)", "answer": "The result of (574 - 170) is 404\n\n####404", "a": 574, "b": 170, "operator": "-", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve (93 / 364)", "answer": "The result of (93 / 364) is 0.2555\n\n####0.2555", "a": 93, "b": 364, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2555}
{"question": "Solve (476 + 571)", "answer": "The result of (476 + 571) is 1047\n\n####1047", "a": 476, "b": 571, "operator": "+", "result": 1047}
{"question": "Solve (186 / 902)", "answer": "The result of (186 / 902) is 0.2062\n\n####0.2062", "a": 186, "b": 902, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2062}
{"question": "Solve (573 + 803)", "answer": "The result of (573 + 803) is 1376\n\n####1376", "a": 573, "b": 803, "operator": "+", "result": 1376}
{"question": "Solve (945 * 51)", "answer": "The result of (945 * 51) is 48195\n\n####48195", "a": 945, "b": 51, "operator": "*", "result": 48195}
{"question": "Solve (459 * 943)", "answer": "The result of (459 * 943) is 432837\n\n####432837", "a": 459, "b": 943, "operator": "*", "result": 432837}
{"question": "Solve (178 / 709)", "answer": "The result of (178 / 709) is 0.2511\n\n####0.2511", "a": 178, "b": 709, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2511}
{"question": "Solve (424 + 856)", "answer": "The result of (424 + 856) is 1280\n\n####1280", "a": 424, "b": 856, "operator": "+", "result": 1280}
{"question": "Solve (45 + 699)", "answer": "The result of (45 + 699) is 744\n\n####744", "a": 45, "b": 699, "operator": "+", "result": 744}
{"question": "Solve (968 + 318)", "answer": "The result of (968 + 318) is 1286\n\n####1286", "a": 968, "b": 318, "operator": "+", "result": 1286}
{"question": "Solve (260 - 355)", "answer": "The result of (260 - 355) is -95\n\n####-95", "a": 260, "b": 355, "operator": "-", "result": -95}
{"question": "Solve (616 * 255)", "answer": "The result of (616 * 255) is 157080\n\n####157080", "a": 616, "b": 255, "operator": "*", "result": 157080}
{"question": "Solve (555 - 111)", "answer": "The result of (555 - 111) is 444\n\n####444", "a": 555, "b": 111, "operator": "-", "result": 444}
{"question": "Solve (650 - 712)", "answer": "The result of (650 - 712) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 650, "b": 712, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (914 - 98)", "answer": "The result of (914 - 98) is 816\n\n####816", "a": 914, "b": 98, "operator": "-", "result": 816}
{"question": "Solve (275 * 468)", "answer": "The result of (275 * 468) is 128700\n\n####128700", "a": 275, "b": 468, "operator": "*", "result": 128700}
{"question": "Solve (365 / 28)", "answer": "The result of (365 / 28) is 13.0357\n\n####13.0357", "a": 365, "b": 28, "operator": "/", "result": 13.0357}
{"question": "Solve (412 * 319)", "answer": "The result of (412 * 319) is 131428\n\n####131428", "a": 412, "b": 319, "operator": "*", "result": 131428}
{"question": "Solve (418 - 970)", "answer": "The result of (418 - 970) is -552\n\n####-552", "a": 418, "b": 970, "operator": "-", "result": -552}
{"question": "Solve (652 / 572)", "answer": "The result of (652 / 572) is 1.1399\n\n####1.1399", "a": 652, "b": 572, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1399}
{"question": "Solve (240 / 310)", "answer": "The result of (240 / 310) is 0.7742\n\n####0.7742", "a": 240, "b": 310, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7742}
{"question": "Solve (852 * 990)", "answer": "The result of (852 * 990) is 843480\n\n####843480", "a": 852, "b": 990, "operator": "*", "result": 843480}
{"question": "Solve (728 - 967)", "answer": "The result of (728 - 967) is -239\n\n####-239", "a": 728, "b": 967, "operator": "-", "result": -239}
{"question": "Solve (625 - 989)", "answer": "The result of (625 - 989) is -364\n\n####-364", "a": 625, "b": 989, "operator": "-", "result": -364}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 295)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 295) is 117115\n\n####117115", "a": 397, "b": 295, "operator": "*", "result": 117115}
{"question": "Solve (473 - 373)", "answer": "The result of (473 - 373) is 100\n\n####100", "a": 473, "b": 373, "operator": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve (716 + 367)", "answer": "The result of (716 + 367) is 1083\n\n####1083", "a": 716, "b": 367, "operator": "+", "result": 1083}
{"question": "Solve (403 / 399)", "answer": "The result of (403 / 399) is 1.01\n\n####1.01", "a": 403, "b": 399, "operator": "/", "result": 1.01}
{"question": "Solve (836 + 808)", "answer": "The result of (836 + 808) is 1644\n\n####1644", "a": 836, "b": 808, "operator": "+", "result": 1644}
{"question": "Solve (97 - 420)", "answer": "The result of (97 - 420) is -323\n\n####-323", "a": 97, "b": 420, "operator": "-", "result": -323}
{"question": "Solve (200 - 262)", "answer": "The result of (200 - 262) is -62\n\n####-62", "a": 200, "b": 262, "operator": "-", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve (540 / 132)", "answer": "The result of (540 / 132) is 4.0909\n\n####4.0909", "a": 540, "b": 132, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0909}
{"question": "Solve (873 * 592)", "answer": "The result of (873 * 592) is 516816\n\n####516816", "a": 873, "b": 592, "operator": "*", "result": 516816}
{"question": "Solve (395 / 341)", "answer": "The result of (395 / 341) is 1.1584\n\n####1.1584", "a": 395, "b": 341, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1584}
{"question": "Solve (827 + 631)", "answer": "The result of (827 + 631) is 1458\n\n####1458", "a": 827, "b": 631, "operator": "+", "result": 1458}
{"question": "Solve (202 + 975)", "answer": "The result of (202 + 975) is 1177\n\n####1177", "a": 202, "b": 975, "operator": "+", "result": 1177}
{"question": "Solve (993 / 9)", "answer": "The result of (993 / 9) is 110.3333\n\n####110.3333", "a": 993, "b": 9, "operator": "/", "result": 110.3333}
{"question": "Solve (149 / 261)", "answer": "The result of (149 / 261) is 0.5709\n\n####0.5709", "a": 149, "b": 261, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5709}
{"question": "Solve (994 / 365)", "answer": "The result of (994 / 365) is 2.7233\n\n####2.7233", "a": 994, "b": 365, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7233}
{"question": "Solve (270 + 478)", "answer": "The result of (270 + 478) is 748\n\n####748", "a": 270, "b": 478, "operator": "+", "result": 748}
{"question": "Solve (892 / 993)", "answer": "The result of (892 / 993) is 0.8983\n\n####0.8983", "a": 892, "b": 993, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8983}
{"question": "Solve (572 + 896)", "answer": "The result of (572 + 896) is 1468\n\n####1468", "a": 572, "b": 896, "operator": "+", "result": 1468}
{"question": "Solve (666 / 290)", "answer": "The result of (666 / 290) is 2.2966\n\n####2.2966", "a": 666, "b": 290, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2966}
{"question": "Solve (322 - 407)", "answer": "The result of (322 - 407) is -85\n\n####-85", "a": 322, "b": 407, "operator": "-", "result": -85}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 357)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 357) is 343434\n\n####343434", "a": 962, "b": 357, "operator": "*", "result": 343434}
{"question": "Solve (186 / 404)", "answer": "The result of (186 / 404) is 0.4604\n\n####0.4604", "a": 186, "b": 404, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4604}
{"question": "Solve (312 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (312 * 400) is 124800\n\n####124800", "a": 312, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 124800}
{"question": "Solve (511 / 438)", "answer": "The result of (511 / 438) is 1.1667\n\n####1.1667", "a": 511, "b": 438, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1667}
{"question": "Solve (98 * 998)", "answer": "The result of (98 * 998) is 97804\n\n####97804", "a": 98, "b": 998, "operator": "*", "result": 97804}
{"question": "Solve (199 - 875)", "answer": "The result of (199 - 875) is -676\n\n####-676", "a": 199, "b": 875, "operator": "-", "result": -676}
{"question": "Solve (140 - 700)", "answer": "The result of (140 - 700) is -560\n\n####-560", "a": 140, "b": 700, "operator": "-", "result": -560}
{"question": "Solve (720 + 994)", "answer": "The result of (720 + 994) is 1714\n\n####1714", "a": 720, "b": 994, "operator": "+", "result": 1714}
{"question": "Solve (619 / 596)", "answer": "The result of (619 / 596) is 1.0386\n\n####1.0386", "a": 619, "b": 596, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0386}
{"question": "Solve (826 - 266)", "answer": "The result of (826 - 266) is 560\n\n####560", "a": 826, "b": 266, "operator": "-", "result": 560}
{"question": "Solve (83 / 339)", "answer": "The result of (83 / 339) is 0.2448\n\n####0.2448", "a": 83, "b": 339, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2448}
{"question": "Solve (822 / 106)", "answer": "The result of (822 / 106) is 7.7547\n\n####7.7547", "a": 822, "b": 106, "operator": "/", "result": 7.7547}
{"question": "Solve (130 + 456)", "answer": "The result of (130 + 456) is 586\n\n####586", "a": 130, "b": 456, "operator": "+", "result": 586}
{"question": "Solve (109 / 43)", "answer": "The result of (109 / 43) is 2.5349\n\n####2.5349", "a": 109, "b": 43, "operator": "/", "result": 2.5349}
{"question": "Solve (161 - 899)", "answer": "The result of (161 - 899) is -738\n\n####-738", "a": 161, "b": 899, "operator": "-", "result": -738}
{"question": "Solve (472 + 862)", "answer": "The result of (472 + 862) is 1334\n\n####1334", "a": 472, "b": 862, "operator": "+", "result": 1334}
{"question": "Solve (317 - 696)", "answer": "The result of (317 - 696) is -379\n\n####-379", "a": 317, "b": 696, "operator": "-", "result": -379}
{"question": "Solve (451 * 343)", "answer": "The result of (451 * 343) is 154693\n\n####154693", "a": 451, "b": 343, "operator": "*", "result": 154693}
{"question": "Solve (869 / 307)", "answer": "The result of (869 / 307) is 2.8306\n\n####2.8306", "a": 869, "b": 307, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8306}
{"question": "Solve (442 / 264)", "answer": "The result of (442 / 264) is 1.6742\n\n####1.6742", "a": 442, "b": 264, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6742}
{"question": "Solve (961 - 721)", "answer": "The result of (961 - 721) is 240\n\n####240", "a": 961, "b": 721, "operator": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve (128 * 64)", "answer": "The result of (128 * 64) is 8192\n\n####8192", "a": 128, "b": 64, "operator": "*", "result": 8192}
{"question": "Solve (829 - 360)", "answer": "The result of (829 - 360) is 469\n\n####469", "a": 829, "b": 360, "operator": "-", "result": 469}
{"question": "Solve (890 - 603)", "answer": "The result of (890 - 603) is 287\n\n####287", "a": 890, "b": 603, "operator": "-", "result": 287}
{"question": "Solve (699 * 273)", "answer": "The result of (699 * 273) is 190827\n\n####190827", "a": 699, "b": 273, "operator": "*", "result": 190827}
{"question": "Solve (955 + 810)", "answer": "The result of (955 + 810) is 1765\n\n####1765", "a": 955, "b": 810, "operator": "+", "result": 1765}
{"question": "Solve (463 * 335)", "answer": "The result of (463 * 335) is 155105\n\n####155105", "a": 463, "b": 335, "operator": "*", "result": 155105}
{"question": "Solve (106 * 227)", "answer": "The result of (106 * 227) is 24062\n\n####24062", "a": 106, "b": 227, "operator": "*", "result": 24062}
{"question": "Solve (110 * 479)", "answer": "The result of (110 * 479) is 52690\n\n####52690", "a": 110, "b": 479, "operator": "*", "result": 52690}
{"question": "Solve (179 - 16)", "answer": "The result of (179 - 16) is 163\n\n####163", "a": 179, "b": 16, "operator": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve (641 - 256)", "answer": "The result of (641 - 256) is 385\n\n####385", "a": 641, "b": 256, "operator": "-", "result": 385}
{"question": "Solve (918 + 325)", "answer": "The result of (918 + 325) is 1243\n\n####1243", "a": 918, "b": 325, "operator": "+", "result": 1243}
{"question": "Solve (857 * 944)", "answer": "The result of (857 * 944) is 809008\n\n####809008", "a": 857, "b": 944, "operator": "*", "result": 809008}
{"question": "Solve (367 * 39)", "answer": "The result of (367 * 39) is 14313\n\n####14313", "a": 367, "b": 39, "operator": "*", "result": 14313}
{"question": "Solve (49 - 878)", "answer": "The result of (49 - 878) is -829\n\n####-829", "a": 49, "b": 878, "operator": "-", "result": -829}
{"question": "Solve (169 - 4)", "answer": "The result of (169 - 4) is 165\n\n####165", "a": 169, "b": 4, "operator": "-", "result": 165}
{"question": "Solve (904 * 137)", "answer": "The result of (904 * 137) is 123848\n\n####123848", "a": 904, "b": 137, "operator": "*", "result": 123848}
{"question": "Solve (739 / 938)", "answer": "The result of (739 / 938) is 0.7878\n\n####0.7878", "a": 739, "b": 938, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7878}
{"question": "Solve (608 * 54)", "answer": "The result of (608 * 54) is 32832\n\n####32832", "a": 608, "b": 54, "operator": "*", "result": 32832}
{"question": "Solve (724 * 718)", "answer": "The result of (724 * 718) is 519832\n\n####519832", "a": 724, "b": 718, "operator": "*", "result": 519832}
{"question": "Solve (324 / 756)", "answer": "The result of (324 / 756) is 0.4286\n\n####0.4286", "a": 324, "b": 756, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4286}
{"question": "Solve (880 - 136)", "answer": "The result of (880 - 136) is 744\n\n####744", "a": 880, "b": 136, "operator": "-", "result": 744}
{"question": "Solve (536 / 243)", "answer": "The result of (536 / 243) is 2.2058\n\n####2.2058", "a": 536, "b": 243, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2058}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 912)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 912) is -314\n\n####-314", "a": 598, "b": 912, "operator": "-", "result": -314}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 987)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 987) is 133245\n\n####133245", "a": 135, "b": 987, "operator": "*", "result": 133245}
{"question": "Solve (970 - 290)", "answer": "The result of (970 - 290) is 680\n\n####680", "a": 970, "b": 290, "operator": "-", "result": 680}
{"question": "Solve (328 - 338)", "answer": "The result of (328 - 338) is -10\n\n####-10", "a": 328, "b": 338, "operator": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve (177 - 579)", "answer": "The result of (177 - 579) is -402\n\n####-402", "a": 177, "b": 579, "operator": "-", "result": -402}
{"question": "Solve (502 * 138)", "answer": "The result of (502 * 138) is 69276\n\n####69276", "a": 502, "b": 138, "operator": "*", "result": 69276}
{"question": "Solve (502 / 775)", "answer": "The result of (502 / 775) is 0.6477\n\n####0.6477", "a": 502, "b": 775, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6477}
{"question": "Solve (529 - 453)", "answer": "The result of (529 - 453) is 76\n\n####76", "a": 529, "b": 453, "operator": "-", "result": 76}
{"question": "Solve (24 - 886)", "answer": "The result of (24 - 886) is -862\n\n####-862", "a": 24, "b": 886, "operator": "-", "result": -862}
{"question": "Solve (909 * 848)", "answer": "The result of (909 * 848) is 770832\n\n####770832", "a": 909, "b": 848, "operator": "*", "result": 770832}
{"question": "Solve (421 - 336)", "answer": "The result of (421 - 336) is 85\n\n####85", "a": 421, "b": 336, "operator": "-", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve (367 * 143)", "answer": "The result of (367 * 143) is 52481\n\n####52481", "a": 367, "b": 143, "operator": "*", "result": 52481}
{"question": "Solve (619 - 731)", "answer": "The result of (619 - 731) is -112\n\n####-112", "a": 619, "b": 731, "operator": "-", "result": -112}
{"question": "Solve (747 + 753)", "answer": "The result of (747 + 753) is 1500\n\n####1500", "a": 747, "b": 753, "operator": "+", "result": 1500}
{"question": "Solve (298 - 857)", "answer": "The result of (298 - 857) is -559\n\n####-559", "a": 298, "b": 857, "operator": "-", "result": -559}
{"question": "Solve (617 * 856)", "answer": "The result of (617 * 856) is 528152\n\n####528152", "a": 617, "b": 856, "operator": "*", "result": 528152}
{"question": "Solve (78 - 519)", "answer": "The result of (78 - 519) is -441\n\n####-441", "a": 78, "b": 519, "operator": "-", "result": -441}
{"question": "Solve (321 * 66)", "answer": "The result of (321 * 66) is 21186\n\n####21186", "a": 321, "b": 66, "operator": "*", "result": 21186}
{"question": "Solve (843 + 930)", "answer": "The result of (843 + 930) is 1773\n\n####1773", "a": 843, "b": 930, "operator": "+", "result": 1773}
{"question": "Solve (953 - 780)", "answer": "The result of (953 - 780) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 953, "b": 780, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (743 + 684)", "answer": "The result of (743 + 684) is 1427\n\n####1427", "a": 743, "b": 684, "operator": "+", "result": 1427}
{"question": "Solve (711 - 496)", "answer": "The result of (711 - 496) is 215\n\n####215", "a": 711, "b": 496, "operator": "-", "result": 215}
{"question": "Solve (904 / 468)", "answer": "The result of (904 / 468) is 1.9316\n\n####1.9316", "a": 904, "b": 468, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9316}
{"question": "Solve (247 / 161)", "answer": "The result of (247 / 161) is 1.5342\n\n####1.5342", "a": 247, "b": 161, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5342}
{"question": "Solve (226 + 617)", "answer": "The result of (226 + 617) is 843\n\n####843", "a": 226, "b": 617, "operator": "+", "result": 843}
{"question": "Solve (153 / 289)", "answer": "The result of (153 / 289) is 0.5294\n\n####0.5294", "a": 153, "b": 289, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5294}
{"question": "Solve (47 * 341)", "answer": "The result of (47 * 341) is 16027\n\n####16027", "a": 47, "b": 341, "operator": "*", "result": 16027}
{"question": "Solve (382 - 238)", "answer": "The result of (382 - 238) is 144\n\n####144", "a": 382, "b": 238, "operator": "-", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve (677 + 621)", "answer": "The result of (677 + 621) is 1298\n\n####1298", "a": 677, "b": 621, "operator": "+", "result": 1298}
{"question": "Solve (233 / 279)", "answer": "The result of (233 / 279) is 0.8351\n\n####0.8351", "a": 233, "b": 279, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8351}
{"question": "Solve (229 - 708)", "answer": "The result of (229 - 708) is -479\n\n####-479", "a": 229, "b": 708, "operator": "-", "result": -479}
{"question": "Solve (672 / 257)", "answer": "The result of (672 / 257) is 2.6148\n\n####2.6148", "a": 672, "b": 257, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6148}
{"question": "Solve (566 + 750)", "answer": "The result of (566 + 750) is 1316\n\n####1316", "a": 566, "b": 750, "operator": "+", "result": 1316}
{"question": "Solve (467 - 564)", "answer": "The result of (467 - 564) is -97\n\n####-97", "a": 467, "b": 564, "operator": "-", "result": -97}
{"question": "Solve (913 / 611)", "answer": "The result of (913 / 611) is 1.4943\n\n####1.4943", "a": 913, "b": 611, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4943}
{"question": "Solve (84 + 937)", "answer": "The result of (84 + 937) is 1021\n\n####1021", "a": 84, "b": 937, "operator": "+", "result": 1021}
{"question": "Solve (79 / 879)", "answer": "The result of (79 / 879) is 0.0899\n\n####0.0899", "a": 79, "b": 879, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0899}
{"question": "Solve (485 + 653)", "answer": "The result of (485 + 653) is 1138\n\n####1138", "a": 485, "b": 653, "operator": "+", "result": 1138}
{"question": "Solve (788 * 481)", "answer": "The result of (788 * 481) is 379028\n\n####379028", "a": 788, "b": 481, "operator": "*", "result": 379028}
{"question": "Solve (938 * 965)", "answer": "The result of (938 * 965) is 905170\n\n####905170", "a": 938, "b": 965, "operator": "*", "result": 905170}
{"question": "Solve (277 - 3)", "answer": "The result of (277 - 3) is 274\n\n####274", "a": 277, "b": 3, "operator": "-", "result": 274}
{"question": "Solve (401 + 730)", "answer": "The result of (401 + 730) is 1131\n\n####1131", "a": 401, "b": 730, "operator": "+", "result": 1131}
{"question": "Solve (309 - 284)", "answer": "The result of (309 - 284) is 25\n\n####25", "a": 309, "b": 284, "operator": "-", "result": 25}
{"question": "Solve (38 - 508)", "answer": "The result of (38 - 508) is -470\n\n####-470", "a": 38, "b": 508, "operator": "-", "result": -470}
{"question": "Solve (641 - 823)", "answer": "The result of (641 - 823) is -182\n\n####-182", "a": 641, "b": 823, "operator": "-", "result": -182}
{"question": "Solve (480 / 126)", "answer": "The result of (480 / 126) is 3.8095\n\n####3.8095", "a": 480, "b": 126, "operator": "/", "result": 3.8095}
{"question": "Solve (284 / 279)", "answer": "The result of (284 / 279) is 1.0179\n\n####1.0179", "a": 284, "b": 279, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0179}
{"question": "Solve (712 * 353)", "answer": "The result of (712 * 353) is 251336\n\n####251336", "a": 712, "b": 353, "operator": "*", "result": 251336}
{"question": "Solve (346 / 800)", "answer": "The result of (346 / 800) is 0.4325\n\n####0.4325", "a": 346, "b": 800, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4325}
{"question": "Solve (605 / 181)", "answer": "The result of (605 / 181) is 3.3425\n\n####3.3425", "a": 605, "b": 181, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3425}
{"question": "Solve (662 + 457)", "answer": "The result of (662 + 457) is 1119\n\n####1119", "a": 662, "b": 457, "operator": "+", "result": 1119}
{"question": "Solve (875 / 873)", "answer": "The result of (875 / 873) is 1.0023\n\n####1.0023", "a": 875, "b": 873, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0023}
{"question": "Solve (180 - 602)", "answer": "The result of (180 - 602) is -422\n\n####-422", "a": 180, "b": 602, "operator": "-", "result": -422}
{"question": "Solve (714 * 466)", "answer": "The result of (714 * 466) is 332724\n\n####332724", "a": 714, "b": 466, "operator": "*", "result": 332724}
{"question": "Solve (598 + 673)", "answer": "The result of (598 + 673) is 1271\n\n####1271", "a": 598, "b": 673, "operator": "+", "result": 1271}
{"question": "Solve (578 + 304)", "answer": "The result of (578 + 304) is 882\n\n####882", "a": 578, "b": 304, "operator": "+", "result": 882}
{"question": "Solve (597 - 934)", "answer": "The result of (597 - 934) is -337\n\n####-337", "a": 597, "b": 934, "operator": "-", "result": -337}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 958)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 958) is -517\n\n####-517", "a": 441, "b": 958, "operator": "-", "result": -517}
{"question": "Solve (551 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (551 - 927) is -376\n\n####-376", "a": 551, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -376}
{"question": "Solve (344 / 762)", "answer": "The result of (344 / 762) is 0.4514\n\n####0.4514", "a": 344, "b": 762, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4514}
{"question": "Solve (109 / 453)", "answer": "The result of (109 / 453) is 0.2406\n\n####0.2406", "a": 109, "b": 453, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2406}
{"question": "Solve (372 * 98)", "answer": "The result of (372 * 98) is 36456\n\n####36456", "a": 372, "b": 98, "operator": "*", "result": 36456}
{"question": "Solve (919 + 716)", "answer": "The result of (919 + 716) is 1635\n\n####1635", "a": 919, "b": 716, "operator": "+", "result": 1635}
{"question": "Solve (33 - 571)", "answer": "The result of (33 - 571) is -538\n\n####-538", "a": 33, "b": 571, "operator": "-", "result": -538}
{"question": "Solve (598 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (598 - 876) is -278\n\n####-278", "a": 598, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -278}
{"question": "Solve (361 + 203)", "answer": "The result of (361 + 203) is 564\n\n####564", "a": 361, "b": 203, "operator": "+", "result": 564}
{"question": "Solve (561 - 490)", "answer": "The result of (561 - 490) is 71\n\n####71", "a": 561, "b": 490, "operator": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve (210 / 820)", "answer": "The result of (210 / 820) is 0.2561\n\n####0.2561", "a": 210, "b": 820, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2561}
{"question": "Solve (264 + 820)", "answer": "The result of (264 + 820) is 1084\n\n####1084", "a": 264, "b": 820, "operator": "+", "result": 1084}
{"question": "Solve (534 * 70)", "answer": "The result of (534 * 70) is 37380\n\n####37380", "a": 534, "b": 70, "operator": "*", "result": 37380}
{"question": "Solve (461 * 556)", "answer": "The result of (461 * 556) is 256316\n\n####256316", "a": 461, "b": 556, "operator": "*", "result": 256316}
{"question": "Solve (141 - 295)", "answer": "The result of (141 - 295) is -154\n\n####-154", "a": 141, "b": 295, "operator": "-", "result": -154}
{"question": "Solve (152 + 536)", "answer": "The result of (152 + 536) is 688\n\n####688", "a": 152, "b": 536, "operator": "+", "result": 688}
{"question": "Solve (389 - 610)", "answer": "The result of (389 - 610) is -221\n\n####-221", "a": 389, "b": 610, "operator": "-", "result": -221}
{"question": "Solve (135 + 211)", "answer": "The result of (135 + 211) is 346\n\n####346", "a": 135, "b": 211, "operator": "+", "result": 346}
{"question": "Solve (706 / 131)", "answer": "The result of (706 / 131) is 5.3893\n\n####5.3893", "a": 706, "b": 131, "operator": "/", "result": 5.3893}
{"question": "Solve (116 / 804)", "answer": "The result of (116 / 804) is 0.1443\n\n####0.1443", "a": 116, "b": 804, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1443}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 884)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 884) is 10608\n\n####10608", "a": 12, "b": 884, "operator": "*", "result": 10608}
{"question": "Solve (29 * 31)", "answer": "The result of (29 * 31) is 899\n\n####899", "a": 29, "b": 31, "operator": "*", "result": 899}
{"question": "Solve (592 / 181)", "answer": "The result of (592 / 181) is 3.2707\n\n####3.2707", "a": 592, "b": 181, "operator": "/", "result": 3.2707}
{"question": "Solve (548 - 922)", "answer": "The result of (548 - 922) is -374\n\n####-374", "a": 548, "b": 922, "operator": "-", "result": -374}
{"question": "Solve (12 * 763)", "answer": "The result of (12 * 763) is 9156\n\n####9156", "a": 12, "b": 763, "operator": "*", "result": 9156}
{"question": "Solve (159 - 264)", "answer": "The result of (159 - 264) is -105\n\n####-105", "a": 159, "b": 264, "operator": "-", "result": -105}
{"question": "Solve (351 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (351 - 317) is 34\n\n####34", "a": 351, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve (584 * 833)", "answer": "The result of (584 * 833) is 486472\n\n####486472", "a": 584, "b": 833, "operator": "*", "result": 486472}
{"question": "Solve (919 - 54)", "answer": "The result of (919 - 54) is 865\n\n####865", "a": 919, "b": 54, "operator": "-", "result": 865}
{"question": "Solve (966 - 412)", "answer": "The result of (966 - 412) is 554\n\n####554", "a": 966, "b": 412, "operator": "-", "result": 554}
{"question": "Solve (755 * 195)", "answer": "The result of (755 * 195) is 147225\n\n####147225", "a": 755, "b": 195, "operator": "*", "result": 147225}
{"question": "Solve (380 * 747)", "answer": "The result of (380 * 747) is 283860\n\n####283860", "a": 380, "b": 747, "operator": "*", "result": 283860}
{"question": "Solve (829 / 91)", "answer": "The result of (829 / 91) is 9.1099\n\n####9.1099", "a": 829, "b": 91, "operator": "/", "result": 9.1099}
{"question": "Solve (936 * 61)", "answer": "The result of (936 * 61) is 57096\n\n####57096", "a": 936, "b": 61, "operator": "*", "result": 57096}
{"question": "Solve (126 * 184)", "answer": "The result of (126 * 184) is 23184\n\n####23184", "a": 126, "b": 184, "operator": "*", "result": 23184}
{"question": "Solve (708 * 31)", "answer": "The result of (708 * 31) is 21948\n\n####21948", "a": 708, "b": 31, "operator": "*", "result": 21948}
{"question": "Solve (247 - 824)", "answer": "The result of (247 - 824) is -577\n\n####-577", "a": 247, "b": 824, "operator": "-", "result": -577}
{"question": "Solve (497 / 172)", "answer": "The result of (497 / 172) is 2.8895\n\n####2.8895", "a": 497, "b": 172, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8895}
{"question": "Solve (1 - 392)", "answer": "The result of (1 - 392) is -391\n\n####-391", "a": 1, "b": 392, "operator": "-", "result": -391}
{"question": "Solve (249 - 378)", "answer": "The result of (249 - 378) is -129\n\n####-129", "a": 249, "b": 378, "operator": "-", "result": -129}
{"question": "Solve (951 * 969)", "answer": "The result of (951 * 969) is 921519\n\n####921519", "a": 951, "b": 969, "operator": "*", "result": 921519}
{"question": "Solve (295 * 400)", "answer": "The result of (295 * 400) is 118000\n\n####118000", "a": 295, "b": 400, "operator": "*", "result": 118000}
{"question": "Solve (995 / 583)", "answer": "The result of (995 / 583) is 1.7067\n\n####1.7067", "a": 995, "b": 583, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7067}
{"question": "Solve (700 - 123)", "answer": "The result of (700 - 123) is 577\n\n####577", "a": 700, "b": 123, "operator": "-", "result": 577}
{"question": "Solve (396 * 340)", "answer": "The result of (396 * 340) is 134640\n\n####134640", "a": 396, "b": 340, "operator": "*", "result": 134640}
{"question": "Solve (840 - 224)", "answer": "The result of (840 - 224) is 616\n\n####616", "a": 840, "b": 224, "operator": "-", "result": 616}
{"question": "Solve (192 * 561)", "answer": "The result of (192 * 561) is 107712\n\n####107712", "a": 192, "b": 561, "operator": "*", "result": 107712}
{"question": "Solve (895 + 973)", "answer": "The result of (895 + 973) is 1868\n\n####1868", "a": 895, "b": 973, "operator": "+", "result": 1868}
{"question": "Solve (138 - 432)", "answer": "The result of (138 - 432) is -294\n\n####-294", "a": 138, "b": 432, "operator": "-", "result": -294}
{"question": "Solve (924 + 668)", "answer": "The result of (924 + 668) is 1592\n\n####1592", "a": 924, "b": 668, "operator": "+", "result": 1592}
{"question": "Solve (693 * 619)", "answer": "The result of (693 * 619) is 428967\n\n####428967", "a": 693, "b": 619, "operator": "*", "result": 428967}
{"question": "Solve (559 * 656)", "answer": "The result of (559 * 656) is 366704\n\n####366704", "a": 559, "b": 656, "operator": "*", "result": 366704}
{"question": "Solve (676 - 872)", "answer": "The result of (676 - 872) is -196\n\n####-196", "a": 676, "b": 872, "operator": "-", "result": -196}
{"question": "Solve (949 + 851)", "answer": "The result of (949 + 851) is 1800\n\n####1800", "a": 949, "b": 851, "operator": "+", "result": 1800}
{"question": "Solve (432 - 452)", "answer": "The result of (432 - 452) is -20\n\n####-20", "a": 432, "b": 452, "operator": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve (903 * 843)", "answer": "The result of (903 * 843) is 761229\n\n####761229", "a": 903, "b": 843, "operator": "*", "result": 761229}
{"question": "Solve (14 * 141)", "answer": "The result of (14 * 141) is 1974\n\n####1974", "a": 14, "b": 141, "operator": "*", "result": 1974}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 278)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 278) is 125656\n\n####125656", "a": 452, "b": 278, "operator": "*", "result": 125656}
{"question": "Solve (705 / 573)", "answer": "The result of (705 / 573) is 1.2304\n\n####1.2304", "a": 705, "b": 573, "operator": "/", "result": 1.2304}
{"question": "Solve (833 - 303)", "answer": "The result of (833 - 303) is 530\n\n####530", "a": 833, "b": 303, "operator": "-", "result": 530}
{"question": "Solve (588 / 801)", "answer": "The result of (588 / 801) is 0.7341\n\n####0.7341", "a": 588, "b": 801, "operator": "/", "result": 0.7341}
{"question": "Solve (650 + 179)", "answer": "The result of (650 + 179) is 829\n\n####829", "a": 650, "b": 179, "operator": "+", "result": 829}
{"question": "Solve (353 / 155)", "answer": "The result of (353 / 155) is 2.2774\n\n####2.2774", "a": 353, "b": 155, "operator": "/", "result": 2.2774}
{"question": "Solve (297 - 6)", "answer": "The result of (297 - 6) is 291\n\n####291", "a": 297, "b": 6, "operator": "-", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve (985 * 203)", "answer": "The result of (985 * 203) is 199955\n\n####199955", "a": 985, "b": 203, "operator": "*", "result": 199955}
{"question": "Solve (941 + 583)", "answer": "The result of (941 + 583) is 1524\n\n####1524", "a": 941, "b": 583, "operator": "+", "result": 1524}
{"question": "Solve (209 + 150)", "answer": "The result of (209 + 150) is 359\n\n####359", "a": 209, "b": 150, "operator": "+", "result": 359}
{"question": "Solve (814 + 952)", "answer": "The result of (814 + 952) is 1766\n\n####1766", "a": 814, "b": 952, "operator": "+", "result": 1766}
{"question": "Solve (77 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (77 / 815) is 0.0945\n\n####0.0945", "a": 77, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0945}
{"question": "Solve (967 * 147)", "answer": "The result of (967 * 147) is 142149\n\n####142149", "a": 967, "b": 147, "operator": "*", "result": 142149}
{"question": "Solve (452 * 511)", "answer": "The result of (452 * 511) is 230972\n\n####230972", "a": 452, "b": 511, "operator": "*", "result": 230972}
{"question": "Solve (827 * 590)", "answer": "The result of (827 * 590) is 487930\n\n####487930", "a": 827, "b": 590, "operator": "*", "result": 487930}
{"question": "Solve (355 + 997)", "answer": "The result of (355 + 997) is 1352\n\n####1352", "a": 355, "b": 997, "operator": "+", "result": 1352}
{"question": "Solve (448 + 530)", "answer": "The result of (448 + 530) is 978\n\n####978", "a": 448, "b": 530, "operator": "+", "result": 978}
{"question": "Solve (219 / 682)", "answer": "The result of (219 / 682) is 0.3211\n\n####0.3211", "a": 219, "b": 682, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3211}
{"question": "Solve (960 - 992)", "answer": "The result of (960 - 992) is -32\n\n####-32", "a": 960, "b": 992, "operator": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve (500 / 478)", "answer": "The result of (500 / 478) is 1.046\n\n####1.046", "a": 500, "b": 478, "operator": "/", "result": 1.046}
{"question": "Solve (380 - 742)", "answer": "The result of (380 - 742) is -362\n\n####-362", "a": 380, "b": 742, "operator": "-", "result": -362}
{"question": "Solve (913 * 834)", "answer": "The result of (913 * 834) is 761442\n\n####761442", "a": 913, "b": 834, "operator": "*", "result": 761442}
{"question": "Solve (656 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (656 * 407) is 266992\n\n####266992", "a": 656, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 266992}
{"question": "Solve (668 + 48)", "answer": "The result of (668 + 48) is 716\n\n####716", "a": 668, "b": 48, "operator": "+", "result": 716}
{"question": "Solve (542 / 511)", "answer": "The result of (542 / 511) is 1.0607\n\n####1.0607", "a": 542, "b": 511, "operator": "/", "result": 1.0607}
{"question": "Solve (1 * 409)", "answer": "The result of (1 * 409) is 409\n\n####409", "a": 1, "b": 409, "operator": "*", "result": 409}
{"question": "Solve (531 / 192)", "answer": "The result of (531 / 192) is 2.7656\n\n####2.7656", "a": 531, "b": 192, "operator": "/", "result": 2.7656}
{"question": "Solve (49 - 254)", "answer": "The result of (49 - 254) is -205\n\n####-205", "a": 49, "b": 254, "operator": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve (359 / 764)", "answer": "The result of (359 / 764) is 0.4699\n\n####0.4699", "a": 359, "b": 764, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4699}
{"question": "Solve (870 + 411)", "answer": "The result of (870 + 411) is 1281\n\n####1281", "a": 870, "b": 411, "operator": "+", "result": 1281}
{"question": "Solve (137 * 958)", "answer": "The result of (137 * 958) is 131246\n\n####131246", "a": 137, "b": 958, "operator": "*", "result": 131246}
{"question": "Solve (764 / 370)", "answer": "The result of (764 / 370) is 2.0649\n\n####2.0649", "a": 764, "b": 370, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0649}
{"question": "Solve (253 - 853)", "answer": "The result of (253 - 853) is -600\n\n####-600", "a": 253, "b": 853, "operator": "-", "result": -600}
{"question": "Solve (875 - 669)", "answer": "The result of (875 - 669) is 206\n\n####206", "a": 875, "b": 669, "operator": "-", "result": 206}
{"question": "Solve (738 + 257)", "answer": "The result of (738 + 257) is 995\n\n####995", "a": 738, "b": 257, "operator": "+", "result": 995}
{"question": "Solve (201 + 11)", "answer": "The result of (201 + 11) is 212\n\n####212", "a": 201, "b": 11, "operator": "+", "result": 212}
{"question": "Solve (12 - 916)", "answer": "The result of (12 - 916) is -904\n\n####-904", "a": 12, "b": 916, "operator": "-", "result": -904}
{"question": "Solve (810 / 81)", "answer": "The result of (810 / 81) is 10.0\n\n####10.0", "a": 810, "b": 81, "operator": "/", "result": 10.0}
{"question": "Solve (760 - 364)", "answer": "The result of (760 - 364) is 396\n\n####396", "a": 760, "b": 364, "operator": "-", "result": 396}
{"question": "Solve (370 / 262)", "answer": "The result of (370 / 262) is 1.4122\n\n####1.4122", "a": 370, "b": 262, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4122}
{"question": "Solve (980 + 968)", "answer": "The result of (980 + 968) is 1948\n\n####1948", "a": 980, "b": 968, "operator": "+", "result": 1948}
{"question": "Solve (832 - 524)", "answer": "The result of (832 - 524) is 308\n\n####308", "a": 832, "b": 524, "operator": "-", "result": 308}
{"question": "Solve (821 - 371)", "answer": "The result of (821 - 371) is 450\n\n####450", "a": 821, "b": 371, "operator": "-", "result": 450}
{"question": "Solve (389 + 19)", "answer": "The result of (389 + 19) is 408\n\n####408", "a": 389, "b": 19, "operator": "+", "result": 408}
{"question": "Solve (393 - 486)", "answer": "The result of (393 - 486) is -93\n\n####-93", "a": 393, "b": 486, "operator": "-", "result": -93}
{"question": "Solve (322 / 348)", "answer": "The result of (322 / 348) is 0.9253\n\n####0.9253", "a": 322, "b": 348, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9253}
{"question": "Solve (245 - 600)", "answer": "The result of (245 - 600) is -355\n\n####-355", "a": 245, "b": 600, "operator": "-", "result": -355}
{"question": "Solve (739 * 498)", "answer": "The result of (739 * 498) is 368022\n\n####368022", "a": 739, "b": 498, "operator": "*", "result": 368022}
{"question": "Solve (609 - 630)", "answer": "The result of (609 - 630) is -21\n\n####-21", "a": 609, "b": 630, "operator": "-", "result": -21}
{"question": "Solve (194 - 204)", "answer": "The result of (194 - 204) is -10\n\n####-10", "a": 194, "b": 204, "operator": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve (900 / 370)", "answer": "The result of (900 / 370) is 2.4324\n\n####2.4324", "a": 900, "b": 370, "operator": "/", "result": 2.4324}
{"question": "Solve (319 + 407)", "answer": "The result of (319 + 407) is 726\n\n####726", "a": 319, "b": 407, "operator": "+", "result": 726}
{"question": "Solve (557 / 484)", "answer": "The result of (557 / 484) is 1.1508\n\n####1.1508", "a": 557, "b": 484, "operator": "/", "result": 1.1508}
{"question": "Solve (698 * 407)", "answer": "The result of (698 * 407) is 284086\n\n####284086", "a": 698, "b": 407, "operator": "*", "result": 284086}
{"question": "Solve (981 / 35)", "answer": "The result of (981 / 35) is 28.0286\n\n####28.0286", "a": 981, "b": 35, "operator": "/", "result": 28.0286}
{"question": "Solve (715 + 336)", "answer": "The result of (715 + 336) is 1051\n\n####1051", "a": 715, "b": 336, "operator": "+", "result": 1051}
{"question": "Solve (324 * 870)", "answer": "The result of (324 * 870) is 281880\n\n####281880", "a": 324, "b": 870, "operator": "*", "result": 281880}
{"question": "Solve (141 * 961)", "answer": "The result of (141 * 961) is 135501\n\n####135501", "a": 141, "b": 961, "operator": "*", "result": 135501}
{"question": "Solve (57 - 716)", "answer": "The result of (57 - 716) is -659\n\n####-659", "a": 57, "b": 716, "operator": "-", "result": -659}
{"question": "Solve (834 + 611)", "answer": "The result of (834 + 611) is 1445\n\n####1445", "a": 834, "b": 611, "operator": "+", "result": 1445}
{"question": "Solve (444 - 923)", "answer": "The result of (444 - 923) is -479\n\n####-479", "a": 444, "b": 923, "operator": "-", "result": -479}
{"question": "Solve (637 * 167)", "answer": "The result of (637 * 167) is 106379\n\n####106379", "a": 637, "b": 167, "operator": "*", "result": 106379}
{"question": "Solve (93 - 33)", "answer": "The result of (93 - 33) is 60\n\n####60", "a": 93, "b": 33, "operator": "-", "result": 60}
{"question": "Solve (858 - 695)", "answer": "The result of (858 - 695) is 163\n\n####163", "a": 858, "b": 695, "operator": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve (884 / 648)", "answer": "The result of (884 / 648) is 1.3642\n\n####1.3642", "a": 884, "b": 648, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3642}
{"question": "Solve (779 + 148)", "answer": "The result of (779 + 148) is 927\n\n####927", "a": 779, "b": 148, "operator": "+", "result": 927}
{"question": "Solve (360 * 834)", "answer": "The result of (360 * 834) is 300240\n\n####300240", "a": 360, "b": 834, "operator": "*", "result": 300240}
{"question": "Solve (197 - 50)", "answer": "The result of (197 - 50) is 147\n\n####147", "a": 197, "b": 50, "operator": "-", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve (234 * 176)", "answer": "The result of (234 * 176) is 41184\n\n####41184", "a": 234, "b": 176, "operator": "*", "result": 41184}
{"question": "Solve (5 + 285)", "answer": "The result of (5 + 285) is 290\n\n####290", "a": 5, "b": 285, "operator": "+", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve (508 * 986)", "answer": "The result of (508 * 986) is 500888\n\n####500888", "a": 508, "b": 986, "operator": "*", "result": 500888}
{"question": "Solve (280 * 869)", "answer": "The result of (280 * 869) is 243320\n\n####243320", "a": 280, "b": 869, "operator": "*", "result": 243320}
{"question": "Solve (790 * 294)", "answer": "The result of (790 * 294) is 232260\n\n####232260", "a": 790, "b": 294, "operator": "*", "result": 232260}
{"question": "Solve (696 * 221)", "answer": "The result of (696 * 221) is 153816\n\n####153816", "a": 696, "b": 221, "operator": "*", "result": 153816}
{"question": "Solve (577 - 661)", "answer": "The result of (577 - 661) is -84\n\n####-84", "a": 577, "b": 661, "operator": "-", "result": -84}
{"question": "Solve (643 - 965)", "answer": "The result of (643 - 965) is -322\n\n####-322", "a": 643, "b": 965, "operator": "-", "result": -322}
{"question": "Solve (983 / 674)", "answer": "The result of (983 / 674) is 1.4585\n\n####1.4585", "a": 983, "b": 674, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4585}
{"question": "Solve (780 / 807)", "answer": "The result of (780 / 807) is 0.9665\n\n####0.9665", "a": 780, "b": 807, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9665}
{"question": "Solve (664 * 792)", "answer": "The result of (664 * 792) is 525888\n\n####525888", "a": 664, "b": 792, "operator": "*", "result": 525888}
{"question": "Solve (437 + 279)", "answer": "The result of (437 + 279) is 716\n\n####716", "a": 437, "b": 279, "operator": "+", "result": 716}
{"question": "Solve (214 / 624)", "answer": "The result of (214 / 624) is 0.3429\n\n####0.3429", "a": 214, "b": 624, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3429}
{"question": "Solve (608 + 837)", "answer": "The result of (608 + 837) is 1445\n\n####1445", "a": 608, "b": 837, "operator": "+", "result": 1445}
{"question": "Solve (452 + 600)", "answer": "The result of (452 + 600) is 1052\n\n####1052", "a": 452, "b": 600, "operator": "+", "result": 1052}
{"question": "Solve (903 - 272)", "answer": "The result of (903 - 272) is 631\n\n####631", "a": 903, "b": 272, "operator": "-", "result": 631}
{"question": "Solve (473 - 472)", "answer": "The result of (473 - 472) is 1\n\n####1", "a": 473, "b": 472, "operator": "-", "result": 1}
{"question": "Solve (753 - 169)", "answer": "The result of (753 - 169) is 584\n\n####584", "a": 753, "b": 169, "operator": "-", "result": 584}
{"question": "Solve (201 - 895)", "answer": "The result of (201 - 895) is -694\n\n####-694", "a": 201, "b": 895, "operator": "-", "result": -694}
{"question": "Solve (87 / 446)", "answer": "The result of (87 / 446) is 0.1951\n\n####0.1951", "a": 87, "b": 446, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1951}
{"question": "Solve (861 / 391)", "answer": "The result of (861 / 391) is 2.202\n\n####2.202", "a": 861, "b": 391, "operator": "/", "result": 2.202}
{"question": "Solve (750 + 471)", "answer": "The result of (750 + 471) is 1221\n\n####1221", "a": 750, "b": 471, "operator": "+", "result": 1221}
{"question": "Solve (96 * 620)", "answer": "The result of (96 * 620) is 59520\n\n####59520", "a": 96, "b": 620, "operator": "*", "result": 59520}
{"question": "Solve (226 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (226 - 706) is -480\n\n####-480", "a": 226, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -480}
{"question": "Solve (224 - 673)", "answer": "The result of (224 - 673) is -449\n\n####-449", "a": 224, "b": 673, "operator": "-", "result": -449}
{"question": "Solve (82 * 713)", "answer": "The result of (82 * 713) is 58466\n\n####58466", "a": 82, "b": 713, "operator": "*", "result": 58466}
{"question": "Solve (865 - 637)", "answer": "The result of (865 - 637) is 228\n\n####228", "a": 865, "b": 637, "operator": "-", "result": 228}
{"question": "Solve (90 - 390)", "answer": "The result of (90 - 390) is -300\n\n####-300", "a": 90, "b": 390, "operator": "-", "result": -300}
{"question": "Solve (835 / 515)", "answer": "The result of (835 / 515) is 1.6214\n\n####1.6214", "a": 835, "b": 515, "operator": "/", "result": 1.6214}
{"question": "Solve (174 / 884)", "answer": "The result of (174 / 884) is 0.1968\n\n####0.1968", "a": 174, "b": 884, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1968}
{"question": "Solve (270 / 390)", "answer": "The result of (270 / 390) is 0.6923\n\n####0.6923", "a": 270, "b": 390, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6923}
{"question": "Solve (55 / 369)", "answer": "The result of (55 / 369) is 0.1491\n\n####0.1491", "a": 55, "b": 369, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1491}
{"question": "Solve (709 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (709 - 384) is 325\n\n####325", "a": 709, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": 325}
{"question": "Solve (282 - 737)", "answer": "The result of (282 - 737) is -455\n\n####-455", "a": 282, "b": 737, "operator": "-", "result": -455}
{"question": "Solve (855 * 780)", "answer": "The result of (855 * 780) is 666900\n\n####666900", "a": 855, "b": 780, "operator": "*", "result": 666900}
{"question": "Solve (758 * 753)", "answer": "The result of (758 * 753) is 570774\n\n####570774", "a": 758, "b": 753, "operator": "*", "result": 570774}
{"question": "Solve (468 / 897)", "answer": "The result of (468 / 897) is 0.5217\n\n####0.5217", "a": 468, "b": 897, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5217}
{"question": "Solve (24 / 711)", "answer": "The result of (24 / 711) is 0.0338\n\n####0.0338", "a": 24, "b": 711, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0338}
{"question": "Solve (913 + 846)", "answer": "The result of (913 + 846) is 1759\n\n####1759", "a": 913, "b": 846, "operator": "+", "result": 1759}
{"question": "Solve (256 + 469)", "answer": "The result of (256 + 469) is 725\n\n####725", "a": 256, "b": 469, "operator": "+", "result": 725}
{"question": "Solve (941 + 233)", "answer": "The result of (941 + 233) is 1174\n\n####1174", "a": 941, "b": 233, "operator": "+", "result": 1174}
{"question": "Solve (299 + 280)", "answer": "The result of (299 + 280) is 579\n\n####579", "a": 299, "b": 280, "operator": "+", "result": 579}
{"question": "Solve (199 + 280)", "answer": "The result of (199 + 280) is 479\n\n####479", "a": 199, "b": 280, "operator": "+", "result": 479}
{"question": "Solve (887 - 428)", "answer": "The result of (887 - 428) is 459\n\n####459", "a": 887, "b": 428, "operator": "-", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve (962 * 882)", "answer": "The result of (962 * 882) is 848484\n\n####848484", "a": 962, "b": 882, "operator": "*", "result": 848484}
{"question": "Solve (423 - 885)", "answer": "The result of (423 - 885) is -462\n\n####-462", "a": 423, "b": 885, "operator": "-", "result": -462}
{"question": "Solve (665 / 677)", "answer": "The result of (665 / 677) is 0.9823\n\n####0.9823", "a": 665, "b": 677, "operator": "/", "result": 0.9823}
{"question": "Solve (394 / 904)", "answer": "The result of (394 / 904) is 0.4358\n\n####0.4358", "a": 394, "b": 904, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4358}
{"question": "Solve (492 - 101)", "answer": "The result of (492 - 101) is 391\n\n####391", "a": 492, "b": 101, "operator": "-", "result": 391}
{"question": "Solve (578 - 202)", "answer": "The result of (578 - 202) is 376\n\n####376", "a": 578, "b": 202, "operator": "-", "result": 376}
{"question": "Solve (472 - 599)", "answer": "The result of (472 - 599) is -127\n\n####-127", "a": 472, "b": 599, "operator": "-", "result": -127}
{"question": "Solve (658 * 415)", "answer": "The result of (658 * 415) is 273070\n\n####273070", "a": 658, "b": 415, "operator": "*", "result": 273070}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 705)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 705) is -185\n\n####-185", "a": 520, "b": 705, "operator": "-", "result": -185}
{"question": "Solve (465 + 97)", "answer": "The result of (465 + 97) is 562\n\n####562", "a": 465, "b": 97, "operator": "+", "result": 562}
{"question": "Solve (210 * 774)", "answer": "The result of (210 * 774) is 162540\n\n####162540", "a": 210, "b": 774, "operator": "*", "result": 162540}
{"question": "Solve (684 * 766)", "answer": "The result of (684 * 766) is 523944\n\n####523944", "a": 684, "b": 766, "operator": "*", "result": 523944}
{"question": "Solve (374 - 805)", "answer": "The result of (374 - 805) is -431\n\n####-431", "a": 374, "b": 805, "operator": "-", "result": -431}
{"question": "Solve (145 / 442)", "answer": "The result of (145 / 442) is 0.3281\n\n####0.3281", "a": 145, "b": 442, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3281}
{"question": "Solve (809 + 460)", "answer": "The result of (809 + 460) is 1269\n\n####1269", "a": 809, "b": 460, "operator": "+", "result": 1269}
{"question": "Solve (277 / 429)", "answer": "The result of (277 / 429) is 0.6457\n\n####0.6457", "a": 277, "b": 429, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6457}
{"question": "Solve (598 + 206)", "answer": "The result of (598 + 206) is 804\n\n####804", "a": 598, "b": 206, "operator": "+", "result": 804}
{"question": "Solve (520 * 684)", "answer": "The result of (520 * 684) is 355680\n\n####355680", "a": 520, "b": 684, "operator": "*", "result": 355680}
{"question": "Solve (75 + 422)", "answer": "The result of (75 + 422) is 497\n\n####497", "a": 75, "b": 422, "operator": "+", "result": 497}
{"question": "Solve (783 - 844)", "answer": "The result of (783 - 844) is -61\n\n####-61", "a": 783, "b": 844, "operator": "-", "result": -61}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 811)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 811) is 0.0444\n\n####0.0444", "a": 36, "b": 811, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0444}
{"question": "Solve (894 * 78)", "answer": "The result of (894 * 78) is 69732\n\n####69732", "a": 894, "b": 78, "operator": "*", "result": 69732}
{"question": "Solve (23 + 773)", "answer": "The result of (23 + 773) is 796\n\n####796", "a": 23, "b": 773, "operator": "+", "result": 796}
{"question": "Solve (923 - 680)", "answer": "The result of (923 - 680) is 243\n\n####243", "a": 923, "b": 680, "operator": "-", "result": 243}
{"question": "Solve (739 / 533)", "answer": "The result of (739 / 533) is 1.3865\n\n####1.3865", "a": 739, "b": 533, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3865}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 528)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 528) is 141504\n\n####141504", "a": 268, "b": 528, "operator": "*", "result": 141504}
{"question": "Solve (408 / 716)", "answer": "The result of (408 / 716) is 0.5698\n\n####0.5698", "a": 408, "b": 716, "operator": "/", "result": 0.5698}
{"question": "Solve (732 - 299)", "answer": "The result of (732 - 299) is 433\n\n####433", "a": 732, "b": 299, "operator": "-", "result": 433}
{"question": "Solve (915 - 593)", "answer": "The result of (915 - 593) is 322\n\n####322", "a": 915, "b": 593, "operator": "-", "result": 322}
{"question": "Solve (566 - 733)", "answer": "The result of (566 - 733) is -167\n\n####-167", "a": 566, "b": 733, "operator": "-", "result": -167}
{"question": "Solve (417 + 449)", "answer": "The result of (417 + 449) is 866\n\n####866", "a": 417, "b": 449, "operator": "+", "result": 866}
{"question": "Solve (193 - 506)", "answer": "The result of (193 - 506) is -313\n\n####-313", "a": 193, "b": 506, "operator": "-", "result": -313}
{"question": "Solve (524 * 197)", "answer": "The result of (524 * 197) is 103228\n\n####103228", "a": 524, "b": 197, "operator": "*", "result": 103228}
{"question": "Solve (105 / 384)", "answer": "The result of (105 / 384) is 0.2734\n\n####0.2734", "a": 105, "b": 384, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2734}
{"question": "Solve (833 + 610)", "answer": "The result of (833 + 610) is 1443\n\n####1443", "a": 833, "b": 610, "operator": "+", "result": 1443}
{"question": "Solve (800 * 558)", "answer": "The result of (800 * 558) is 446400\n\n####446400", "a": 800, "b": 558, "operator": "*", "result": 446400}
{"question": "Solve (784 / 233)", "answer": "The result of (784 / 233) is 3.3648\n\n####3.3648", "a": 784, "b": 233, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3648}
{"question": "Solve (115 / 442)", "answer": "The result of (115 / 442) is 0.2602\n\n####0.2602", "a": 115, "b": 442, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2602}
{"question": "Solve (657 / 234)", "answer": "The result of (657 / 234) is 2.8077\n\n####2.8077", "a": 657, "b": 234, "operator": "/", "result": 2.8077}
{"question": "Solve (135 * 692)", "answer": "The result of (135 * 692) is 93420\n\n####93420", "a": 135, "b": 692, "operator": "*", "result": 93420}
{"question": "Solve (54 / 606)", "answer": "The result of (54 / 606) is 0.0891\n\n####0.0891", "a": 54, "b": 606, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0891}
{"question": "Solve (896 * 854)", "answer": "The result of (896 * 854) is 765184\n\n####765184", "a": 896, "b": 854, "operator": "*", "result": 765184}
{"question": "Solve (447 + 665)", "answer": "The result of (447 + 665) is 1112\n\n####1112", "a": 447, "b": 665, "operator": "+", "result": 1112}
{"question": "Solve (31 * 635)", "answer": "The result of (31 * 635) is 19685\n\n####19685", "a": 31, "b": 635, "operator": "*", "result": 19685}
{"question": "Solve (829 * 73)", "answer": "The result of (829 * 73) is 60517\n\n####60517", "a": 829, "b": 73, "operator": "*", "result": 60517}
{"question": "Solve (442 - 688)", "answer": "The result of (442 - 688) is -246\n\n####-246", "a": 442, "b": 688, "operator": "-", "result": -246}
{"question": "Solve (480 / 120)", "answer": "The result of (480 / 120) is 4.0\n\n####4.0", "a": 480, "b": 120, "operator": "/", "result": 4.0}
{"question": "Solve (586 - 855)", "answer": "The result of (586 - 855) is -269\n\n####-269", "a": 586, "b": 855, "operator": "-", "result": -269}
{"question": "Solve (266 - 720)", "answer": "The result of (266 - 720) is -454\n\n####-454", "a": 266, "b": 720, "operator": "-", "result": -454}
{"question": "Solve (536 * 764)", "answer": "The result of (536 * 764) is 409504\n\n####409504", "a": 536, "b": 764, "operator": "*", "result": 409504}
{"question": "Solve (636 - 492)", "answer": "The result of (636 - 492) is 144\n\n####144", "a": 636, "b": 492, "operator": "-", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve (327 + 641)", "answer": "The result of (327 + 641) is 968\n\n####968", "a": 327, "b": 641, "operator": "+", "result": 968}
{"question": "Solve (348 / 899)", "answer": "The result of (348 / 899) is 0.3871\n\n####0.3871", "a": 348, "b": 899, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3871}
{"question": "Solve (439 + 542)", "answer": "The result of (439 + 542) is 981\n\n####981", "a": 439, "b": 542, "operator": "+", "result": 981}
{"question": "Solve (842 / 579)", "answer": "The result of (842 / 579) is 1.4542\n\n####1.4542", "a": 842, "b": 579, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4542}
{"question": "Solve (603 / 227)", "answer": "The result of (603 / 227) is 2.6564\n\n####2.6564", "a": 603, "b": 227, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6564}
{"question": "Solve (66 / 191)", "answer": "The result of (66 / 191) is 0.3455\n\n####0.3455", "a": 66, "b": 191, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3455}
{"question": "Solve (268 * 695)", "answer": "The result of (268 * 695) is 186260\n\n####186260", "a": 268, "b": 695, "operator": "*", "result": 186260}
{"question": "Solve (348 - 123)", "answer": "The result of (348 - 123) is 225\n\n####225", "a": 348, "b": 123, "operator": "-", "result": 225}
{"question": "Solve (796 - 982)", "answer": "The result of (796 - 982) is -186\n\n####-186", "a": 796, "b": 982, "operator": "-", "result": -186}
{"question": "Solve (919 - 298)", "answer": "The result of (919 - 298) is 621\n\n####621", "a": 919, "b": 298, "operator": "-", "result": 621}
{"question": "Solve (840 - 989)", "answer": "The result of (840 - 989) is -149\n\n####-149", "a": 840, "b": 989, "operator": "-", "result": -149}
{"question": "Solve (630 - 690)", "answer": "The result of (630 - 690) is -60\n\n####-60", "a": 630, "b": 690, "operator": "-", "result": -60}
{"question": "Solve (367 / 939)", "answer": "The result of (367 / 939) is 0.3908\n\n####0.3908", "a": 367, "b": 939, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3908}
{"question": "Solve (484 + 12)", "answer": "The result of (484 + 12) is 496\n\n####496", "a": 484, "b": 12, "operator": "+", "result": 496}
{"question": "Solve (59 / 657)", "answer": "The result of (59 / 657) is 0.0898\n\n####0.0898", "a": 59, "b": 657, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0898}
{"question": "Solve (990 * 881)", "answer": "The result of (990 * 881) is 872190\n\n####872190", "a": 990, "b": 881, "operator": "*", "result": 872190}
{"question": "Solve (54 - 195)", "answer": "The result of (54 - 195) is -141\n\n####-141", "a": 54, "b": 195, "operator": "-", "result": -141}
{"question": "Solve (897 + 82)", "answer": "The result of (897 + 82) is 979\n\n####979", "a": 897, "b": 82, "operator": "+", "result": 979}
{"question": "Solve (264 * 381)", "answer": "The result of (264 * 381) is 100584\n\n####100584", "a": 264, "b": 381, "operator": "*", "result": 100584}
{"question": "Solve (274 * 898)", "answer": "The result of (274 * 898) is 246052\n\n####246052", "a": 274, "b": 898, "operator": "*", "result": 246052}
{"question": "Solve (21 / 327)", "answer": "The result of (21 / 327) is 0.0642\n\n####0.0642", "a": 21, "b": 327, "operator": "/", "result": 0.0642}
{"question": "Solve (222 - 354)", "answer": "The result of (222 - 354) is -132\n\n####-132", "a": 222, "b": 354, "operator": "-", "result": -132}
{"question": "Solve (993 / 624)", "answer": "The result of (993 / 624) is 1.5913\n\n####1.5913", "a": 993, "b": 624, "operator": "/", "result": 1.5913}
{"question": "Solve (413 / 876)", "answer": "The result of (413 / 876) is 0.4715\n\n####0.4715", "a": 413, "b": 876, "operator": "/", "result": 0.4715}
{"question": "Solve (317 / 171)", "answer": "The result of (317 / 171) is 1.8538\n\n####1.8538", "a": 317, "b": 171, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8538}
{"question": "Solve (111 - 766)", "answer": "The result of (111 - 766) is -655\n\n####-655", "a": 111, "b": 766, "operator": "-", "result": -655}
{"question": "Solve (859 - 822)", "answer": "The result of (859 - 822) is 37\n\n####37", "a": 859, "b": 822, "operator": "-", "result": 37}
{"question": "Solve (974 - 1)", "answer": "The result of (974 - 1) is 973\n\n####973", "a": 974, "b": 1, "operator": "-", "result": 973}
{"question": "Solve (303 + 338)", "answer": "The result of (303 + 338) is 641\n\n####641", "a": 303, "b": 338, "operator": "+", "result": 641}
{"question": "Solve (139 + 371)", "answer": "The result of (139 + 371) is 510\n\n####510", "a": 139, "b": 371, "operator": "+", "result": 510}
{"question": "Solve (797 - 621)", "answer": "The result of (797 - 621) is 176\n\n####176", "a": 797, "b": 621, "operator": "-", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve (814 / 939)", "answer": "The result of (814 / 939) is 0.8669\n\n####0.8669", "a": 814, "b": 939, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8669}
{"question": "Solve (89 * 404)", "answer": "The result of (89 * 404) is 35956\n\n####35956", "a": 89, "b": 404, "operator": "*", "result": 35956}
{"question": "Solve (222 * 5)", "answer": "The result of (222 * 5) is 1110\n\n####1110", "a": 222, "b": 5, "operator": "*", "result": 1110}
{"question": "Solve (589 / 440)", "answer": "The result of (589 / 440) is 1.3386\n\n####1.3386", "a": 589, "b": 440, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3386}
{"question": "Solve (439 + 120)", "answer": "The result of (439 + 120) is 559\n\n####559", "a": 439, "b": 120, "operator": "+", "result": 559}
{"question": "Solve (739 + 539)", "answer": "The result of (739 + 539) is 1278\n\n####1278", "a": 739, "b": 539, "operator": "+", "result": 1278}
{"question": "Solve (359 * 860)", "answer": "The result of (359 * 860) is 308740\n\n####308740", "a": 359, "b": 860, "operator": "*", "result": 308740}
{"question": "Solve (902 + 561)", "answer": "The result of (902 + 561) is 1463\n\n####1463", "a": 902, "b": 561, "operator": "+", "result": 1463}
{"question": "Solve (119 + 756)", "answer": "The result of (119 + 756) is 875\n\n####875", "a": 119, "b": 756, "operator": "+", "result": 875}
{"question": "Solve (680 - 481)", "answer": "The result of (680 - 481) is 199\n\n####199", "a": 680, "b": 481, "operator": "-", "result": 199}
{"question": "Solve (859 - 562)", "answer": "The result of (859 - 562) is 297\n\n####297", "a": 859, "b": 562, "operator": "-", "result": 297}
{"question": "Solve (193 + 795)", "answer": "The result of (193 + 795) is 988\n\n####988", "a": 193, "b": 795, "operator": "+", "result": 988}
{"question": "Solve (997 - 384)", "answer": "The result of (997 - 384) is 613\n\n####613", "a": 997, "b": 384, "operator": "-", "result": 613}
{"question": "Solve (8 * 691)", "answer": "The result of (8 * 691) is 5528\n\n####5528", "a": 8, "b": 691, "operator": "*", "result": 5528}
{"question": "Solve (157 / 916)", "answer": "The result of (157 / 916) is 0.1714\n\n####0.1714", "a": 157, "b": 916, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1714}
{"question": "Solve (766 + 16)", "answer": "The result of (766 + 16) is 782\n\n####782", "a": 766, "b": 16, "operator": "+", "result": 782}
{"question": "Solve (171 - 820)", "answer": "The result of (171 - 820) is -649\n\n####-649", "a": 171, "b": 820, "operator": "-", "result": -649}
{"question": "Solve (668 / 381)", "answer": "The result of (668 / 381) is 1.7533\n\n####1.7533", "a": 668, "b": 381, "operator": "/", "result": 1.7533}
{"question": "Solve (700 * 441)", "answer": "The result of (700 * 441) is 308700\n\n####308700", "a": 700, "b": 441, "operator": "*", "result": 308700}
{"question": "Solve (670 * 976)", "answer": "The result of (670 * 976) is 653920\n\n####653920", "a": 670, "b": 976, "operator": "*", "result": 653920}
{"question": "Solve (560 - 245)", "answer": "The result of (560 - 245) is 315\n\n####315", "a": 560, "b": 245, "operator": "-", "result": 315}
{"question": "Solve (624 + 571)", "answer": "The result of (624 + 571) is 1195\n\n####1195", "a": 624, "b": 571, "operator": "+", "result": 1195}
{"question": "Solve (728 / 359)", "answer": "The result of (728 / 359) is 2.0279\n\n####2.0279", "a": 728, "b": 359, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0279}
{"question": "Solve (174 - 656)", "answer": "The result of (174 - 656) is -482\n\n####-482", "a": 174, "b": 656, "operator": "-", "result": -482}
{"question": "Solve (26 / 388)", "answer": "The result of (26 / 388) is 0.067\n\n####0.067", "a": 26, "b": 388, "operator": "/", "result": 0.067}
{"question": "Solve (581 - 631)", "answer": "The result of (581 - 631) is -50\n\n####-50", "a": 581, "b": 631, "operator": "-", "result": -50}
{"question": "Solve (527 - 986)", "answer": "The result of (527 - 986) is -459\n\n####-459", "a": 527, "b": 986, "operator": "-", "result": -459}
{"question": "Solve (695 / 209)", "answer": "The result of (695 / 209) is 3.3254\n\n####3.3254", "a": 695, "b": 209, "operator": "/", "result": 3.3254}
{"question": "Solve (253 - 876)", "answer": "The result of (253 - 876) is -623\n\n####-623", "a": 253, "b": 876, "operator": "-", "result": -623}
{"question": "Solve (397 * 305)", "answer": "The result of (397 * 305) is 121085\n\n####121085", "a": 397, "b": 305, "operator": "*", "result": 121085}
{"question": "Solve (554 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (554 - 927) is -373\n\n####-373", "a": 554, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -373}
{"question": "Solve (572 + 270)", "answer": "The result of (572 + 270) is 842\n\n####842", "a": 572, "b": 270, "operator": "+", "result": 842}
{"question": "Solve (163 * 134)", "answer": "The result of (163 * 134) is 21842\n\n####21842", "a": 163, "b": 134, "operator": "*", "result": 21842}
{"question": "Solve (597 + 841)", "answer": "The result of (597 + 841) is 1438\n\n####1438", "a": 597, "b": 841, "operator": "+", "result": 1438}
{"question": "Solve (932 - 710)", "answer": "The result of (932 - 710) is 222\n\n####222", "a": 932, "b": 710, "operator": "-", "result": 222}
{"question": "Solve (13 - 233)", "answer": "The result of (13 - 233) is -220\n\n####-220", "a": 13, "b": 233, "operator": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve (16 * 675)", "answer": "The result of (16 * 675) is 10800\n\n####10800", "a": 16, "b": 675, "operator": "*", "result": 10800}
{"question": "Solve (582 + 851)", "answer": "The result of (582 + 851) is 1433\n\n####1433", "a": 582, "b": 851, "operator": "+", "result": 1433}
{"question": "Solve (381 + 475)", "answer": "The result of (381 + 475) is 856\n\n####856", "a": 381, "b": 475, "operator": "+", "result": 856}
{"question": "Solve (63 / 527)", "answer": "The result of (63 / 527) is 0.1195\n\n####0.1195", "a": 63, "b": 527, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1195}
{"question": "Solve (692 - 942)", "answer": "The result of (692 - 942) is -250\n\n####-250", "a": 692, "b": 942, "operator": "-", "result": -250}
{"question": "Solve (441 - 431)", "answer": "The result of (441 - 431) is 10\n\n####10", "a": 441, "b": 431, "operator": "-", "result": 10}
{"question": "Solve (676 / 145)", "answer": "The result of (676 / 145) is 4.6621\n\n####4.6621", "a": 676, "b": 145, "operator": "/", "result": 4.6621}
{"question": "Solve (713 - 849)", "answer": "The result of (713 - 849) is -136\n\n####-136", "a": 713, "b": 849, "operator": "-", "result": -136}
{"question": "Solve (74 * 563)", "answer": "The result of (74 * 563) is 41662\n\n####41662", "a": 74, "b": 563, "operator": "*", "result": 41662}
{"question": "Solve (990 - 14)", "answer": "The result of (990 - 14) is 976\n\n####976", "a": 990, "b": 14, "operator": "-", "result": 976}
{"question": "Solve (533 * 868)", "answer": "The result of (533 * 868) is 462644\n\n####462644", "a": 533, "b": 868, "operator": "*", "result": 462644}
{"question": "Solve (285 / 141)", "answer": "The result of (285 / 141) is 2.0213\n\n####2.0213", "a": 285, "b": 141, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0213}
{"question": "Solve (833 * 40)", "answer": "The result of (833 * 40) is 33320\n\n####33320", "a": 833, "b": 40, "operator": "*", "result": 33320}
{"question": "Solve (661 * 358)", "answer": "The result of (661 * 358) is 236638\n\n####236638", "a": 661, "b": 358, "operator": "*", "result": 236638}
{"question": "Solve (902 * 939)", "answer": "The result of (902 * 939) is 846978\n\n####846978", "a": 902, "b": 939, "operator": "*", "result": 846978}
{"question": "Solve (232 - 719)", "answer": "The result of (232 - 719) is -487\n\n####-487", "a": 232, "b": 719, "operator": "-", "result": -487}
{"question": "Solve (401 + 357)", "answer": "The result of (401 + 357) is 758\n\n####758", "a": 401, "b": 357, "operator": "+", "result": 758}
{"question": "Solve (549 * 725)", "answer": "The result of (549 * 725) is 398025\n\n####398025", "a": 549, "b": 725, "operator": "*", "result": 398025}
{"question": "Solve (677 - 504)", "answer": "The result of (677 - 504) is 173\n\n####173", "a": 677, "b": 504, "operator": "-", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve (864 - 37)", "answer": "The result of (864 - 37) is 827\n\n####827", "a": 864, "b": 37, "operator": "-", "result": 827}
{"question": "Solve (559 - 61)", "answer": "The result of (559 - 61) is 498\n\n####498", "a": 559, "b": 61, "operator": "-", "result": 498}
{"question": "Solve (344 * 302)", "answer": "The result of (344 * 302) is 103888\n\n####103888", "a": 344, "b": 302, "operator": "*", "result": 103888}
{"question": "Solve (540 - 140)", "answer": "The result of (540 - 140) is 400\n\n####400", "a": 540, "b": 140, "operator": "-", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve (588 / 885)", "answer": "The result of (588 / 885) is 0.6644\n\n####0.6644", "a": 588, "b": 885, "operator": "/", "result": 0.6644}
{"question": "Solve (243 / 132)", "answer": "The result of (243 / 132) is 1.8409\n\n####1.8409", "a": 243, "b": 132, "operator": "/", "result": 1.8409}
{"question": "Solve (846 - 118)", "answer": "The result of (846 - 118) is 728\n\n####728", "a": 846, "b": 118, "operator": "-", "result": 728}
{"question": "Solve (999 / 373)", "answer": "The result of (999 / 373) is 2.6783\n\n####2.6783", "a": 999, "b": 373, "operator": "/", "result": 2.6783}
{"question": "Solve (325 * 96)", "answer": "The result of (325 * 96) is 31200\n\n####31200", "a": 325, "b": 96, "operator": "*", "result": 31200}
{"question": "Solve (45 / 217)", "answer": "The result of (45 / 217) is 0.2074\n\n####0.2074", "a": 45, "b": 217, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2074}
{"question": "Solve (973 / 235)", "answer": "The result of (973 / 235) is 4.1404\n\n####4.1404", "a": 973, "b": 235, "operator": "/", "result": 4.1404}
{"question": "Solve (825 - 466)", "answer": "The result of (825 - 466) is 359\n\n####359", "a": 825, "b": 466, "operator": "-", "result": 359}
{"question": "Solve (620 / 774)", "answer": "The result of (620 / 774) is 0.801\n\n####0.801", "a": 620, "b": 774, "operator": "/", "result": 0.801}
{"question": "Solve (798 / 913)", "answer": "The result of (798 / 913) is 0.874\n\n####0.874", "a": 798, "b": 913, "operator": "/", "result": 0.874}
{"question": "Solve (96 - 402)", "answer": "The result of (96 - 402) is -306\n\n####-306", "a": 96, "b": 402, "operator": "-", "result": -306}
{"question": "Solve (795 + 344)", "answer": "The result of (795 + 344) is 1139\n\n####1139", "a": 795, "b": 344, "operator": "+", "result": 1139}
{"question": "Solve (148 + 138)", "answer": "The result of (148 + 138) is 286\n\n####286", "a": 148, "b": 138, "operator": "+", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve (36 / 18)", "answer": "The result of (36 / 18) is 2.0\n\n####2.0", "a": 36, "b": 18, "operator": "/", "result": 2.0}
{"question": "Solve (748 + 452)", "answer": "The result of (748 + 452) is 1200\n\n####1200", "a": 748, "b": 452, "operator": "+", "result": 1200}
{"question": "Solve (244 / 184)", "answer": "The result of (244 / 184) is 1.3261\n\n####1.3261", "a": 244, "b": 184, "operator": "/", "result": 1.3261}
{"question": "Solve (26 - 582)", "answer": "The result of (26 - 582) is -556\n\n####-556", "a": 26, "b": 582, "operator": "-", "result": -556}
{"question": "Solve (204 - 850)", "answer": "The result of (204 - 850) is -646\n\n####-646", "a": 204, "b": 850, "operator": "-", "result": -646}
{"question": "Solve (329 - 649)", "answer": "The result of (329 - 649) is -320\n\n####-320", "a": 329, "b": 649, "operator": "-", "result": -320}
{"question": "Solve (244 + 538)", "answer": "The result of (244 + 538) is 782\n\n####782", "a": 244, "b": 538, "operator": "+", "result": 782}
{"question": "Solve (639 / 786)", "answer": "The result of (639 / 786) is 0.813\n\n####0.813", "a": 639, "b": 786, "operator": "/", "result": 0.813}
{"question": "Solve (222 * 766)", "answer": "The result of (222 * 766) is 170052\n\n####170052", "a": 222, "b": 766, "operator": "*", "result": 170052}
{"question": "Solve (237 - 706)", "answer": "The result of (237 - 706) is -469\n\n####-469", "a": 237, "b": 706, "operator": "-", "result": -469}
{"question": "Solve (962 - 317)", "answer": "The result of (962 - 317) is 645\n\n####645", "a": 962, "b": 317, "operator": "-", "result": 645}
{"question": "Solve (676 * 215)", "answer": "The result of (676 * 215) is 145340\n\n####145340", "a": 676, "b": 215, "operator": "*", "result": 145340}
{"question": "Solve (680 - 495)", "answer": "The result of (680 - 495) is 185\n\n####185", "a": 680, "b": 495, "operator": "-", "result": 185}
{"question": "Solve (806 / 274)", "answer": "The result of (806 / 274) is 2.9416\n\n####2.9416", "a": 806, "b": 274, "operator": "/", "result": 2.9416}
{"question": "Solve (180 * 894)", "answer": "The result of (180 * 894) is 160920\n\n####160920", "a": 180, "b": 894, "operator": "*", "result": 160920}
{"question": "Solve (166 * 761)", "answer": "The result of (166 * 761) is 126326\n\n####126326", "a": 166, "b": 761, "operator": "*", "result": 126326}
{"question": "Solve (690 + 748)", "answer": "The result of (690 + 748) is 1438\n\n####1438", "a": 690, "b": 748, "operator": "+", "result": 1438}
{"question": "Solve (292 + 343)", "answer": "The result of (292 + 343) is 635\n\n####635", "a": 292, "b": 343, "operator": "+", "result": 635}
{"question": "Solve (596 - 471)", "answer": "The result of (596 - 471) is 125\n\n####125", "a": 596, "b": 471, "operator": "-", "result": 125}
{"question": "Solve (805 - 162)", "answer": "The result of (805 - 162) is 643\n\n####643", "a": 805, "b": 162, "operator": "-", "result": 643}
{"question": "Solve (678 + 70)", "answer": "The result of (678 + 70) is 748\n\n####748", "a": 678, "b": 70, "operator": "+", "result": 748}
{"question": "Solve (738 / 3)", "answer": "The result of (738 / 3) is 246.0\n\n####246.0", "a": 738, "b": 3, "operator": "/", "result": 246.0}
{"question": "Solve (591 + 909)", "answer": "The result of (591 + 909) is 1500\n\n####1500", "a": 591, "b": 909, "operator": "+", "result": 1500}
{"question": "Solve (109 * 690)", "answer": "The result of (109 * 690) is 75210\n\n####75210", "a": 109, "b": 690, "operator": "*", "result": 75210}
{"question": "Solve (322 - 927)", "answer": "The result of (322 - 927) is -605\n\n####-605", "a": 322, "b": 927, "operator": "-", "result": -605}
{"question": "Solve (769 * 284)", "answer": "The result of (769 * 284) is 218396\n\n####218396", "a": 769, "b": 284, "operator": "*", "result": 218396}
{"question": "Solve (280 * 524)", "answer": "The result of (280 * 524) is 146720\n\n####146720", "a": 280, "b": 524, "operator": "*", "result": 146720}
{"question": "Solve (597 - 315)", "answer": "The result of (597 - 315) is 282\n\n####282", "a": 597, "b": 315, "operator": "-", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve (699 / 815)", "answer": "The result of (699 / 815) is 0.8577\n\n####0.8577", "a": 699, "b": 815, "operator": "/", "result": 0.8577}
{"question": "Solve (879 * 290)", "answer": "The result of (879 * 290) is 254910\n\n####254910", "a": 879, "b": 290, "operator": "*", "result": 254910}
{"question": "Solve (937 * 696)", "answer": "The result of (937 * 696) is 652152\n\n####652152", "a": 937, "b": 696, "operator": "*", "result": 652152}
{"question": "Solve (714 - 999)", "answer": "The result of (714 - 999) is -285\n\n####-285", "a": 714, "b": 999, "operator": "-", "result": -285}
{"question": "Solve (163 / 620)", "answer": "The result of (163 / 620) is 0.2629\n\n####0.2629", "a": 163, "b": 620, "operator": "/", "result": 0.2629}
{"question": "Solve (863 / 443)", "answer": "The result of (863 / 443) is 1.9481\n\n####1.9481", "a": 863, "b": 443, "operator": "/", "result": 1.9481}
{"question": "Solve (888 + 353)", "answer": "The result of (888 + 353) is 1241\n\n####1241", "a": 888, "b": 353, "operator": "+", "result": 1241}
{"question": "Solve (162 + 353)", "answer": "The result of (162 + 353) is 515\n\n####515", "a": 162, "b": 353, "operator": "+", "result": 515}
{"question": "Solve (139 / 421)", "answer": "The result of (139 / 421) is 0.3302\n\n####0.3302", "a": 139, "b": 421, "operator": "/", "result": 0.3302}
{"question": "Solve (275 - 468)", "answer": "The result of (275 - 468) is -193\n\n####-193", "a": 275, "b": 468, "operator": "-", "result": -193}
{"question": "Solve (597 + 871)", "answer": "The result of (597 + 871) is 1468\n\n####1468", "a": 597, "b": 871, "operator": "+", "result": 1468}
{"question": "Solve (979 * 71)", "answer": "The result of (979 * 71) is 69509\n\n####69509", "a": 979, "b": 71, "operator": "*", "result": 69509}
{"question": "Solve (352 - 842)", "answer": "The result of (352 - 842) is -490\n\n####-490", "a": 352, "b": 842, "operator": "-", "result": -490}
{"question": "Solve (848 + 205)", "answer": "The result of (848 + 205) is 1053\n\n####1053", "a": 848, "b": 205, "operator": "+", "result": 1053}
{"question": "Solve (947 * 838)", "answer": "The result of (947 * 838) is 793586\n\n####793586", "a": 947, "b": 838, "operator": "*", "result": 793586}
{"question": "Solve (555 + 680)", "answer": "The result of (555 + 680) is 1235\n\n####1235", "a": 555, "b": 680, "operator": "+", "result": 1235}
{"question": "Solve (815 - 757)", "answer": "The result of (815 - 757) is 58\n\n####58", "a": 815, "b": 757, "operator": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve (186 / 953)", "answer": "The result of (186 / 953) is 0.1952\n\n####0.1952", "a": 186, "b": 953, "operator": "/", "result": 0.1952}
{"question": "Solve (199 + 106)", "answer": "The result of (199 + 106) is 305\n\n####305", "a": 199, "b": 106, "operator": "+", "result": 305}
{"question": "Solve (520 - 294)", "answer": "The result of (520 - 294) is 226\n\n####226", "a": 520, "b": 294, "operator": "-", "result": 226}
{"question": "Solve (586 / 411)", "answer": "The result of (586 / 411) is 1.4258\n\n####1.4258", "a": 586, "b": 411, "operator": "/", "result": 1.4258}
{"question": "Solve (156 - 131)", "answer": "The result of (156 - 131) is 25\n\n####25", "a": 156, "b": 131, "operator": "-", "result": 25}
{"question": "Solve (453 - 130)", "answer": "The result of (453 - 130) is 323\n\n####323", "a": 453, "b": 130, "operator": "-", "result": 323}
{"question": "Solve (672 - 28)", "answer": "The result of (672 - 28) is 644\n\n####644", "a": 672, "b": 28, "operator": "-", "result": 644}
{"question": "Solve (333 * 117)", "answer": "The result of (333 * 117) is 38961\n\n####38961", "a": 333, "b": 117, "operator": "*", "result": 38961}
{"question": "Solve (158 / 854)", "answer": "The result of (158 / 854) is 0.185\n\n####0.185", "a": 158, "b": 854, "operator": "/", "result": 0.185}
{"question": "Solve (197 * 627)", "answer": "The result of (197 * 627) is 123519\n\n####123519", "a": 197, "b": 627, "operator": "*", "result": 123519}
{"question": "Solve (523 - 825)", "answer": "The result of (523 - 825) is -302\n\n####-302", "a": 523, "b": 825, "operator": "-", "result": -302}
{"question": "Solve (692 * 626)", "answer": "The result of (692 * 626) is 433192\n\n####433192", "a": 692, "b": 626, "operator": "*", "result": 433192}
{"question": "Solve (498 + 45)", "answer": "The result of (498 + 45) is 543\n\n####543", "a": 498, "b": 45, "operator": "+", "result": 543}
{"question": "Solve (516 - 779)", "answer": "The result of (516 - 779) is -263\n\n####-263", "a": 516, "b": 779, "operator": "-", "result": -263}
{"question": "Solve (215 + 814)", "answer": "The result of (215 + 814) is 1029\n\n####1029", "a": 215, "b": 814, "operator": "+", "result": 1029}
{"question": "Solve (410 * 737)", "answer": "The result of (410 * 737) is 302170\n\n####302170", "a": 410, "b": 737, "operator": "*", "result": 302170}
